[♪♪♪]
[SIGHS]
[GROANING]
[INDISTINCT
ANNOUNCEMENTS OVER PA]
Think you'll be okay
waiting here by yourself?
Yeah, whatever.
Sir, if you'd like to smoke,
you need to be another
20 feet from the door.
So roll me further, bitch.
[SIREN APPROACHING]
What's coming?
Male, Caucasian. Early
40s. Multiple gunshot wounds.
EMT: BP is 70.
Seven-zero over palp.
Pulse 140. One-four-zero.
Weak and thready
at the brachial.
No breath sounds on the
right side, the belly is rigid.
DOCTOR: Appears pale and
diaphoretic. How many wounds?
EMT: We found four.
Shoulder and hip.
Right lung in
lower left quadrant,
no visible exit wounds.
DOCTOR: Let's get him two grams
of oxygen. What's his hemoglobin?
EMT: Seven-point-three.
Need two large-bore
IVs, six units O-neg.
Type and cross
for six more units,
chest x-ray and KUB.
Notify the OR,
we are on the way.
OR 1 is clear. Let's
put him in there.
[LEFT LANE CRUISER'S "WAYNEDALE"
PLAYING OVER CAR STEREO]
PETE: Yo, Jesse,
sorry I'm late, man.
♪ Feel free to go knocking
down We're gonna... ♪
Damn, brother, look at you.
That's messed up.
How are you feeling? You okay?
Actually,
I'm great.
♪ Waynedale, Waynedale ♪
[♪♪♪]
GALE: I don't understand.
I thought things
were going pretty well.
I... I thought we were
kind of simpatico.
You know? We were
becoming a real team.
Uh... Not... Not so much, no.
Is this about the temperature
setting the other day?
Because I can assure
you that will not happen...
No, it's bigger than that, Gale.
It... It's much more than that.
Could you elaborate?
Well, uh, yes,
of course I could,
but I don't think either of us
would necessarily
benefit from a prolonged...
Phew, uh...
Yeah, so...
Yeah.
I set up the entire lab.
You said you liked
the configuration.
And I do.
For the most part.
Look, you're a
fine chemist, really,
with a promising future.
It... It's just that...
That I... Uh...
That... That we just have
different rhythms, Gale.
Y-you see... It's...
It... It's as if I'm classical,
but you are... Are more jazz.
Jazz. Jazz. Yes.
And God knows there is
nothing wrong with jazz.
It's simply that I require...
Classical. Exactly.
[DOOR OPENS]
Oh, shit.
Man, this is the bomb.
What's up, partner?
Oh. I can't believe this.
This is my replacement?
JESSE: Oh, Jesus.
Hi. Gale.
Nice to meet you. What's up?
Damn, we should've
ditched that RV months ago.
It's all, like,
shiny up in here.
Uhn! Ha-ha-ha.
I'm sorry, I must be
missing something.
I don't mean... I
don't mean to be...
JESSE: Oh! This...
No.
- -makes no sense.
[JESSE LAUGHS]
So...
I guess this is...
JESSE: Oh, dear mother of God.
This is for the best.
Two hundred
pounds a week. Got it?
Yeah.
JESSE: Oh, man. Oh.
Mr. White.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Wow.
[CHUCKLES]
Okay, there's a lot to show you.
Some new techniques to learn.
What, now? Yes, now.
We've only got a couple days
before our next batch is due.
And I need to get
you up to speed.
Right on. I'm just saying...
How's the cell
service down here?
It's nonexistent.
We're shielded.
There's a hard line for
emergencies. Come on.
So you haven't talked
to anybody today,
other than, you know,
Captain Nerd there.
Why?
Your brother-in-law.
What about him?
DOCTOR 1: What's the story?
DOCTOR 2: He was unresponsive.
You getting exposure
on those wounds?
Two units of saline.
DOCTOR 2: Bivalve mass.
Breath sounds bilaterally.
Femur's like a
wet bag of gravel.
Other one's not much
better. Get those boots off.
See if you get a pulse.
Get blood-pressure
cup or an ABI?
Where's that blood?
WOMAN [OVER PA]:
Dr. Bording to Cardiology.
Sir, can I help
you? Uh... Yeah, I...
It's all right. He's
family. Thank you.
Marie. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, honey.
I'm so sorry.
I don't know what to say.
[SNIFFLES]
How is he? I don't know.
They won't really tell us
anything. He's still in surgery.
They shot him four times.
Oh, Christ.
Where's Holly?
SKYLER: I got a sitter.
Hey, how are you, huh? Fine.
Yeah?
Sure?
I'm... I'm fine. I just
need some fresh air.
Okay.
Here. Let me get the door.
I got it. I'm fine.
Walt. Walt, this
is ASAC Merkert.
Hank's brother-in-law, Walt.
Hello. I'm very sorry.
Thank you. I mean...
Can you tell us
anything? Any details?
Right now, all we know is
two men ambushed Hank.
They didn't have any ID on
them. Probably Mexican nationals.
Their tattoos
indicated an affiliation
with a drug cartel.
Why did they attack Hank?
We're not sure yet.
It could be in relation
to an investigation
Hank was working,
or it could be a message
to the DEA in general.
They had an axe.
The cartels tend to be dramatic.
Jesus.
Where are they? I
mean, did they...?
Hank got both of them.
He killed one outright,
the other one's upstairs
in critical condition.
Your brother-in-law's
one tough son of a bitch
to take them both out,
considering he didn't
even have his gun.
He didn't have his gun?
Why didn't Hank have his gun?
Marie, the assault charge.
I had to suspend Hank
pending the investigation.
That means I had to
take away his weapon.
You had to take it.
MERKERT: It's standard
procedure. No one...
Okay. All right, listen.
If you would have all listened
to him right from the start
and let him arrest
that little degenerate,
he wouldn't have to take
things into his own hands.
He would've had a gun and
could've defended himself.
Marie, let's just... No. Just...
It's their fault.
He didn't have a gun.
Honey, this isn't helping you.
You.
What kind of partner are you?
You were supposed to back
him up, and where were you?
Where were you?
Texas.
And you.
You're supposed to
protect your agents,
instead of taking their guns,
not supporting them,
not backing them up.
Marie. Marie. When they...
Honey, let's just go
and sit down, okay?
I'm not doing anything
until these two get the
hell out of here. I mean it.
Sorry... MARIE: Go.
You are not welcome here.
The DEA is not welcome
here. SKYLER: Okay, honey.
Come on.
Come on. Let's go sit down.
[SNIFFLES]
It's not just them.
It's you, Walt.
This Pinkman that
Hank was looking for,
Hank would have never
even heard his name,
if you hadn't bought
marijuana from him.
Marie...
Do you ever think
about that, Walt?
Do you?
Do you think about everything
that you have put him through?
SKYLER: Marie, stop.
You're upset, and you're
looking for someone to blame,
and it's understandable,
but don't blame Walt.
It's not his fault.
[SIGHS]
[SOBBING] I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Sweetheart... WALT:
No. No. Don't...
[SOBBING]
It's okay. It's Hank.
It's all right. Shh.
[♪♪♪]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
MAN: All right, you're done.
Okay, next.
[SIREN WAILING]
[SIGHS]
Hello.
Hello, hello, hello.
Yeah.
[GRUNTS THEN GROANS]
Yo, yo, yo.
Jesse Pinkman in the house.
Oh, my dear God.
[LAUGHS]
Wow.
WOMAN [OVER PA]: Walter
White to the nearest courtesy phone.
Walter White, please
pick up a courtesy phone.
JESSE [OVER PHONE]: Yo,
we working sometime this year?
What the hell are you thinking?
Why are you calling me here?
I tried your cell and it
went straight to voicemail.
How am I to get a
hold of you? You aren't.
Look, man. It's
been a whole day.
How long is this
grieving process?
Just put a clock on it for me.
All I'm saying is we
have a schedule, right?
My family comes
before your schedule.
Dude, it's not my schedule.
We have responsibilities here.
I'll get there when I get there.
You know what? Whatever.
I'll just cook on my own.
You will do no
such thing. Why not?
Well, uh, for starters,
you aren't the
least bit familiar
with any of the equipment.
There's gotta be some
sort of manual, right?
And I can read.
Jesse, touch nothing.
Yo. Stop treating me
like I'm like your assistant.
I'm not your bitch
to order around.
We're partners. Remember?
I need you to sit
patiently and wait,
I will be there
as soon as I can.
Thank you very much
for your kind words.
We... We really
do appreciate that.
What, is your wife there?
Uh... Yes. Yes, she is.
She would be happy to... To
know that you asked about her.
Please do keep
us in your thoughts.
Hey, tell your douche
bag brother-in-law
to head towards the light.
So I'm thinking, um,
maybe we should go get
everybody some breakfast.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Do you know who that was?
SKYLER: You know, these
eggs are really not too bad.
Look at that. Look at what?
At what? This. These spots.
This fork is absolutely filthy.
Tell me you see this.
You've got good
eyes. Look at that.
Marie, those are
just water spots.
That's fine.
Those are not "water spots."
It's dirt.
This silverware's
obviously not been cleaned.
It's covered in germs
from someone else's mouth.
God knows what.
Seriously, Aunt
Marie, it's water spots.
Ours at home aren't any better.
Yours at home are
irrelevant. We're in a hospital.
They need to be held
to a higher standard.
They have a responsibility.
Well, I'm not actually sure
if the cafeteria necessarily
qualifies as being
part of the hospital.
It's in the same building.
It's all under the same roof.
Do you think that sick people
aren't eating with this
bacteria-infested silverware?
My God, how are you supposed
to survive this death trap?
[SIGHS]
SKYLER: Marie...
I survived.
I had my lobectomy
at this hospital.
Remember that?
Remember how scared we all were?
I didn't wanna act like
it, but I was terrified.
All that week,
all I could think of
was how they were
actually going to cut me open
and take out a part of me
that was with me my entire life.
I... I couldn't get that
image out of my head.
I think the scariest part
was when they
took me into pre-op.
Lying there, waiting for
them to anesthetize you.
Knowing that you may
never wake up again.
Huh. Actually,
what I really remember
about that day
is driving to the hospital.
Skyler, you remember me
wanting to drive that day?
Yeah. Heh.
Anyway, there we are.
We're driving up Central,
and we hit every green light.
I mean, every single light
that we hit... Shoo. Green.
It's just... When
does that happen?
Just like, bang, bang,
green the entire way.
And the whole time, all
I could think about was:
"Why today?
"Why? Why can't I just spend
a few extra minutes in
the car with my family?"
I never wanted to be stuck
in traffic so bad in my life.
At least I was with my family.
I had that.
Anyway, I survived this place.
And I'm not half the
man your husband is.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Yes?
BOLSA [IN SPANISH]: What
the hell is going on there?
[IN ENGLISH] I was
gonna ask you the same.
[IN SPANISH] You
know about my men?
GUS [IN ENGLISH]: I heard
they attacked a DEA agent.
Why would they do that?
[IN SPANISH] What's the matter?
Spanish not good enough anymore?
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
[IN ENGLISH] I
didn't order this,
and my men would
never do this on their own.
Someone gave the go-ahead.
GUS: Are you accusing me?
I'm just saying they
wouldn't act on their own.
I am not in the habit of
picking my own pocket.
I assume that the next
shipment will be delayed.
Any thoughts on
when it might arrive?
A week, a month.
There's too much
focus on the border.
We lay low for the time being.
We lay low, and then
we get the real story
from my man who survived.
Your man is in custody.
[IN SPANISH] God bless America!
[IN ENGLISH] He's
innocent until proven guilty.
I'll get him the best lawyer,
and then we'll learn the truth.
Well, keep me apprised.
Any time you got that kind
of proximity to the spine,
there's always
cause for concern,
but as I say, it's
really too soon to tell.
He's out of surgery,
at least, which is...
Out of surgery, on
his way to recovery.
All right. And where's that?
Unfortunately, you
can't see him just yet.
We're gonna have to
wait for him to stabilize.
How long will that take?
I can't really say.
It could be hours.
But we'll let you know just
as soon as you can see him.
Thank you.
SKYLER: Um... Maybe we should
get you home for a couple hours?
Get some rest?
I'm not going anywhere.
WALT JR.: Me neither.
Well, is anyone else
dying to brush their teeth,
or is it just me?
What if I ran over to the house
and picked up a few things?
Marie? I could
swing by your place.
That would be
great. Thanks, Walt.
Okay.
[CHATTERING]
GOMEZ: Walt. Walt.
We just heard he
came through. Uh...
Yeah, well, it's, uh, you
know, guardedly good news.
Thank God. I'll take it. Yeah.
Hey, guys, this is Hank's
brother-in-law, Walt.
Good to meet you. Hi. Hey.
We were just
swapping Hank stories.
That could go on all day.
God knows, there's
a million of them.
[MEN CHUCKLING]
Meanwhile...
Miserable piece of shit.
Guy who shot him, one
that's left, he's up there.
Got the painkillers going
on, resting comfortably.
Your tax dollars at work.
You ought to see what
Hank did to that bastard.
Wanna see?
Come on, let me show you.
[MONITOR BEEPING]
You comfortable,
you piece of shit?
[MONITOR STARTS TO BEEP FASTER]
[♪♪♪]
[ALARM BEEPING]
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
[CHATTERING]
MAN 1: You got him?
MAN 2: Come on.
MAN 1: All right. MAN
2: Easy now, easy.
JESSE: Oh. Whoa.
[PRINCE FATTY'S "SHIMMY
SHIMMY YA" PLAYING]
♪ Shimmy shimmy ya
Shimmy, shimmy yay ♪
♪ Shimmy, shimmy ya
Shimmy, shimmy, shimmy ya ♪
♪ Hey, baby, we like it raw ♪
[WHIRRING]
♪ Oh, baby, we like it raw ♪
♪ Yes, baby, we like it raw ♪
♪ Shimmy, shimmy ya
Shimmy yay, shimmy yay ♪
♪ Gimme the mic
And I will take it away ♪
Come here.
Oh... Uhn.
No.
[YELLS]
Oh, shit.
♪ Oh, baby, we like it raw ♪
♪ Yes, baby, we like it raw ♪
[SINGING JESSE &
BADGER'S "FALLACIES"]
♪ Fallacies One for you and... ♪
[GROANS]
♪ Oh, baby, we like it raw ♪
♪ Shimmy, shimmy ya
Shimmy yay, shimmy yay ♪
♪ Gimme the mic
And I will take it away ♪
♪ The Wu-Tang thing
Was the kung-fu king ♪
♪ We get to it faster
We're so crazy rappin' ♪
♪ In a-Brooklyn ♪
[AIR HISSES]
♪ In a-Brooklyn Hear this now ♪
♪ Leave it to people
For the hip-hop crew ♪
♪ Got 'em the style
Let me kick into you ♪
♪ In a-Brooklyn ♪
[AIR HISSING]
Yeah.
♪ Shimmy, shimmy ya
Shimmy, shimmy, shimmy yay ♪
♪ Shimmy ya Shimmy,
shimmy, shimmy ya ♪
♪ Shimmy, shimmy, shimmy
Shimmy, shimmy ya... ♪
[DOOR CLOSES]
Finally. About damn time.
Why isn't there
anything cooking?
WOMAN 1 [OVER PA]: Walter
White to the nearest courtesy phone.
WOMAN 2 [OVER PHONE]:
Operator. This is Walter White.
I'll connect you.
JESSE: Yo, we got
problems, big ones.
Reverend, so nice
of you to call. Again.
Turn your phone on already.
You know, I will
definitely look into that.
I'll tell you what.
Why don't I just call you
right back on my cell phone?
Okay?
I told you to wait.
I don't know how many
more ways I could say it.
Yeah, dick, I was waiting,
and then that creepy,
quiet guy showed up.
Gus came by? Not him, man. Um...
Apparently I'm not
worthy of meeting him.
It was the other one. The one
that I'm qualified to speak to.
He started asking questions too.
Like why haven't
we cooked anything.
All right, we have a quota.
It's due tomorrow. Do you
seriously not care or what?
Because that guy, he's
got, like, the dead eyes.
Let me ask you something.
Do you remember when we
were out in the desert with Tuco?
Oh, you mean when he put
a machine gun to my head?
Yeah, I think that does
ring a tiny bell. Why?
No. He kept... He
kept saying that...
That someone was coming
up from Mexico to get us.
Do you remember?
Now, who was that?
What has this got to do with...?
Look, I don't
know. It was, um...
Uh...
His cousins.
Right, Jesse? It was...
It was his cousins.
Yeah, cousins.
Whatever, man. Why?
Any news?
No change.
Okay, well, I, uh...
I didn't know whose
toothbrushes were whose,
so I just stopped
by the drugstore.
Thank God for
travel sizes, right?
SKYLER: Thank you. Yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, I think I'm gonna
go wash my face.
I'm going crazy.
Do you wanna come? Yeah.
WOMAN [OVER PA]: Nurse
Franklin, please page the operator.
Nurse Franklin,
page the operator.
I got candy bars.
Oh, um...
Is this, uh, what
you were asking for?
Yeah. Yeah?
Yeah, I, uh... I
skimmed through it.
Looks interesting. Yeah, um...
Uncle Hank gave it to me.
Well, what's it about?
Um, Pablo Escobar, this
big drug guy in the '80s.
Yeah. Yeah. I remember
seeing him on the news.
Well, it... It's more about
the guys who investigated him
and tried to bring him down.
Some of them were DEA, you know?
Uncle Hank said that they
were worth learning about
that everybody knows
who Pab... Pablo Escobar is,
but nobody knows about the
guys that brought him down.
I guess I never
thought about it.
He said that good
guys never get ink
like the bad guys do.
So he gave it to me.
Figured I'd read it.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Uh... I... I need to...
I'll be right back, okay? Okay.
[INDISTINCT
ANNOUNCEMENTS OVER PA]
No, I... I assure you. We
are hard at work. Absolutely.
GUS [OVER PHONE]: So I can expect
delivery by tomorrow as scheduled.
Well, uh...
Unfortunately, uh...
WALT: Unfortunately,
we're not going to be able to
keep our schedule this week.
But not for lack of trying.
Is there something
I should know?
Well, to be completely
honest with you,
Gale really screwed us up.
I mean, not... Not on
purpose, of course,
but he just... He
set us way back.
And we've been playing
catch-up ever since.
And, um... And I've had
to be out running errands
and trying to keep us on target.
Uh... Some of the equipment
wasn't calibrated correctly...
Well, it's just all very
technical and... And boring.
But rest assured that...
That we will... We will
do whatever it takes.
It has my total attention.
We'll cook through the
weekend if necessary.
We will have 400 pounds
for you by next week.
I have your word on that?
You do. You have
my word on that.
Thank you for the update.
MAN: Yeah. Right.
Any news?
No, I'm just... Just wandering.
How's everybody doing?
Uh, well, as well
as can be expected.
It's this not knowing,
that's the hardest
part, I think.
Anything new on these guys?
Who they are? What they wanted?
No, nothing yet,
but we'll get it.
Steve...
Do you think there
could maybe be others?
Buddy, nobody's getting to Hank.
That was their one
shot and they blew it.
So no.
No way.
Jesus.
I'd love to walk in there
and shoot that bastard
right in the head.
Me too.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Yeah?
Oh, yeah?
Great. We'll be right down.
Food's here.
Hey, you like Pollos Hermanos?
MAN 1: You guys
coming? MAN 2: Yeah.
Um, on occasion, yeah.
Owner's a big
booster for the DEA.
He heard what happened.
He's gonna feed every
cop in the building.
That's... That's
wonderful. Yeah.
And, apparently, he's
bringing it by personally.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
MARIE: I don't even
know what to say.
SKYLER: That's an incredible...
Good, huh? Delicious.
MARIE: That's so generous
of you. Thank you very much.
SKYLER: Yes, thank you.
Guys, did you hear that?
Mr. Fring is offering
a 10,000-dollar reward
on any information
about the case.
Well, that's...
That's wonderful.
Wow, thank you, Mr. Fring.
You're very welcome.
Men like your husband
are the thin blue line
between us and these animals.
I only wish I could do more.
Well, we do
appreciate your support.
This reward could turn
the tide here. It'll really help.
Again, I can't express
how sorry I am.
As it happens, I actually
met Agent Schrader.
MARIE: Really?
Our fund run,
couple of months ago.
Mr. Fring was one
of our sponsors.
I, uh, talked for a few
minutes with your husband.
As a matter of fact,
Mr. White, your name came up.
Really? Heh.
Yeah, there happened to
be a collection jar out for you,
and we spoke briefly
about your health concerns.
I hope that there's
been good news.
Uh...
Things have improved, yes.
GUS: That's wonderful to hear.
It was clear to me how
deeply he cares for you.
Well, I have taken up
enough of your time.
Um... Thank you again very much.
It was a great
pleasure to meet you.
Thank you. WALT
JR.: Yes, thank you.
Let me walk you out.
Oh, no, it's not necessary.
MARIE: It's amazing.
You know, I didn't
say thank you.
I'll walk him out.
Be right back.
Good to see you.
Enjoy the chicken?
Good. Good. Excuse me.
Uh... My pleasure. My pleasure.
Thank you. Thank you.
It's good chicken,
huh? Good. Yeah.
Mr. Fring. I, uh... Mr. White.
I just wanted to
thank you again.
It's my pleasure.
Uh, may I...? May I speak
with you? Just a moment.
You knew. You...
You knew my brother-in-law
was with the DEA.
I investigate everyone
with whom I do business.
What careful man wouldn't?
He is not a problem
for us, for our business.
Your being here is...
Is this some sort of message?
I'm supporting my community.
I hide in plain
sight, same as you.
Are we done?
No, listen, I, uh...
This attack on
my brother-in-law,
I don't... I don't
understand it.
I don't know what it means.
Please, if you have
some knowledge
that you could share with me...
I fear for my family.
I'm sure they'll be fine.
I am told the assassin that
survived is gravely injured.
It's doubtful he'll live.
Now thank me and shake my hand.
Thank you. Thank you again.
You're quite welcome, Mr. White.
MAN: Did you hear that?
[CHATTERING]
We're going up? MAN: Come on.
What's going on?
What's happening?
DOCTOR: Starting chest
compressions. One, two, three, four.
One, two, three... NURSE: Defib?
No reason. Patient
is in asystole.
Continuing chest compressions.
One, two, three, four.
Give me a liter of saline.
I can't get a pulse back.
One, two, three, four.
NURSE: Still nothing.
DOCTOR: All right,
stopping compressions.
Time? Eight forty-three.
DOCTOR: Time of death, 20:43.
[EKG FLATLINING]
Burn in hell, you piece of shit.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Yes? Juan?
BOLSA: I assume
you heard the news.
Your man died. I heard.
It's unfortunate.
Yeah, unfortunate.
And meanwhile, I have
Federales surrounding my house.
You know what I think, Gustavo?
I think you're behind all this.
Why would I do this?
How would it serve me?
That's the part I'm
trying to figure out.
Go off on your own, maybe.
Would you actually
think that would work?
GUS: You sound like
you're under a lot of stress.
Maybe you should call me back
when you're seeing
things more clearly.
I see things clear enough.
One DEA gets shot, all of
Washington starts barking.
The D.F. suddenly has
to put on a big show,
and I wind up with
Federales in my rosebushes.
But just for a while.
Appearances, politics.
Are you still there, Gustavo?
Yes.
I'm here.
I'll weather this. I always do.
My brother's a police chief.
I got connections.
They'll get me through.
And when I get proof,
and the others find
out what you've done,
maybe we come pay you
a visit. Maybe we can...
[GLASS SHATTERING OVER PHONE]
[BOLSA SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[MEN SHOUTING IN SPANISH]
[GUNFIRE]
[CRASHING]
[GUNFIRE OVER PHONE]
Skyler. Skyler. Marie. Marie.
Oh, how is he? Tell
me something good.
I think he's stable enough
now for you to go see him briefly.
I'm sorry, I'm afraid it's
immediate family only.
We're all family. I understand.
But we have a certain
protocol here that we need...
We're all family.
[MACHINES BEEPING]
[♪♪♪]