[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[WIND HOWLING]
[AMERICA'S "A HORSE WITH
NO NAME" PLAYING ON STEREO]
♪ In the desert You can
remember your name ♪
♪ 'Cause there ain't no
one For to give you no pain ♪
♪ La-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la ♪
[SINGING TO MUSIC ON STEREO]
♪ La-la-la-la ♪
♪ After two days
In the desert sun ♪
♪ My skin began to turn red ♪
♪ After three days ♪
♪ In the desert fun ♪
♪ I was looking at a riverbed ♪
[TIRES SCREECHING]
♪ To think it was dead ♪
♪ You see I've been
through the desert ♪
♪ On a horse with no name ♪
♪ It felt good To
be out of the rain ♪
♪ In the desert You can
remember your name ♪
[POLICE SIREN WAILING]
♪ Because there ain't no one ♪
♪ For to give you no pain ♪
♪ La-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la ♪
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
♪ After nine days ♪
♪ I let the horse run free... ♪
Good morning, officer.
Sir, can you turn
the music down?
Oh, okay.
[LOWERS STEREO VOLUME]
Down means off.
[STEREO TURNS OFF]
You know why I pulled
you over this morning?
Well, I'm... I'm pretty
sure I wasn't speeding.
I've been using the
cruise control, so I...
No, sir, your windshield.
License and
registration, please.
Right.
Uh...
This... This was
from Wayfarer 515.
My house was
in the debris field.
Okay.
And that's what
shattered my windshield,
some piece of
wreckage from the plane.
I understand.
You know of flight
515, the plane crash?
You're wearing the ribbon.
Yes. I'm quite aware
of Wayfarer 515.
I was one of the
first responders
on the scene that day.
Then what are you doing?
Citing you, sir.
What? What, you
don't believe me?
Sir, regardless of how that
windshield was damaged,
this car is unsafe to
drive in this condition.
Stay in the car, please.
Wait. Wait just a
minute. Just one minute.
Sir, I asked you to
stay in the vehicle.
I can get out of my car.
Listen... No, you listen to me.
It's time for you
to listen to me.
Take a deep breath, calm
down. This is America.
Get back in that car. I have
rights. You understand?
At least have the common
decency to hear me out.
Step back now. Did
you hear what I said?
Calm down. You're
giving me a ticket?
I told you that my house
was in the debris field.
Do you have the remotest
inkling of what that means?
Sir, calm down. Hellfire
rained down on my house
where my children
sleep! Step back now.
There were body
parts in my yard!
Are you kidding? Last warning.
You got two seconds
to stand down.
Or? I'm gonna pepper-spray you.
Pepper-spray
me. That is perfect.
Pepper-spray the
man who's expressing
his opinion under
the First Amendment.
[GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
[♪♪♪]
HANK: Lastly a little something
from down El Paso way.
Border Patrol came
across multiple homicides
just this side of the border.
Truck turns out to be a chicken
run out of Juarez into Laredo.
Border Patrol's been
playing hide-and-seek
with these polleros
for two years.
But this time, soon as they
made it across, someone hit them.
Hit them hard.
We're talking a driver
and nine illegals.
No sign of the shooters.
So this truck was carrying
more than just people.
What are we looking
at, weed, coke or meth?
Doesn't look like they
were transporting narcotics.
Then why'd the Border
Patrol kick this to us?
They didn't. I pulled it.
You ask me, this is high-end
cartel work. Los Zetas, maybe.
Question is, why do we
have Juarez-style action
on our side of the DMZ?
They sending a
message? Clearing a path?
Or was this about stopping
one particular border-hopper?
Maybe one of
those extra-crispies
knew something he shouldn't.
Anyway, keep your eyes open.
All right, that's
it. Slow news day.
Add one more to the countdown.
Oh, yeah? What's that, Gomey?
We're waiting on that
famous blue meth of yours.
Twenty-nine days
since we saw it last.
[PHONE RINGING]
It's still out there,
Gomey. Don't worry.
Local P.D. I gotta take this.
Gomey, go beat your piñata.
Rest of you jokers,
too damn quiet in here.
Catch some bad guys.
Schrader.
Hey, what's up, Walt?
What?
[HAMMERING]
Jesse?
Hey, Dad.
Fixing up the house, huh?
Doing a little work, yeah.
JESSE: Well, I'll
bounce. It's cool.
You doing okay?
JESSE: Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
Good. I just happened to be
driving by and saw the sign.
So you're selling the place.
In this market.
Can you believe it?
I see you moved the
garage. That's bold.
Your mother's idea.
It's quite an operation.
We did all new stucco,
all new master suite,
sandblasted,
fumigated the basement.
Right on.
Yeah.
You know, fixing up the place
totally increases resale value.
I read that in, I wanna
say, like TIME magazine.
So, what'd you do with
the upstairs bathroom?
All redone. New tiles in
the bathrooms and kitchens,
granite countertops,
new appliances.
All top-of-the-line.
Damn. That's great, Dad.
Think I can get a tour?
Uh, these guys are
trying to finish up.
Maybe we'd better
stay out of their way.
There are pictures
on the website,
if you want to take a look.
Cool.
You're looking healthy.
I'll tell your mother.
She'll be happy.
Thanks.
You know, I could
come by sometime
for dinner or something.
Yeah. Sometime.
Okay.
Later, Dad.
HANK: You know, look,
he's a high-school teacher.
He's never been in
trouble a day in his life.
He finds out he's
got lung cancer
and now his wife kicks
the poor bastard
out of his own house.
I mean, look, guys, if
anybody rates a little slack,
here's the guy.
Hey, Walt, uh, remember
Officer Cavanaugh?
Officer, I'm very sorry
that I lost my temper.
There's no excuse
for my behavior.
It was disrespectful.
Yeah. Thanks, man.
[EXHALES]
She's divorcing me.
I don't know what
to tell you, buddy.
It is what it is.
She doesn't want
me to see the kids.
She said that?
Yeah.
[ENGINE STARTS]
SAUL: You don't
write, you don't call.
God.
It's a disaster.
SAUL: It is not a
disaster. Oh, okay.
It's not a disaster, all right?
She's not going to the cops,
she's not gonna
tell a living soul.
You wanna know why?
One word: blowback.
If she blabs, it'll be
a disaster, for her.
That DEA brother-in-law?
Screwed. You were
right under his nose.
He'll be lucky if they
let him bust glue-sniffers
at the hobby shop.
The kids? Paging Dr. Phil.
My daddy's a drug dealer
and my mommy turned him in.
And the house? Gone.
Feds would come and RICO
her and the kids out on the street.
Ooh. Good luck
arguing with them on that.
No. It's not gonna happen.
She's bluffing and she knows it.
Her going to the police
is not the point, Saul.
She's out of my life.
Do you understand?
I've lost my family.
Everything that I care about.
Hey, buddy. Heh, heh.
It's bad. It's a
calamity. Oh, my God.
But we live to
fight another day.
And after a decent
interval of time,
well, there are
other fish in the sea.
You've been out of
circulation for a while.
You'll be just amazed
at what's out there.
Thailand, the Czech Republic.
I mean, those women are
so grateful to even be here.
In the meantime, idle hands
are the devil's plaything.
So why don't you
get back on the horse
and do what you do best?
First step: Talk to our
friend and get cooking.
I can't be the bad guy.
What?
Okay. Heh, heh.
You know, we'll revisit.
Just promise me you won't
hang yourself in the closet.
[SIGHS]
Pop-pop!
Pop-pop, the ice cream man!
[GRUNTS]
Huh?
Don't tell your mom. Okay.
[PHONE VIBRATING]
Yeah. SAUL: It's me.
We may have a
wife problem. Uh-huh.
Look, I need eyes on it.
You got an address?
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
ON HEADPHONES]
Hey. Dinner's gonna be late.
Uncle Hank and Aunt
Marie are bringing takeout,
but if you're hungry, I
could rustle something up.
Okay.
Hey, buddy, pass
the ketchup, will you?
What? I've had enough
trans-fat for one lifetime.
Two-day drive from
the nearest ocean
and you're eating raw
fish. That's all I'm saying.
[CHUCKLES]
Been a while since that
minnow's been swimming.
Right, buddy? Ha, ha, ha.
Yeah.
You know, Flynn here is
looking for a part-time job,
so, I don't know, if you know
of anything you might want to...
My name's Walter, Jr.
Like, what, you can't
even say his name?
Um, if you've changed your
mind about being called Flynn,
all you need to
do is just tell me
you don't want
to be called Flynn.
You know, Dad didn't
show up till fourth period.
And his eyes were all red,
like he's been
crying or something.
But you, you don't even care.
And now he won't
even drive me home.
He won't say why,
but I know it's because
you told him not to.
Honey, I... What?
I don't know what
your problem is.
You may not love
him anymore, but I do.
I mean, why you gotta be...?
Why you gotta be such a bitch?!
Hey, hey, hey. No,
no, no. Oh, God.
You can't talk to
your mom like that.
Hank, no. Hank.
Hank, it's... It's all right.
Hey, hey.
Skyler, I know
that you must have
your reasons for all
of this. [DOOR SLAMS]
Sky, the... Ahem.
I... I know it's none
of my business,
but keeping Walt
from the kids? I mean...
You're right, Hank.
It's none of your business.
MARIE: Oh, my
God. After all of that?
Please, tell me that
you are still not curious.
There's nothing to
be curious about.
Oh, please.
The day I heard the words
"second cell phone," I knew.
Believe me. Seen
it a hundred times.
Okay. All right.
So, what? Stop
dancing around it.
What is it exactly that you
have seen a hundred times?
Please, please, enlighten me.
Look, a guy like Walt?
Nice guy, decent, smart.
But, let's face
it, underachiever,
dead-end life, okay?
He gets cancer. Time's
running out. Mid-life crisis.
He acts up. He steps out.
And the wife, she catches him.
I mean, it's a story
as old as time.
Look, do the math, Marie.
It only comes out one way.
Knowing Walt, he felt so guilty,
he probably told her himself.
I... I don't know.
I think if he cheated on her,
she would have told me by now.
It just feels like
something more.
[CAR DOOR LOCK CHIRPS]
Yes, yes, yes, 24/7
coverage. Need you ask?
How much is this gonna run me?
Ha, ha. Jesus, I'm in
the wrong business.
Yeah, I'll call you.
Return of the prodigal,
welcome back to the living.
How you feeling? I'm good.
Of course. The world's
your oyster. Am I right?
Unencumbered young
man with, uh, stacks of cash.
Hey, I'm jealous. Hand
to God, I'm jealous.
You know, speaking of cash, uh,
you know what's giving
me heartburn lately?
Your former partner.
This guy, he works
like a bastard, right?
Builds a business single-handed.
Finally the big money shows up
and what does he
do? He walks out.
Talent like that and he
flushes it down the crapper.
It's like Michelangelo
won't paint. Heh.
Look, I know you're
out of it and all,
but you wouldn't talk
to him, would you?
Help him pull his
head out of his ass?
Yeah, all right, all
right, scratch that.
Yeah, he won't listen to me,
he's not gonna listen to you.
All due respect.
You want a job?
A job?
Who's got a job for me?
I do.
[LIGHT MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO]
[SNORING]
WOMAN: There you go.
[♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
[BELL DINGS]
[DINGS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[DINGING]
Hey. Hey.
Thought I'd, uh,
well, visit, if you don't
mind. Of course not.
You don't need the
room, do you? No, no, no.
I just... I just needed some
more space to spread out.
I just wanted to say
hello to little Holly here.
Hey, girl. Hi,
baby. Oh, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay. Oh, yeah.
She's a beauty. Look at her.
Hey, thanks for being so
flexible on me coming in.
I just wish we had
you back full-time.
You do brighten up the place.
Listen, believe
me, this is, uh...
I don't want to bring this up,
but I can't sign off
on these quarterlies.
I'm sorry, I just can't.
Is that right?
If you're gonna do this,
it can't be so glaring.
Glaring.
Okay.
That does sound bad. Show
me what's bothering you.
Keller.
Oh.
Again. Oh, God, I'm sorry. I
know how you feel about this.
Revenue with no backup.
Here, here and here. I
don't even know what to say.
Yeah, um...
Yeah, well, okay. This
is... This is fixable, right?
How about if I just
push 28,800, um,
out of this into next quarter?
Would you sign it then?
Um...
I'm just saying I can't
sign it as it currently exists.
Fair enough.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you for the heads-up.
You won't have to deal
with this again, I swear.
What if your kids found out?
If my kids found out?
This. What you're doing.
Someday they're
gonna be old enough.
How would you
explain it to them?
Well, put me on the
spot, why don't you?
I guess maybe I'd, um...
I'd say that, uh, I
might have feet of clay,
but that whatever I did,
I did thinking of them.
You know, trying to provide.
And I'd ask them to try to
take the time to understand...
[LAUGHS]
You know what? Truth is,
I haven't thought
that far ahead, Skyler.
I'm just trying to keep
my head above water, so...
I'd better get back to it.
[PHONE VIBRATING]
Oh, God.
Hi, Walt.
Listen, I can't tal...
I'm at work right now...
What?
Louis dropped him off. He
was here when I got home.
No, no, no, of course.
No, he's not staying.
He understands that.
I'll bring him
anywhere you want.
WALT JR.: Dad.
Well, yeah. It is rush hour.
I mean, I could fight traffic
and bring him down
to Beneke now.
But wouldn't it
be easier if we...?
Right, okay, good. So
we'll meet you at the house.
Okay, bye.
Why are you doing this?
She's just trying to
keep me from seeing you
and you're helping her.
Well, son, I mean, your
mother, she has her reasons.
What reasons?
They're, uh...
Well, they're...
Well, they're just a
little difficult to delineate.
But, I mean, yes,
there are two sides
to every story, always.
But she, uh...
Yeah.
This is just how it has
to be for now, okay?
Now, look, your
home is your home
and that is where
you belong, okay?
But it's where you belong.
Dad, it's your house.
Uncle Hank, Aunt Marie,
everybody knows that you
haven't done anything wrong.
Everybody is on your side.
Well, it's... It's not about
taking sides, though.
How can you let her
treat you like this?
Come on. How
can you just take it?
Now just listen to me, okay?
No matter what,
all of this has nothing to do
with how we feel
about you, okay?
We both love you
very, very much, okay?
You and your sister
will come first always.
Hm?
Come on.
Let's, uh...
Let's try to see this
in a positive light,
okay? Both of us.
Let's just buck up.
And I'll take you home.
Let me first just hit
the old bathroom here.
Hello. Good afternoon.
Nice to meet you. Saul Goodman.
MR. PINKMAN: Nice to meet you.
You're not that lawyer on
late-night television, are you?
Better call Saul!
Ha, ha, ha. Ha, ha.
I get it all the time.
We're here to discuss the sale
of the property at 9809 Margo.
I get it. Flat-fee
clients, am I right?
Well, folks, today's
your lucky day.
I represent a client who
shall remain nameless.
However, for our purposes,
you might just as well
visualize a large bag of money.
This individual wants to buy
your house today for cash.
Cash? Cash. I know,
in this economy.
In fact, the money is
already burning a hole
in my client's account.
You can ask Mr. Gardiner.
I've shown him the
pertinent financials.
It's the only reason
we're sitting here.
Fair enough. We get a few
papers signed and notarized,
we can take care
of this right now.
In fact, I could wire you your
money this very afternoon.
There's just one
little hair in the soup.
The price.
We feel 875 is very fair.
But I suppose there's
always a little, uh, wiggle room.
Well, why don't you
wiggle us on down to 400
and you got yourselves a deal?
Four hundred thousand?
What is that, a joke?
No, that's my offer.
That's less than half-price.
We put almost that much
into the renovations alone.
Why don't we just
cut the clown act
and you tell us what
you're willing to come up to?
Four hundred thousand.
That's my final offer.
This is a waste
of time. Ridiculous.
How could you imagine
we'd entertain this?
Come on.
I thought some
allowance was in order
once I heard about the meth lab.
The one that used
to be in the basement.
I looked over your signed
disclosure statements
and I don't see any
mention of a meth lab. Nope.
Oh, you got your termite
inspection. That's good.
But no meth lab.
Now, some would call that fraud
in service of
concealing a felony.
I, myself, am more
open-minded. But it is tricky.
Don't get me wrong. I
applaud your cojones.
I mean, good try
at sneaking a meth-contaminated
property past a buyer.
I mean, could've been a
good deal for you. Too bad.
Now, I could file a suit
and encumber this
property indefinitely.
Or I could start some
criminal proceedings.
But I don't think any of
us want that, now, do we?
How about it, counselor?
Do you concur?
[GRUNTS]
There you go, son.
Come on. It's
not Devil's Island.
[GRUNTS]
Okay.
Oh, hey. Hello.
Uh... Hm...
Brought pizza. Yeah.
Well, I'm making dinner.
Okay, I'll just
put it in the fridge.
It's even better the next day.
Hi, honey.
I...
Sorry.
Yeah.
Skyler.
I mean, what kind of example
do we want to set here, right?
I mean, can't we
at least just sit down
and eat a piece
of pizza together?
Just hash things
out like adults?
[CLANGING IN HOUSE]
We have discussed
everything we need to discuss.
I thought I made
myself very clear.
I got dipping sticks.
[DOOR LOCKS]
Argh!
[ENGINE STARTS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[♪♪♪]
[PHONE RINGING]
WALT [ON RECORDING]: You've
reached Walt's temporary number.
Please, leave a message.
[ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS]
SKYLER [ON PHONE]: Ugh. When I
went out this morning to get the newspaper
I saw a pizza on our roof.
Would you know
anything about that?
[GROANS] Listen to me, Walt.
You need to control yourself.
Calm down, accept the
situation and keep your distance.
If you can't manage that, I
will get a restraining order.
[BEEP]
Ugh!
Skyler. Skyler.
Got your restraining order
right here! Restrain this!
Oh.
[GROANS]
[GRUNTING]
Breaking even is not so bad.
In this economy, a lot of
people would kill to break even.
Poor Jake. He had his heart
set on going to Space Camp.
[CAR APPROACHING]
Oh, no.
Oh, God. This is all we need.
Hey, Mom, Dad. How's it going?
Jesse, it's really
not a good time.
Come on.
MRS. PINKMAN: Jesse,
the house has been sold.
The new owners are
expected at any moment.
Where do you think
you're going? Inside.
[JINGLING]
I bought the place.
SKYLER: Be back by 7, okay?
Love you.
Bye.
[TIMBER TIMBRE'S
"MAGIC ARROW" PLAYING]
♪ Mystic palm Gem and tarot ♪
♪ A few escape
Your magic arrow ♪
♪ I saw you reel
them in For miles ♪
♪ Each captivated
Crooked smile ♪
♪ And you know you
can Heal them all ♪
♪ Your double
diamond Disposition ♪
♪ Refractions of
Your center prism ♪
♪ Your magic arrow
Flies precision ♪
[DOOR BANGING]
Argh!
[GRUNTS]
[COUGHING]
[GRUNTING]
No!
Oh, God.
[CAR APPROACHING]
[♪♪♪]
[WALT SINGING AMERICA'S
"A HORSE WITH NO NAME"]
♪ It felt good To
get out of the rain ♪
[SINGING INDISTINCTLY]
[♪♪♪]
[WALT HUMMING]
[WALT HUMMING ON RADIO]
♪ La-la-la-la ♪
It's me. There's something
he should know about.
Hold on.
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
[♪♪♪]
[WALT SINGING AMERICA'S
"A HORSE WITH NO NAME"]
[WATER RUNNING]
WALT: ♪ In the desert You
can remember your name ♪
♪ 'Cause there ain't no
one For to give you no pain ♪
♪ La-la ♪
♪ La-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la ♪
[WALT HUMMING]
♪ You see I've been through ♪
♪ The desert On a
horse with no name ♪
[PHONE VIBRATING]
♪ In the desert You can
remember your name ♪
[WALT HUMMING]
♪ You see I've been
Through the desert ♪
♪ On a horse with no name ♪
♪ Felt good To
get out of the rain ♪
♪ In the desert You can
remember your name ♪
♪ No one for to
give You no pain ♪
♪ La-la-la ♪
[HUMMING]
[CLOCK TICKING]
[♪♪♪]