SKYLER: ♪ Hush, little
baby Don't say a word ♪
♪ Mama's gonna buy
You a mockingbird ♪
♪ And if that
mockingbird Won't sing ♪
[BABY COOING]
♪ Mama's gonna buy
you A diamond ring ♪
♪ And if that diamond
ring Turns brass ♪
♪ Mama's gonna buy
you A looking glass ♪
♪ So hush, little
baby Don't you cry ♪
♪ Daddy loves you And so do I ♪
[♪♪♪]
[ALARM BEEPING]
[BEEPING STOPS]
[♪♪♪]
Surprised he doesn't
make us do that.
JESSE: The pack totally
has a pecking order.
And the head hyena,
he's the man, you know.
All the other ones have
to, like, kiss his ass.
I mean, literally.
It's so gross.
They have to lick his junk.
I can't believe they
even showed it on TV.
[GROANS]
Yo, if this is
supposed to be all, like,
major-league and all,
we should have
equipment maintainer guys.
And water boys, you know?
Yo, Gatorade me, bitch.
Get us a couple
flunkies in here.
Treat us right.
JESSE: Okay, 15
hours starts now.
I'm gonna hit it, if
that's cool with you.
I don't understand. What?
These numbers,
they just don't add up.
Told you. Dude's
totally boning us.
No, it's not that.
It's our output. We're
off. We're .14 percent off.
Point one-four.
That's, what, like...?
What does that mean?
It means we should be
netting more than we're netting.
So how far off are we?
It's not negligible.
Ball-parking at it,
I'd say we're a quarter
to a half a pound shy.
That's weird.
Well, what about spillage?
Spillage?
You know, when, like,
just stuff gets spilled.
Nothing gets spilled.
A little maybe.
What about evaporation?
It wouldn't account
for this much.
The materials
aren't out that long.
What about the other one?
The drops, like on...
Like on, like, cold beer.
Condensation? Yeah.
No.
Well, what about the
crap that gets left behind?
You know, all the gunk
we scrape out of the vats.
Gotta add up to
like a gallon each.
Did you work that in?
Vestiges. Yeah. Vestiges.
Bet that's it.
Bet that's totally it.
[CLAPS]
Hey, Mr. White.
Mr. White. Huh?
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, why?
Nothing.
Are you coming?
Yeah, in a minute.
All right, see you tomorrow.
[FLY BUZZING]
All right.
Shit.
Bastard.
Son of a...
[YELLS]
Come on, you...
Come on, come on.
Son of a...
Ah!
Come on.
Son of a bitch.
Ha!
That's great.
[GROANS]
All right.
[FLY BUZZING]
You little bastard.
Ooh! Ooh!
[COUGHING]
[FLY BUZZING]
[♪♪♪]
[WIND WHISTLING]
WALT: Shut the door!
My ears are popping.
Shut the door. Move.
JESSE: Feels like on an
airplane. What the hell's doing that?
WALT: Positive pressure.
Positive what?
God, it frigging kills, yo.
Well, just move your jaw around.
I am moving it around.
It's not working. Just
yawn or something.
Stop acting like such a baby.
Damn.
What positive? Positive what?
Pressure. I've turned
the ventilation up
to keep the outside out.
There's been a contamination.
Wait. What?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey, hold up.
WALT: Something
got into the lab.
So, uh, what do we do?
I mean, do we...?
Wait. Wait. I mean,
shouldn't we be wearing masks?
No, no, it's not that
kind of contaminant.
So it's, like, not dangerous?
Mr. White, talk to me here.
Not to us particularly, no.
What the hell is that?
This is, uh...
I made it.
So exactly what
kind of contaminant
are we dealing with here?
A fly.
What do you mean?
A fly, like... Like,
what do you mean?
I mean, a fly. A housefly.
Like, uh, one fly?
Singular?
What did it do?
It got into the lab.
I'm trying to get it out.
Okay? Understand?
No, man, not really.
I can't say that I'm
really following you here.
Dude, you scared
the shit out of me!
When you say it's
contamination, I mean,
I'm thinking like an
Ebola leak or something.
Ebola.
Yeah, it's a disease on
The Discovery Channel
where all your intestines
sort of just slip
out of your butt.
Thank you. I know what Ebola is.
Uh-huh. Now, tell me.
What would a West African virus
be doing in our lab? Hm?
So you're chasing around a fly,
and in your
world, I'm the idiot.
Jesse, listen.
This fly...
No, any fly cannot
be in our lab.
It's a problem. It's
a contamination.
And that is in no way a
misuse of the word. Okay?
So in terms of
keeping our cook clean
and our product unadulterated,
we need to take
this very seriously.
Now do you understand?
So is that your fly-saber?
This is a swatter.
And it happens to work
quite well, thank you.
Uh-huh. Hey,
what happened to your head?
Nothing. I'm fine.
You didn't hit it, like
really, really hard?
My head is not
the problem, Jesse.
The fly is the problem.
You didn't happen to maybe
try our product, did you?
Jesse, I know this seems
unusual to you, a layman.
A fly. I get it. It seems
insignificant, right?
But trust me,
in a highly controlled
environment such as this...
any pollutant...
no matter how small...
could completely...
Hello?
What?
Were you here all night?
Have you even slept?
No. Jesse, look. I'm fine, okay?
Will you just
please focus on...?
[BEEPING]
[BEEPING STOPS]
Okay, look, we're running late,
so let's just get started.
The sooner we do it,
the sooner we're done.
Fricking finally.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?
It's time to alkaline.
Have you not
heard a word I said?
No cooking until
this fly is dealt with.
Have I been speaking to myself?
The timer went off, yo.
How long is this batch
gonna be good for?
An hour? Two?
The batch will be
good for nothing
if we don't clear
the contaminant.
"Clear the contaminant."
We're making meth here,
all right? Not space shuttles.
We're making nothing
until we catch this fly.
What fly? All right?
Where the hell is this fly?
Not like I even seen the thing.
Maybe your positive pressure
blew it out the
door or something.
No, no, it is here.
It is around, okay?
He's around,
and I am not going
to expose this batch
to the open air and
contamination, period.
Now, you can leave me
to deal with this myself
or you can help
me. But you are right.
We are running out of time.
So I need your answer right now.
Okay.
Hey, tick-tock, yo.
Look, I like making
cherry product,
but let's keep
it real, all right?
We make poison for
people who don't care.
We probably have the most
un-picky customers in the world.
No, no, no. No rationalizing.
We'll find it any
minute. Don't give up.
Did you know that there's
an acceptable level of rat turds
that can go into candy bars?
That's the government, Jack.
Even the government
doesn't care that
much about quality.
You know what is okay
to put in hotdogs, huh?
Pig lips and assholes.
But I say, hey,
have at it, bitches,
because I love hotdogs.
And, you know,
see what I'm try...?
What are you doing?
Oh, hey.
Look, let me just top it
off, all right, really quick.
You know, a little
sodium hydroxide,
shut the lid. No harm
done. Then we're golden.
It stays closed.
That's an order.
You can't order
shit, Adolf, all right?
We're 50-50 partners, remember?
Ow!
God, what is your problem?
Freaking psycho. Oh!
Jesse. Oh, God.
It, like, hit bone. Jesse.
Jesse.
You see it, right?
You see it?
Yeah.
Get it.
You want me to get it?
Yes.
Whoa.
Slow. Move slowly.
I know. I'm moving slowly, yeah.
Absolutely. I'm just gonna
need your swatter thing.
Come on.
Oh, yeah. It's okay, come on.
Yeah.
Yeah, come on.
Just make it count.
Yeah, no, no, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna make
it count, all right.
Okay. Now, on three.
Okay.
One...
Oh! Motherfuck...!
Yeah. You like that,
huh? Hurts, huh?
Did you get it?
I think so, yeah.
Where is it?
I don't know. What
does it matter?
Who cares? I got it.
Oh, Jesus,
seriously? Where is it?
It's right there. Look.
Look. See? I told you I got it.
This is a raisin.
Look, I definitely
got it, man, all ri...
[FLY BUZZING]
Oh, man.
He's got some skills, yo.
I'll give him that.
Look.
I feel like I'm running out of
ways to explain this to you,
but once more, I shall try.
This fly is a major
problem for us.
It will ruin our batch.
And we need to destroy it
and every trace of
it so we can cook.
Failing that...
we're dead.
There is no more room for error.
Not with these people.
All right, how about
we go get some air?
"Get some air"?
Your answer to,
"We're sliding headfirst
into a massive crap..."
Hey, hey, hey, Mr. White.
All right, I understand that
the fly is a serious thing now.
All right? I'm on board.
I'm just saying, you know,
maybe if we went
and got some air
it would help us come up
with a plan on how to catch it.
Then come back down
here and subtract his ass.
Oh, wait, do you
have your keys? Yeah.
You sure? Last thing we
need is to get locked out.
Yeah. Hey!
If you're not gonna help
me, stay out of my way!
Hey!
Yo, yo, does somebody
have an ax I can use? El ax-o!
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
El ax-o!
[CUMBRE NORTEÑA'S "SIMPLEMENTE
AMAME" PLAYING ON RADIO]
[FLY BUZZING]
There we go.
Say good night.
[CLATTERING]
Son of a bitch!
Son of a...
Damn it.
Where in the hell is that...?
What the hell?
[KNOCKING]
Need some juice maybe?
JESSE: Knock yourself out.
It's a real one.
Yeah, like yours was working.
No, no, no.
Look, we're trying
to decontaminate.
You don't decontaminate
by contaminating further.
What the hell is all this?
Here, how about this?
"Non-toxic glue strips."
Yeah, baby. It's got pheromones,
all right? I got a butt-load.
We hang them up
all over the place.
It won't be able to resist.
I sure hope we have enough.
JESSE: I'm gonna go
out on a limb and say yeah.
WALT: Do you see him?
How long do you think
you've been awake?
Why do you keep asking me that?
Just figure, you know,
you could use some
coffee, is all. I know I could.
How about it?
Yeah.
You take cream and
sugar? Black is fine.
Why don't you just leave him be?
Let the traps do the work.
These pheromones
are supposed to kick ass.
Bet we catch this
mofo any second.
Thank you.
You ever have,
like, a wild animal
trapped in your house?
Not that I can recall, no.
We did, this one time,
back when it was
my aunt's house,
back before she died of cancer.
It was a possum. Big
freaky-looking bitch.
Hey, since when did they
change it to "opossum"?
What's up with that?
I mean, when I was coming
up, it was just "possum."
You know, "opossum"
makes it sound
like he's Irish or something.
I mean, why they gotta
go changing everything?
Whatever. It's just
big rats anyways.
Giant pink-tailed rats
with their pink rat faces.
Totally freaky, like alien rats.
Actually, it's not so
much that he got trapped,
but he was living there,
you know, under the house.
You could hear him going
from, like, room to room,
always scurrying around.
Sometimes I'd see
him outside at night
and it would just,
you know, freeze.
I mean, it's like you're
not looking right at it, right?
I mean, it thinks
it's fooling you.
That's what they do.
I mean, they play
dead or whatever.
It's just so lame.
Is there a discernible
point to this story?
A point that you'll
be arriving at
sometime in the near future?
It was just a total
bitch to get out.
You know, it took forever.
Guy came, set all these traps
and all and he finally got it.
But my aunt, you know,
she didn't believe it.
I mean, she kept insisting
she could still hear the thing.
I mean, you could not
tell her any different.
She started keeping
an old umbrella,
you know, by her chair.
Man, she would just bang
on the floor and yell at it.
Even gave it a name.
It was Scrabble.
Yeah, that was it.
You know, "Scrabble,
just knock it off."
Bang, bang, bang.
She got like that
toward the end.
Got obsessive about stuff.
Just got mad about stuff.
We didn't know what was up.
It wasn't like her
to be that way.
But it turned out
that the cancer
had spread to her
brain and that was why.
It, um, metastasized.
But it was good that
that was when we decided
to take her to the doctor,
because then we
knew what was up.
You know, got her
some treatment.
Meds, so she wasn't
stressing all the time.
It was a lot better after that.
You know, she was a lot happier.
Where the hell is he?
I've been to my
oncologist, Jesse,
just last week.
I'm still in remission.
I'm healthy.
Okay, so good. Great.
Well...
no end in sight.
That's great.
Well...
I missed it.
There was some perfect
moment and it passed me right by.
I had to have
enough to leave them.
That was the whole point.
I mean, none of this...
None of this makes any
sense if I didn't have enough.
But it had to be before
she found out. Skyler.
It had to be before that.
Perfect moment for what?
To drop dead?
What, you saying you wanna die?
I'm saying I've lived too long.
I mean,
you want them to actually
miss you, you know?
You want their
memories of you to be...
But she just won't...
She just won't understand.
I mean, no matter
how well I explain it,
these days, she just has this...
This...
I mean, I truly
believe there exists
some combination of words.
There must exist certain
words in a certain specific order
that would explain all of this,
but with her, I just...
I just can't ever
seem to find them.
Mr. White, how about
you just sit down?
You know, I was thinking
maybe before the fugue state,
but before the fugue state,
I didn't have enough money.
So no, not then.
And plus, my daughter
wasn't born yet.
It had to be after
Holly was born.
Mr. White...
Definitely before the surgery.
Oh, Christ.
That damn second cell phone.
I mean, how could I possibly...?
Ah, I know the moment.
It was the night Jane died.
Yeah, I...
I was at home and
we needed diapers,
and so I said I'd go,
but it was just an excuse.
Actually, that was the night
I brought you your
money, remember?
Yeah, I remember.
But afterward, I
stopped at a bar.
It was odd. I never do that,
go to a bar alone.
I just walked in, sat down.
I never told you.
That you went to a bar?
No, I...
I sit down and this
man, this stranger,
he engages me in conversation.
He's a complete stranger.
But he turns out to be
Jane's father, Donald Margolis.
What are you talking about?
Of course, I didn't
know it at the time.
I mean, he was just
some guy in a bar.
I didn't put it together
until after the crash
when he was all over the news.
Jane's dad.
I mean, think of the odds.
Once I tried to calculate them,
but they're astronomical.
I mean, think of the odds
of me going in, sitting down,
that night in that
bar next to that man.
What did you talk about?
Oh...
Water on Mars.
Family.
What about family?
I told him that I had a daughter
and he told me he had one too.
Then he said,
"Never give up on family."
And I didn't.
I took his advice.
The universe is
random. It's not inevitable.
It's simple chaos.
It's subatomic particles in
endless aimless collision.
That's what science teaches us.
But what is this saying?
What is it telling us when,
on the very night that
this man's daughter dies,
it's me who's having
a drink with him?
I mean, how can that be random?
Hey, come on. Hey, sit down.
No, no. No, it's...
No. No.
No, that was the moment.
That night.
I should never have left home.
Never gone to your house.
Maybe things would have...
Oh, thought I was...
I was at home watching TV.
It was some...
Some nature program
about elephants.
And Skyler and Holly
were in another room.
I could hear them
on the baby monitor.
She was singing a lullaby.
If I had just lived right
up to that moment,
and not one second more...
[FLY BUZZING]
that would have been perfect.
Yeah. He's not coming down.
Must be Thailand-hot up there.
That's why he likes it.
Thailand's hot, right?
Yeah.
Then that's why.
Oh, Jesus. Hey, hey, wait. Here.
[WHEELS ROLLING]
He's not coming down.
He's staying up there forever.
[CLATTERING]
What are you...?
What are you doing?
What do you think?
I'm gonna get that bitch.
No, you're gonna
break your neck.
Yeah, yeah. Just...
WALT: No, seriously,
you're... This is a bad idea.
[JESSE GRUNTING]
JESSE: Damn it.
WALT: Jesse.
Just hold onto it.
Hold it still?
[JESSE GRUNTING]
[FLY BUZZING]
[CREAKING]
Jesse.
I'm sorry.
Sorry for what, being a lunatic?
I'm sorry about Jane.
Yeah.
Me too.
I mean...
I'm very sorry.
It's not your fault.
It's not mine either.
It's no one's fault,
not even hers.
You know, we are
who we are, Mr. White.
You know, two junkies
with a duffel bag full of cash.
Like you said, we both would've
been dead within a week.
But I miss her, though.
God, I do.
Whoa. Whoa.
Jesse.
Come down.
Wait. I'm so close.
Let it go.
We need to cook.
What about the contamination?
It's all contaminated.
[FLY BUZZING]
JESSE: All right, well,
I definitely scared him.
Probably stay out of our way.
[FLY BUZZING]
Yeah! Oh, zap!
Somebody got got, yo!
Did you see that, Mr. Wh...?
[WALT SNORING]
Bins are packed?
Bins are packed.
How's the yield?
Two-oh-two and change.
You okay getting home?
Yeah. Better. Thanks.
Mañana, then.
Jesse, come here.
I couldn't chance
saying it inside.
For all I know, the
lab's wired for sound.
That's half a pound
I said we were off by.
Now, I'm not
accusing you, but if...
You understand? And
if they ever found out...
I didn't take shit.
I'm just saying that I won't
be able to protect you.
Who's asking you to?
[FLY BUZZING]
[♪♪♪]