So cigarettes and gas is $79.70.
Crap.
There's an ATM right outside.
Yeah, I don't have a card.
Well, you can write a
personal check with ID.
Kind of in between
banks right now.
You think I could
just come back later?
I'm totally good for it.
I'd come back, I swear.
If it were me, I'd be totally,
you know, "No problem."
But my dad is this
ginormous hard-ass.
He was in Fallujah for a year.
And he always
checks the receipts.
I mean, like, always.
I gotta call him. I'm sorry.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on a second.
Maybe we could...
trade.
Ever try it?
I mean, I smoke
pot a lot sometimes.
I party.
But...
But that stuff's
really addictive, right?
Not really. It's just a
media thing. You know?
What's it like?
It's awesome.
Everything's
maximum interesting.
You get these really cold and
sharp-like action
dagger feelings.
It's awesome.
Come on. What do you say?
[DOOR BEEPING]
Have a nice day.
[♪♪♪]
SAUL: So how does it feel?
Does it hurt?
Yeah, it's tight.
SAUL: Yeah, but is it painful?
It's hard to breathe.
Well, you need your
breathing. Heh, heh.
Although let's not
lose sight of the fact
that you were the victim of
a terrible accident, Antonio,
so some discomfort
is to be expected.
["BATTLE HYMN OF THE REPUBLIC"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Let's go with that one.
[SAUL SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
A cashier's check, por favor.
Oh, and spread the word.
I'm building a
class-action, flight 515.
Victims' families
would be great.
I'll take anyone on the ground
who suffered emotionally.
Anxiety, sleeplessness.
You get the picture.
Trouble?
WALT [ON RECORDING]: Ted
Beneke? You cannot be serious.
That guy is a joke.
SKYLER: You called my bluff.
WALT: What does that mean?
SKYLER: You dared
me to tell the police
and I couldn't
do it, so you win.
If you want to stay
in this house, fine,
but we are not married anymore.
WALT: I told you that I was
done cooking meth, Skyler.
I promised you that.
SKYLER: So what?
WALT: At least I
didn't run off to go...
Jesus! I mean,
everything that I did,
I did for this family.
SKYLER: Just keep
telling yourself that.
WALT: What's that mean?
SKYLER: You don't
like it, then leave.
And take your drug money.
WALT: That's what you want.
[LOUD WHIRRING ON RECORDING]
Jesus.
Garbage disposal.
WALT: You think this
will get me to move out?
You can screw Ted, you can screw
the butcher, the mailman.
Whoever you want.
Screw them all.
I'm not going anywhere.
SKYLER: Suit yourself.
[DOOR SLAMS ON RECORDING]
Is this a good or bad thing?
WALT: Suit myself. You
want me to suit myself?
I'll suit myself to his face!
It's a bad thing.
Hello.
Walter White to see Ted Beneke.
I'm sorry. Mr. Beneke's
on a conference call.
Mm. Hmm. Okay.
I will wait.
It could be a while.
I have all the
time in the world.
Okay.
[CHUCKLES]
Here we go. Okay. Excuse me.
Mr. Beneke's not
available. Ted? Come on.
RECEPTIONIST: Sir, excuse me.
Excuse me.
Ted, I can see you.
I can see you standing
right there in your office.
Now, come on.
Open the door.
Come on, let's talk.
I just want to talk. That's all.
Come on, let's be men about
this. Okay? How about that?
Aha.
Hey, Walt. I'm kind of in
the middle of something now.
Oh, yes, you are.
So open the door.
You're damn right.
You're right in the middle.
Just open the door and
let's talk about it, okay?
Open the door, Ted, right now.
You don't want to
be a man about it?
Plan B. How do
you like that? Plan B.
RECEPTIONIST:
We have a situation.
Walt. Walt. Walt.
What are you doing?
I'm talking with Ted.
Next time, you'll open the door.
MAN: Freeze! Come
on. WALT: Oh, damn it.
No, I'm just here to talk.
I just want to talk to him.
MAN: Outside. Let's go.
WALT: God. Can I just
talk? I just want to talk to him.
Calm down. I'm
just... Okay, all right.
All right, all right, all
right. I'm calm. I'm calm.
MAN: Asshole.
Ow!
What do you want?
Hey! Hey, come on.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You act like you're the
first guy this happened to.
I caught my second wife
screwing my stepdad, okay?
It's a cruel world,
Walt. Grow up.
I just wanted to talk to him.
Yeah, well, now
I'm talking to you.
Consider this an intervention.
You could have been arrested
back there. You understand.
Speaking as your lawyer,
I'm always looking
for billable hours.
But speaking as your
business associate,
I'm strongly advising that
you get your shit together.
Just cool it with this Beneke
guy, at least for now. Okay?
Let's talk shop, because I
think this is a great opportunity
to channel some of that negative
energy into something positive.
How did you know? Sorry?
About Skyler. About
where to find me just now.
How did you know?
That's just my meticulousness.
Don't bog down in detail, Walt.
The lesson here should
be... Did you bug my house?
[SCOFFS]
Yeah, but I didn't know
it was your house, did I?
You'd moved out. Besides,
you basically told me to.
I told you to?
You strongly
hinted that I should.
You were worried your wife
might say something to the police.
What? No, no, that's not true.
When the hell did I say that?
Let's not get lost in the
who, what and whens.
The point is we did our due
diligence and she didn't talk.
She kept quiet. She
stood by you, Walt,
which, if you ask me, is
the ironical silver lining here.
I mean, on the one hand,
sure, she snuck
off the reservation
to get some dirty,
damp and deep.
On the other hand...
[GRUNTING]
Off me.
You're fired!
You're done! SAUL: Good!
"Oh, boohoo, I won't
cook meth anymore."
You're a crybaby. Who needs you?
I'm unplugging the website,
so no more money laundering.
How do you like that?
I want those bugs
out of my house today.
I want them out now!
You just bought a
$300 suit, psycho!
Go.
Great, drilled right
into the stucco.
Oh.
A little bit of
putty, you'll be fine.
Just make sure you
get all of those things.
A, these things
cost $800 apiece.
B, you're not that interesting.
So yeah, I'll get
all of them, Walter.
Great line of work, by the way.
Real upstanding field.
Yeah, well,
I enjoy it.
You're free to
leave now. Anytime.
You know, Walter,
sometimes it doesn't hurt to
have someone watching your back.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[♪♪♪]
CARMEN: Mr. White?
Hi.
What's up?
CARMEN: I can't begin to understand
what you're going through, Walt,
with all of your health concerns
and the stresses
you've been under.
But still, as educators,
there are certain
responsibilities
we need to be meeting here
to the school and to
the students themselves.
Of course.
Is this a Wheaten Terrier?
Uh... Norfolk.
Norfolk?
That's surprising.
Walt, could you come back over
here and have a seat, please?
Sure.
You've been
absent a lot recently.
And when you are here at school,
there have been some
behavioral questions.
And frankly I'm concerned.
Thank you.
Are you feeling okay?
Do you think maybe
I should call Skyler?
Um...
No.
Let's just keep this...
What...?
Hey!
Walt, what's wrong with you?
[WOMAN ON PA
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
You know, look, you're the one
always talking about D.C., okay?
This is how you get there.
You answer the bell.
You pay your dues.
Besides, you know, it's a
big deal to get picked for this.
El Paso's like the Super Bowl.
I could get killed
crossing the street, okay?
Whatever. You
know, I want to go.
What about last time?
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Schrader.
Hey, sheriff. Yeah.
Blue, huh?
Yeah, yeah. Thing is...
Thing is I'm supposed to be
getting on a plane right now.
The stuff this guy had was
blue. You sure about that?
Yeah.
Yeah, I want to talk to him.
Taxi.
[HORN HONKS]
Hi. Man, I'm sorry.
I needed to talk to you, but
you weren't at your apartment.
No, I moved back home.
That's good, right?
Yeah.
Yo, did you just get fired?
No.
No, no, no.
It's more like a sabbatical.
Indefinite. Yeah.
So, what's up?
Should we go somewhere?
No, this is fine.
So I want an intro to your guy.
What guy?
Your guy. Your distribution guy.
The guy Saul hooked you up with.
No, no, no. Come on, Jesse.
I thought about it... God.
And I want to.
It's the one thing I'm good at.
No, that is just not true.
You're good at a
lot of things, son.
Like what?
What about your sobriety?
I told you, I'm not using.
Ever.
I just want back
into the business.
Well, I don't. I'm sorry.
I know, and that's cool.
I'm not asking you to cook.
What's this?
In the end, I just went
with two reflux condensers.
I didn't want to lose
track of my pH levels.
But I did everything else
just like you taught me.
Super careful in my amounts
and watched the numbers
every step of the way.
So, what do you
think? It's good, right?
What in the hell is this?
What? What?
This. This.
This is my product.
This is my formula.
This is mine.
It's our product, but yeah,
I was gonna cut you in.
Oh, you were gonna cut me in?
No, no, no. I cut you in.
What the hell is your problem?
All I'm asking is for
you to set a meet.
Absolutely not. Why?
Because I am not gonna lend
my name to an inferior product.
I mean, look at
the diameters here.
What did you use for reduction?
Don't tell me.
Platinum dioxide, right?
No. Mercury-aluminum amalgam.
The dioxide's too
hard to keep wet.
All right, well, you
must've done it wrong, then.
Your color is all cloudy,
so you were struggling
with distillation too.
Now, this is very
shoddy work, Pinkman.
I'm actually
embarrassed for you.
What?
No way. I gave out samples
and everyone said
it was the bomb.
[SCOFFS]
Oh, they said it was the bomb.
And who were they, I wonder?
A bunch of meth heads?
Yeah. Yeah.
They should know,
right? Yeah, well, sorry.
I can't help you. Fine, ass-wad.
I'll contact the guy myself.
Oh, yeah? Well, good luck.
Because my guy is a pro and
he doesn't deal with junkies.
You know what? Eat
me. Anytime, loser.
Hey, hey, hey!
Wait. Hey!
[♪♪♪]
I can't believe it's only 4:00.
This day is dragging.
[WHISPERING] Okay.
[SKYLER MOANING]
I wish I could stay.
TED: So stay.
What's stopping you?
Heh, heh. What, like
everything, you mean?
How about my lunatic husband
refusing to leave the house?
[CLEARS THROAT]
So move in here.
And then my son
hating me even more.
That'll pass. I went
through that with the girls.
They adapt.
And now everyone at work thinks
I'm an evil
ladder-climbing whore.
They're all fired,
effective immediately.
What else? Heh, heh, heh.
Oh, aren't you the answer man?
Where did it, um...? Ahem.
Where did it go wrong,
exactly, with you and Walt?
I mean, I always
saw him as kind of...
mild-mannered.
Something, I don't know,
change when he got sick or...?
I don't know what changed, Ted.
And I just don't feel really
comfortable talking about it.
Sorry.
Just asking out
of self-interest.
Gotta make sure I don't
make the same mistake.
I would be amazed.
Just let me see if I'm
following you here, Russell.
You got this stuff from
some guy at Gasparza's
who was wearing tan pants
and who you're 80 percent
sure had a mustache.
That's it, right?
That's your brain working
at maximum capacity?
[GRUNTING AND PANTING]
Russell.
Everything all right in there?
Mel. The dude's name was Mel.
Well, there you go. See?
You served an
actual earthly function.
I can't believe I
remembered that.
Mel who? Does he
have a last name?
Yeah, uh, Mel.
Wait.
Was it Mel
or Mark?
It was definitely an M name.
Oh, man, I'm losing it.
Wait, wait.
Yeah.
It's gone.
It was an M name though. Yeah.
I remember the "muh" sound.
All right, well, we'll go
with the "muh" sound.
Thanks a lot.
Appreciate it. Yeah.
He definitely had tan pants.
Remind me to get a vasectomy.
Okay, it's after 9, so this
bar that Girl George is at,
probably wall-to-wall
dirtbags by now.
Let's go have
a little looky-loo,
see if we can't find
this M-named clown.
What? It's a lead.
Lead to what? To Heisenberg.
I told you it was
only a matter of time
before this guy booted up again.
Here we go, my friend.
Don't hate me because
I'm beautiful, Gomey.
Just apologize
and buy me a beer.
Man, you're reaching.
This stuff could be a knockoff
or left over from an older cook.
How do you know
Heisenberg's gearing up again?
How do I know?
Because I know.
I don't get it.
This is the reason why you're
blowing off the task force?
Chase down teeners?
I'm getting tired of all
the second-guessing.
If you're not
sufficiently stimulated
by this investigation,
do us both a favor
and ask for a transfer.
What is up with you lately?
Starting bar fights,
turning down El Paso,
and now this bullshit?
Do you need to talk
to someone or what?
Talk to someone?
Talk to who?
I'm not trying to step
on your toes, bro. Okay?
I'm just worried
about you. That's all.
Appreciate that, bro.
Now take your
hand off my shoulder.
Yeah, yeah, the
one that was on TV.
Did any little piece
fall on your property?
I'm not looking for an
entire wing here, Mr. Linkas.
It could be a nut or a bolt.
It could be a bag of peanuts,
just so long as it caused
you pain and suffering.
Oh, no, no, no. Closed.
Calling you back.
You had your chance. I told
you to get him cooking again.
You blew it off and
now it's too late.
The guy's gone
mass maniac on us!
All I wanted was to show
you two your potential.
And what do I get in
return? A bone contusion.
You wanna see the
scar? I wish you two had...
Hi, there.
How in the hell did
you get Walt to...?
I made it.
You know the guy who
knows the guy, right?
Well, good news is
for a stage-three cancer,
the guy's doing well physically.
Mentally, the guy's a disaster.
He's gone off the rails
over this thing with his wife.
My opinion, he's not
coming back. Not on his own.
Your friends were at his
place again, by the way.
They drew something on
the street outside his house.
The scythe.
Animals.
Does the lawyer know? Should he?
No.
If you want this guy to produce
again, why not just tell him?
You stand between him
and an ax in the head.
I don't believe fear to
be an effective motivator.
I want investment.
For now, I'm simply
interested in time frame.
He will live for the
foreseeable future, yes?
Foreseeable.
Couple years at least,
barring acts of God
and men with axes.
Oh.
From the lawyer, I'm
supposed to let you know
the Pinkman kid
is looking to sell.
I don't work with junkies.
That's what I thought you'd say.
Probably for the best.
What I hear, he and
Walter are splitsville.
Really?
That's what Goodman
says. Cats and dogs.
Do the deal.
Mm.
Hmm.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[CELL PHONE BEEPING]
WOMAN [OVER PHONE]:
You have one unheard message.
MAN [ON RECORDING]: Agent Schrader,
you need to be calling me back ASAP.
I've got Texas breathing down
my neck and I'm not about...
CARA: No, I haven't seen Matt
since my dad fired
him, like, a while ago.
Where can I find him, you think?
No idea. Haven't seen him.
I know. You said
that a few times.
Yeah, because I
haven't seen him.
I don't know what else to say.
What's your name, darling? Cara.
Where did this come from, Cara?
I... I... I don't know.
What is it? Drugs?
Look, I'm just gonna
come right out and say it.
You're a bad liar, Cara.
Don't get me wrong. Not
the worst I've ever seen.
Once had a guy try to explain
the dope balloon up his butt
on bad Thai food.
Still, you're not
a very good liar.
I honestly don't know... Stop.
You look like a good kid. I'm
not here to get you in trouble.
But you need to tell me
where this came from right now!
I never do stuff like
this. I swear to God.
I tried it and I hated it,
so I just gave it to Matt.
Okay, and who gave
it to you? Some guy.
He came in a couple days ago
and wanted to trade it for gas.
Some guy? What's his name?
Okay, what...?
What did he look like?
[CRYING]
I don't know.
He looked pretty normal.
You know, um, white.
I think his hair
was lightish brown.
He had really blue eyes.
They were really, really blue.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
dreamy. Okay, what else?
Piercings, jewelry, distinctive
articles of clothing. Come on.
Come on.
Listen to me.
It's real important that I find
the person that had these drugs.
So if you can remember
anything else...
Come on, think. Come
on, now. Come on.
He drove an RV.
Okay, good, good.
What can you remember?
What kind of RV?
What color? Did you
spot a license plate?
I don't know the kinds,
and I didn't see the license.
But the color was, I think,
white, brownish color.
I'm sorry.
I know I'm not helping you...
but, please, don't tell my dad.
[SOBBING]
Cara.
Please, tell me that
that camera works.
Damn it.
[♪♪♪]
Bingo.
These eggs are good, Mom.
Thanks.
WALT JR.: Hey, you know
what's weird? Dad's website.
It's been three days
since the last donation.
Yeah, well, people
lose interest.
Um...
So how long are you off for?
A few weeks.
I'll play it by ear.
I probably pushed it,
you know, going
back to work too soon.
Think I can get a ride today?
Louis has a
doctor's appointment.
Yeah.
Hey, so, Dad can
babysit now, right?
You won't have to take
Holly to work every day.
Sometime, maybe.
Yeah, we'll see.
[♪♪♪]
What's up?
I think you'll
seriously enjoy, yo.
[ENGINE STARTS]
Wait. No, no. No way.
Hey! Hey!
Hey. What the hell?
This is only half.
That's right. It's your half.
Yo, where's the
other half, bitch?
I mean, the whole
thing was crazy.
Poor bastard. I
felt sorry for him.
I think he actually thought we
were the cable guys, you know.
Anyway, uh, sorry about
those missed calls, chief.
I'm changing providers.
It won't happen again.
Are you going to El Paso, Hank?
Hell, yes. With pointy
boots and bells on.
Got this break in
the Heisenberg case.
The blue meth, you
mean? The teenth?
Yeah, well, that
teenth got things rolling.
I traced it to a gas
station in Cibola.
That's where I got these.
The station's closed-circuit
was down... Surprise, surprise.
But I was able to pull
some of these snapshots
off an ATM security camera.
We always thought these
guys might be camper-cooking.
First off, your typical
Class C motor home
is gonna grunt at least 5000
pounds of interior fixtures.
Appliances,
furniture, built-ins,
5000 pounds at least, okay?
See how high that
suspension's riding?
No way, no how, this thing's
carrying that kind of weight.
This thing has been cleared out
and stripped down
to its tight-and-curlies.
For what? Blood bank?
Maybe a bookmobile?
There's no clear
view of the plates.
Yeah, well, you can
only get so lucky, right?
But there's no front
plate. Tells me it's likely
New Mexico registration.
I check with DMV.
There are only 29 of
these early-'80s Bounders
registered in the state.
Only 29?
Yeah.
So I gotta go, you know,
knock on some doors.
They need you in El Paso, Hank.
You bet. I'm just gonna wrap
up this Heisenberg thing first.
You're refusing the
assignment. I'm not. I'll go.
It's just I need some more time.
You're not hearing
me, Agent Schrader.
You're out of time.
Are you going to El
Paso now, tonight?
It's a simple yes or no.
No. I can't.
But that's only
because I'm really close
to something big here.
Better get to it, then.
MAN [ON RADIO]: This is KECA
480, Albuquerque's news radio.
KECA news time, 10:13.
Our top story this
hour, Donald Margolis,
the air-traffic controller
criticized for his role
in the recent air disaster
in which 167 persons died,
was rushed to an area
hospital early this morning,
apparently the victim of a
self-inflicted gunshot wound.
Police won't say
whether or not...
[CHANGES STATION]
♪ All I took Was just one look ♪
♪ It has just begun ♪
♪ The two of us are one ♪
♪ Spending all our days ♪
♪ In the Valley of the Sun ♪
♪ Here eyes were
like The velvet stars ♪
[MAN WHISTLES]
[GRUNTS]
Your half.
♪ All I took was Just one look ♪
♪ I knew that this
Was really love ♪
[CAR HORN HONKING]
Okay, okay.
♪ The two of us are one ♪
♪ Spending all our days ♪
♪ In the Valley of the Sun ♪
[♪♪♪]