WOMAN [OVER
RADIO]: KDK-12, come in.
KDK-12. KDK-12.
WOMAN: Hey, Bobby, need
you to look in on Mrs. Peyketewa.
Is she all right?
Her daughter called
from California.
She hasn't heard from her
in a while, kind of worried.
Will do.
[BIRD CAWING]
[CHAIN JINGLING]
Miss Peyketewa, hello.
Miss Peyketewa.
[♪♪♪]
[DOORKNOB RATTLES]
[FLIES BUZZING]
[♪♪♪]
KDK-12 here. Janet,
Jesus, we got a homicide.
WOMAN: Come again?
Miss Peyketewa, she's dead.
I need some backup out
here. Okay. On their way.
Whoever's in there,
show yourself right now!
Hold it right there.
Let me see your hands.
Hands!
All right, down.
On your knees.
You understand me?
Do you speak English?
[COP SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
I said, down. On
your knees. Down!
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
[♪♪♪]
Damn it, get down.
On your knees.
Do it.
On your knees or I'll fire!
[♪♪♪]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Yeah? SKYLER: I
found the papers.
Right where you
left them, in the crib.
Yeah, well...
You know best, right?
Anything else?
Do you have any thought
about how we're going to
approach this with Walter Jr.?
WALT: Well, he's still my son.
I mean, he will
remain... Of course.
My point being
the divorce.
Well, I, uh...
I think he gets it, don't you?
I mean, I...
I think he saw it coming.
He sees your unhappiness and...
SKYLER: My unhappiness?
My completely out-of-the-clear
blue-sky unhappiness?
Really?
WALT: Look, as
you said, for the best.
Yeah.
Okay. Um...
Last thing and
then I'll let you go.
In the child support worksheet,
you list medical, dental,
child care, transportation,
housing, education,
food, clothing.
That's right, all of it.
Walt.
No. Skyler, you wanted me out,
I'm out, but I will
provide for my family.
Not with that money.
You'd be making us
accessories after the fact.
How do you think we've
been paying our bills
these last six months?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
I have to go.
Yep, I was right.
Three units available,
exact same floor plan.
I can call over, get you
in to see any of the others.
No, no, this one's fine.
I'll take it.
[CHUCKLES]
Now, unfortunately, this
one is the model, so...
Yeah, I like it.
I like everything about it.
I'll take it as-is.
[CHUCKLES]
Name one thing in this
world that is not negotiable.
You have to clean
the fryer. Yes, sir.
GUS: We try to clean
them every night,
but make sure it's off before
you open the intake valve.
Good. Now, I suggest
that you add this to your
Monday maintenance schedule.
MANAGER: Yes, sir.
Now, select freezing mode,
clock button off, press and
hold auto-control until it beeps.
Main valve on, main switch on.
Give the compressor time for
the needle to enter the green.
Yo, for real?
This is all you? All me.
PETE: Heisenberg
who? That's what I say.
My man Jesse can cook.
Check it, yo. It ain't
cloudy or dirty or nothing.
Just the right shade of
blue. BADGER: Good shade.
Check out that crystal size.
If that bitch was any bigger,
it would be a Jolly
Rancher. Be my guest.
You sure?
I feel kind of dickish with
you being in rehab and all.
No. I can watch, yo.
I can cook and I can
watch. PETE: Go for it.
I tried it last week.
I'm still coming down.
Go easy.
Okay.
[SNIFFS]
[BADGER LAUGHS]
[GRUNTING]
Whoo! Riverdance.
Hey, hey, stop marking up
my floor, dumb-ass. Come on.
[LAUGHING]
Bow before me.
Wow.
I am Lord of the Dance. Huh?
Shit.
I gotta try that again.
Yeah, no, I think you're good.
That is awesome, Jesse.
I feel like somebody
took my brain out
and boiled it in,
like, boiling hot...
It's the bomb, man, seriously.
Like... Like anthrax.
[CHUCKLES] Good.
So, um...
you ready to talk some business?
You mean this is not,
like, just recreational?
I know
what you're thinking.
Trust me, it's not
gonna be like it was.
All right, never
How's that? We sell it safe.
All right? We sell it smart.
We don't get
greedy, like before.
I don't know, man.
Combo and all.
Still,
man's gotta make his living.
If it's like Jesse says
and we're not greedy...
I mean,
I guess I can see it.
Had a good thing going before
we started pushing our luck.
If it can go back
to being like that...
Hey, it will be.
Step one, we build inventory.
Badger, go see Clovis.
Get the RV in shape,
tune-up, oil change,
brake lights, and whatnot.
Cops always pull you
over for brake lights. Not us.
Cautious.
Right on. You got it.
You know that buzzer thing?
Leave the key in the
ignition, and it buzzes?
Just have him put
in one of those too.
Skinny, you're in
charge of supplies.
I'll get you a list.
PETE: Right on.
Yeah?
BADGER: Yeah. All right.
JESSE: So, uh...
we good? BADGER: Yeah.
Good?
All right. PETE:
Let's do this thing.
Brandon Mayhew.
I know you.
Small world, Albuquerque.
[ALARM BEEPS AND BUDDY
STUART'S "SUN SHINE ON ME" PLAYS]
♪ So shine on me today ♪
♪ Sun, drown my tears away ♪
♪ How I need Your warm embrace ♪
♪ To shine upon My crying face ♪
♪ Poor sun, shine on me today ♪
♪ Sunshine ♪
♪ Come on, sunshine ♪
♪ Let me have One of your rays ♪
♪ Sun, shine on me today ♪
♪ Sun, dry my tears away ♪
♪ Make the trees
And flowers grow ♪
♪ And you can make
My troubles go ♪
♪ Sun, shine on me today ♪
WALT: Wanna talk about it?
Why? It's not like I get a vote.
You know, ironically,
I think you're gonna see
much more of me from now on.
Sure.
Well, just as much
of me at least.
I'm taking you to the school,
to and from, every day.
What, I don't get a
vote in this either?
I gotta stop going with Louis
just because
you're feeling guilty?
I do feel guilty.
I am the man that I am, son,
and there's plenty that I
would change about that, but...
Here we are,
and this is just what it is.
You know what? Call me crazy,
but I'm actually feeling
very good about the future.
GUS: Morning.
They're back.
I'm wondering if we should
maybe call the police or something.
Why?
They're doing nothing wrong.
Okay, let's put this
on Table 33, okay?
[WORKERS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[WHIRRING]
MAN: Hello there.
Uh, Mr. White, I presume?
WALT: Oh, yes. Hi.
I, um...
Sorry. I-I'll, uh...
I'll be right down.
Hi. Gale Boetticher. Hi.
You're my new lab
assistant, I take it.
Yes, I am.
I suppose you'll wanna
hear my qualifications.
I have my résumé here for you.
I received my bachelor's
degree from UNM.
My master's from the
University of Colorado.
Organic chemistry
with a specialty in...
It's all right there.
"X-ray crystallography."
Really?
I could talk about
that for hours.
Ah, I would love to.
But first, I'm
curious about this.
Uh, that's a little
pet project of mine.
See, in my opinion, it's all
about the quinic acid level.
You want just north of
4800 milligrams per liter,
but if you over-boil
to get there,
you'll leach your tannins.
Bitterness, yuck.
So I pull a mild vacuum.
That way, I can
keep the temperature
no higher than 92 C and...
Let's see...
Judge for yourself.
Oh, my God.
My God, that is the best
coffee I've ever tasted.
[CHUCKLES]
Sumatran beans,
and I also have to
give credit to the grind,
but thank you, Mr. White. Walt.
Please, call me Walt.
Why the hell are we making meth?
[VINCE GUARALDI'S
"GINZA" PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
[CORK POPS]
Hey. Heh, heh.
Tell me,
with the phenylacetic
acid solution,
you said 150 drops per
minute for the first 10 minutes
and then 90 for the
remainder. Why is that?
Well, my thinking is,
by tapering the phenyl,
you get an oilier aqueous
layer, and hence...
Better benzene extraction.
Exactly.
But actually, I prefer ether.
Oh, I'll have it for tomorrow.
Gale, I'm wondering how you...
Ended up here.
Well, actually,
I'm still wondering
how I ended up here, but, yes.
I mean, I can't imagine
we strike each
other as criminals.
Well, there's crime
and then there's crime,
I suppose.
I'm definitely a libertarian.
Consenting adults
want what they want,
and if I'm not supplying it,
they will get it somewhere else.
With me, they're getting
exactly what they pay for.
No added toxins or adulterants.
Yeah, I was doing it the
way you are supposed to,
pursuing my doctorate at
Colorado, NSF research grant.
I was on my way,
jumping through hoops,
kissing the proper behinds,
attending to all
the non-chemistry
that one finds
oneself occupied by.
You know that world. Hm.
That is not what
I signed on for.
I love the lab.
Because it's all still magic.
You know?
Chemistry?
I mean,
once you lose that...
It is.
It is magic.
It still is.
[BOTH LAUGH]
And all the while, I
kept thinking about
that great old Whitman poem:
"When I Heard the
Learn'd Astronomer."
I... I don't know it.
Oh, anyway...
Well, can you recite it?
[LAUGHS]
Pathetically enough, I could.
All right, well... Oh.
No, no, come on. Come on.
Yeah?
When I heard The
learn'd astronomer
When the proofs, the figures
Were ranged in columns Before me
When I was shown the
charts And the diagrams
To add, divide And measure them
When I, sitting
Heard the astronomer
Where he lectured
With much applause
In the lecture-room
How soon, unaccountable
I became tired and sick
Till rising and gliding out
I wander'd off by myself
In the mystical moist night-air
And from time to time
Look'd up in perfect
silence At the stars
Yes.
I am a nerd.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Bravo. Thank you.
HANK: Come on, Pinkman.
You little rat bastard.
Get off your lazy ass
and go break the law.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hey, baby. MARIE: Are
you ever coming home?
Marie, I'm working, all right?
Did you find it? The RV?
HANK: No. Working on it, so...
Why can't you just arrest
him, make him tell you?
It's not that simple.
There's a thing
called the Constitution.
Constitution, blah, blah, blah.
[SIGHS]
This kid, I swear to
God, I wish I just could...
[HANK GROANS]
This is that Pinkman character?
That's the one.
Positive the little
bastard's got an RV.
I just don't know
where he keeps it.
Until he actually leads
me to it or does something,
I'm stuck here, Marie, so sorry.
Well, not to bring
up ancient history,
but I, for one, can
think of someone
who might know something.
Possibly.
It's worth a shot.
Yeah?
Who?
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello. HANK: Oh, hey, buddy.
Hey, how you doing?
Oh, hey, Hank. What's up?
Listen, I hate to bother you.
I just had a quick
question. Shoot.
I only ask this because
I'm at a, you know,
dead end here, potentially.
I'm working a case and...
[SIGHS]
You know that I would
never put you on the spot
or make you uncomfortable.
Hank, you could
just cut to the chase.
Back when we lost you and I
was trying to track you down
through your former
student, Jesse Pinkman.
Now, you know that I
know that once upon a time
he may have dealt
you a little weed.
Hank... Just a little.
And I so do not care about that.
As far as I'm concerned,
you never inhaled.
Like you said, cut to the chase.
Do you remember if this
Pinkman kid ever had an RV?
[♪♪♪]
You know, a
recreational vehicle,
you know, like a Winnebago-type
deal, brown and beige?
Uh...
Why?
It's long story, but I'm
personally of the opinion
he's moved on from weed
and graduated to
selling crystal meth,
using it as a rolling lab.
Walt?
[VIBRATING]
Yo.
What, Mr. White?
[GROANS]
[PHONE REDIALING]
SAUL [OVER PHONE]:
How's my favorite genius?
Is this a secure line?
Is this a secure...?
Yes, what's with the...?
Hey, hello to you too.
Listen, we've got a
problem, a DEA problem.
I'm listening. My
brother-in-law,
he knows about the RV.
What RV?
Our RV,
the one which
contains a meth lab,
which is covered
with my fingerprints.
What does "knows about" mean?
Does he have it?
Has he searched it?
No, he knows it exists,
and he's trying to find it.
He has linked it to Jesse.
It's only a matter of time
before he tracks it down.
So get rid of it! What are
you doing sitting there?
Have Pinkman get rid
of it. You don't go near it.
My brother-in-law, he is
surveilling Jesse's house.
So he might have tapped the
phones or bugged his house.
Jesus. Plan A, then.
Go. Get to it
before the feds do.
And do what exactly?
I mean, what...?
The thing... The
thing is the size of a...
It's RV-size.
I mean, where do I go to
make an RV disappear?
I'm not David Copperfield.
What do I look like,
the RV disposal people?
Did you not plan
for this contingency?
No.
Next time, plan
for it, would you?
The Starship Enterprise
had a self-destruct button.
Okay. Aw, shut up.
I'm just saying, you're
good with tools and all.
Why don't you invent a
water-powered car, you know?
You did that, you
would be rolling in it.
Socket wrench.
The big one.
BADGER: What? You
scared of the Arabs?
You out of your minds?
Why is this in the open?
CLOVIS: Who are you?
BADGER: He's Heisenberg.
Is this drivable? Yeah.
I was changing the oil.
Finish it. We'll wipe it clean,
take it out to the desert.
Come on, help me.
Hold up. What's this about?
The DEA, the Drug
Enforcement Administration.
You've heard of them,
haven't you? I know you have.
They know all about this RV
and they're trying
to find it right now.
I want this off my property now.
No, no, we have got
to destroy the evidence.
We've gotta rig
this thing to burn.
Not here. Get it out of here.
Now, listen to me. I
need your help, okay?
If I go down, we all go
down. Do you understand?
All right, just...
I know a better way.
I know a guy that'll wipe this
off the planet, no questions.
Call him.
Hey, what about Jesse?
WALT: What about him?
Hey, it's me. Wanna
hear something weird?
Now, listen to me.
You get that address.
Now, Badger, I don't care how.
You find out
where he's taking it.
Oh, yeah.
Excuse me. Are you leaving?
MANAGER: Excuse me, gentlemen,
these booths are for
paying customers only.
Cynthia, it's okay.
I'll handle this.
[IN SPANISH] What
can I do for you?
[IN SPANISH] You know.
Sunset.
WALT: Ninety-six,
97, 98, 99, 100.
Beyond recovery, right?
Beyond recovery means...
I got it. Beyond recovery.
Obliterated, no
evidence. Hey, don't worry.
When we're through with it,
it's gonna be about yay big.
Then we flatbed it
over to Long Beach,
ship it across the Pacific.
Chinese turn it
into patio furniture,
so mind at ease.
Listen, can you do me a favor?
I'm obviously gonna need a ride.
Could you call a cab?
You got it. Pleasure
doing business.
Thank you. I'll be right
behind you. I just need to...
[EXHALES]
[DOOR OPENS]
The hell you think
you're doing? Me?
This is mine just as much as
yours. You don't get to just...
Oh, God. JESSE: What?
[♪♪♪]
What?
He's here.
JESSE: Who's here?
Oh, no.
Oh, God.
You led him right to us.
[♪♪♪]
Oh, shit.
[BANGING ON WINDOW] Shit.
HANK: Jesse Pinkman, you
wanna add resisting arrest?
We'll add it. No
skin off my ass.
Last chance to
do it the easy way.
[DOOR RATTLING]
MAN: Got a warrant?
HANK: Who are you, huh?
Who are you and what
do you know about this RV?
Well, I'm the owner of this lot,
which means you're
trespassing on private property.
As far as the RV goes,
seems to me it's locked,
which means you're
trying to break and enter,
so I say again,
you got a warrant?
[CHUCKLES]
Well, I don't need one
if I've got probable
cause, counselor.
MAN: Probable cause
usually relates to vehicles,
is my understanding.
You know, traffic
stops and whatnot.
See these round rubber things?
Those are wheels.
This is a vehicle.
This is a domicile, a residence,
and thus protected by
the Fourth Amendment
from unlawful
search and seizure.
Why don't you just go out...?
Did you see this drive in here?
How do you know it runs?
Did you actually
witness any wrongdoing?
It seems to me you're
just out here fishing.
Don't see that holding
up in a court of law.
[CHUCKLES] Oh, yeah?
Look at these.
What do those look like to you?
They sure look like
bullet holes to me.
There was a firearm
discharged inside of this domicile.
There's a judge or two out there
who'd see that
as probable cause.
Call the Albuquerque police...
[WHISPERING] How
could you have known
that they were there
before you took off the tape?
[WHISPERING] What?
How could you have
known that they were there
before you took off the tape?
Say it. Say it.
MAN: DEA operation, there's
guys rushing in like the wrath of...
[IN NORMAL VOICE] How
could you know they were there
before you took off
the tape? That's right.
Probable cause needs
to be readily apparent.
Huh.
There's somebody in there.
[WHISPERING] "Private
domicile and I won't be harassed."
HANK: I'll give
you three seconds
to get your ass out
here. One, two...
This is my own private domicile
and I will not be harassed.
Bitch.
[CHUCKLING]
Fine. You want your warrant?
I'll have my guys
bring it out here
and deliver it on a little
satin pillow. How's that?
I waited this long.
I'll wait a little longer.
[SIGHS]
Hey, Vicky.
Yeah, Schrader. Get
me Merkert, will you?
[♪♪♪]
You know, I say...
I say we just ram him.
All right?
I mean, we... We...
We start her up and just
ram the shit out of his truck.
We make our escape. Right?
Yeah, he'd, uh, he'd
shoot me in the head.
Yeah, he'd shoot me in the head.
So, what do we do, man, huh?
What do we...? What?
Please tell me
you got something.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Yeah, I got something.
It's me.
We need your help.
[EXHALES]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Yeah.
WOMAN: Is this
Mr. Henry R. Schrader?
Yeah. Who's this?
Sir, this is Officer
Elaine Tanner
with the Albuquerque police.
Is your wife Marie Schrader?
Yes, why?
I'm sorry to inform
you that your wife's
been in an automobile accident.
She's being airlifted to
Los Ranchos Medical Center
and should be
arriving there shortly.
How is she? What's
her condition?
I don't have the
current information.
But I think you might wanna
get there as soon as possible.
You're gonna have to
start paying me more.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[♪♪♪]
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
S[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Marie? MARIE:
I'm just checking in.
I'd love to have some idea
of whether I should
cook dinner or not.
Are you okay? Yeah.
Why?
Hank?
What's up?
[♪♪♪]
[LOS ZAFIROS' "HE
VENIDO" PLAYING]
[SPEAKING IN
SPANISH] I told you before.
You will not kill Walter White.
Not until my business
with him has concluded.
We've waited long enough.
We won't wait any longer.
You'll have to.
The decision
is not yours to make.
Explain to me, why
this man White?
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
He betrayed your
cousin Tuco, yes.
But he's not the one
who murdered him.
Was there not another man
who pulled the trigger?
A DEA agent.
Bolsa says the
DEA is off-limits.
North of the border
is my territory.
My say.
As a show of respect,
I say yes.
The agent's name is
Hank Schrader.
May his death satisfy you.
[♪♪♪]