[♪♪♪]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Well, hello there.
SKYLER: Hi, I hope
we're not too late.
No, no. Perfect timing. Okay.
Stan, this is my husband, Walt.
Hi.
Good to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Sandia Laboratories, huh? Yeah.
I hear some fascinating
stuff goes on out there.
Yeah, well, you know. Heh, heh.
Working on anything
you can talk about?
I'm picturing giant
space lasers. Am I right?
Honestly, what I do
would bore you senseless.
Giant space lasers?
Now, that sounds cool.
I'll bring it up at our
next staff meeting.
Well, just remember I get
a cut. All right. It's a deal.
So this is it, honey.
What do you say?
You wanna take a tour?
Sure. Okay.
Look, how about I
give ya'll some privacy?
I'll go out to the car,
make a few calls.
Take as much time as you need.
All right. Okay, thanks.
He's a nice guy.
He doesn't push.
Yeah. So as you can see,
there's this, uh, kind
of flow going on here.
It's a nice big
living room. Yeah.
And, um, this is
the dining area.
Oh, the dining area. Right.
Yes. Oh, and, uh...
it's got a pool.
Ah, pool is nice. Mm-hm.
Backyard could
be a little bigger.
And... Oh, there's
a breakfast bar
kind of dealie
here, which is nice.
And, um, I don't know,
the kitchen's really spacious
and, you know, got
good appliances and...
How many bedrooms?
Three. Told you.
They're all pretty
good size and...
Oh, this is the first one here.
And then there's
two more at the back.
Only three bedrooms?
We're gonna need at
least five, don't you think?
Five? Yeah.
What, do I look like I'm
about to drop a litter?
No, no, no. We'll have
three kids total, eventually.
Yeah, but we'll need a
spare room for a study,
so that I can work at home
and you can write, huh?
Yeah, no. I don't think
this is gonna be enough.
Okay, um, what
about a wine cellar?
[IN BRITISH ACCENT] I mean,
we certainly cannot be expected
to live without a wine cellar.
Very funny. I just think we
need to set our sights high is all.
At least, higher than here.
[IN NORMAL VOICE] Walt,
this is a good neighborhood.
It's got a good elementary
and, supposedly,
a very good high school,
and believe me, because I
have definitely looked everywhere.
For our price range,
this is as good as it gets.
Well, then let's
stretch our price range.
Truly. I mean, why...?
Why buy a starter house
when we'll have to
move out in a year or two?
Did you win the
lottery and not tell me?
I'm serious.
Come on. Why be cautious?
We've got nowhere to go but up.
[♪♪♪]
[SIGHS]
[PHONE RINGING]
Yeah. MIKE: Walter, you see us?
Yeah. I see you.
I'd like you to
exit your vehicle
and start walking toward us.
And then what? I'm
gonna need some...
Some kind of assurance.
I assure you, I could kill
you from way over here
if it makes you feel any better.
[♪♪♪]
Walter, you've been busy.
You wanna put your arms out to
your sides for me, if you would?
You know I haven't
slept since Thursday?
I was out all night
cleaning up after you.
I need my sleep.
You said no half measures.
Yeah. Funny how words can
be so open to interpretation.
You get your car fixed? Not yet.
MIKE: You're gonna
wanna get your car fixed.
WALT: Let's see
how this goes first.
[♪♪♪]
Has your condition worsened?
Excuse me?
Your medical condition.
Has it grown worse?
Not that I know of, no.
Is there a ringing in your ears?
Are you seeing bright
lights or hearing voices?
I'm quite well, thank you.
GUS: No. Clearly, you are not.
No rational person would
do as you have done.
Explain yourself.
My partner was about
to get himself shot.
I intervened.
Some worthless junkie.
For him, you intervene
and put us all at risk.
Some contemptible junkie
who couldn't keep the
peace for eight hours.
That's right. He couldn't.
He was angry because
those two dealers of yours
had just murdered
an 11-year-old boy.
I heard about it.
He should have let
me take care of them.
Maybe.
Then again, maybe he thought
it was you who gave the order.
Are you asking me
if I ordered the
murder of a child?
I would never ask you that.
Where is Pinkman now?
I wouldn't know.
Couple of time
zones away, at least.
Beyond that, I'd
only be guessing.
He has enough
money to last forever,
he knows he needs
to keep moving.
You'll never find him.
I don't know, Walt,
it's what I do, after all.
He's out of the picture.
I saved his life,
I owed him that,
but now he and I are done,
which is exactly what
you wanted, isn't it?
[SIGHS]
You've always struck me
as a very pragmatic man.
So if I may, I would like
to review options with you.
Of which, it seems
to me, you have two.
Option A:
You kill me right here and now.
Apparently, I have made
that very easy for you.
You can kill me, no witnesses,
and then spend the
next few weeks or months
tracking down Jesse
Pinkman, and you kill him too.
A pointless exercise, it seems
to me, but that is option A.
What is option B?
I continue cooking.
You and I both
forget about Pinkman.
We forget this ever happened.
We consider this a lone hiccup
in an otherwise long and
fruitful business arrangement.
I prefer option B.
You'd need a new assistant.
I could get right on that. No.
This time, I choose.
Your car,
get it fixed.
Yeah.
[DOOR RATTLING]
Really?
It's good to see you.
Thanks.
It's good to be back.
Well, shall we?
By all means, Gale, let's cook.
MIKE: What about that rhinoceros?
You think he'd make a good pet?
GIRL: No. MIKE: No?
Don't you think if
you called to him,
he'd come running
for his supper?
I bet he would. I bet
he'd come running:
Boom-duh-boom-duh-boom.
You're silly, Pop-Pop.
Well, a little. But he'd
probably knock everything over.
Plus, there's that
big nose of his.
That's not a
nose, that's a horn.
Is that so? His
real nose is little.
Hm.
I learn all kinds of
things being with you.
Okay, June bug,
these are for you.
What about the rest?
The rest are for me.
No, they're not. You're
too old for balloons.
[GROANS]
You're never too old for
balloons. Give me a hug.
I see your mama.
Don't keep her waiting.
Bye, Pop-Pop. Bye, baby.
WOMAN: Hi, sweetie. Did
you have fun with Pop-Pop?
[♪♪♪]
[BEEPING]
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[BOTH SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[SILENCED GUNSHOTS]
[SILENCED GUNSHOT]
[SPEAKING IN CHINESE]
Please. Please, no.
Argh!
[♪♪♪]
Chow, you have anything
you wanna tell me?
Thank God you're here.
They keep me prisoner.
They keep you prisoner.
I don't do nothing
for them ever.
They try and make me. I say, no.
They steal my chemicals.
I can't stop them.
I am businessman.
You're a business...
The lady out front...
Hey, lady, are you still there?
Ask her if she's still there.
[SPEAKING IN CHINESE]
[WOMAN SPEAKING IN CHINESE]
She says, yes.
How's her driving? Driving.
Is she good behind the wheel?
Good. She's good driver.
Licensed? Dependable?
She has a Camry.
Good.
Ah!
[GRUNTING]
The trucks will be here
first thing in the morning.
I strongly recommend that
you return our calls next time.
So have her drive
you to the hospital.
[CHOW GRUNTING]
She's gonna need her shoe.
[CHOW WHIMPERING]
Where'd they cross?
Laredo, looks like.
They didn't exactly
send their A players.
But like you said,
it's cartel, all right.
Probing for weakness.
Hm.
Well, they didn't find any.
What about Pinkman?
I'm making inquiries.
[LIQUID GURGLING]
WALT: Yeah, that's two.
All right, let's close it up.
All right, bring it down.
You ready?
[MACHINE WHIRRING]
[MACHINE BEEPING]
Okay, we're good.
You can take your mask off now.
GALE: Does that guy ever leave?
When exactly did that start?
It's new.
We had a, uh...
We had a little drama with
the person you replaced.
Sorry to hear that.
No, it'll be fine.
Things will continue
to smooth out and, uh...
Yeah, it'll be fine.
By the way, if you're at all
worried about working with me...
No, I'm not.
Because whatever my
shortcomings last time,
I intend for things to go
perfectly from here on out.
So if there is...?
Gale, you're great.
Seriously. I just...
However you like
things to be done
is exactly how
we're gonna do them.
Period.
From here on out, so...
Please, teach me.
Okay.
[MELLOW JAZZ MUSIC
PLAYING ON STEREO]
[MAN SINGING IN ITALIAN ON
STEREO AND GALE SINGING ALONG]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[STEREO TURNS OFF]
Gale. It's good to see you.
Mr. Fring.
Wow, this is...
I should have called first.
I'm not interrupting
anything, am I?
No. No, no, not at
all. Please, come in.
Can I offer you something?
A crème de menthe?
No. No, thank you.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
Oh, no, no. It's
no inconvenience.
I need to talk to you
about something.
Something rather pressing.
If push came to
shove, I was wondering
how soon you might be able
to take over the lab yourself.
You and an assistant.
Why would...?
Why would push come to shove?
Has Walter ever talked to you
about why he got into
this particular line of work?
Uh...
I guess I assumed it was
because it pays so well.
It is, but specifically,
has he ever spoken to you
about his health problems?
I'm not surprised. He's
a very private person.
What exactly are
his health problems?
He's dying of cancer.
It is why he does this,
to provide for his family,
which he's accomplished.
They will never want for
anything. He's seen to that.
How long does he have?
That is very much the question.
He does not wanna talk about it.
And every time I
bring it up with him...
I don't know that he's fully
accepted the reality of it.
And not to sound cold-blooded,
but I am running
a business here.
No, I understand.
I have a very large
investment in this.
There's so much overhead
that I can't afford to shut down.
Not even for a week.
So you understand my concern.
And my desire for continuity.
I do. Absolutely.
Now, I intend to keep
Walter on as long as he wants,
assuming that he's
physically up to it.
But as he cannot or will not
tell me how long that might be,
I must prepare for the
worst-case scenario.
Well, worst-case scenario...
Uh...
I suppose if we had
at least a few more
cooks together.
You don't think
you're ready now?
Well, I mean,
he is such a...
A master.
There's always
more for me to learn.
But I'm thinking that if we had,
say,
one or two more cooks.
One more...
I guess would do it. I suppose.
I believe in you, Gale.
I know that when the time
comes, you will be ready.
What's up?
Walt, is there...?
Um...
Any particular trick to
purging the catalyst bed?
No, it's pretty straightforward.
I'll show you when we get there.
[SIGHS]
[HEADSET BEEPS]
Yeah?
Tell him I'm in conference.
[POP MUSIC PLAYING ON
SPEAKERS IN ADJACENT ROOM]
Can't you see I'm in conference?
MIKE: I'm looking
to find a client.
I was hoping you could
help me out with an address.
Which client? Jesse Pinkman.
Jesse-Pinkman-in-the-phone-book
Jesse Pinkman. Hm.
How would one track
him down, I wonder.
[MASSAGER TURNS OFF]
You're still here.
I need your full
attention, Saul.
Jesse Pinkman.
Current whereabouts.
The sooner you tell me,
the sooner you get back to
whatever the
hell this is exactly.
What am I, an 8th-grade hall
monitor? Current whereabouts.
Let me tell you
something, Mike, you...
Whoa, you are good right there.
Now, let's both get comfortable.
Now, when I say, I'm
looking for Pinkman,
we both know why, don't we?
You pretending otherwise
only wastes my time
and serves to annoy me.
Look, Mike,
there are rules to
this, uh, lawyer thing.
Is that right? Yeah.
Attorney-client privilege.
That's a big one.
And that's something
I provide for you.
So if I give up Pinkman,
well, then you're
gonna be asking,
"Old Saul gives
them up pretty easy.
What's to keep him
from giving me up?"
You see? So then,
where's the trust?
I trust the hole in the
desert I'd leave you in.
Yeah, that's an argument.
Saul,
don't make me beat you
till your legs don't work.
Now tell me where to find
him. You know it's the right thing.
I can't tell you,
Mike, all right? I...
Look, if I was to tell you,
well, I just... I couldn't
live with myself.
I'm sorry.
But who's to say I didn't write
the address down
in my day planner?
Or on a scratch piece
of paper somewhere?
Who's to say I didn't
write down a location
strictly for my own
professional use?
Do not touch
anything on my desk.
I'm gonna leave the room,
make myself a Nescafé.
SAUL: I'm just looking out for
you, that's all. Like a mother hen.
Believe me, money-laundering
ain't what it used to be.
God, do I miss the '80s.
You're wasting your time.
I'm buying the car wash,
end of story.
Well, one look at this place,
you're gonna fall in love, so...
Heh, heh. Huh?
Was I right?
Where else you gonna
find a cash-only business
that's this fun?
Unless we're talking
massage parlors, and, uh,
I don't see it. Shall we?
SAUL: You ever
actually play laser tag?
You know, it's good cardio.
Plus, you get to
shoot at kids. Heh.
SAUL: You got your bumper
cars over there down that way.
Got your arcade here,
all the latest video games.
Snack bar's there.
Nothing stopping you
from selling beer
to the parents.
That's a whole new
revenue stream...
WALT: All right,
already. We're good.
Holy Christ.
We're good? This constitutes
good where you're from?
My car is bugged? I said,
maybe. Maybe bugged.
I'm being followed? What the
hell have you gotten me into?
My own PI is threatening
to break my legs.
That's like Thomas Magnum
threatening that little prissy
guy with the mustache.
Over and above. Service-wise,
this is over and above.
You and I survive this,
oh, I'm seriously
rethinking my pricing, yeah.
And that goes double
for you, Hip-Hop.
Okay, my guy's no dummy, right?
So I give us maybe 24 hours
before he figures out that
address goes nowhere.
You guys do your
thing, make it snappy.
I'll go see if they have
"Tetris" or something.
So how you holding up?
Hm.
You?
I got my old job back.
At least until they kill
me and Gale takes over.
So he's their boy,
huh? He's their boy.
How long you think you've got?
Well, he asks a lot of questions
about the cooking process.
I try to be as
vague as possible,
but I got that guy
Victor watching me,
listening to every word I say.
You know, maybe that
the only thing saving me
is Gale's fastidiousness.
And once he feels confident
that he knows my entire method...
So, what do we do?
You know what we do.
There's got to be
some other way.
Maybe it's better for
you to just go to the cops.
All right? I mean, I can't
believe I'm saying that and all,
but for your family.
Hey, the DEA would love you,
all the shit you
could tell them.
Federal witness protection,
that's a good deal.
As for me, I'll hit the road,
yo. I mean, I'll make it.
We had a good run.
But it's over.
Never the DEA.
The cook can't stop.
That's the one
thing I'm certain of,
production cannot stop.
Gus can't afford to.
So if I'm the only
chemist that he's got,
then I've got leverage, and
leverage keeps me alive.
It keeps you alive too.
I think I can see to that.
If I'm the only
chemist that he's got.
I can't do it, Mr. White.
Like you said, I'm...
I'm not a...
I can't do it.
I'll do it.
I'm gonna need your help.
I mean, they're watching
me day and night.
They never leave me alone
with Gale, not for a moment.
Hell, I don't even know
where the man lives.
He's not in the phone book,
I can't find him
on the Internet,
and I can't do it in the
lab, Victor's always there.
But if I could just
shake Victor, for
even an hour one night,
I think then that
I may be able to...
make it look like an accident.
There's got to be
some other way.
I'm all ears.
But when it comes down to
you and me versus him, I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry,
but it's gonna be him.
Now, you are the
only edge that I've got,
as long as they don't
know that you're in town.
But I need you to track
him, get me his address.
And I'll do the rest.
Look, I saved your life, Jesse.
Are you gonna save mine?
[♪♪♪]
[PHONE VIBRATING]
[LINE RINGING]
JESSE: Yeah?
Please, tell me you found him.
6353 Juan Tabo
Boulevard. Apartment 6.
You there? Yeah.
6353 Juan Tabo.
Number 6. Got it.
He's home? Yep.
Anyone watching the place?
No. Looks pretty much wide-open.
When are you gonna do it?
Tonight.
Once it gets dark.
Don't do this, Mr. White.
Please. Go to the cops.
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
VICTOR: We got a problem.
Some kind of chemical
leaking in your lab.
Better come with me.
I'll, uh... I'll follow you.
They tell me to
bring you, I bring you.
Come on, get in the car.
[♪♪♪]
[MACHINE WHIRRING]
I don't know if it's a
barrel leak or what,
but you got something
mighty stinky down there.
After you.
Walter, the sooner you
figure out what this is,
the sooner we all go home.
Please, don't do this.
Mike,
you don't have to do this.
Yeah, unfortunately,
I do, Walter.
Downstairs.
I'll cook. I'll cook for free.
There won't be any more
trouble, I promise you.
No. If I could
just talk to Gus...
No. I can make him understand.
If I could talk to Gus,
I can convince him.
Just let me, please... Please!
Please, let me talk to
him! Shut up! Shut up.
I can't do it. I'm sorry.
I'll give you Jesse Pinkman.
Okay? Like you
said, he's the problem.
He's always been the problem.
And without him, we would...
And he's in town, all right?
He's not in Virginia or wherever
the hell you're looking for him.
He's right here in Albuquerque
and I could take you to him.
I'll take you right to him. Huh?
What do you say? Where is he?
Right now, you
give me an address.
I don't... He moves.
He moves around.
But if you let me call
him... No, no, please.
No, I just... My
phone. I'll just...
It's just my phone. I'll call
him, and I'll have him meet me.
All right? Okay?
Okay?
[LIGHTER CLICKING]
[PHONE VIBRATING]
Did you do it?
Mr. White?
No, I didn't do it.
I can't now.
It's gonna have to be
you. What? No way, man.
Listen to me. You're
closer than we are.
You'll have a 20-minute lead.
They've got me at the
laundry. They're going to kill me.
Jesse, do it now!
Son of a bitch!
WALT: Do it, Jesse! Do it!
Huh.
Just what the hell
was that exactly?
You might wanna hold off.
Yeah?
Why?
Because your boss
is gonna need me.
6353 Juan Tabo, Apartment 6.
Yeah.
[CHINESE MUSIC BLARING ON
STEREO AND KETTLE WHISTLING]
[PHONE VIBRATING]
[WHISTLING STOPS]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[VIBRATING]
[STEREO TURNS OFF]
Hi. How can I help you?
[WHIMPERING]
GALE: Take whatever you want.
I have money. I have...
I got a lot of money.
I have...
Please, don't do this.
You don't... You...
You... You don't
have to do this.
[♪♪♪]