[THE ASSOCIATION'S
"WINDY" PLAYING]
♪ Who's peekin' out
From under a stairway ♪
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
♪ Calling a name ♪
♪ That's lighter than air ♪
♪ Who's bending down
To give me a rainbow ♪
♪ Everyone knows it's Windy ♪
♪ Who's tripping down
The streets of the city ♪
♪ Smilin' at
everybody She sees ♪
♪ Who's reachin' out
To capture a moment ♪
♪ Everyone knows it's Windy ♪
♪ And Windy has stormy eyes ♪
♪ That flash at
the sound Of lies ♪
♪ And Windy has wings to fly ♪
♪ Above the clouds
Above the clouds ♪
♪ And Windy has stormy eyes ♪
♪ That flash at
the sound Of lies ♪
♪ And Windy has wings to fly ♪
♪ Above the clouds
Above the clouds ♪
♪ Who's tripping down
The streets of the city ♪
♪ Smilin' at
everybody She sees ♪
♪ Who's reachin' out
To capture a moment ♪
♪ Everyone knows it's Windy ♪
Hey, guys.
[♪♪♪]
So if it's okay,
I was thinking about
using this one for the test.
Mom's brakes are very sticky,
and you barely press down
on them and it's like a screech.
Sure.
But I'm good?
Yeah, you're great. Why?
Um... Are my feet okay?
Ah. I looked it up.
New Mexico says all I
need is a note from a doctor.
I know it's not the
right way and all,
but once I get my provisional,
I can keep working at it.
Well, as long as it gets you
safely from point A to point B,
then who am I to argue?
[HOLLY COOING]
Hi.
You're a sweet girl. Yes,
you are. Yes, you are.
I know.
[CAR APPROACHING]
Here you go. Here you go.
All right. Thank you.
Got it? Yeah.
Okay. All right. Ah.
So 9 a.m. Saturday?
Yes, 9 a.m. Saturday.
So which means pick
me up about 8:30?
I'll be here with
bells on. What?
Um... It's just a saying.
Don't worry, I won't
be wearing bells.
Hey. Hey, Mom.
Hi. Um... Do you
have a minute? Yeah.
Could you keep an eye
on your sister for me?
Sure. See you, Dad. Thanks.
Bye, son. Hey, good work
today. WALT JR.: Thank you.
Have you thought any more
about what we discussed?
"Thought any more"
meaning reconsidered? No.
So show me the flaw in it.
Uh... Flaws, Skyler.
Flaws. Plural, not singular.
[SCOFFS]
Where do you want me to start?
Hey, I don't love
this situation, all right,
that you put me in.
However, let's just stick
with what makes sense here.
You took the seed
money you won gambling,
you invested it in the car
wash that you helped run.
You hired your wife
as a bookkeeper,
because, guess what,
she's a bookkeeper.
That is a story an auditor can
believe. What am I missing?
You're missing that you should
take this money that I give you
and not look too closely at it.
So if, God forbid, I get caught,
you maintain
plausible deniability.
Okay, my estranged husband
who, when he was working,
made $43,000 a year,
starts shoveling money at me.
And when the police
come, I'm supposed to say:
"Gee, I, never thought
about it, officers.
Made sense to me." Really?
That, in your mind, is
plausible deniability?
I'll tell you what, Walt,
I'd rather have them think
I'm Bonnie what's-her-name
than some complete idiot.
So you're promoting
caution here.
And you want a believable story.
That, it seems to
me, is the safest way
to make the best out of
a very bad situation, yes.
Ah. But I'm noting
a little hole in
your plot though.
Why would your estranged
husband be doing all this for you?
Because he loves his family
and desperately
wants a reconciliation,
though it may be
hopeless and futile.
Then again, he'd try anything.
I'm just not buying it. No,
I think it would be better
if the husband were
no longer estranged.
Mm. Yeah.
Maybe if he were back
sleeping in his own bed.
Wow.
It's suddenly a fantasy story.
I am at least gonna be
a part of this household.
Dinner with the family
every night of the week.
Not every night, no.
Six nights a week.
You get one night off.
Dinner two nights. Not weekends.
With 24 hours' notice. Six nights
a week. You get one night off.
Five nights a
week, with no notice.
Three. Six hours' notice.
Five nights a week,
two hours' notice.
Four. Don't push it.
And I want my own
key to the house.
No.
For emergencies and appearances.
I am going to
babysit my daughter,
I'm going to help my
son with his homework.
I am going to be a
part of this family.
And that is how we'll
sell your little fiction.
How about we stop somewhere
afterward and get a beer?
Uh...
No. Thanks, though.
Maybe some other time.
Seriously.
Get a beer with me.
[RED GARLAND'S "SOFTLY
BABY" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
What?
What the hell are you doing?
That's ours, right?
Look at it and tell
me if that's ours.
Yes, it's ours. Now put it away.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Where did you get that?
Did you take it from the lab?
I bought it from the two
guys who killed Combo.
They had Combo
shot down in the street,
and now it's our
product they're selling.
Which means they
work for our guy. Right?
What? No. What is that?
That's hearsay. Do
you have any proof?
I heard it from the sister
of the kid who shot him.
Hear how I just said "kid"?
This kid, he's 11 years old.
Shot Combo on orders.
These two scumbags,
they got him dealing.
They got him...
And you know he's not the first.
They use kids
because, hey, why not?
Easy to control. Easy to fool.
All they get is juvie if
they ever get caught.
Hearts and minds, right?
Get them young and
they're yours forever.
These guys killed Combo.
They used this little
kid like some puppet.
They used him
to shoot my friend.
[SIGHS]
So why are you telling me this?
[WHISPERING] I need your help.
[WHISPERING] How?
I need ricin. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Look, these two...
Hey. No.
Hey, they gotta go. All right?
I got the entire
thing figured out.
No. The delivery
method, everything.
All I need from you
is the poison, that's all.
No... Look.
Otherwise, you
don't gotta lift a finger.
No. You don't even know
what you're talking about.
Not even...
Look, you don't
get how right this is?
You don't get how
the whole entire world
would be better off?
No. We're not even
talking about this.
I know a woman who buys from
these two once or twice a week.
She brings them hamburgers.
They sit in their
car and get hungry,
so she brings them food,
and they knock a
few bucks off her price.
There's your delivery
system right there.
I could be a mile away. Jesus.
A meth-head you're
trusting to do this?
Know what? That meth-head
stood up to your brother-in-law.
He questioned her for five
hours. She didn't give it up.
You know how it is you know it?
Because you're not
in prison right now.
Well, I know I would
be in prison after this.
Prison or worse. And
I'd be right alongside you.
No, Jesse, you
cannot be serious.
This is a ridiculous idea.
It's ridiculous? What, so you're
saying it's not gonna work?
How about back
when it was your plan?
Back when we were
gonna use it on Tuco.
Apples and oranges.
Guy eats ricin,
two or three days
later he gets the flu
or a heart attack or
something and he keels over.
That's what you said.
Untraceable back to us.
To... To me.
Not even that other
scumbag we work for
is ever gonna figure it out.
Yo. It was a good plan
back when it was Tuco,
and it's a good plan now.
Tuco wanted to murder
us. These guys don't.
Apples and oranges.
Do I really have to sit here
and explain the
difference to you?
Combo was us, man.
He was one of us.
Does that mean nothing?
Why didn't you
go after these guys
two or three months ago?
Because I just
found out about them.
What's to find out?
It's a dispute over turf, right?
I mean, how hard
could it have been
for you to track them
down on their turf
and kill them months ago?
Because back then, you
were too busy getting high,
feeling sorry.
Now, murder is not part
of your 12-step program.
This is not some amends
that you have to make.
What you are talking
about here is pointless.
This achieves nothing.
It accomplishes nothing.
If you don't see
what it accomplishes,
then there's no way I
can explain it to you.
Jesse, listen to me.
You are not a murderer.
I'm not, and you're not.
It's as simple as that.
Jesse.
I'm doing it.
With or without you.
[MARIE HUMMING]
Knock, knock.
Chrissakes, Marie, you don't
say "knock, knock," you... like that.
Well, I like saying it.
Well, that's not the rules.
Okay? You knock
your way, groucho,
I'll knock mine.
But look, see? I win.
Not so fast.
Christ, again?
That's three in a row.
Got a fricking Paul
Newman over here?
Have you been playing
cards with your dad?
No. Why?
How is your old man?
Back teaching?
No. Uh... I don't think
either of them are working
right now. Yeah. How
they swinging that?
WALT JR.: I don't know. Hey,
did you know the doctors
told your Uncle Hank
that he can get out of
here anytime he wants?
Oh, yeah? That's great.
Yeah, I'm not so
sure about that.
WALT JR.: Why not?
What? That's what they said.
Because they want the room.
They hit the sheets with
Lysol, reset the meter,
and wheel the next slob in here.
We went over
this, Marie. Drop it.
Are... Are you not well enough?
Jesus, kid, you too?
Do I look well enough?
I'm shitting in pans,
peeing in pitchers.
I can't move my legs. Got it?
So people in wheelchairs
should be in hospitals?
What about people on crutches?
Maybe I should be in here too.
That what you're trying to say?
That's exactly what I'm saying.
Deal, you little prick.
Pssh.
Bitch.
You know I'm hourly, right?
He promised me
that he would be here.
Oh, he promised.
Why didn't you tell
me? Let's wait then.
That's a joke. The
kid ain't coming.
Okay, so, what's plan B?
I don't know.
I really don't.
Well, let's brainstorm.
You really think he's serious?
That's why I'm here, Saul.
The way he was talking,
he is going to do it.
Or try, at least.
Okay, so, well, we pay him off.
No, no, it's not about money.
It's about getting
him off the streets.
Getting him to calm down.
Maybe...
What if we, maybe...?
Could you get him arrested?
You...?
You want your criminal associate
taken into police custody?
No, now listen. I know...
I know it sounds risky.
It wouldn't be anything
that would get him
into real trouble,
and nothing that could
lead back to our business.
Just some minor
offense. Pinkman in jail?
I don't know. I'm
picturing it and...
No, not jail as in "jail" jail.
I'm talking about
one of those situations
where you're in
an orange jumpsuit
picking up litter
along the highway.
That's jail.
You're talking about
a level-two joint.
Something that keeps him
off the street for, say, 30 days.
Then by the time he gets out,
tempers have cooled and
hopefully we can move on.
Well, Roswell Correctional's
pretty low impact, you know.
In the past, I've
recommended Springer,
but I'm hearing chancy
things about their bathrooms
since they renovated.
So...
So it... It's possible, right?
Yeah. Well, it falls under my
Premium Services Package,
but you can afford
that. I'll call my PI.
JESSE: You understand
what you have to do?
And you can never
talk to anyone, right?
I mean, ever. Understand?
Yeah.
I found this stuff
on the Internet.
Takes days to kick in.
Just keep quiet and this
won't ever come back to you.
You okay with this, right?
Just think of it like it's
the same thing as always.
You're just delivering
some hamburgers.
It's not just delivering
hamburgers.
Hey. You got a kid, right?
What's his name?
Patrick.
All right, imagine
these two guys
had Patrick working as a mule.
Making him kill people.
Wouldn't you do anything
to protect your kid?
Of course I would. I do
all kinds of things for him.
Okay, so,
these guys are
using kids like that.
They gotta go. Right?
Good.
[♪♪♪]
Tomorrow.
I'll be in touch.
WALT: Yeah. I bet
that tastes good, huh?
[MAKES EATING SOUNDS]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Hey.
Come here, baby.
Okay. Here we go.
Here we go.
What are you doing? If you
need to talk, use the phone.
This isn't a phone talk, Walter.
Your wife's out, right?
Aww. Ha-ha.
Isn't she something?
I got a granddaughter
a few years older.
What can I do for you?
Oh.
Have a seat, Walter.
I spoke to Goodman about
Pinkman and this plan of yours.
And? Well, I'm not gonna do it.
Why?
Because it's moronic.
Saul said you've done
things like this before.
That's not the moronic part.
Okay. So, what's the problem?
The problem is the
boss wouldn't like it.
Saul?
My boss.
Your boss.
Mm.
This is a professional courtesy.
No one knows I'm
here. Understand?
But our employer would
find out, like always.
And if Pinkman were arrested,
he'd take it as a problem.
Walt,
you got a good thing
going here. We all do.
You wanna risk it
all on one junkie?
Now, I realize you
two have a history,
but this kid's been on
the bubble a while now.
It's a long time coming.
What is?
[CHUCKLES]
Um...
[SIGHS]
I used to be a beat
cop, a long time ago.
And I'd get called out
on domestic
disputes all the time.
Hundreds, probably,
over the years.
But there was this one guy,
this one piece of shit
that I will never forget.
Gordie. He looked like Bo
Svenson. You remember him?
Walking Tall? You
don't remember?
No.
Anyway, big boy, 270, 280,
but his wife... Or
whatever she was...
His lady was real
small. Like a bird.
Wrists like little
branches. Hmm.
Anyway, my partner and I'd get
called out there every weekend,
and one of us would
pull her aside and say:
"Come on, tonight's the
night we press charges."
And this wasn't one of those
"deep down, he loves me" setups.
We got a lot of
those, but not this.
This girl was scared.
She wasn't gonna cross
him. No way, no how.
Nothing we could do but
pass her off to the EMT's,
put him a car,
drive him downtown,
throw him in a drunk tank.
He sleeps it off, next
morning, out he goes.
Back home.
But one night,
my partner's out
sick, and it's just me.
And the call comes in
and it's the usual crap.
Broke her nose in the
shower kind of thing.
So I cuff him, put him in
the car and away we go.
Only that night,
we're driving into town,
and this sideways asshole
is in my back seat
humming "Danny Boy."
Heh. And it just
rubbed me wrong.
So instead of left, I go
right, out into nowhere.
And I kneel him down and I
put my revolver in his mouth,
and I told him, "This is
it. This is how it ends."
And he's crying,
going to the bathroom
all over himself.
Swearing to God he's
gonna leave her alone.
Screaming, much as you
can with a gun in your mouth.
And I told him to be quiet.
That I needed to think about
what I was gonna do here.
And, of course, he got quiet,
goes still and real quiet.
Like a dog waiting
for dinner scraps.
Then we just stood
there for a while.
Me, acting like I'm
thinking things over,
and Prince Charming
kneeling in the dirt
with shit in his pants.
And after a few minutes, I
took the gun out of his mouth,
and I say, "So help me, if
you ever touch her again,
I will such and such and
such, and blah, blah, blah."
It was just a warning?
Mm-hm.
Of course.
Just trying to
do the right thing.
But two weeks
later he killed her.
Of course.
Caved her head in with the
base of a Waring blender.
We got there, there
was so much blood,
you could taste the metal.
Moral of the story is,
I chose a half measure
when I should have
gone all the way.
I'll never make
that mistake again.
No more half measures, Walter.
[DOOR CLOSES]
JESSE: Man, I don't get this.
I don't get this at all.
All I'm seeing is the kid.
So where are they?
I don't know. They're
always around.
Burgers are getting cold.
So is it, like, fast?
Don't sweat it. All right?
You're just doing what you do.
Hey, nobody's
gonna know anything.
Can I have another bump?
Look, you had your bump.
Get this thing done, then
you can have all you want.
[KNOCK ON WINDOW]
Gonna need you to come with me.
Take a walk.
Where we going?
[DOOR OPENS]
Sit down.
I understand that
you have a problem
with two of my employees.
It is true that they killed
one of your associates.
It is possible
they acted rashly.
But, on the other hand,
there was provocation.
The man was selling
on their territory.
There is blame on both sides.
This will go no further.
It will be settled
right here, right now.
You told him?
Wait outside.
Listen to me.
You have one friend
in this room. This man.
Those men outside are
my trusted employees.
And when I learned
what you intended to do...
If it wasn't for this man and
the respect I have for him,
I would be dealing with
this in a very different way.
You don't look at
him. You look at me.
This is what happens now.
My men will come back inside,
and you will shake their
hands and you will make peace.
And that will be
the end of this.
No.
Jesse.
Pardon me? They use kids.
These assholes of yours,
they got an 11-year-old kid
doing their killing for them.
You're supposed to be a
reasonable businessman.
This how you do business?
You okay with this? You
got anything to say here?
Bring them back.
No more children.
Understand?
And you...
you keep the peace.
Say it.
Yeah. I'll keep the peace.
Shake hands.
Jesse, your actions,
they affect other people.
Sometimes compromises
have to be made
for the best of reasons.
Jesse. Jesse.
[GRUNTS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Marie, let the people who
get paid to do this do this.
The people who get paid
to do this do a lousy job.
[SIGHS]
So I guess this is
what you want, huh?
Just lying in a hospital bed
getting sponge
baths from nurses.
Marie.
It's time to go home, Hank.
How many times I gotta tell
you, Marie? Not till I'm well.
Hey, hey, hey. What...
What... What are you doing?
I'm just seeing.
Seeing what? Seeing what I see.
I'm not at my best here, Marie.
We'll see.
Nothing's gonna happen.
I say it will.
No. I'm in this
bed for a reason.
It's a waste of time.
Besides, what if
someone comes in?
I don't care if
someone walks in.
Marie, what's wrong with you?
I'll tell you what.
If I can get the groundhog
to see his shadow...
It's not gonna
happen. I'm sorry.
I'm betting it will.
And if he does, you
check out of here.
[LAUGHS]
I'm not gonna bet on
whether I can get a boner.
There's no bet. There's
no bet here. No bet.
You afraid you'll lose?
You know what, you're just...
You're just being
foolish, you know?
Come on. What's the point?
The point is you're not
completely hopeless.
We have a bet?
You know what?
If it'll get you out
of here quicker.
You got one minute.
One minute? Yeah.
All right. That's a cakewalk.
You know, this is just...
This is just sad. I mean...
I really feel sorry for
you, Marie, you know?
I really do. It's just, uh...
Heh. It's pathetic.
[SOFTLY] That's
good, keep talking.
Protest. Struggle.
Marie, give up. I
mean, seriously, it's...
not...
gonna happen.
[CHUCKLES]
Bad day?
I don't even know.
Anyway,
it's better now.
[PHONE RINGS]
[BOTH GROAN]
[CHUCKLES]
Tell them you're busy.
Hello?
Grandma?
Slow down.
Slow down, I can't...
Oh, God.
[SOBBING]
[♪♪♪]
[INDISTINCT POLICE
RADIO CHATTER]
[SIRENS WAILING]
[SOBBING]
ANDREA: Tomas!
No.
You have to let me in. Please.
[♪♪♪]
JESSE [ON RECORDING]:
Hey, it's me. Wait for the thing.
[PHONE BEEPS]
Jesse, you are
now 42 minutes late.
I'm starting without you.
WOMAN [ON TV]: What is "wasabi"?
TREBEK: Wasabi. Right you are.
Four-letter word for 1200.
TREBEK: Pilots and musicians
know this word derives...
Dinner's almost ready, okay?
Okay. TREBEK: Kevin.
What is "solo"?
TREBEK: That's the word.
This guy's good. KEVIN:
Four letter word, 2000.
TREBEK: "A loud, harsh cry,
Walt Whitman's was barbaric."
"Yell." What is "yawp"?
TREBEK: Kevin.
KEVIN: What is "yawp"?
TREBEK: Yawp.
KEVIN: Tokyo, 1200.
TREBEK: This crustacean...
What the heck's a yawp?
Hmm? Uh... A yawp is
a yell. I'll be right back.
That's what I said.
What is crab? TREBEK: No.
Uh... Okay to use
your bathroom, right?
Yeah, okay.
JESSE [ON RECORDING]:
Hey, it's me. Wait for the thing.
[PHONE BEEPS]
Look, I hope you're not
waiting for an apology
because I did not rat you out.
I was looking out for
your best interests,
as well as my own.
And I stand by my
decision 100 percent,
so we'll just have
to agree to disagree.
Anyway, just call me back.
[TV PLAYING INDISTINCTLY]
So the TV turns
itself off? Yeah.
Oh. I'll get it.
NEWSCASTER [ON TV]: the
beginning of an early cold snap.
First, more on our top
story... Where's the remote?
The murder of a young
boy in the South Valley.
Police have yet to
release a statement,
but sources indicate that
11-year-old Tomas Cantillo
may have been the victim
of a gang-related execution.
An anonymous tip brought
police to a playground
in the 4700 block of Eighth
Avenue late last night.
Paramedics were
called to the scene
but were unable
to revive the boy.
A gruesome crime...
Can you turn that off?
And yet another casualty
in what appears to be
the city's ongoing
struggle Walt?
Against drugs and the
gangs that peddle them.
We'll be passing
along... [TV CLICKS OFF]
Hand me your dad...
I'm sorry, it's just, uh,
they've been talking about
that all day, and it's just...
No. Yeah.
SKYLER: Hey, uh, did
you know your dad and I
are thinking about maybe
starting a business together?
WALT JR.: Seriously?
[♪♪♪]
WALT JR.: What kind of
business? SKYLER: Um...
We're thinking maybe a car wash.
WALT JR.: What do
you mean? Like the...?
I'm sorry, I... I have to go.
[SNIFFING]
[COUGHS]
[CAR APPROACHING]
[GROANS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SNIFFLING]
[♪♪♪]
[GUN COCKS]
[CAR APPROACHING]
[GASPING]
Oh, my God.
[GRUNTS]
[GASPS]
Run.
[♪♪♪]