[MAN GASPING]
[CLUCKING]
[PEOPLE SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[PANTING]
[♪♪♪]
[PAPER RUSTLING]
ANNOUNCER [OVER TV]:
We bring you breaking news.
Good afternoon. In
the last several minutes,
KOB has received
dozens of reports
of what appears to be a
crashed aircraft, possibly two.
On Albuquerque's east side.
As of yet details are scarce
but callers describe witnessing
an explosion overhead,
followed by falling
debris. Visible now...
crash investigators
with the National
Transportation Safety Board
are expected on
site this evening.
But officials warn
that with a debris field
of this magnitude,
the investigation...
Officials are now saying
that the Boeing 737
was being re-routed, or
vectored, through the airspace,
which is standard procedure
according to an FAA spokesman.
The eight-seat King Air
350 was a charter flight,
operating out of
St. George, Utah,
bound for Amarillo, Texas.
It, uh, sounded like hail,
like heavy hailstones.
It was just, um, bump-bump-bump,
all over the neighborhood...
indicating that the final
death toll now stands at 167.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
167.
This mid-air collision
left many wondering
how such an accident
could take place
in a system with so
many safeguards.
That the collision which
brought down Flight 515
was caused by
improper air traffic control.
We have the
bombshell confirmation
out of Oklahoma City
today as the FAA confirmed,
it was indeed a lone
air traffic controller's
fateful mistake.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
is Donald Margolis,
a 19-year veteran
of the FAA's Air Route Traffic
Control Center in Albuquerque.
Margolis recently returned to
work after a five-week absence,
which was due to,
quote, "a personal loss".
While it's now
known that Margolis
had recently lost
a daughter to a...
BANFIELD: Drug
overdose a month before.
His troubled daughter
Jane Margolis, aged 26,
apparently had a long
history of substance abuse.
Friends of the family say
the death of his only child
hit Margolis particularly hard.
Coming as it did little
more than a month before,
many are questioning the
timing of his return to work,
and are wondering how
much blame truly lies
with those who let
this grieving father...
[GASPS]
No! No! No!
[GRUNTING]
[YELLS]
[GASPING]
WOMAN: I usually open
with "So sorry you're here."
Where would you like to begin?
Um, I really just need this
quick and easy, you know?
As quick as something
like this can be. So...
Okay. Is that mutual?
Does your husband
go along with that?
Does he know?
Well, I mean, he certainly
knows we're separated, so...
Has he moved out?
Uh, we're in the process
of moving him out.
Yeah. Today, hopefully.
And in the meantime, my...
My son and, uh, my daughter
and I are staying
with my sister.
So you've moved out?
Well, yes, just temporarily.
Only so he could
get his things and...
That was, uh, supposed
to happen last week,
but then came the crash and...
Oh, God, you
weren't one of the...?
Right, yeah. Right
beneath the flight path.
And, um, we had
debris land in our yard,
and all over our
neighborhood, so...
Mm, so terrible. Yeah.
Apparently, even, um,
you know, parts of bodies.
So I certainly couldn't
bring myself to...
So awful. I know.
Anyway, I was certainly
not ready to move back.
But it's time.
And, um, I'm sure we're driving
my sister and her
husband up a wall.
Well, you definitely
wanna maintain residency
in your actual home.
It just puts you in a better
position in regards to custody.
Two children, you said?
Yes. Um, Holly here,
and then I have a son
in high school, Walter Jr.
They need to stay with me.
Okay.
How long have you been
married? Sixteen years.
And it's not an apartment,
it's a house that you live in?
Mm-hm. Do you own outright,
do you have a mortgage?
Yes, there's
definitely a mortgage.
We have, um,
maybe 15 years on it.
What about other
debts or assets?
Do you feel you have
a good understanding
of you and your husband's
financial situation?
Is your husband
employed? Here's the thing.
I'm really not looking for
any sort of, uh, loopholes,
or, um, I don't know, just...
No, no loopholes.
I just intend that
every one of my clients
get a full and honest accounting
of what it is they owe
and what it is they own.
To that end, I say let's
leave no stone unturned.
You'd be amazed what I've seen
partners hide from one another.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
HANK: Walt?
Hey, buddy?
Hey, Walt?
Hey. HANK: There you are.
Listen, I, uh...
You know, well...
It's, uh...
It's time.
HANK: The shittiest week
since 9/11, okay? Bar none.
This is it. We're living it.
I speak with some authority
because we definitely had
some shitty weeks.
But this here? I
mean, call, you know,
call freaking Guinness
Book of World Records.
Am I talking too much?
Am I? I am, right? I know.
But this situation between
you and, uh... Uh...
I don't know. I'm not
asking, by the way.
It's none of my business.
I do not wanna get in
the middle of you two.
I'm just saying, listen, okay?
You beat a little
tactical retreat, huh,
you regroup, and then boom.
You know, absence makes the...
Yeah.
I'm, uh, pulling for you,
man. I'm pulling for you.
Whoa, whoa. No
heavy lifting. I got it.
No, it's okay.
I got it.
Jesus. What do you got
in there, cinder blocks?
Half a million in cash.
[LAUGHS]
That's the spirit.
I got it, I got it.
[LAUGHS]
[GRUNTS]
[BAG THUDS]
MAN: Who's here
for self-improvement?
Come on, give me
a show of hands.
Who among you is here hoping
they can actively
improve who they are?
All right. See, that's
your first mistake.
You should be here to
learn self-acceptance.
Hey, honey, you, uh...
You want another waffle?
[PHONE RINGING]
I still got the iron out.
I could, uh, cut
up some bananas.
SKYLER [ON RECORDING]: Hi, you've
reached Walt, Skyler, Flynn and Holly.
Please leave us a
message. [PHONE BEEPS]
WALT: Uh, hey. Hello,
everybody. Good morning.
I was just checking
in and thought I'd, uh,
pass along the current
contact information.
You certainly can always
reach me on my cell,
I've always got
that on me, but, uh,
in terms of a mailing address,
I'm here at the Beachcomber,
and you know what?
It's actually very
nice, very pleasant.
Not as high-end as the Oakwood,
but not as corporate... Oh,
hey, would you please...?
WALT JR.: Hey, Dad, it's me.
[WALT JR. SIGHS]
No, I'm not okay. I don't
know what's going on.
Nobody's telling me
jackshit around here.
Hey, Flynn. WALT JR.: Whatever.
I... I don't even care anymore.
Can... Can you just
give me a ride to school?
I'll take you to school.
Yeah. No, I'm ready now.
SKYLER: Flynn, I'm
taking you to school.
All right, I'm here.
See you soon.
[♪♪♪]
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Okay.
[KNIFE CLINKING]
CARMEN [OVER SPEAKERS]:
May I have your attention, please?
As all of you know,
last week our city
suffered a terrible tragedy
that none of us
will ever forget.
Today we're going to take
time out of our schedule
to gather in the gym and talk.
I just find it, you know,
really, really hard
to concentrate.
Because of all the horrors,
you know, we perceived.
It just really gets inside
your brain and, uh...
In college, they have this thing
where if your
roommate kills himself,
like, if you come
home and find him
hanging in the
closet or whatever,
it's basically an
automatic A for you.
And I just think that that
kind of compassion is...
Is something to...
Okay. Thank you, Barry.
Who wants to go next?
No judgments,
guys. Just feelings.
You can say anything
and everything
that's on your mind. Anyone?
There you go, honey.
I just keep asking myself...
CARMEN: Honey, could
you please stand up?
Thank you.
I just keep asking myself,
"Why did this happen?"
I mean, if there's
a God and all,
why does he allow
those innocent people
to die for no reason?
Okay, can we just
keep it secular, honey?
Anyhow, I haven't really
been sleeping much.
Does anyone else have that?
I just keep hearing
that... That sound.
That boom.
It just plays over
and over in my head
like it won't ever stop.
CARMEN: Thank you, sweetheart.
Is there anyone
else? BOY: Over here.
Uh, ahem.
My neighbor, he heard the crash
and he ran outside, and
he found, like, this seat.
Like an airline seat.
Like what you
have on an airliner?
Well, anyway, the seat was
standing perfectly upright
in his front yard right
next to his Sea-Doos,
because, like, he has Sea-Doos.
But there was still a pair
of legs buckled into them.
Human legs.
Jesus H. Christ.
You okay? WALT:
Yeah, sorry. I'm...
I was just moved.
CARMEN: Maybe we
should hear from the faculty.
Certainly this tragedy didn't
only affect our students.
Mr. White, would you
like to say something?
And by the way,
welcome back. Hm?
[ALL APPLAUD]
It's so good to have you back.
Uh...
I... I guess what I
would... Sorry, sorry.
[CLEARS THROAT]
I guess what I
would wanna say is,
to look on the bright side.
First of all, nobody on
the ground was killed.
And that...
I mean, an incident like this,
over a populated urban center?
That right there, that's just
gotta be some minor miracle.
So...
Plus, neither plane was full.
You know, the 737 was, what, uh,
maybe two-thirds full,
I believe? Right, yes?
Or maybe even
three-quarters full?
Well, at any rate, what
you're left with casualty-wise
is just the 50th-worst
air disaster.
Actually, tied for 50th.
There are, in truth,
53 crashes throughout history
that are just as bad
or worse. Tenerife.
Has anybody...? Anybody
hear of Tenerife? No?
In 1977, two fully loaded 747s
crashed into each
other on Tenerife.
Heh. Does anybody
know how big a 747 is?
I mean, it's way
bigger than a 737,
and we're talking
about two of them.
Nearly 600 people
died on Tenerife.
But do any of you
even remember it at all?
Any of you? I doubt it.
You know why? It's
because people move on.
They just move
on. And we will too.
We will move on, and
we will get past this.
That is what human beings do.
We survive, and, uh...
We survive and... And
we overcome. Yeah.
We survive. We survive and...
Okay? Thank you.
[MIKE FEEDBACKS]
Good.
[♪♪♪]
[GOAT BLEATING]
Hey, how's your
Aunt Marie doing?
Fine. I... I guess.
You make sure you say
hello to her for me, will you?
Why don't you just come
inside? It's your house.
No, I...
[CAR DOOR SLAMS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
He's gone.
MARIE: Hey, Flynn. How's tricks?
How's what? Tricks.
It's an expression.
How are you?
Why... Why you gotta
treat him like this?
Why you gotta be like this?
Why can't you just talk even?
Hey, hey, hey. Cool
down, okay? Okay?
Out of the mouths of babes, huh?
[DOOR SLAMS]
Wow.
You know, try not
to hold it against him.
You know, I mean, the poor kid,
he's probably just
dying of curiosity.
You know, and I guess it would
be natural for him to wonder.
I mean, he's probably
just wondering,
"What is it that could
have gone so wrong
that my mother
would leave...?" Marie.
I can't help you get
through this, Skyler.
If you won't tell me
what it is that Walt did?
Well, you know what, I don't...
I don't remember
asking you, all right?
So if you wanna be supportive,
be supportive without prying.
That would be really
great. "Prying." Okay.
Well, prying's a strong word.
So helpful.
LEADER: It's that
voice inside your head.
It's that sneaky,
rat-bastard, 24/7 voice.
You guys know
what I'm talking about.
That voice that tells you
you're not good enough.
Not good enough for what?
Not good enough to be what,
president of the United States?
Well, okay, so maybe
you're not that good.
But now,
are you good enough
to deserve your share
of basic human happiness?
Are you good enough to be
okay with who and what you are?
I say yes.
But it doesn't
matter what I say.
It's your voice,
which means you're
the only one that hears it.
Which means you're the
only one that can fight it, right?
Jesse, we never hear from you.
What's going on? You
can tell me I'm full of shit.
It's okay, I don't mind.
Just come on. Let us in on it.
So, like, what makes
you the expert?
I don't think I ever
said I was that.
JESSE: Yeah, but you're
the one sitting here, right?
Telling us "thus" and "so,"
"be happy," "forgive
yourself," blah, blah, blah.
Have you ever
really hurt anybody?
I don't just mean disappointed
your mother or whatever,
but did you ever
really hurt someone?
I killed my daughter.
It was July 18th,
which is my birthday.
July 18th, 1992.
I was high on cocaine
and I was drunk.
Cocaine wasn't an issue
because I had bought myself
two grams as a birthday
present. I had plenty left.
But I was out of vodka.
And this is in
Portsmouth, Virginia,
where instead of selling
liquor in the supermarkets,
they have these ABC stores,
which close at 5 p.m., and
right then it was like 4:42.
So I'm arguing with my wife.
"Come on. Go to the ABC
for me, it's my birthday.
Come on. They're
not gonna sell it to me."
And she's saying "No, no."
So I'm pissed.
And the clock is ticking,
so I jump in my truck.
She's my 6-year-old daughter.
She's playing at the
end of the driveway.
So...
How do you not hate yourself?
I did hate myself
for a long time.
But it didn't stop me from
drinking and getting high.
It just made it that much worse.
Self-hatred, guilt, it
accomplishes nothing.
It just stands in the way.
Stands in the way of what?
True change.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[SIGHS]
[CLEARS THROAT] Skyler.
Is this a good time to talk?
Yeah. Come in. Please.
Skyler.
Uh...
[SIGHS]
Do you wanna start?
Okay.
Why... Why are you doing this?
Why are you even
thinking this way?
Is it to punish me?
I am not punishing you, Walt.
This is punitive,
is what this is.
We are happily married.
[SCOFFS]
I am happily married.
I am happy. We're just...
I love you, Skyler. And I
would do anything for you.
Would you even consider...?
I mean, Jesus!
You come in here and you
wave these papers in my face,
when there's a... A whole
other, entire side to this thing.
There's your side
and there's my side,
and you haven't
heard my side yet.
You haven't heard
any of it at all.
You're a drug dealer.
No. What...? How...? What?
[EXHALES]
Yeah.
How else could you possibly
make that kind of money?
Marijuana.
That Pinkman kid.
No?
Oh, my God, Walt.
Cocaine?
It's methamphetamine.
But I'm... I'm a
manufacturer, I'm not a dealer.
Oh.
Per se. I... It...
It doesn't mean...
No, Skyler!
Listen to me. Skyler,
listen... No, no!
There are a lot
of angles to this.
It's complicated, all right?
So please, let's...
Please, let's just sit back
down and we'll talk it through.
I'm gonna make you a deal, Walt.
I won't tell Hank
and I won't tell your
children or anybody else.
Nobody will hear it from me.
But only if you
grant me this divorce
and stay out of our lives.
No, Skyler... I mean it.
Now let me the hell out
of here before I throw up.
BOY: Take care, buddy.
Bye, Jesse.
Your windshield's broken.
Yeah.
Little friction in the
marriage right now.
Strictly temporary.
We're just...
We're just taking
a little break.
That's you, over there.
Listen, uh, money.
Saul has got it for you, so as
soon as you're feeling better...
I'm better.
You're better? Really?
What, the rehab?
It... It helped?
Yeah. I'm done using.
That's excellent. That's...
That's very good,
Jesse. Boy, very good.
You know, um, in spite
of how bad things got,
it really could be looked
at like a wake-up call
for both of us.
I mean, you know,
just to get our lives
back together again
and on the straight and narrow.
You been following
this airplane crash?
Yeah.
You know it was Jane's dad
who accidentally
crashed them together
because he was so torn up?
Okay, look, let me stop
you right there, all right?
You are not
responsible for this.
Not in any way,
shape or form, all right?
Now, I... I am very
up-to-date on this thing,
probably far more than you are,
and there are... There
many factors at play there.
Yeah?
For instance,
there's some sort of
collision radar on the jet
that may not have
been working properly.
Now that's public record.
You can look that up.
And the whole system is
run on 1960s technology.
No.
No, really, I blame
the government.
You either run from things
or you face them, Mr. White.
Well, what exactly
does that mean?
I learned it in rehab.
It's all about accepting
who you really are.
I accept who I am.
And who are you?
I'm the bad guy.
[PEOPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Here's some napkins
for you. Enjoy.
Is the food to
your satisfaction?
Very much.
It's good to see you again.
May I? Please.
[SIGHS]
I have an offer that I think
will be of interest to you.
I, uh, actually
am not here to...
I'm here because I owe
you the courtesy and respect
to tell you this personally.
I'm done.
It has nothing to do
with you personally.
I find you extraordinarily
professional,
and I appreciate the
way you do business.
I'm just making a change
in my life, is what it is.
And I'm...
I'm at some... Something
of a crossroads,
and it's brought
me to a realization.
I am not a criminal.
No offense to any
people who are,
but this is not me.
I'd like you to hear my
offer, notwithstanding.
It won't change
my mind, I'm sorry.
Three million dollars for
three months of your time.
Three months, then out.
Three million?
May I take this as a "yes"?
[SIGHS]
I have money. I have more
money than I know how to spend.
What I don't have is my family.
The answer is still no.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
[METALLIC CLANGING]
[IN SPANISH] That's it!
Did you feel it?
Texas!
I've made this trip three times,
and every time there's
three big bumps,
and that's how you know.
We are officially in Texas!
This time I got a
job waiting for me.
I got a cousin who's
got a body shop.
Yo, that's for me, homes.
They call me "Olive Oil"
because I paint them slick.
I do pearlescent,
color-shift, you name it.
I painted cars for some of
the biggest gangsters
in Michoacán.
Wow, those are beautiful boots.
Not much good
for working, but...
Hey, what's on the
toes there? Little silver...
[GUNSHOTS]
[IN ENGLISH] What's
going on in there?
[GUNSHOTS]
[GUNSHOT]
[♪♪♪]