[LIGHTER CLICKS]
TORTUGA [IN SPANISH]: More.
Another.
[IN SPANISH] Careful, señor.
Hot day like today,
too much oil in the machine
can cause it to blow a gasket.
There are two kinds
of men in this world.
Those who drink
and those who pour.
Shut up and fill my glass.
Hey, you two.
Yes, you.
I used to be just like you.
Worked dirt for the
man till my hands bled.
But no more.
Because I learned that a
man can never drink his fill
by waiting in line for the tap.
MAN [IN SPANISH]: Listen to him.
He can teach you something.
Hey, how you doing, boss?
BOLSA: Good to
see you, my friend.
You know, I never pegged
you for such a deep thinker.
I keep thinking I
should write a book.
Maybe, maybe...
So, what brings you to this
burro's asshole of a town?
I knew I would find you here.
Don't you have
something to deliver?
Cutting it close, aren't you?
Ah, lots of time.
Tortuga may be slow out
of the gate, but he always...
Finishes first. [LAUGHS]
Yes, I know. Just
like your namesake.
I like the way
you talk, Tortuga.
Yeah?
You've got such
a way with words.
They flow like a waterfall.
I like that about you.
Salud. Salud.
I'm so stupid. I
missed your birthday.
No, I feel terrible.
So bad I came all the way
here to this burro's asshole
to give you your present.
Present?
Come on, no need to
go through the trouble.
Forget it, I wanted to.
I have it for you in the back.
Back there? Yes.
Come. Follow me.
It's perfect!
BOLSA: Do you really like it?
Oh.
I love it!
What a great pet it will make.
Thank you, boss!
Excellent.
Let me sign it for you.
Let me sign it...
"For the big talker."
[SCREAMING]
[♪♪♪]
MIKE: He's still breathing.
Well, by the looks of him, he
has no idea how close he came.
I'm assuming Saul Goodman
doesn't need to know.
Mum's the word.
[ENGINE STARTS]
♪ Old MacDonald
had a farm E-I-E-I-O ♪
♪ And on this farm
He had a duck ♪
♪ E-I-E-I-O ♪
♪ With a quack, quack here
And a quack, quack there ♪
[SINGING OFF-KEY]
♪ Old MacDonald
had a farm E-I-E-I-O ♪
[HUMMING]
♪ Old MacDonald
had a farm E-I-E-I-O ♪
SKYLER: Oh, son of a bitch.
Hang on, baby.
[DIALING]
[PHONE LINE RINGING]
WALT [OVER PHONE]: Hello.
Walt? Are you in the house?
Oh, hey, Skyler. Yeah, it's me.
What? What the hell
are you doing in there?
I'm back.
No, no, you're not back, Walt.
You're not back.
Get... Get out of there.
Well, it's... It's my
house too, Skyler.
I'm staying. End of story.
We had an agreement. I
didn't agree to anything.
Now, look, just come on inside
and we'll talk this
through, okay?
No. No. There's
nothing to talk about.
I am not coming in
there until you get out.
Well, suit yourself.
SKYLER: Walt.
Walt?
[SIGHS]
SKYLER: What is wrong with you?
Skyler, I have every
right to be here.
No, you don't.
You don't live here anymore.
We're getting a divorce.
I don't agree to a divorce.
Well, it's not up to you.
If you don't get out
of here right now,
I'm gonna call the police
and I'm going to
tell them everything.
I mean it, Walt.
There's the phone.
[CRYING]
SKYLER: It's ringing.
WOMAN [OVER PHONE]:
Albuquerque Police Department.
Operator number 314.
How may I help you?
Albuquerque Police
Department. How may I help you?
Yes, I, uh... I want to
report a disturbance, please.
No, no, it's not... It's
not exactly, it's, um...
It's a domestic issue.
Okay.
They're connecting me.
Right hand to
God, I will tell them.
Do what you have to do, Skyler.
This family is everything to me.
Without it, I have
nothing to lose.
Fine.
Yes. My name is Skyler White.
I need police assistance
at my home right away.
My soon-to-be-ex-husband
broke into my house,
and I need an officer to
come and remove him.
It's 308 Negra Arroyo Lane.
Okay. Okay.
Thank you.
They're coming.
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
Dad's here? WALT:
Great, he's home.
WALT JR.: Dad. Hey, son.
How are you? Oh!
Are... Are you back for good?
Why are you home so soon?
I... I'm not.
Ah.
Hey, I am starving. How
about a grilled cheese?
Yeah, sure. You want one too?
Walter, your dad and I
have something
we need to discuss.
When your sandwich is
ready, I'll bring it to your room.
Mom, ca-can't it wait?
I haven't seen
Dad in, like, forever.
Walter? WALT: How was school?
WALT JR.: It was good.
WALT: Yeah? Homework?
WALT JR.: No, not really.
WALT: What does that mean?
[WALT LAUGHS]
Mmm.
So are you gonna
be at work tomorrow?
WALT: Yeah, that's the plan.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Hello, ma'am. We were
called about a disturbance?
It's more of a trespassing
situation, really, but...
Yeah, that was me.
You called the cops on Dad?
SKYLER: I came home
from work, and he was back.
He had just moved
back into the house.
And I asked him to leave,
but he won't listen. I just...
I want him out. I want
him out of the house.
Okay, Mrs. White,
there's a couple
questions I need to ask you.
It's important you
answer honestly.
Did he strike you?
No.
Has he ever hit you?
No. This is not about violence.
This is about trespassing.
About him being
here against my will.
Okay. Trespassing.
You're divorced, then?
No, working on it. Um...
Right now, were separated.
Legally separated?
Well, there's not a court
order, if that's what you mean.
But we've been living
apart for almost two weeks,
give or take.
I-I changed the locks.
Isn't that breaking
and entering?
Whose name is on the title?
Both of us. It's...
It's jointly owned.
We can't arrest a man for
breaking into his own house.
Not without a court order
requiring he stays away.
Unless he's threatened
you or the kids.
No. Not...
[HOLLY CRYING] Not physically.
But having him in
the house is just...
It's... It's not a good
thing. Excuse me.
I got her, honey. Come here.
Here we go.
You hungry? You
hungry? Here we go.
Oh. That was it.
I'm sorry, officer.
Where were we?
COP: Disagreements.
Yes, well, we've
had our share of that.
I haven't...
I haven't been the most
attentive husband lately.
Mrs. White, would this be easier
if we stepped
outside for a minute?
No.
Nope.
I'm fine right here.
I'm gonna level with you, ma'am.
If you want him
out of the house,
you'll have to help me.
Is it possible maybe he's
broken any laws that you know of?
Anything at all.
Anything that we can
work with here, just tell me.
Even if it's just a suspicion,
I can work with that.
I'll get him out of
the house for you.
COP: What's your
take on all this?
WALT JR.: It's my mom's fault.
She won't even
say what my dad did
and it's because he
didn't do anything.
I don't know why
she's being this way.
My dad, he is a great guy.
WALT: Son, it's
not your mom's fault.
Mrs. White.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
There's no legal basis
for us to remove your
husband from the house.
Next time you feel things
are getting out of control,
you should call this
number. It's the family hotline.
I'd really look into
some counseling.
Best of luck to you folks.
Listen, thank you,
officers. We're sorry.
Why you gotta...? Why
you gotta do this to Dad?
Junior, wait, come on.
Don't blame your
mother for this.
[DOOR SLAMS]
Sorry.
[SHUSHING]
[HOLLY CRYING]
Welcome home.
[PHONE DIALING]
[DOORBELL RINGING]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
He lives. Happy
housewarming, kid.
Don't look so glad
to see me. Thanks.
Oh, interesting
decor. It's, uh, subtle.
The whole minimalist thing
never really blew
my hair back, but hey.
So how are you doing?
Staying clean?
Good. I was kind of worried
that you were back to old habits
since I didn't hear
from you, you know.
You realize how stupid it is
to ignore your
counsel's phone calls?
What if I was trying to warn you
the DEA was gonna kick
down your door? What then?
Why don't you
spare me the sermon
and get to why you're here?
Fair enough.
Remember the other day
when I brought up the idea
of you getting back in
touch with your, uh, partner?
Well, I kind of wanted
to re-float that boat.
I'm not suggesting you
yourself get back to cooking.
I mean, you being
in rehab and all.
I only want you to convince
the master chef to do his thing.
So, what do you say?
Sure, man. Whatever.
Okay. Whatever what?
I mean, you gonna call him?
I said I'll handle it.
Now, bounce, will you? Please?
Final thought.
Look at this place.
You're house-poor,
you got no bankroll.
If you get the
maestro cooking again,
I'll make it worth your while.
[SIGHS]
Call him.
[DIALS]
JANE [ON RECORDING]: If you're
trying to sell me something, four words:
"Do Not Call list."
However, if you're
cool, leave it at the beep.
[HANK SIGHS]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Schrader.
Yes, sir. Yeah, what's up?
Yeah?
[LAUGHS]
That's great news,
sir. Thank you.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely,
you can bet on that.
Hey, listen, thanks again, sir,
I really appreciate you
stepping to the plate. Thank you.
[LAUGHING]
So you gonna keep
me in suspense or what?
What's the good news?
Merkert called in
a couple favors.
El Paso wants me back. Ahh.
Hey, man, congrats,
man. That's fantastic.
Thank you. Yeah.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[CAR ALARM BEEPS]
[♪♪♪]
Hello.
[ALL CLUCKING AND PEEPING]
[♪♪♪]
[BELL DINGS]
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
GUS [IN SPANISH]:
Gentlemen. Welcome.
Thank you for coming.
Any difficulty at the border?
The day I can't get
across the border
is the day I retire.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
Please, come in.
I apologize that it's not
wheelchair accessible.
BOLSA: My apologies, Gustavo.
Of course, you should
have been advised.
It's your territory, you had
a right to bless the order.
But...
We had no reason to believe
the man was of concern to you.
Indeed, he is.
So you're in business
with this Heisenberg.
I don't know him by
that name, but yes.
I've made no
secret of the fact that
I have always done business
with certain local
manufacturers.
You and I, we still
make money together.
It's never affected
our relationship.
Don Salamanca had
a nephew named Tuco.
Yes, I knew of him.
BOLSA: Then perhaps you know
Don Salamanca mentored
him in the business.
Thought of Tuco as a son.
When Don Salamanca
was no longer able,
Tuco took over for his uncle.
He was a key man
in our organization
north of the border.
He was loyal.
This Heisenberg, Walter White,
he was one of
Tuco's local suppliers.
Until he betrayed Tuco.
So now you see, blood
must be repaid by blood.
Tuco's cousins here,
they have the right
to exact vengeance.
The Salamanca
family, the cartel,
stands shoulder to shoulder.
[BELL DINGS]
Don Salamanca.
Gentlemen.
I feel your loss deeply.
Please accept my condolences.
I have no issue with
your right to vengeance.
But I am presently engaged
in business with this man.
When our business is done,
he will no longer be
of any concern to me.
Until then...
I need him alive.
[BELL DINGING RAPIDLY]
Excuse us.
I don't tell you how to fry
your chickens, Gustavo.
You should leave matters of
my organization's politics to me.
Do I not run my own territory?
Of course you do.
And I will advise
them to be patient.
But I recommend you finish
your business with the man quickly.
Or you risk losing the
good graces of the cartel.
That would not be wise.
And those boys inside,
I cannot guarantee
that they will listen.
They are not like you and I.
[DIALS]
JANE [ON RECORDING]: If you're
trying to sell me something, four words:
"Do Not Call list."
However, if you're
cool, leave it at the beep.
If you're trying to sell
me something, four words:
"Do Not Call list."
However, if you're
cool, leave it at the beep.
[♪♪♪]
If you're trying to sell me
something, four words...
[SIGHS]
[HOLLY CRYING]
Oh, sweetheart. Sweetie,
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's okay, my girl.
Yes, it's okay. It's okay.
Mama's got you.
Oh, I've got you.
Yes. Yes.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
WALT: Skyler? Want some help?
Skyler, can I use the bathroom?
[SNIFFING]
God...
[URINE TRICKLING]
WOMAN: What do you
mean? Against your will?
SKYLER: Yes. Very
much against my will.
He just... He
showed right back up.
And he doesn't want a
divorce. Won't even consider it.
I called the police on him.
I was... I was so clo...
So close to what?
Nothing. Never mind.
Skyler, I can't
advise you properly
if you don't give
me all the facts.
Understand, I'm bound by
the attorney-client privilege
to keep everything
you tell me a secret.
I can't tell a soul unless
you authorize me to.
Even if it's something illegal?
Especially if it's illegal.
I'm your lawyer, not the
police. My job is to protect you.
[WHISPERING] My
husband makes meth.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Methamphetamine.
Your husband's a drug dealer?
He's a manufacturer,
technically.
They, um... They
call them cooks.
I looked it up on the Internet.
This is my advice,
and you should take it:
Sue your husband for
divorce immediately.
Let me go to the police and
tell them what you just told me.
I'll go in ex parte to
get a restraining order
from the court today.
If he comes anywhere
near you and your children,
he'll go straight to jail
no questions asked.
This is a no-brainer.
It's the best thing for
you and your family.
I can't.
I can't do it.
I don't want my son to find out
that his father is a criminal.
I just...
I can't do that to him.
In the end, it may
not be up to you.
Drug dealers have a
way of getting caught.
Walt has lung cancer.
His treatment bought
him some time.
But the doctors, they all
say that sooner or later...
I can't see why I should
lay all this on my family
when things may...
resolve themselves on their own
without anyone else knowing.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
Man, did I lose a
bet or something?
What are we doing
in this shithole?
Just relax, will you?
GOMEZ: Relax?
This is the kind of
place you get knifed.
We should have
went to Chili's, man.
All right, already. Jesus.
GOMEZ: Outback Steakhouse.
It's not too late. They
got that Blooming Onion.
What's wrong with
spicing things up a little?
This spice looks
like it's been through
a couple of guys already.
So when you headed
back down to El Paso?
Uh, you know. Between
all the packing, errands,
getting my ducks in a
row, maybe a week or two.
Week or two? Come on, man.
I'd be dying to get back in.
Not like there's nothing
going on up here.
What are you talking about?
Ain't jack going on up
here. It's quiet as hell.
I'm gonna hit the head.
[♪♪♪]
Those two over there.
I think they're holding.
Man, in this place, the
bartender's probably holding.
All right. Whoa,
whoa. What you doing?
Calling A.P.D.,
what do you think?
Since when can't we
handle a couple dirtballs?
Come on. Courtesy call.
What if Vice is running
some kind of undercover op?
Screw it. It's your turn to pay.
[♪♪♪]
Where you going?
Gotta take a leak.
Jesus, get yourself some Flomax.
♪ I said Lord Take me downtown ♪
♪ I'm just looking
For some tush ♪
♪ I've been bad I've been good ♪
Stand up.
♪ I ain't asking for much ♪
MAN: You got a
problem with us, bitch?
Your move.
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
DEA. Don't move.
Go out and tell my partner
to get his ass in here.
♪ Take me back Way back home ♪
♪ Not by myself ♪
[DIALS]
JANE [ON RECORDING]: If you're
trying to sell me something, four words:
"Do Not Call list."
However, if you're
cool, leave it at the beep.
If you're trying to sell
me something, four words:
"Do Not Call..."
[PHONE BEEPS]
[PHONE LINE RINGING]
[PHONE LINE BEEPING]
RECORDING [ON PHONE]: The
number you have reached, 149-4985,
in area code 505 is no longer...
[♪♪♪]
[FRONT DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES]
[GARAGE DOOR OPENS]
[SIGHS] [GARAGE DOOR CLOSES]
WALT: Skyler.
Can we talk?
ASAC wants to see you.
And?
We were hanging back,
we saw a deal go down.
I went outside to call it in.
You stayed to keep
an eye on the suspects.
That's when they attacked you.
What I didn't tell him is that
you left your gun under the seat
before you went back inside.
WALT: I've done
a terrible thing.
But I did it for a good reason.
I did it for us.
That is college
tuition for Walter Jr.
And Holly 18 years
down the road.
That is health insurance
for you and the kids.
For Junior's physical therapy,
his SAT tutor.
It's money for groceries,
for gas,
for birthdays and
graduation parties.
Skyler, that money is for
this roof over your head,
the mortgage that you are
not going to be able to afford
on a part-time bookkeeper's
salary when I'm gone.
Walt, I... Please. Please.
This money, I didn't steal it.
It doesn't belong
to anyone else.
I earned it.
The things I've
done to earn it...
the things that
I've had to do...
I've got to live with them.
Skyler...
all that I've done,
all the sacrifices that I
have made for this family,
all of it will be for nothing
if you don't accept
what I've earned.
Please.
I'll be here when you
get home from work.
You can give me
your answer then.
Hey, Sky.
[SIGHS]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Hey, some coffee?
Yeah.
That report's looking real
good. I like how it looks.
Good.
Are your kids home?
[CLEARS THROAT]
[SIGHS]
Ooh. Ooh, ooh.
It's here! It's here!
Everybody, come on
in! Look! [DOOR OPENS]
Hey, Mrs. White.
Oh.
Hey, Louis.
Hey, uh, thanks for
having me over for dinner.
Um, sure.
Hey, Skyler.
I'm, uh, cooking dinner.
Pot roast.
Uh, could you...?
So how was your day?
Good. Good.
Excellent.
I hope you don't mind,
I invited Louis to
stay for dinner tonight.
You know, as a thank-you
for driving Walter
Jr. To school for us.
We've been kind of absent,
but, I tell you, Louis
really pitched in.
Um...
Look, I just wanna say
that I feel good about
our talk this morning,
and I'm very eager to hear
what you're thinking about,
about what we talked about.
But, you know, whenever
you're ready, of course.
[SIGHS THEN CHUCKLES]
Honesty is good.
Don't you think?
I fucked Ted.
SKYLER: Boys, dinner.
Iced tea? WALT JR.: Yeah.
SKYLER: Louis?
WALT JR.: Thank you.
LOUIS: Yes, please.
SKYLER: All right.
I want you boys both
to eat your salad, okay?
WALT JR.: Really?
SKYLER: I know
nobody likes salad,
but it's good for you.
Thanks, darling.
WALT JR.: Thank you.
[♪♪♪]