[♪♪♪]
[WALT BREATHING HEAVILY]
[CAR DOOR BEEPING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
I got it, I got it.
You're like a bee at
a damn picnic, Marie.
[IMITATING BEE BUZZING]
Morning. Hey, buddy.
Ready to get your rocks on?
See? I knew it.
"Mineral show" is just some
sort of guy code for "strip club."
Yeah. You got your singles?
Got it? Yeah.
Don't let him get
too crazy, okay?
Cram one more
giant geode in here,
we'll be sleeping in the garage.
HANK: Got it. I
got it. I'm sorry.
[GRUNTS]
HANK: Christ. Longest week ever.
[HANK LAUGHS]
Here's just hoping we
get something good.
Keep your fingers crossed.
Relax, buddy, this
ain't no spy movie.
[CHUCKLES]
It's more like Rocky, you know?
[HUMMING "EYE OF THE TIGER"]
♪ Get the bad guy ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 'Cause it's the
eye Of the tiger ♪
♪ It's the thrill Of the fight ♪
♪ Risin' up ♪
[MUMBLING LYRICS]
[CLEARS THROAT] [CUTS IGNITION]
But... What are
you doing, buddy?
Leaving.
No, go inside, order
something like last time.
Avoid suspicion.
Besides, I want a vanilla shake.
We'll use the drive-thru.
All right, baby, let's
see what we got.
What the hell? Look at this.
Bum, bum, bum, bum, bum.
That's work. That's home.
That's work, that's home.
What, this guy...
he goes two places
every day, all week?
It's unbelievable.
Chicken-slinging son of a bitch.
Hank, is it possible
that maybe, just maybe,
he's not your guy?
A guy this clean
has got to be dirty.
[SIGHS]
What's the play here, buddy?
How do I get this guy?
Yeah.
How?
[♪♪♪]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[DIALING]
Yes, hi.
I live on the 4900
block of Doswell Place,
and I want to report
a very suspicious man who's
lurking in my neighborhood.
He's sitting in a
blue sedan, and he...
He's been staring
at a particular house
for a very long time.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
If you would, I
would appreciate it.
All right.
I guess we'd better get started.
I already did.
Yeah?
Hey, uh...
Got one of those for me?
One of those what?
Cigarette.
[SCOFFS]
Look, it's still in
there, all right?
I didn't get a chance yet.
Just give me one.
[COUGHS]
Hm!
So, what have you been up to?
What?
You know, just
a day in the life.
What do you do after work?
Go home. Watch TV.
What do you watch?
I don't know, stuff.
Well, like what?
Like, uh, Ice Road Truckers.
Ice Road Truckers.
What happens on that one?
Guys drive on ice.
[CHUCKLES]
I am gonna do it.
You gotta inhale, by the way.
What the hell, man?
Don't you have
enough cancer already?
Look.
I said...
I'd do it. I'll do it.
Yeah, well,
what does it matter?
We're both dead men anyway.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[CALCULATOR WHIRRING]
[BUTTONS TAP]
[BEEPS] [PHONE LINE RINGS]
WALT [OVER PHONE]: Hi. Hi.
Am I, uh, catching
you at a bad time?
No. I have a few minutes.
So
Mr. I'm-Almost-16-So-Leave-Me-Alone
doesn't want a big
thing for his birthday.
Wants to hang out with friends.
Which is fine by me. You?
Fine by me.
Okay. So I figured a
low-key family dinner,
no official party,
and we bite the bullet
and buy him a car.
Used, I was thinking,
would be best.
But no more than five years old.
Airbags, safety-rated, all that.
Do you, um, have any
thoughts on what kind?
Or should I just
go ahead and...?
Yeah. No, you just go ahead.
Okay.
Listen, on another subject,
I just wanted to tell you
that business is good.
Really good.
So good that I'm
thinking, maybe,
you don't need to even
work your second job.
You're turning a profit?
We're coming close.
Give us another
month or two and, yeah,
we'll be there.
All of this to say,
maybe you could start
thinking about an exit strategy.
I'm working on it.
Okay.
[BEEPS OFF]
[RINGING]
[WALT GRUNTS]
Hello?
HANK [OVER PHONE]:
Hey, buddy. Wake you?
No, Hank. I'm up.
Oh, good. Uh, what you doing?
I'm...
Hey, listen, I'll cut to
it. Another favor to ask.
I'm thinking about Gus Fring,
how he never goes anywhere.
One restaurant,
home, back and forth?
Which now I'm even
more convinced is bullshit,
because the man owns
13 other restaurants, right?
So I started thinking about
this little empire of his, right?
Fourteen restaurants.
Who supplies them?
What's the base of operations?
So I do a little
digging, and bingo.
Pollos Hermanos has a
main distribution center.
Uh, it's not far from town.
The place is huge. I mean,
I'm looking at it
online right now.
It's a... It's a big warehouse.
And rows of these
long poultry buildings,
or hatcheries, or
whatever you call them.
Lots of space to
hide illicit activity.
Sounds promising, right?
Huh.
So, what do you say, buddy?
Got another field trip in you?
[HANK CHUCKLES]
Uh...
You know, Hank,
I'm... I'm... I'm...
I mean, It sounds
great, it really does.
But I'm...
You know, I won't lie.
You caught me somewhat...
indisposed.
What do you mean, like...
Like taking-a-dump indisposed?
Yeah. That's...
Embarrassingly, that's it.
You know, it's just...
[SIGHS]
upset stomach and,
you know, everything...
Yeah.
It's out of control.
And it's really explosive.
Bad Tex-Mex at the mall.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I get it.
You don't have to
paint me a picture.
One guy in a diaper
is enough for this trip.
Yeah, and I'm sorry, Hank.
Don't be. I've been
asking a lot of you lately.
I appreciate it.
I'll find another ride for this.
Another ride?
Yeah. I can get
someone else to take me.
Uh, my trainer, Chuck.
Maybe I'll... I'll ask him.
Well, look, I'm... This is
probably just a 24-hour thing.
Maybe 48 hours at the most.
And, um, do you
think you can possibly
hold off for a day or two?
Oh, jeez, buddy, I mean, I...
You know, I just...
I would just really
love to be the one to
be able to take you there.
And... And, I mean,
I've just... I've just really
enjoyed, you know,
the time with you
and helping you and...
Well, yeah.
Okay, sure. If it means
that much to you.
[CHUCKLES]
Just, you know, give me a
call when you're feeling up to it.
Thank you. I... I will. Okay.
Bye.
[PHONE BEEPS OFF]
[DIALING]
[PHONE LINE RINGING]
MIKE [OVER PHONE]: Yeah.
Uh, Mike, listen.
I just want to say
first off, don't be angry.
What is it, Walter?
My brother-in-law,
my DE... He...
Soon, he will probably,
in the near future,
take a ride out to a
certain distribution center
to look around for things.
You know, just...
look around for
things. And, yeah.
[PHONE LINE CLICKS]
Mike?
Where's this all going?
Elsewhere.
[STEAM HISSING]
All set. Please give this to
your car-care professional.
Thank you.
[THOMAS DOLBY'S "HYPERACTIVE"
PLAYING OVER RADIO]
So a hand wax for you today?
Okay, great.
Give this to your
car-care professional.
And the black Explorer...
We could shampoo
your floor mats,
but deluxe detailing is
the best bang for your buck.
Oh, and SUV's are extra.
And please give this to
your car-care professional.
Thank you.
Please give this to your
car-care professional.
Hey, Sky.
Oh, my God. Ted.
What are you...?
Someone from the office,
uh, said you worked down here.
So I thought I'd
come down and say hi.
Wow. Well,
hello. [TED LAUGHS]
You look great.
No. No, I don't.
I... I probably
just look crazed.
Not at all. You look happy.
Last time I saw you...
Hi, there.
Um, I guess, Skyler,
I'm gonna need to talk to you.
[WHISPERING]
Ted, I really don't think
we have anything to talk about.
Actually, we do.
SKYLER: An audit?
Wait, an audit tomorrow?
How long have you had this?
Um, a while.
I debated, you
know, contacting you.
Contact me? What
about a lawyer, Ted?
Ted, this is...
This is the CID.
The criminal division.
My God, you're facing
a felony charge here.
A $100,000 fine on top of
the taxes you already owe,
plus five years in prison.
Yeah. It's bad.
Yeah, it most certainly is.
Look, here's the thing. I
was wondering, maybe,
if, um...
there's some way you
could help with this.
Help?
Help how?
Well, with your knowledge
of how the books
got the way they are,
maybe there's some way
you could undo what's in there.
You want me to
uncook your books?
Well, maybe there's some
method or some accounting trick
you could, you know, use...
Ted, it doesn't work like that.
The damage is already...
My name.
My signatures
are all over those books.
Skyler, I'm
accountable, not you.
Let me explain what's
gonna happen here, okay?
Once the CID sees
this is willful tax fraud,
they are going to build
the strongest possible case.
And once they
start down that path,
they have an 80
percent conviction rate.
That's because they're
allowed to monitor your mail
and tap your phones.
And not just you, Ted,
everyone involved
in those books.
I can't have this in my life.
I cannot be audited.
Skyler, you're going to be
fine, okay? They're after me.
It's the captain they want,
not some cashier at a car wash.
No offense.
I'm sorry. I, uh...
Look, I don't want
you to worry, okay?
I'm going to figure out a way
through this, somehow. Okay?
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
Here.
JESSE: So is he gonna kill him?
Is who gonna kill who?
Gus.
Is he gonna kill
Mr. White's brother-in-law?
I mean, he's the reason
for all of this here, right?
Because it's totally logical
for him to off the dude.
A-hole DEA agent
poking around your junk.
Who needs that, right?
Makes sense to get
rid of him for good.
[WATER SLOSHING]
But killing a cop,
I don't know.
It could look suspicious
if the dude investigating
you suddenly up and dies.
Then there's...
There's Mr. White,
who would be even more apeshit
if he had family
getting murdered.
He'd never cook for Gus again.
Guess there's a lot
of angles to consider.
If something were to happen,
would you have a problem?
Who really cares what I think?
[GUNSHOT]
MAN: Get down, get down!
[♪♪♪]
[GUNSHOTS]
Son of a bitch.
You get comfortable, kid.
We may be here a while.
Hey.
Get down!
[♪♪♪]
[GUNFIRE]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Sí.
[IN SPANISH]
[LIQUID SLOSHING]
[DOORBELL BUZZING]
Should I even ask?
I wouldn't.
So, what, is this going
to be a regular thing now?
Meth cooking and
corpse disposal? Jesus.
Just grab us a
spare barrel, Walter.
What was it this time?
What did this poor
bastard do to piss off Gus?
Or did Gus just need to
send another message?
Shut your mouth.
You shut your mouth,
or I'll shut it for you.
I don't want you talking to me
or Jesse. Just get the barrel.
And if you ever plan
on calling the cops
on one of my guys again,
you go ahead and
get two barrels.
[MACHINERY WHIRRING DISTANTLY]
Yo. Like, um...
I guess I never thanked
you for what you did.
Thanks.
Next time don't stand
there like an idiot.
Move your feet.
Running and so forth.
But seriously, what...?
What was the deal with Gus?
The deal?
That Terminator shit.
Walking right into the bullets.
What the hell was he doing?
The cartel needs Gus.
His distribution network.
They're not looking to kill him.
But, what? The rest of
us are like open season?
Is he doing anything about that,
or do we keep hanging
out for target practice?
Kid, enough.
You got questions,
ask him yourself.
IRS AGENT: And here again.
Unreported income.
That's more than a
year straight so far.
Do you want to say something?
Because I'm having a
hard time figuring it out.
I'd have to, um,
have a look at the
copies of the receipts
to refresh my memory.
Take all the time
you need, Mr. Beneke.
That's why we're here.
[DOOR OPENS]
Oh, I am so sorry I am late.
I got lost. Hey, Ted.
Sky. Mwah.
Whoo! This building
is so confusing.
There are doors everywhere.
Hi. You are...?
Special Agent James Bekaris.
Ooh, "special." Skyler White.
Ms. White, you are
the accountant of record
for many of these
reports, correct?
Guilty as charged.
Perhaps you can you shed light
on this history of
missing revenue?
Missing? Mm-hm.
No, it's there.
No. Revenue most definitely
flowed through this company,
but it's not all accounted
for in your reports.
Huh!
Let's take a look.
Hm...
Oh, well, you know,
this account here,
that is Mr. Keller's account.
And Mr. Keller is an
old friend of Ted's dad.
And he always sends
an electronic payment,
which personally I hate,
because I'm a paper person.
But Mr. Keller is one of
those environmental people.
So anyway, since there
wasn't a physical check,
I didn't enter it into the
book. But the money is there.
Ms. White, you've read
Section 61 of the IRC?
I did not follow
what you just said.
How gross income for
a business is defined.
You're not allowed to do that.
Well, I think I am.
No, you're not.
You know what they
say about opinions.
Everyone's got one.
[LAUGHS]
But seriously, I am.
Doesn't matter if it's
an electronic check
or a paper check,
income is income.
You're not allowed
to not declare it.
When I input everything
into the Quicken,
nothing flashed red, so that's
gotta mean it's okay, right?
Quicken. Mm-hm.
You used Quicken to manage
books for a business this size.
I did. Oh, do you
guys use that here?
Because it is the best.
It's like having a calculator
on your computer. Amazing.
How did you get this job?
Oh, Ted hired me.
No, I mean your qualifications.
What are your qualifications?
Where did you get your training?
Ooh, well, I haven't
had any training, per se.
I've always been naturally
good with numbers.
Got a good instinct
for them. Right, Teddy?
[SIGHS]
Right.
This is all falling
into place now.
Ms. White, I just have to ask.
You're not managing accounts
anywhere else, are you?
Right now? No.
I'm a cashier at a car wash.
I'm not, uh, really clear
about what happened in there.
What happened was good news.
Ignorance of the law
doesn't equate to criminality.
It equates to ignorance.
Look, pay your back
taxes, pay the penalties,
and move on from this.
Just put it behind you.
Ha! Pay with what?
I owe them $617,000.
What am I...?
Look, just figure
it out, all right?
And you've just dodged prison.
Sell your assets.
Get rid of the BMW,
take out a second mortgage...
Second mortgage? I
have a lien on my house.
I don't have any assets.
There are no
assets left to sell.
Ted, if you don't pay them,
they will reopen
the investigation,
and that little fiction
I just spun up there
is gonna completely unravel.
You have to settle.
Wish I could.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
GUS: Come in.
I hope you brought an appetite.
Yeah, I guess.
Mike mentioned you
have some questions.
JESSE: Yeah.
GUS: We'll eat first,
and then we'll talk.
Right on.
What am I doing here?
I know you have concerns.
What happened yesterday
to my man at the farm,
it was a terrible thing.
Oh, the dude getting
his head blown off? Yeah.
I have invited you into my home,
prepared food so
we could sit and talk.
Discuss what's going
on in this business,
our business, like men.
And I will explain
everything that is happening.
I will answer your questions.
But first,
I need you to answer
one question for me.
Can you cook Walter's formula?
What?
Walter's formula.
Can you produce his product
without any help? Alone.
No.
Why?
You're asking me if I can
cook Mr. White's crystal?
Without him?
Me?
The junkie loser you
were about to waste
and dump in the
desert a month ago?
This your plan? Huh?
Invite me in your house,
make whatever this is...
be my buddy, and
make me feel important.
Then get me to
keep cooking for you
after you kill Mr. White?
You wanna... You
wanna talk like men?
Let's talk like men.
You kill Mr. White, you're
gonna have to kill me too.
That is not what I asked you.
You are here
because circumstances
with the cartel are untenable.
And I need your help.
I need you to help
prevent an all-out war.
Now, if you would...
answer the question.
[BEEPS]
Hey, you, uh... You headed out?
Yeah.
[ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS]
JESSE [OVER ANSWERING
MACHINE]: Yo, Mr. White.
I really gotta talk to you.
I don't know if you're
with your family,
but this is important.
So I'm hoping you
could come over.
Thank God. Come on in.
You, uh... You want
a beer or something?
No.
Should I sit down?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sorry, go ahead.
Okay, so, um...
Okay, so word has
come down that they...
They want me to go to Mexico.
There's some... Some
sort of war brewing
between Gus and the cartel.
"Word has come down"?
Yeah, the cartel has been...
Has been messing
with Gus' operation.
Like jacking trucks to,
like, send a message.
And, you know, yesterday,
that dude we brought to the lab.
I mean, they shot
him right in front of me.
I mean, just blew his head open.
I mean, some sniper nailed
him from like a mile away.
Anyway, uh, they've
been holding them off.
But between the
cartel taking potshots
and your brother-in-law
trying to throw a net
over the whole deal,
it's like what you call
a rock-and-a-hard-place
situation.
So, Gus is gonna cave.
So the cartel wants half
of Gus' entire operation,
and they want your formula.
And he's gonna give it to them.
Well, I... I gotta
give it to them.
I mean, I'm supposed
to go to Mexico and...
And teach a bunch
of cartel chemists
how to cook a batch of blue.
You know, and Gus
doesn't trust you,
so I gotta go.
I mean, you're the chemist, man.
You know, not... Not me. I
mean, let's say I go down to...
You know, go over there...
Go... Go to the jungle or whatever,
you know, and they
got like actual chemists,
like cartel chemists
asking me chemistry stuff
that I don't know how to
answer because I'm not you.
And what if, like,
all the equipment
is in Mexican
instead of English?
You know? Oh!
I don't know. I don't know.
I mean, if... If I mess this up,
I am dead, you know? All of us.
Mr. White, look, I... I need...
I need your help.
Okay, maybe you could...
Maybe you could, like, coach
me or something, you know.
Or you can, like,
give me some notes.
Mr. White?
So you saw Gus?
What? No.
You didn't see Gus.
No.
Then who told you all of that?
It was... It was passed
down, like I said.
"Passed down." By whom?
By, uh... By Mike and them.
I mean, they did. They...
So "they" doesn't include Gus.
You haven't been with Gus.
You haven't seen Gus.
You haven't spoken to Gus.
Why are you...?
You weren't at Gus'
house last night.
What?
What the hell? Jesus.
Still here.
It's still here.
Jesus.
You look me in the
eye and you tell me
that you weren't at
his house last night.
I, um...
Look, I didn't have
a chance, all right?
Okay? I knew you
would react this way.
I knew you would freak
out and wouldn't believe me.
That's... That's why
I didn't say anything.
Look, there was just this
one big pot of stew, okay?
He just made this one big
pot and we both ate from it.
What was I supposed to
do, huh? Poison myself?
Two hours and 18 minutes,
and you couldn't figure
out a way to give it to him?
He never left the room.
You lying little shit!
You had one thing
to do, one thing.
That is the only
thing, I might add,
that would save our lives.
And you were right there.
You were in his house.
And you didn't
have the guts to do it.
Two hours and 18 minutes?
You never had any intention
of killing him, did you?
How did you know I was
at his house last night?
Were you following me?
This.
This is how I knew.
You bugged my car?
7:10 to 9:28 p.m.
Two hours and 18 minutes.
But you had no
intentions, did you?
Not the slightest intention.
Everything that I
have done for you...
Oh!
You put a bug on my car?
I'm sorry, after everything
you've done for me?
What you've done for me?
You killed me, is
what you've done!
You've signed my death warrant!
And now you want
advice? I'll give you advice:
Go to Mexico and screw
up like I know you will,
and wind up in a
barrel somewhere!
[GRUNTS]
[EYEGLASSES
CLATTERING] [GASPING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[YELLS]
You son of a...
[BOTH YELLING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[BOTH GASPING AND PANTING]
[♪♪♪]
Can you walk?
Yeah.
Then get the fuck out of
here and never come back.
[PANTING]
[WALT GROANS]
[♪♪♪]