[MAN EXHALES SHARPLY]
[MIKE BREATHING HEAVILY]
[♪♪♪]
[TRUCK RATTLING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[AIR BRAKES HISS]
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
[♪♪♪]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
[MAN 1 SPEAKING SPANISH]
[MAN 2 SPEAKING SPANISH]
MAN 2: You want
me to open the doors?
[MAN 1 SPEAKING SPANISH]
MAN 2: Here. The
keys. Take them.
[MAN 1 SPEAKING SPANISH]
MAN 1: Why you talking?
MAN 2: No! No, no, no...
[GUNSHOT THEN BODY HITS GROUND]
[♪♪♪]
[GUNSHOT]
[GUNFIRE]
[GUNSHOTS]
[SHELL CASINGS CLATTER]
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪]
MAN: Gambling destroyed my life.
Me, my family,
everything I loved.
It was like a robbery,
only I was the thief.
It's amazing the stories
you tell yourself to justify it.
The lies that lead you
to just one more hand,
one more spin, one
more roll of the dice.
This is our deal,
okay? Marie, no.
You guys are not
lifting a finger. I mean it.
We're bringing everything.
So... This is not up for debate.
Great.
Sweetie, don't worry.
We're not gonna say
one word about the bills.
We just wanna bring
everyone up to speed.
All right, I'll see
you soon. Bye.
[SIGHS]
So...
Tonight's the night.
No turning back.
Well...
Okay. Let's do this.
WALT: Okay. So first,
I assign point values.
Correlate to the
effect of removal.
You're gonna split the
eights? Skyler, please.
Now, the mathematical principle
known as the Kelly Criterion,
upon which I devised
my own strategy...
Not dissimilar to
the MIT system...
Walt, you're not teaching them.
You wanted me to be thorough.
Play. You're taking too long.
You don't think it behooves
me to be able to explain this?
It behooves you to
be a pro, that's all.
That's the fiction.
So, chop-chop.
Don't chop-chop me.
Now, we both know
that the first decision
is whether or not to
split or to surrender.
On eights. Split them.
Good on both.
Next decision is whether
to double down or not.
Which you should be
doing. On an 11, yes. Double.
WALT: Okay, this hand
over here, we have a soft 18.
The final decision is whether
or not to hit or to stand.
Hit it.
Becomes a hard 15.
Dealer has a nine. I see that.
Hit it.
Oh.
Okay, let's see what I got.
And 21.
Damn. Yup.
Okay, the key thing
to remember here
is that it's not
about any one hand.
The key is the number
of hands per hour.
Mm. Let's go again.
Zero, minus one, 0.6.
Okay.
[TAPS ON TABLE]
Walt.
It's not as if I don't
know how to play.
I certainly more than
understand how to count cards.
Let's just keep going.
No, you know what? I'm
in recovery, remember?
I shouldn't even be playing.
And that is the fiction that
we should be sticking to.
You know what?
You're right. Yeah.
Wow. Okay. Um...
We're not leaving
anything to chance.
All right. Let's get
started. Got a lot of...
Walt. We got a lot
of ground to cover.
What is this?
We have to get
our story straight.
We've gotta be on the same page.
A script? Bullet points.
Bullet points? We got a novella.
This is smart. You really
wanna try to sell a DEA agent
some full-of-holes story
about how we have enough
money to buy a car wash?
Am I supposed to memorize
this? We need to practice.
We need to be
word-perfect. Within reason.
We need this story to
be solid and sympathetic
and, most of all,
completely believable.
The story that you
already told Marie.
You think she hasn't told Hank?
Ha. Come on, this is Marie
we're talking about here.
No, she hasn't.
[SCOFFS]
She hasn't.
Hank thinks his insurance
is paying for everything.
Marie's not telling him
we're paying his therapy bills.
And neither are we.
And why is that again?
Really?
If we have the gambling story...
Did you take money, Walt?
You remember
Gretchen and Elliot?
I seem to recall you'd rather
sell drugs than take help.
Fine.
Marie will tell Hank
in her own time.
And at least we'll have
laid the groundwork.
And coming clean
with Hank and Juni...
Appearing to come clean will
be the best thing for everyone.
We talked about this.
Okay? We agreed about this.
Yes, we did. It's just...
What?
Never mind. Just...
Okay. So...
I really think we should
tag team the narrative, okay?
We'll each be responsible
for certain portions of the
story and then we can...
We can hand off so we
don't leave anything out,
and it'll seem natural.
Okay. So I'm gonna
launch with the exciting news
that we are buying a car wash.
Yay.
The next logical question
Hank will probably ask is:
"Where are you
getting the money?"
To which I'll say:
We wanna tell
you the whole story.
It's a doozy, so
hold onto your hats.
Do you like that?
Sure.
It accomplishes two
things. It keeps it light
while letting them know
to expect something big.
WALT: Uh-huh.
Yeah. No. It's a doozy.
Okay. Anyway, that's
where you will take over,
starting with your diagnosis.
Pages one and
two. Okay. And it's...
It's gonna run
parallel to the truth,
which makes it
easier, but, um...
Just make sure to
really hit the cancer.
Really touch on
the fear and despair.
It's good to remind them
and to get their sympathy.
We want them to understand
why you'd do something so stupid.
Now, after that, per pages
three and four, after you say:
"Gambling became an addiction,
and I just couldn't control it."
Do you see that? Yes.
In the middle. Okay.
I put in that line about
robbery, from the GA meeting.
That was good.
So next, I'll chime in about
how it affected our marriage,
starting with the
confusion, the deceit,
why we couldn't tell anyone...
I'm terribly, terribly
ashamed of my actions.
Yeah. Two "terribly" s?
It's to show contrition. I
just wouldn't use that word.
I would never say
the word "terribly."
Phrase it however you want.
You're jumping ahead. Now...
And why...? And why
am I so ashamed?
Do I really need to answer that?
I was, and am,
providing for our family.
Let's just pick up
where we left off.
I'm weak, I'm out of control.
This makes me look like crap.
This has to be a
warts-and-all story.
That's how we'll sell
it. We both look bad.
How do you look bad exactly?
Where is the "I slept
with my boss" bullet point?
I can't seem to
find that anywhere.
For a fired schoolteacher
who cooks crystal meth,
I'd say you're coming
out pretty much ahead.
I don't like it. I don't want
Junior thinking less of me.
At least you won at gambling.
I'm the bitch mom who
wouldn't cut you slack.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I put
you through all of this.
How's that sound? Hm?
Here.
Two "sorry" s.
I believe we were on page five.
So after you say how
very sorry you are,
in your own words, of course,
we're almost to the end.
And then I say how
proud I am of you
for joining a 12-step program.
And this is where I
think we should enact
how we're feeling, you know?
Just a suggestion.
You might look down at
the floor with remorse. Hm?
What? You don't have to mean it.
You just stare down
at your feet, Walt, okay?
Then I'm gonna...
I was thinking of
taking Marie's hand
and saying something
emotional like:
It's such a relief to tell you.
We're glad we have a
strong family to help us.
That we can all
support each other.
And then maybe
I'll tear up a little.
I don't know.
We'll see what
happens in the moment.
You're gonna cry on cue?
I said, I don't know. Maybe.
When you dab your eyes,
with your right hand or left?
One tear? Two tears? How
many? This has to be convincing.
Especially to Hank. I'm
doing the best I can here, Walt.
And yes, I'm thorough.
Maybe lying doesn't come
as easily to me as you.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Hey.
Guys! Come on in! Hi! Hey.
Good to see you! Hey.
HANK: You little punk! Hey. Hey.
Great to see you. How you doing?
Look at my little
princess. She's getting big.
Yeah. And heavy too.
Is that food I'm smelling?
I might get an
honest-to-God meal here?
You look good.
Thank you, sweetheart.
Your Aunt Marie, she's
cute, but she could burn water.
You are so hilarious. Show
the boys your rock collection.
We're gonna get
organized. It'll be 20 minutes.
You have a rock collection?
It's a mineral collection.
Just something I've...
You wanna see it?
Sure. All right.
Let's go see it.
Oh, hey, let me...
Hey, no. I... I got it.
Come on, guys. It's
down the hall here.
HANK: That one, that's rhodonite.
It's manganese inosilicate.
WALT JR.: Cool. What
makes it be all pink like that?
That's the manganese
part. It oxidizes, like rust.
WALT: Manganese can
have an oxidation state
of between minus-three
and plus-seven,
which takes it through a range
of colors. Purple, green, blue.
Its most stable state is
plus-two, which is pale pink.
So...
Exactly. Whatever
the hell he said.
Anyway, you get the idea.
WALT: Yeah, it's interesting.
Interesting stuff, that.
Really.
Oh, hey. Yeah, give me that.
Give me that file, will
you? Check this out.
I've been working
on something here.
I'm doing a little consulting.
You know, weighing
in on a case for A.P.D.
Put that in for me.
Put that in over there.
Hank, what is this?
It's not a dead body?
Oh, no, no, no.
Nothing like that. No.
Seriously, you guys
you gotta check this out.
This is good. Ready?
Let me get it going here.
[NEW WAVE MUSIC PLAYING ON TV]
[LAUGHS]
Look at this guy. Look at...
♪ Machine is waiting
All systems are go ♪
♪ Are you sure Control
is not convinced ♪
♪ But the computer
Has the evidence ♪
♪ No need to abort ♪
♪ The countdown starts ♪
HANK: Oh, man. You
can't make this stuff up.
♪ Four, three, two, one ♪
♪ Earth below us ♪
WALT JR.: Who is this?
HANK: That, my friends,
is Albuquerque's public
enemy number one.
♪ Calling, calling ♪
♪ Home ♪
SKYLER: It's such a
relief to finally tell you.
We're just so glad we
have a strong family
to help us through this.
That we can all
support each other.
Jesus. I don't even
know where to... Holy shit.
Ah. Yeah.
Walter H. White.
Man of hidden talents.
Dad, you're such a stud.
How much did you win exactly?
Dad?
I don't think I
have exact figures.
It's enough to... After taxes,
of course, to buy the car wash.
Maybe even pay for
a couple of halfway
reasonable college educations.
Damn, Dad, why'd you quit?
I can totally get a car for
my birthday now, right?
Son, I'm terribly, terribly
ashamed of my actions.
Would you excuse me, please?
I need to use the restroom.
Wow.
[♪♪♪]
HANK: Walt?
Hey! Whoa.
Oh, sorry.
Thought you
might have fallen in.
No, no, I just...
Hey, man, that was
some big stuff back there.
No, we wanted to
be thorough, so...
Yeah, well, it was quite a tale.
Couldn't have been easy
to, you know, talk about.
You know, Walt, if you...
You can always
bend my ear, right?
I mean, if you ever need to talk
or just blow off
some steam, I'm here.
Not going anywhere, so...
Thanks, Hank.
Same goes for me, you know.
If you ever wanna
bounce anything off me,
I don't know, casework,
anything, really.
Sometimes just talking
something through,
you know, really can
make a difference.
HANK: We're not talking
bathtub crank here.
This is a big-ass operation.
You know, hundreds of
pounds a week. Maybe more.
So who is this person?
What do you know about him?
Other than he's deader
than a Texas salad bar
and has a decent set of pipes?
I'd say he's my guy.
Your guy?
There's this mystery
man I've been chasing
for the better part of a year.
Cooks the purest meth that me
or anyone else has ever seen.
Goes by the name of Heisenberg.
Hm. Yeah. Pretty weird, huh?
I looked him up. It
was one of Hitler's guys.
A physicist named
Werner Heisenberg.
Real cute, huh?
With a handle like that,
guy's gotta be some sort of...
Some sort of an egghead.
No offense. Heh, heh.
And here we go. Gale
"Major Tom" Boetticher.
Anyway, I just wanna
see if I'm, you know,
not barking up the wrong
tree, chemically speaking.
As far as I can make out,
he's writing about a
phenylacetone cook, right?
Yeah. Yeah. Pretty
rare these days,
but it does jibe with the
blue stuff I've been tracking.
"Two sticks dairy-free
soy margarine,
two-third cup turbinado sugar."
[HANK LAUGHS]
It's a recipe for vegan s'mores.
There's all kinds of
crazy crap in there.
Yeah, like, you know,
top-ten recumbent bicycles,
indoor composting tips.
All right next to the mother of
methamphetamine syntheses.
This guy was a... Man,
he was a real character.
Yeah, he seems unique.
Yeah. Let me show you
something. Give it here.
Right here at the... Right
here at the top it says:
"To W.W. My star,
my perfect silence."
W.W. Heh, heh, heh.
I mean, who do
you figure that is?
Woodrow Wilson?
Willy Wonka?
Walter White?
Heh.
You got me.
W.W. Hm.
Wait a minute.
Let me see this...
for a second, because
I think I remembered...
Ah. Here.
Yes.
Yeah.
"When I Heard the
Learn'd Astronomer."
Learned.
And from time to time
Look'd up in perfect
silence At the stars.
It's a poem by Walt Whitman.
Your W.W.
You freaking brainiac.
[HANK LAUGHS]
I must have skipped that
day in school or something.
I been chasing my tail about
that one. Bet you're right.
Well, I'm glad I
could help. Yeah.
Walt Whitman. Huh.
So you think this Gale
person is your Heisenberg?
Yeah, I think so. Yeah.
God, I wanted to get this guy.
It looks like you did.
No, I mean, you know,
me personally, you know?
I wanted to be the one to
slap the handcuffs on him,
that kind of shit.
Popeye Doyle waving to Frog One.
If I recall, at least from
the first French Connection,
Popeye Doyle never
actually caught him.
Heh.
Yeah, I guess me
and old Popeye, huh?
Day late and a dollar short.
What about the
person who killed him?
A.P.D.'s problem, not mine.
Any leads? My buddy Tim says
they got some fingerprints
they're trying to ID.
Eyewitness saw a person
of interest. Might get lucky.
Somebody knows. They'll
track the shooter eventually.
[El-P'S "FLYENTOLOGY"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Jesse.
[GRUNTS]
♪ Freak flash, admission
Of the faithfully shaken ♪
♪ Now trapped 30
thousand and droppin' ♪
♪ It's on and poppin' At last ♪
♪ Keep me in the sky
That's all that I cry ♪
♪ I'll become your servant
If it's worth your time ♪
♪ Keep me in the sky
That's all that I'll say ♪
♪ I'll become your soldier
At least for this day ♪
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[CLIPPERS WHIRRING]
♪ There is no
intellect In the air ♪
Jesse.
JESSE: What's up?
♪ Just a working example
Of faith versus physics ♪
♪ Flyentology ♪
♪ Everybody Get
your ticket today ♪
WALT: I need to talk to you.
Okay.
♪ Flyentology Fly, flyentology ♪
Now.
Go ahead.
Would you stop doing
what you're doing, please?
I'm not done, yo.
And that dude's next.
[WHIRRING STOPS]
What the hell? What is wrong...?
We have business to discuss.
So discuss. Jesus.
Let go of me.
Gale's murder is
being investigated.
Uh, duh.
I have it on good authority
they found fingerprints.
Not mine.
We done here? No,
we are not done here.
What if they are yours?
How can you be so sure?
Because I'm here.
Your brother-in-law's
got a hard-on for me,
if the cops found
fingerprints... Shh.
If the cops found my
prints within five blocks,
they would've
picked me up by now.
What about the casing?
Oh, my God. Or casings?
How many times did
you shoot him, anyway?
Jesse, did you
pick up the casings?
Did you pick them up?
No.
Yeah, well...
Listen, we gotta go over
this step-by-step, everything.
Tell me exactly what happened
from the moment you got there.
I got in, I got out. No.
No, I need to know specifics.
We'll start from the beginning.
You drove over there.
You went to his door, right?
Jesse, I need
you to concentrate.
This is very important.
Did you knock or ring?
Knock or ring?
Knock.
Good, good. That's
very good. Now listen.
Assume Gale answered the
door. What happened after that?
Did he recognize you?
Did you say anything
to each other?
Did you walk into the room or
did you shoot him right there?
What?
Who wants to make
100 bucks? Yeah.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
SAUL: Look, the
kid's probably right.
If they had anything on him,
he'd be locked up already.
What about my brother-in-law?
He suspects Jess...
He knows Jesse is involved
in the sale of blue meth.
That was Hank's
one-and-only lead.
What if he puts two
and two together,
and he goes after
Jesse for the murder?
Goes after him how,
on his Rascal scooter?
Ahem. That perhaps
sounded insensitive.
But if he goes after him,
I'll sue his ass
for police brutality,
harassment, assault
and 16 other things.
No, history those two have
together, being what it is,
gotta figure your
brother-in-law's smart enough
not to go down that road.
Goose egg. Bubkes.
That's what the cops got.
I wouldn't worry about it.
Yeah, what else should
I not worry about, Saul?
Should I not worry Gus plans
to murder me at first chance?
That my drug-addicted partner
doesn't seem to care
whether he lives or dies?
You should see his
house. It's like skid row.
He has actual
hobos living there.
Now, how long before Gus
decides he's too big of a risk?
Jeez, I got Mike, that
grunting, dead-eyed cretin
sucker-punching me in the face.
I've got Gus
wielding a box cutter.
I mean, Western Union,
message received.
Let me ask you. When did
this stop being a business?
Why am I the only person
capable of behaving in
a professional manner?
[MUTTERS]
Any way you slice it,
everyone is in danger.
I mean, how can
I protect anyone?
My family, Jesse, myself?
My name never comes
up with those guys, does it?
And meanwhile, we're
buying this stupid car wash.
Oh, yeah. That ship
has sailed, bon voyage.
We are committed. We
already told our family about it.
And now Skyler, I'm
sure she believes...
She needs to believe that
everything is neat and tidy.
And she's telling herself I
work in this quiet little lab
with a white lab coat
and a pocket protector,
and when my contract is
up, I'll just hang it all up,
tip my hat and walk away.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, God.
How did everything
get so screwed up?
Yeah, you do have a little
shit-creek action happening.
You know, FYI, you
can buy a paddle.
This is a last-resort,
back-pocket kind of thing,
but if you really gotta
protect yourself, disappear...
Poof.
There's a guy who
can make it happen.
They call him a "disappearer."
For a substantial fee,
and I do mean substantial,
you and your loved ones
can vanish. Untraceable.
I mean, he sets you
up with a whole new life.
What, like a witness
protection kind of thing?
Beyond. I mean, off the grid.
New identities, new everything.
No one would ever
be able to trace you.
Be clear. This is an end
game, if you get my meaning.
I mean, there's no coming back.
[SIGHS]
So you want his card?
God, there's gotta be
something else that I can do.
Some way to keep everything
from spiraling out of control.
From what you told me,
it sounds like Pinkman
is first up in the
imminent-demise department.
Gus won't risk letting
the police find Jesse.
I know him. He won't.
MAN: I'm not kidding. If you
think about it, you can't even see it.
How can you know how bad
radio frequencies, microwaves
and cell phones are getting you?
You could be strolling
through security at the airport...
Hey, wake up, bitches.
MAN: You get waved through
a full-body x-ray scanner.
Next day, you could
be dead or dying
from all the radiation
they say is safe.
But there's no way. It has to
deliver a concentrated dose.
Enough to penetrate clothes.
The accumulated amount
could be dangerous to
susceptible individuals,
especially from
a rural area. Yo.
The ozone layer is already
thin because of the cow farts.
Yo! Oh, hey.
Make sure there's pizza
here when I get back.
All right? Enough for
everybody. Oh, yeah.
I can do that. I can
definitely do that.
Not a problem. I can get
the stuff, the pizza and stuff.
But as far as the financial
situation, you know...
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
Just hang on. Hang
on. Yeah, yeah.
And you know, the
concentrated doses,
it's gonna fuck with
your bone marrow,
and it's gonna mess up...
Because... Because
especially if you have cancer.
You know, because if you gotta
get a bone-marrow transplant,
your odds are 60 percent.
You got a 60 percent chan...
Hey.
MAN: Oh.
JESSE: Hey, hey.
Get some dipping sticks too, yo.
Yeah, I can definitely
get dipping sticks.
All right. I can get them.
[BOTTLES CLATTER]
[GRUNTS]
[CAMERA WHIRRING]
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
♪ 808, ooh, 808 ♪
♪ 808, kick drum Kick drum ♪
♪ 808, snare drum
Snare drum, clap ♪
♪ Got an 808 this
and a this And a that ♪
♪ Got an 808 boom
And an 808 bat ♪
[CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY]
Hey, smoke it up, bitches.
[CROWD CHATTERING]
♪ 808 ♪
[DRAWER CLOSES]
[VIDEO GAME BEGINS]
MAN: Gotcha!
[SIGHS]
MIKE: Wake up.
Wake up.
What's up?
What's up with your ear?
Downstairs. Now.
Where is everybody?
I invited your guests to leave.
Know who this is?
Nope. You ought to.
He's been at your
house for three solid days.
Okay.
He stole your money.
That $78,000 or
so look familiar?
This is it? That's it.
[COUGHS]
JESSE: Okay. Thanks.
Wanna know what's next for
Little Miss Pissed-in-His-Pants?
No. You sure, now?
Yep. Don't wanna
take a wild guess?
You're gonna kill him.
Is this the part where
I beg you not to do it?
Oh, please, please.
And then what?
I'm supposed to
promise, cross my heart,
to straighten up and
fly right or toe the line
or some other crap
that I'm not gonna say?
Is that what your little
show here was all about?
You're on thin ice,
you little shithead.
You know that?
[LAUGHS]
You ain't gonna smoke
that dude in there.
You know how come I know?
You went through the trouble
of putting a blindfold on him.
I'm going back to bed.
Let yourselves out.
[DOOR OPENS]
GUS: I'm sorry to
keep you waiting.
How's the ear? Mending.
What can I do for you?
It's Pinkman.
He's become
increasingly incautious.
He's a risk. A liability.
I know he and Walter
come as a team
and that Walter won't like it,
but something's gotta be done.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[MACHINERY WHIRRING]
You gotta be kidding.
JESSE [ON ANSWERING MACHINE]:
Hey, it's me. Wait for the thing.
Right. This is
message number three.
You'd better be
ready in two minutes,
because I am right
outside your door.
[♪♪♪]
Jesse.
Jesse!
Damn it.
JESSE: Hey, it's
me. Wait for the thing.
Oh, great.
Jesse!
This is perfect.
You are a piece of
work, you know that?
[GRUNTS]
Jesse?
Jesse.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
JESSE: Hey, it's
me. Wait for the thing.
[TONE BEEPS]
[♪♪♪]
[CAMERA WHIRRING]
Where is he?
Gonna ask where we're going?
Nope.
[♪♪♪]