[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
[♪♪♪]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
What did you say to
Gus? Because he's onto us.
Yeah. I didn't say jack.
What do you mean he's onto us?
He's walking to his car,
then suddenly he isn't.
Does he have some
kind of sixth sense?
Jesus, what did you say to him?
Could I ask my own question
right now, at this point?
Did you just bring a
bomb into a hospital?
What?
Was I supposed to
leave it on his car?
You're supposed to
bring it into a hospital?
[PANTING]
Oh, my God.
Look, where can we find Gus?
Name a place. Name one
place where I could surprise him,
where he won't see me coming.
Because his house, the laundry,
the restaurant,
the factory farm,
they are all wired with cameras.
One place.
Think.
Jesse, think.
Where is it? Where?
Because if you can't tell me,
we are dead.
[PANTING]
[WHISPERING] Jesse.
I don't... I don't know.
Well, maybe...
Excuse me. Jesse Pinkman?
Uh, yeah.
Hi. Detective Kalanchoe.
This is Detective Munn,
Albuquerque Police.
We were wondering if we
could have a few minutes,
maybe go someplace and talk.
About what? Sorry,
didn't catch your name.
About what?
It concerns Brock Cantillo
and a statement you
made to his mother.
How about you come with us?
We just want to clear
things up. No big deal.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[♪♪♪]
JESSE: So am I under arrest?
KALANCHOE: You're not
under arrest. We're just talking.
JESSE: So if I
get tired of talking,
want to get up and leave...
We'd prefer you didn't.
You'd prefer.
Jesse, why'd you
tell Brock's mom
the boy had been poisoned?
[SIGHS]
Look, I think this
has been, you know,
uh, what do you call it?
Overblown, because
all I basically said
was "Had the doctors thought
maybe Brock got poisoned?"
In a cover-all-bases
kind of sense.
Yeah. No, I'm sure
they appreciated that,
you helping them out like that,
especially with how
specific you were.
Ricin. Wow.
KALANCHOE: That's
definitely a big one.
You don't see that every
day, so when doctors hear that,
they take it very seriously.
As do we.
As does the FBI.
Okay. And nice, you know,
you trying to
help out like that,
you know, professional courtesy,
sharing your expertise.
I ain't got no expertise.
All right? I just, you know...
You just happen to
guess this one rare poison
might be the thing that put
this little boy in the hospital.
And congratulations,
because his doctors,
they're beginning to
think you might be right.
So why ricin? How'd
you come up with that?
[SIGHS] Man, I think I've...
I don't know. I must've saw
it on House or something.
Huh. Yeah, you know, like House
or the Discovery Channel.
Sometimes your brain just
makes these connections.
Does it? Mine does.
That's interesting.
Look, I got to get back.
But we're still talking.
So I'm not under
arrest, but I can't leave.
So, then, I guess I
should call my lawyer.
Right?
We're just having a
simple conversation, Jess.
Why can't we keep
talking, keep it light?
Man, you know how it is
when the lawyers get to it.
Suddenly everything's
a big pissing match,
like, every time.
Adversarial. Adversarial.
Then we gotta
book you, blah, blah.
You know. You've been
around the block, Jesse.
You're no Boy Scout.
Saul Goodman.
That's my guy.
So do I gotta call
him, or do you?
[RINGING] [PAPER
SHREDDER WHIRRING]
[KNOCKING AT DOOR]
[KNOCKING PERSISTING]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[MAN GRUNTS]
What the hell you doing?
I need Saul right now.
So you just break in? I
see you're here, by the way.
If you'd bothered to answer
the phone or the door,
maybe I wouldn't
have... Forget it.
Is he here? Is that
a serious question?
Why would he be here?
But you know where he is.
I need a number. [LAUGHS]
Look, let me explain
something to you.
My partner and
I... Are in danger?
Whoop-dee-freaking-doo.
Why do you think he's not here?
And how's that news, exactly,
the two of you being in danger,
after doing something idiotic?
And what gives you the
right to break down my door?
Look, I just need a
number, okay? That's all.
You are such a pain in my ass.
You know that?
You're the reason I gotta
go on unemployment.
I was looking forward to
getting out of here, but no!
Now I got to wait around all day
for a plate glass guy to
come and fix this door.
And who pays for this?
Okay, you know what?
Here, look. I'm giving you
everything. All of it, okay?
There's one, two, three...
Look, there's got to be at
least $1700 there, okay?
That'll cover the
cost of the door.
Now, I apologize profusely.
Please, the phone number.
Door like this is gonna
cost way more than 1700.
What? For a plate of glass? No.
Oh, yeah, I bet it does.
I bet you it winds up costing...
20,000.
[LAUGHS]
Are you insane?
Who the hell is going
to charge $20,000
for a plate glass door?
There's no reputable vendor w...
Now I'm thinking 25.
I'll be right back.
[GRUNTS]
[DIALS]
Yes, Albuquerque, New Mexico.
The number of Rebecca Simmons,
306 Negra Arroyo Lane.
Would you connect
it for me, please?
Thank you.
Becky, hi, it's Walter White.
Listen, I wa...
I'm... I'm... I'm fine.
I'm fine. How are you?
Oh, good, good.
Yes, cats are...
Listen, Skyler and
I are out of town.
We're on our way up to Santa Fe,
and Junior just told us
that he thinks he may
have left the burner on...
On the stove.
Yes, God forbid there's a fire.
Well, that's... That's
why I'm calling.
I... I just wanted to ask,
and I'm sorry to do this,
but do you still have the key?
You do? Good.
And would you be willing to...?
Oh, you are a life saver.
Thank you so much.
Yes.
Okay.
Okay, I'll await your call.
Thank you so much. Bye-bye.
[PHONE BEEPS OFF]
There you go.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Becky?
Oh.
Oh, that's good.
That's a relief.
I owe you one, bigtime.
[♪♪♪]
[COUGHS]
[GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪]
So how's he doing?
You could at least say, instead
of being a couple of dicks.
Jesse, if you cared at
all about that little boy,
prove it to me.
Tell us what you know.
I told you what I
know. Tell us again.
What are you, like...
Like broken records?
I was trying to be helpful.
End of story.
Guess we'll have to wait and
see what the tox screen says.
Oh, look at this.
Isn't this cozy?
What'd you tell them?
I told them they were
a couple of dicks.
Heh. He's a wordsmith.
Well, detectives,
it's been a pleasure.
Now, up you go. Make
like you got manners.
Make like you
respect the rule of law.
Au revoir, auf Wiedersehen,
hasta luego, get the hell out.
Buh-bye.
That's it. Pick it up.
Follow your partner.
And one, two...
Thank you.
Christ. You two.
All I can say is if I
ever get anal polyps,
I'll know what to name them.
You gonna get me out of here?
Ah.
Hm. No.
Not even if I could.
You know, the FBI's going
to show up on this ricin thing,
and then you're in
it for the duration.
You know, you're
a lot safer in here.
They tried to get your
partner in his home.
Jesus.
Is he okay?
Well, he's okay
like a fruit fly's okay.
We're all on the clock
here, thanks for that.
You want to stick your
wangs in a hornet's nest,
it's a free country,
but how come I get
sloppy seconds, huh?
[SIGHS]
You got anything for me?
Tell me I didn't poke
my head up for nothing.
[SIGHS]
Yeah.
I've been thinking.
And?
Casa Tranquila.
What's Casa Tranquila?
It's an old folks' home
off Paseo Del Norte.
Our boy tells me
Fring took him there
to visit one of the patients,
someone Pinkman says
you'll definitely remember:
Tio Salamanca.
Old guy in a wheelchair.
Um, doesn't talk,
rings a bell.
I don't mean "Does
that ring a bell?"
I mean, the guy
actually has to ring a bell.
I... Yes, I know. I remember.
So, what, once every blue moon,
Gus goes and visits
an old cartel associate.
That... That doesn't help me.
I can't very well hide out
in a nursing home for six months
hoping, on the off chance,
that he comes back.
It's not even like
they're friends.
Pinkman said it was like
he was torturing the old guy.
What does that mean?
He told him the last
of his family was dead.
He seemed to enjoy telling him.
Afterward, Pinkman
asked him about it.
All Gus would say
was this Tio character
once murdered
someone close to him.
Wait.
Tio murdered
someone close to Gus?
I know it sounds not
particularly fruitful,
but, uh, sorry, that's...
That's all I got.
They're enemies,
not friends.
Your next number
in this coverall game,
where you cover
the whole shmoley,
is B-number-3.
Like Goldilocks
and the Three Bears.
That's number 3
in your B column,
followed by O-74.
That's O-74 on the
other side of your card.
[BINGO BALLS RATTLING]
Now we have that lucky
number: B-number-7.
Is it lucky for you?
B-7.
In the "I" row, 2-1.
I-21...
I know you despise me,
and I know how badly
you want to see me dead,
but I'm willing to bet
that I know a man whom
you hate even more.
BINGO CALLER: Those N's just
keep coming. They're sticking together.
I am offering you an
opportunity for revenge.
BINGO CALLER: 4-8.
The continental United States,
excluding Alaska and Hawaii.
[HEAVY BREATHING]
[BELL RINGING]
Okay, I'm here.
How you doing this
morning, Mr. Salamanca?
You need something? [BELL DINGS]
You need to go poopie? Huh?
Did you go poopie already? No?
What do you need?
You want me to get
the board for you?
Okay.
All right.
Okay, here we go.
A-E-I...
[BELL DINGS] Row I.
I-J-K-L-M-N...
[BELL DINGS] First letter: N.
A-E...
Row E.
E... Second letter-E.
A-E...
Row E. E...
Next letter: E.
A... [BELL DINGS]
Row A. A-B-C-D...
[BELL DINGS]
Next letter: D.
A... [BELL DINGS]
Row A. A-B-C-D...
[BELL DINGS] Next letter: D.
A-E...
[BELL DINGS] Row E.
E... [BELL DINGS]
E. A...
[BELL DINGS] Row A.
A... [BELL DINGS]
Next letter: A.
A-E-I-O-U...
I don't think we're finished.
A-E-I-O-U... [HUFFING]
Finish the word, Mr. Salamanca.
Is it "dear"?
Is it "deal"?
Honey, "dea" isn't a word.
Help me out here.
[PHONE RINGING]
[SIGHS]
Hey, son, what's up?
When exactly are
you getting here?
Uh, just as soon as I can.
Look, this is a
serious situation,
and you're not
taking it seriously.
Give me the phone. Let me talk.
No, I am taking
it very seriously.
Just give it to me, Walt.
I'm very concerned about
Uncle Hank and his safety.
But whomever is making
these threats against him,
I can assure you there's
absolutely no interest in me.
I'm not on... On anyone's radar,
and besides your
mother... Give it to me!
Walter? Did you
hear what he said?
Get over here. No more excuses.
Marie, I... I will be there
just as soon as I can.
I promise. Hold on.
You want to weigh in here?
Maybe you could talk
some sense into him.
Marie, he'll get here
when he gets here, so...
Well, I hope you sell
plenty of air fresheners.
I hope you just have a
banner day over there.
Okay, Walt? Don't
worry about a thing here.
Goodbye.
And thank you
for all of your help.
Huh?
Anything?
Hi, everyone.
SKYLER: Hi, Steve. How's
everybody holding up?
HANK: Just the
man I want to see.
Come here, look at this.
Jesus, enough with the laundry.
No, no, no, hear me out.
This panel, if I'm
reading it correctly,
is a 7200-amp service.
This place has two of them.
That's a whole
lot of juice, brother.
Laundry this size typically
has maybe half that.
So, what's with the extra panel?
What are you, Thomas Edison?
I asked a bunch of electricians.
They have their own chat rooms,
like where all they
talk about was wiring?
Freaking Internet... Find
anything on it these days.
What do you say?
Pop over, have another look-see?
Listen...
I think we possibly have
a lead on something.
Yeah?
I have this guy at the office.
He says he has some
kind of information.
The thing is, he'll
only give it to you,
in person.
Okay.
Remember Hector Salamanca?
What, you mean the old
cripple guy with the bell?
Rather crap on
our floor than talk?
Don't remember him. Why?
Well, he's the guy.
His nurse calls us,
says he wants to powwow.
[SIGHS]
So we have this guy at
the office for three hours,
and he still just
wants to talk to you.
Do not even think
about going down there.
Marie.
This is clearly a ploy
or a trick or something
designed to get Hank
out into the open.
That's all this is.
That's what we
thought. MARIE: Well...
It's been years since
this guy's been a player.
His nephew's gone.
Doesn't have anybody.
The nurse checks
out... Don't know nothing.
Guess I just don't
see an angle in it,
if there even is one.
Of course, if you did
want to talk to this guy,
there's no safer place.
I don't think this
sounds like a good idea.
Yeah, I agree, Uncle Hank.
It is a ridiculous idea,
and there is no way
that you are going to do it,
end of story.
Hank, thanks for coming down.
HANK: No problem at all.
Good to see you, sir.
So, Mr. Salamanca,
you had something to tell me?
A-E-I-O...
[BELL DINGS]
Row O.
P-Q-R-S...
First letter: S.
A-E-I-O-U...
[BELL DINGING]
Second letter: U.
A... [BELL DINGS]
B-C...
[BELL DINGS]
A-E-I...
J-K... [BELL DINGS]
[BELL DINGS]
J-K-L-M...
A-E-I-O-U...
[BELL DINGS] Row U.
V-W-X-Y...
[BELL DINGS] All
right, that's enough.
Thank you.
Yeah, thanks. I,
uh... I can spell.
Well, you got that out
of your system now?
Shall we try this one more time?
[BELL DINGS]
[NURSE CLEARING THROAT]
A-B...
[BELL DINGS]
F... [BELL DINGS]
A-E-I-O-U...
[BELL DINGING]
A... [BELL DINGS]
B-C... [BELL DINGS]
Yeah, we... We got it.
I am... I am... I am
just so, so sorry.
At least this time
he didn't shit himself.
Guess that's progress.
[♪♪♪]
[DIALS]
GUS [OVER PHONE]: Yes.
We may have a problem.
I got eyes on the DEA.
They just had a visitor.
Hector Salamanca.
I don't even know what
to say to you right now.
You just sit here, and
you think about how far
that kind of behavior
is gonna get you.
Not far, let me tell you.
[CREAKS]
Any second thoughts?
Then let's get to work.
[DEVICE CLICKS, BEEP PULSES]
[DEVICE CLICKS,
BEEP PULSING STOPS]
WOMAN: Hello.
[WOMAN GIGGLES]
Hi...
Hi.
WOMAN: Hello.
[CHUCKLING] Hi.
[♪♪♪]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[TIRES SQUEAL]
Mr. Pinkman.
You're free to go.
Why?
What happened?
Tox screen came back.
No ricin poisoning.
Surprised, huh?
No, why should I be?
Your jacket.
Till we meet again.
Okay, okay...
Hey, yo! Yo! Right here.
[DIALING]
Hey, Andrea,
um, I'm just checking on Brock.
Uh, hey, it sounds like...
I mean, listen,
just call me if
you can, all right?
I'm headed back over.
All right.
Hey, excuse me.
[TASER ZAPS]
[GRUNTS]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Yes.
TYRUS [OVER PHONE]:
We picked up Pinkman.
No witnesses.
What about Hector?
I've checked inside and out.
No wires, no camera,
no surveillance.
A police cruiser rolled
through about an hour ago.
Seemed routine.
It's just him,
alone in his room.
[SIGHS]
All right.
I'm on my way.
Maybe it's better if...
If I do this myself.
I do this.
[PHONE BEEPS OFF]
[♪♪♪]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
TYRUS [OVER
PHONE]: It's all clear.
Wait here.
[♪♪♪]
GUS: What kind of
man talks to the DEA?
No man.
No man at all.
[CHAIR SCRAPING FLOOR]
A crippled little rata.
What a reputation
to leave behind.
Is that how you want
to be remembered?
[SIGHS]
Last chance to
look at me, Hector.
[SCREAMS]
[EXPLOSION]
[ALARM BLARING]
[PEOPLE SHOUTING DISTANTLY]
Oh, Jesus. Oh, Jesus.
[GASPS]
WOMAN [OVER
RADIO]: the same vote.
Hey, it's that time again
where we tell about
your own personal hell
known as the afternoon commute.
How bad are things looking?
MAN: Southbound 25,
got an accident at Jefferson
on the right shoulder,
so stay to the left as you
move through that area,
and things have slowed
to a crawl at the Big I.
No surprises there.
WOMAN: Hang on.
I hate to interrupt you here,
but I do have breaking news,
coming out of the North Valley.
An explosion reported
at a nursing home,
the Casa Tranquila Nursing Home.
MAN: Oh, no. WOMAN:
You heard of that place.
We've got very few
details on it so far.
The initial report is, though,
as many as three people
may have been killed.
MAN: Oh, no.
WOMAN: The news is disturbing.
We'll get more information
as soon as it comes.
Situation over there,
I imagine, is hectic.
What's traffic looking like?
MAN: I know where the home is.
If you're moving
through that area,
we're talking about east
and westbound Paseo
in the North Valley.
You've got to avoid that area.
WOMAN: Our hearts
going out to the victims.
[ENGINE STARTS]
More details soon.
Coming up on Coyote
102.5, Aerosmith, Def Leppard.
Keep it right here on
New Mexico's finest rock.
[CONTAINER CLATTERS]
You wanna cook
with a broken arm?
Next step, CO2.
Do it.
[GAS HISSING]
[ALARM BUZZES]
Hey.
I better hear them click.
[CLICKING]
[ALARM BUZZES]
[ELEVATOR WHIRRING]
What, you got a
problem with stairs?
[GUNSHOTS]
[BODIES THUD]
[PANTING]
[ELEVATOR DOOR CLOSING]
[WHISPERING] Please, please...
Gus is dead.
We've got work to do.
[♪♪♪]
[ALARM BEEPING]
Vámonos.
[EXPLOSION RUMBLES]
[MAN SHOUTING IN SPANISH]
Uh, he's gonna pull through.
Yeah?
[SNIFFLES]
Yeah, it looked, uh,
kind of touch-and-go there
for a while, but he's gonna...
He's gonna make it.
Thank God.
Oh, thank God.
[SIGHS]
You know, still saying
it wasn't the ricin.
I don't understand.
Then what was it?
Saying it was most likely
a flower called
lily of the valley.
Yeah, it's... It's,
like, common.
It's got these red berries on it
that I guess taste sweet,
and sometimes
little kids eat them
and wind up poisoning
themselves, and that's it.
Nothing more.
So Gus didn't
poison him after all.
Still, he...
He, uh... He had to go, right?
You're damn right.
Gus had to go.
Um, you know, I should...
I should get back.
Andrea's waiting.
[DIALS]
I'm here at Casa Tranquila,
where three are dead
following an explosion
that rocked this
care facility today.
[PHONE RINGING]
The fireball completely
consumed one resident's room
and damaged areas nearby.
Walt?
Tell Dad to turn on his TV. Shh!
Let me get where I can
hear. Tell him Hank was right.
Walt?
WALT [OVER PHONE]:
How are you doing?
How am I doing? How are you?
I'm, uh...
I'm doing quite well.
[SIGHS]
I'm good.
Jesus, Walt, the news here.
Gus Fring is dead.
He was blown up
along with some person
from some Mexican cartel,
and the DEA has no
idea what to make of it.
Do you know about this?
Walt? I need you to...
It's over.
We're safe.
Was this you?
What happened?
I won.
[DANGER MOUSE & DANIELE
LUPPI'S "BLACK" PLAYING]
♪ We touched the
walls Of the city streets ♪
♪ And didn't explain Sadly
showed us our ways ♪
♪ Of never asking why ♪
♪ Cast down It was heaven sent ♪
♪ And to the church
No intent to repent ♪
♪ On my knees ♪
♪ Just to cry ♪
♪ Until you travel
To that place ♪
♪ You can't come back ♪
♪ When the last pain Is gone ♪
♪ And all that's left Is black ♪
♪ Looking at up at
those stars In the sky ♪
♪ Those white clouds
Have turned it black ♪
[♪♪♪]