[CHING]
[DOOR BELL DINGING]
Hello, would you like to try
our breakfast chicken
chalupa combo meal?
Gus Fring.
Excuse me?
Gustavo Fring, your boss.
Now, please.
Mr. Fring isn't here right
now. Is there some...?
He's here. His car is
parked out front. He's here.
He was here. Mr. Fring was...
You just go in the back and
you tell him it's Walter White.
Understand?
He'll know what it's about.
I'll wait.
[♪♪♪]
[INAUDIBLE]
[DISHES CLATTERING]
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
[DOOR BELL DINGLES]
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
MAN: Yeah, let me
get a chalupa special.
Hello?
MIKE [OVER PHONE]: Walter,
what exactly are you doing?
Where's Jesse?
Jesse's with me. He's fine.
What, do you expect
me to just believe that?
I'm crossing my heart, Walter.
Where is he?
Hold on.
JESSE: Yo.
Jesse? Yeah. What's up?
Jesse, w-w-where are you?
With Mike.
[WHISPERING] I
know you're with Mike.
Are... Are you all right?
Does he have a gun on you?
No.
What's going on, then?
We're driving.
Driving.
Driving where?
I don't know.
Um, north?
[SIGHS]
Why is he driving you?
Where is he going?
Beats me.
I... I don't... Put
Mike back on.
Hello again.
Mike, tell me now
exactly what is going on.
Jesse's with me today.
So, what you need to do
is to go back to your lab
and get on with the cook.
You're gonna have to muddle
through this one without him.
That's what's going on.
But it doesn't...
Goodbye, Walter.
Mike...
[♪♪♪]
Sir.
Excuse me. Hey. You're
not allowed back there.
Excuse me, sir.
As I said, sir,
Mr. Fring is not here.
This area is for employees only,
and I have to ask that
you leave immediately.
What you told
Mr. White, that's...
It's just bullshit, right?
What, you, uh, figure on
just leaving me in some ditch?
What do you care?
I don't.
But I'll tell you now,
you better shoot
straight, old man,
or I'll slice off your other
ear before this is over.
[TRUNK CREAKING CLOSED]
[CLEARS THROAT]
[SIGHS]
You coming?
We gotta do this
six more times today
with a lot of miles in between.
I'd like to finish before dark.
[CAR DOOR CREAKING CLOSED]
[ENGINE STARTING]
HANK: This freaking
guy, I tell you what.
It's like Scarface had sex
with Mr. Rogers or something.
[LAUGHS]
Who does this, you know?
Your boy Heisenberg,
thought we had him already.
Yeah. Keep dreaming.
Yeah, no. Getz busted
him a few months back.
Yeah, well, no offense
to Detective Doogie
Howser there,
but all he caught
was a dipshit lifer
by the name of Jimmy In-'N-Out.
This one, he's your Heisenberg?
Yeah, I believe he is.
So, what are you thinking?
Rival drug gang taking
out the mastermind?
Any names I should check out?
I wish I could help you there.
Only two people I know
connected with the blue stuff.
One is a
beanie-wearing jizz stain
by the name of Brandon
Mayhew, street name "Badger."
Definitely not a player.
And the other one
is Jesse Pinkman.
He and I have a history.
Yeah.
You see Pinkman as a shooter?
That would surprise me.
Well, we have a composite
of a person of interest.
It's a guy the neighbors
saw at Boetticher's place
right after the shooting.
Yeah. Sorry.
No, hang on to it, just in case.
We got a couple of
prints we're hoping to ID.
If I get any kind of hit,
I'll keep you in
the loop on that.
You know, um, Tim,
look, I appreciate what
you're doing, really.
You know, keeping
me involved and all.
But, you know,
finding this guy
Heisenberg dead like this...
I have to say, it...
kind of feels like
closure to me, you know?
Hank, you really
are a big help here.
No, I know. I...
I get it, really.
But I'm done.
[COUGHS]
[SIGHS]
You don't need to do that.
This is why I'm out here, right?
To be, like, your backup?
Uh-huh.
So if I'm out here in
a guard-type capacity
to watch over the money,
that means I need,
like, a gun, right?
Nope.
[SIGHS]
I mean, isn't that,
like, completely idiotic
for me to be out
here without a gun?
You haven't said dick
about what I'm
supposed to be doing.
Now I'm supposed
to do it without a gun?
How does that even make sense?
What? I can smoke, right?
Not a chance.
[ENGINE STARTING]
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪]
[MAN SINGING IN SPANISH]
[WOMAN SINGING IN SPANISH]
[SIGHS]
[SPUTTERING]
[ROCK MUSIC BLARING OVER RADIO]
[ROCK MUSIC TURNED OFF]
♪ Fallacies, fallacies ♪
♪ One for you And two for me ♪
[YAWNING]
[SIGHS]
It's finally hitting me
what the plan is here.
It's to bore me to death.
So mission accomplished,
because it's totally working.
Great job.
You know, I really
do get what's going on
with all the dead
drops and bags of cash.
Me and my boys had
the exact same system
when I was running things.
My crew.
Nowhere near the same
cheese you guys are slinging,
but same theory.
You know, maintain separation
between dealer and supplier,
reduce risk,
et cetera.
Look, don't you
think it'd be good
if there was some back-and-forth
communication here?
You got me riding shotgun
to every dark anal
recess in the state.
Be nice if you
clued me in a little.
I mean, I'm here
to do a job, right?
And, I mean, yo,
like, if I'm the guy,
then you should just tell
me what the hell is up.
What?
You are not the guy.
You're not capable
of being the guy.
I had a guy, but now I don't.
You are not the guy.
Then what the hell
am I doing here?
I don't know. It's not my call.
I just do what I'm told.
And now you're gonna
do what you're told,
which is to sit here, shut up,
and stay in the car till we
finish our pickups. You got it?
[♪♪♪]
[WOMAN SINGING IN SPANISH]
[GRUNTING]
[SIGHS]
[MACHINE BEEPING]
[PANTING]
[WHIRRING]
[SIGHS]
[WATCH BEEPING]
Oh!
We having second thoughts?
Every hour of every day.
[ALAN CHUCKLES]
Let me tell you, that
is perfectly normal.
But your expectations
are realistic.
You have a good,
solid business plan.
I'm feeling very confident.
You have an excellent
shot at making this work.
[SIGHS]
Walt?
Hm? SKYLER: Are you good?
Yeah.
[EXHALES]
All right.
Well, my congratulations
to the both of you.
Thank you very much, Alan.
It is my pleasure.
Mr. White.
Best of luck. Thank you.
I'm bringing the car over
first thing next week
for a wash and wax.
Oh, we'll be looking for you.
I'll be there. [SKYLER LAUGHS]
Thank you again. You're welcome.
Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
Wow.
It's official.
How are you feeling?
I'm...
Well, I'm... How do you feel?
Um...
Nervous.
Scared.
This is a big step, Walt.
If we don't do this right...
We'll be fine.
We will?
Tell me again.
We will be fine.
Believe it.
If we're gonna do this, I
mean, really gonna do this,
then we have to
promise each other
no more secrets.
There can't be any
mistakes like before.
There has to be
complete honesty.
I'm all for that.
Good.
Well, then, um,
how about a drink to celebrate?
Well... Well, we own
a big-ass car wash now.
We do. I guess that
merits a celebration.
Nothing too expensive.
Right. Right.
Non-fancy liquor it is.
Yes.
Just as long as it
gets the job done.
Oh.
[ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS]
WALT [OVER ANSWERING
MACHINE]: Uh, i-it's me.
I just wanted to say that I
was thinking about you and...
And the kids, and, uh...
I love you.
[ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS]
[MOANING]
[BOTH PANTING]
Okay. Okay.
Just take it off.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
[SKYLER MOANING]
[SIGHS]
The sheets, they smell
different than I remember.
Hm? Don't they?
Oh.
New fabric softener. Oh.
Yeah, I like it.
I, uh, also got a new haircut.
I don't know if you...
Oh, yes, I... I was
gonna say something.
Were you, really?
[LAUGHS]
I do like it.
Thanks.
So, um,
dinner tomorrow night?
I told Marie that we'd come
over and eat with them.
Think maybe you'll be free?
Yeah.
Yeah, we can do that.
That'll... That'll be nice.
Good.
Marie says it's
about the only thing
that'll get Hank
out of his room.
WALT, JR.: Mom?
[DOOR CLOSES]
Ooh.
Hey, Mom? Dad?
WALT: Hey, son.
Where are you?
WALT: Uh, we're...
We're back here.
We'll be out in a minute.
Oh, God.
[WHISPERING] Seriously?
I'm parked in the driveway.
Oh, this is going to make
for some very interesting
dinner conversation.
He is definitely gonna ask
about our living situation now.
Maybe, um...
Maybe you should move back in.
You know, just so it's, uh,
easier to explain to everyone.
You think?
[WATCH BEEPING]
I have to get back to work.
You know, schedule.
Yeah.
[FORKLIFT WHIRRING]
[FORKLIFT BEEPING]
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Damn it.
Hey!
Hey! This is a two-man
job. I can't do it alone.
I'm done. That's it.
Finished. Nothing else happens
until I get my partner back.
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
[FOOTSTEPS]
Jesse?
Where's Jesse?
I need him.
You people have me down here
trying to complete a
two-man operation by myself!
It's unacceptable.
It's dangerous and
counterproductive.
Jesse operates
the forklift, not me.
That's just one of the many,
many things he
does around the lab
that keeps us on
schedule, so I suggest
that you get him back
down here as soon as you...
Are you listening to me?
Hello?
[FORKLIFT WHIRRING]
[FORKLIFT BEEPING]
Where do you want it?
This is it, right? Last stop?
Last stop?
Hey, I've been counting,
yo. No more pickups after...
[DOOR CLOSES]
♪ Fallacies, fallacies ♪
[YAWNS]
♪ One for you And two for me ♪
♪ Fallacies... ♪
[♪♪♪]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[SIGHS]
[MEN SINGING IN
SPANISH OVER RADIO]
Yeah. I'm gonna need
to be picked up. Now.
Garcia's on Central. Honk once.
I'll meet you in
the parking lot.
Cancel that.
Hey, this dude...
This dude was coming
right at me with a...
With a shotgun.
They, like, blocked the alley
and they were gonna rip us
off. I didn't have a choice, okay?
I had to put it in reverse,
slam into the
guy's car, and just...
[SIGHS]
I saw.
You saw.
Oh, Jesus.
I just...
I don't know.
Go ahead, kid.
Smoke up.
[CAR SQUEALING]
[SIGHING]
Morning.
Hey. Good morning, son.
You want me to
pour you some juice?
I'll take a coffee.
Didn't know you
started drinking coffee.
Yeah. I also started tying
my own shoelaces too,
all by myself.
[CHUCKLING] Go grab a mug.
Milk? Sugar?
Just black.
Black. I like it.
Hey, Dad, I, uh...
I just gotta say...
I... I just wanted to
say it's really cool
to have you here.
Thank you, son.
It's cool to be back home.
It just feels...
Mom said you're moving
back in this Tuesday.
She...?
She said that?
Yeah.
Tuesday, is it?
Huh.
How about that?
[POUNDING]
Jesse. Jesse.
Yo, what's up?
What are you doing?
Um, breaking ice.
No, I mean, what are you...?
What are you doing here?
Where's your car?
Mike dropped me off.
Jesse.
Jesse!
What happened
yesterday? Where were you?
I was out with Mike,
helped him make pickups.
Picking up what?
Cash. Dead drops.
Mike made the pickups
and I guarded him.
You...
guarded Mike?
What is this, some
kind of a joke?
Hey, know what? Two dudes
tried to rob us and I saved the stash.
I took care of business,
just like I'm taking care
of business right now.
You wanna stand
there dicking around,
or you wanna suit
up and get to work?
Get in gear, yo, if
you wanna do this,
because I'm meeting up
with Mike this afternoon.
What, again? Why?
Guess I have two jobs now.
[INDUSTRIAL MUSIC
PLAYING OVER HEADPHONES]
[POUNDING RESUMES]
WOMAN [OVER SPEAKERS]: Los
Pollos Hermanos, can I take your order?
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Any injuries?
Twisted ankle, nothing too bad.
It all went like you thought
it would, more or less.
I will, of course, reimburse you
for the damage to your vehicles.
Hm.
Questions? Uh-huh.
More than a few, yeah.
But I know better than to ask.
Anyway,
just like you wanted.
The kid's a hero.
[CAR DOOR CLOSING]
SKYLER: Just the idea of owning
a car wash seems so daunting,
but I have to remind...
Who is the most
beautiful little girl
in the world? I think it's you.
So coming into a
business like this,
that's up and running
and fully operational,
puts us way ahead of the game.
You know, we're gonna still
have some changeover time,
and we'll have to
hire some people.
But we do have a staff
in place, so, you know,
luckily we'll be able to hold on
to most of Bogdan's employees.
We might lose a few to the
UltraWash across town, though.
[LAUGHS]
They're making a grab, I hear.
You gonna put the kid
to work? I've got school.
I'm not talking about you.
Talking about your sister.
I wouldn't let you
near my car. Ha, ha.
Hey, that's not a
bad idea, you guys.
You should put
Holly on the sign.
Like a mascot?
Like the Gerber baby.
I would get my car
washed there every day
if I saw her face out front.
What about me?
The goal is to bring customers
in, not scare them away, so...
Walt, there's another
bottle in the kitchen.
Just help yourself. Ah. Good.
WALT, JR.: Um, maybe we could
roll Uncle Hank through the car wash.
He could be the first customer.
[MARIE LAUGHS]
The wipe-down crew
would clean you up good.
[ALL LAUGH]
HANK: I got your
wipe-down right here.
MARIE: Hank, can we just
maybe get through one meal
without you
grabbing your crotch?
So, what are you gonna
do with Holly all day?
You can't take her to work
with all those chemicals
and migrants hanging around.
SKYLER: Marie... MARIE:
What? That can't be safe.
SKYLER: Fortunately, five
minutes from the car wash,
there is the top
child-care center in the city.
The National Child
Care Association
gives it really high ratings.
So that's a huge
relief and, you know,
we could walk
there if we had to.
HANK: Sky, I gotta
tell you, I'm just...
I'm really, really impressed.
You came together on this.
I'm really happy that
it's working out for you.
SKYLER: It's been a little
scary, but it needed to be done.
And we get possession
of the keys tomorrow.
MARIE: Oh, that's awesome.
HANK, JR.: I... I...
I can't wait to see
what kind of car I'm going
to get for my birthday,
now with all this
money rolling in.
SKYLER: I think you've been
spending too much time around Hank.
WALT, JR.: The squeaky wheel
gets the grease. Right, Uncle Hank?
HANK: Squeaky and greasy.
That's you, my friend.
[SKYLER LAUGHS]
Hey, Nick the Greek,
you gonna share
that bottle or what?
Oh. Yeah. Sorry.
WALT, JR.: Who's Nick the Greek?
He's a famous
big-time card player.
Hank, that's not funny.
What? It's a compliment.
Well, that's even worse, then.
You're giving
positive reinforcement
to behavior that Walt is working
very, very hard to change.
Right, Skyler?
Yeah.
I don't see how it's bad.
Dad's raking in the
beaucoup bucks now.
You know, I just think maybe
we could change the subject?
Yeah. Sure. You
know. Absolutely.
Hey, Uncle Hank, what about
that case you were looking at
with that crazy singing guy?
Ah, I'm off that.
I... I gave my assessment
to A.P.D. I'm done.
The case of the
crazy singing guy.
Hm, sounds like an
Encyclopedia Brown story.
Crazy is... Is the wrong word.
This guy, Gale Boetticher,
he was... He was eccentric.
A real character, you know?
He's... He's dead now.
SKYLER: Who was he?
WALT, JR.: He was a meth cook.
HANK: Uh, he was a meth chef.
I mean, we're
talking five stars.
Candles and white tablecloth.
Hey, I can't believe these words
are gonna come out of my mouth,
but he was a genius,
plain and simple.
I mean, boy, if he had
applied that big brain of his
to something good, I
don't know, who knows,
he could've helped humanity
or something like that.
I mean, how many actual
geniuses are there in the world, right?
If he'd kind of taken his
life in a different direction,
who knows?
Hank...
not to tell you your business,
but I'm not sure I agree.
What do you mean? Well, I mean,
you showed me that
notebook, and from what I saw...
And this is just
my humble opinion.
From what I saw
on those papers...
Genius?
Not so much.
I mean, there was no reasoning,
no deductions in those pages.
So to my eye, all his brilliance
looks like nothing more
than just simple rote copying.
Probably of someone else's work.
Believe me, I have been
around enough students to know.
This genius of yours...
maybe he's still out there.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Hank.
Oh, hey, babe.
Uh, Tim stopped by.
He... He brought over
some file boxes on that case.
Thought I'd take another peek.
That's great.
Sorry about the mess.
No, no, no. Don't be.
You want me to make some coffee?
Yeah.
Yeah, that'd be good.
Hm.
You find something?
Oh, just this guy
I'm looking at.
You know, everything
he... He buys and eats
is organic, fair trade, vegan.
Since when do vegans
eat fried chicken?
[♪♪♪]