[GIGGLES]
How's it coming?
[CHUCKLES]
Very, very well.
It's a flurry of deliveries.
Feels like Christmas morning.
[SIGHS] It's exciting.
It's really coming together.
And I'd like to point out
that if you have any
understandable questions
about the price tag...
[BANGS]
That sound? Quality.
At Pfizer, at Merck, that
unit would be right at home.
That goes for all of it.
Good. I want you to
have what you need.
Oh. Well,
I doff my proverbial
cap to you, sir. Ha-ha.
When do you think
we'll be up and running?
Within a month, I'd say.
Two weeks.
Or, yeah, two weeks.
Good. Very good.
By the way, that sample
you asked me to run?
I ran it, and it is quite good.
Thank you very much, Gale.
You can give that
to Victor to discard.
Uh, sure.
Is that our competition?
I'm sorry? The, uh...
It really is quite good.
The purity, of course,
I'm speaking of,
speaking strictly
in chemical terms.
And I can't, as of yet,
account for the blue color,
but if that is our competition,
we have our work cut
out for us, so to speak.
You don't have any
competition, Gale,
not as far as I'm concerned.
After all, how pure can pure be?
Well, it can be
pretty darn pure.
Mr. Fring,
I can guarantee you
a purity of 96 percent.
I'm proud of that figure.
It's a hard-earned figure, 96.
However, this
other product is 99.
Maybe even a touch beyond that.
I'd need an instrument
called a gas chromatograph
to say for sure,
but, um, that last 3 percent,
it may not sound
like a lot, but it is.
It's tremendous.
It's a tremendous gulf.
Gale, for our purposes,
96 percent will do just fine.
Please, don't let
this trouble you.
Yeah. It's just...
I'd love to know who
synthesized it, is all.
[SIGHS]
A man who wants to work with me.
A trained chemist,
like yourself.
But it won't happen.
I don't consider
him a professional.
If he's not, I don't know
what that makes me.
I'm not trying to talk
myself out of a job...
With this person, there
are other considerations.
His is the best I've
ever seen, hands down.
And I look at this
place that you've built,
the money you're investing,
sparing no expense.
And I know...
I know that you want the best.
[♪♪]
[GUNSHOT]
[GASPING]
MAN: 6353 Juan
Tabo. Apartment 6.
[PEOPLE MURMURING]
MAN: No, no. Eubank's west.
It's between Eubank and
Spain, but Mazatlan's closest.
[♪♪]
I don't know. I
just heard the one,
like, you know, a
backfire, a truck backfiring.
[VIBRATING]
I came out of my apartment.
A couple came out.
No. No, nobody saw.
Did you guys see anybody?
Guys, did you...? I don't know
if they speak English too good.
I don't think they saw anybody.
It was just this one loud...
This very loud pop
and that was all.
No arguing or like that.
So you guys good in directions
there? You want me to...?
They coming east or west?
If heading east,
tell them there's an Exxon
on their left-hand side.
Then it's straight residential.
You want me to what? Yeah.
No. I'll stay on the line.
[DOOR OPENS THEN
FOOTSTEPS RUNNING]
You know him?
We all heard this shot.
I don't think you
ought to go in there.
Mister, this is a crime scene.
You don't wanna touch anything.
Mister?
Mister, are you listening to me?
[♪♪]
[PANTING]
Little bastard.
Drive.
[♪♪]
[DOOR OPENS]
What the hell happened?
He's gone?
Look at me.
Gone?
You sure?
VICTOR: Gone.
Splattered all over.
MIKE: Oh, Jesus. Jesus.
Oh, shit.
All right.
So...
Shit.
All right, you do a sweep?
VICTOR: Couldn't. People there.
People? He get himself
seen by these people?
What about you?
Yeah. So what?
Just another looky-loo.
I guess I'd better
get this over with.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
SKYLER: Hey.
Oh, jeez, I woke you
up. I woke you up.
No, no, no, it's okay. I
needed to get up anyway.
Are you coming in?
No. It's kind of my
only time to run errands.
I just needed to... Ah.
I...
Sorry.
It's okay.
And thank you,
bigtime, as always.
They seem to be getting
bigger instead of smaller.
Not really sure
what that's all about.
Please, for God's sake,
tell me if this is getting
to be too much for you.
Absolutely not, okay?
It's absolutely fine.
Okay.
Does this mean
what I think it means?
What? You and Walt?
What?
His car is in the driveway.
It's not a state secret.
I... Oh. All right. Okay.
I'm not pressing. I just...
I think that it's great.
That's all, all right?
I'm out of here. Okay.
Oh, hey. A big howdy-do
to Mr. I'm-Not-Here.
[TEE DOUBLE'S "BRINGING IT BACK"
PLAYING INDISTINCTLY OVER SPEAKERS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
WOMAN [ON RADIO]: In
Albuquerque today. But you know what?
It always is when you have
330 days of sunshine a year.
MAN: On morning
commute, northbound 25,
we've got a two-car
accident on the right shoulder.
You gotta be careful.
Also, from the west side,
we've got another accident,
Paseo del Norte
and Second Street.
That one's on the left
shoulder, so be on the lookout.
That's a look at your morning
commute on Coyote 102.5.
[DOOR OPENS]
Oh, hey.
Breakfast? [YAWNS]
Yeah. Yeah? Okay.
All right. What you want?
[WALT SIGHS]
All right, look.
So I make it 10 to
9, which means...
Shut up.
Which means we need to start
a cook in the next 10 minutes
to keep to our schedule.
Gus' schedule.
And as angry as he may
be, I don't believe he's willing
to forfeit an entire batch.
That just might
make him angrier.
Come on, Mike. Let us cook.
Isn't that what this
whole thing is about?
[MACHINERY WHIRRING]
That's right, genius. Watch me.
We ain't missing no cook.
[DOOR RATTLING]
[BANGING ON DOOR]
[SIGHS]
We're closed.
Closed.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[HEAVY BREATHING CONTINUES]
[PHONE RINGING]
Saul Goodman and Associates.
I'll see if he's
in. Please hold.
[PHONE BEEPS]
Saul, Skyler White calling.
Saul.
[DEVICE BEEPING]
[SIGHS]
Saul, Skyler White on the line.
Saul.
Hey.
Skyler White.
What the hell does she want?
[DEVICE CLICKS OFF]
He's nowhere to be found.
I called his condo,
every number I have.
SAUL: Yeah, I'm sure he's fine.
You're sure?
As in, you know where he is?
[LAUGHS] Well, I'm
not the man's keeper,
but Walt's a big
boy. He'll turn up.
SKYLER: Mr. Goodman,
something is going on.
Why would he leave
his car in my driveway?
People carpool to work, right?
It's good for the environment.
He carpools? He carpools
to his job at a meth lab?
Hey, whoa. Oh-ho,
you're breaking up there.
I didn't quite catch
that last... Whew!
You're a Chatty Cathy today.
Okay, do you know anything?
Anything at all? Please, I'm
looking for some help here.
Look, Walter is fine, okay?
I guarantee that,
hundred percent.
One hundred percent.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[PHONE LINE HUMMING]
You got a passport, right?
[DOORBELL BUZZING]
Yeah. Albuquerque.
I'm in Nob Hill.
I need the number
for a locksmith.
I don't know. Pick one.
You sure there's nothing?
No, it's not even
me. It's state law.
Are you sure there isn't
some sort of...? I don't know.
No. Nothing.
Maybe a car registration.
That would have your address.
No, but I can't
even get in my car.
My car keys were
on the same ring.
[HOLLY CRYING]
My God, my credit cards,
my... It's all right, sweetheart.
My driver's license,
my checkbook.
I have to start
canceling all that.
My whole life was in that purse
and he just cut it
right off my shoulder.
We could've been stabbed.
I'm sorry, really. But
without proof of residency...
I can take you down to my shop.
You're welcome to
wait, file a police report.
I can't believe this. I
cannot believe this day.
I know. It's just, it's the law.
Oh, my God. My
medication. I bet it's gone.
[PANTING]
Oh, God, not now, not
this. Gotta call the pharmacy.
Are you okay?
Please, just...
Please, just take her.
Please. Just take her, please.
Oh. Oh, God.
Not now. No. Not now.
[HOLLY CRYING]
[SKYLER SIGHS]
Oh, you're a lifesaver. Truly.
Here you go, sweetheart.
Oh, there you go.
[PANTING AND SIGHING]
Um... How do you...? How
do you wanna deal with the bill?
I... Unfortunately, all
my cash was taken so...
That's fine. We'll
mail it to you.
Will you? You know
where I live, right?
Sir, again, thank you so much.
Really. Yeah.
[♪♪]
[TYPING ON KEYBOARD]
[DOOR CLOSES]
MARIE: Hey there. I'm back.
How was PT?
I heard it was very good.
Mm.
I'm really liking
this new therapist.
He keeps me in the loop,
always has time for
a phone call. It's...
I like it.
So?
Tell me all about it.
I heard you broke
new ground today.
I broke new ground?
That's what he said. Tell me.
I walked 16 feet in 20 minutes,
which is up from my
15 and a half yesterday.
And had maybe this
much less shit in my pants.
So, yeah, Marie, if you and him
and everybody in
America took a vote,
changed the meaning
of the English language,
yeah, I guess I
"broke new ground."
Well, call it a
figure of speech,
but I am seeing progress.
Definite progress.
You're ordering a new rock?
I'm bidding on a new mineral.
It's a nice one.
What? It's pretty.
I need the thing.
Okay, numero uno?
Dos.
Okay.
[HANK GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
It has all those pretty
little crystals. I like that.
Okay.
All right, I just
wanna go on record,
we should all be wearing masks.
We should be wearing masks.
[MIKE SIGHS]
Bet he forgets the aluminum.
Guaranteed.
Guarantee he forgets.
Mm-hm. Oh, you don't know
what the hell you're
doing, do you?
You forgot the aluminum.
One of the first steps in the...
Son of a bitch.
[DOOR OPENS]
[GLOVES SNAPPING]
All right, let's talk
about Gale Boetticher.
He was a good man
and a good chemist,
and I cared about him.
He didn't deserve
what happened to him.
He didn't deserve it at all.
But I'd shoot him again tomorrow
and the next day
and the day after that.
When you make it Gale versus me,
or Gale versus Jesse,
Gale loses, simple as that.
This is on you, Gus.
Not me, not Jesse.
Gale's death is on you.
I mean, really, what
did you expect me to do,
just simply roll over and
allow you to murder us?
That I wouldn't take measures,
extreme measures
to defend myself?
Wrong.
Think again. And whatever
it is you're planning there,
whatever it is, the point that
you're trying to make here,
let me... Let me suggest that
you keep one thing in mind.
Without us, without
Jesse and myself,
you have no one to
make your product.
Certainly not him.
This person doesn't know
what the hell he's doing.
Been watching him for weeks.
I know every step of his cook.
Oh.
Do you really? You?
[SCOFFS]
Really? Oh, so please tell me.
Catalytic hydrogenation,
is it protic or aprotic?
Because I forget.
If our reduction
isn't stereospecific,
how can our product be pure?
I mean, is 1-phenyl-1-hydroxy-
2-methylamino-propane,
containing, of
course, chiral centers
at carbons number one and
two on the propane chain?
Then reduction to
methamphetamine
eliminates which
chiral center is it again?
Because I forgot.
Come on, help me out, professor.
Gus.
We're here. Come
on. Let us work.
All his bullshit aside,
it's called a cook.
Everything comes down
to following a recipe.
Simple, complicated,
it doesn't matter.
The steps never change,
and I know every step.
WALT: Oh, is that what you want?
This short-order cook?
You're not flipping hamburgers.
What happens when you
get a bad barrel of precursor?
How would you even know it?
And what happens in the
summer when the humidity rises
and your product goes cloudy?
How would you guard
against that, huh?
Gus.
You do this, all
you'll have left
is an $8 million
hole in the ground.
This lab,
this equipment is
useless without us.
Without Jesse and myself,
you have no new product.
You have no income.
Your people out
there will not be paid.
Your distribution
chain collapses.
Without us,
you have nothing.
You kill me, you have nothing.
You kill Jesse,
you don't have me.
You won't do this.
You're too smart.
You can't afford to do this.
Please.
Let us just go back to work.
We're here.
Let us work. We're
ready to go to work.
We'll just pick up
right where we left off.
[VICTOR GASPING]
[BLOOD SPURTING]
[GROANING]
[VICTOR CONTINUES GASPING]
[GAGS]
[BLOOD DRIPPING]
[PANTING]
[FAUCET SQUEAKS]
[WATER RUNNING]
[PANTING]
GUS: Well?
Get back to work.
[♪♪]
[GRUNTING]
Listen, we'll just
lay this down.
Put him in feet first.
Grab his shoe.
Here. Wait, wait,
wait. Just lift him up.
There. All right.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
WALT: Oh, God.
JESSE: You push
that way, I'll hold him in.
WALT: Okay, ready? One...
Oh, shit.
JESSE: Wait, wait. Wait.
[BARREL CREAKING]
WALT: Forget that. Okay.
[PANTING]
Come on. Up.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Get down.
WALT: Okay, okay.
I never use this stuff. Are
you sure it'll do the job?
Trust us.
[♪♪]
[MACHINERY WHIRRING]
[OVER SPEAKERS]  ♪
There was once a time ♪
♪ When I didn't mind ♪
♪ If I never saw the light ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I can truly say ♪
Here you go, hon.
Get you anything else?
No, I'm good. Thanks.
♪ Oh, I don't mind ♪
♪ If my hair Starts
turning gray ♪
♪ There's not much
That I can do ♪
♪ Mm-hm ♪
♪ Long behind me I have
Left my younger days ♪
How you doing?
No, I mean, you know,
how are you doing?
You did the only
thing that you could.
I hope you understand that.
[EASY-LISTENING MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Thoughts?
Any thoughts on what
our next move might be?
What next move?
Our next move.
Our next move, given the
fact that at the first opportunity,
Gus will kill us.
What, that wasn't an
opportunity just now?
Seemed like a damn
good opportunity to me.
No, no. Golden, I would say.
We bought ourselves
some time, yes, but...
The question is how much.
He'll be looking
for another chemist.
He's not gonna
find another chemist.
Hm.
Where is he gonna
find another chemist?
It's not just about
somebody being able
to run a lab that big.
Someone he can trust,
someone he knows will
keep their mouths shut.
Yeah. Good luck with that.
Bet it took him
years to find Gale.
Bet he's sorry now.
[CHUCKLES]
Are you sure you're okay?
Now we all understand
each other. Right?
What do you mean? I mean,
him and us, we get it.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
We're all on the same page.
And what page is that?
The one that says:
"If I can't kill you,
you'll sure as shit
wish you were dead."
[CHUCKLES]
[SLURPS]
Yo, excuse me.
Thanks.
[JESSE SIGHS]
Here. DRIVER: Thank you, sir.
Have a good one.
Thanks.
[COUGHS]
Hi.
Um, it's parked over on Amsden.
Junior was about to get
up and he would've seen it,
so I wanted to avoid
a lot of questions.
Smart.
Well.
Kenny Rogers.
Yeah.
You okay?
Right as rain.
Do you have your keys?
Yeah.
Um... It's parked three
blocks down on the right.
Yeah.
[ALEXANDER'S "TRUTH" PLAYING]
♪ The truth is that I
never shook my shadow ♪
♪ Every day it's trying To
trick me into doing battle ♪
♪ Calling out "faker"
Only get me rattled ♪
♪ Want to pull me back ♪
♪ Behind the fence
With the cattle ♪
♪ Building your lenses
Digging your trenches ♪
♪ Put me on the front line
Leave me with a dumb mind ♪
♪ With no defenses
But your defense is ♪
♪ If you can't stand
To feel the pain ♪
♪ Then you are senseless ♪
[♪♪]