[VIDEO GAME GUN FIRING]
[MAN GROANING OVER TV]
[GUNSHOTS] [GROANS]
MAN 1 [OVER TV]: It came out
of nowhere. You gotta help us.
MAN 2: Look at
all this damn water.
MAN 1: Yeah, don't drink that.
Ain't no telling if
it's gonna be poison.
[GUNSHOTS]
Nothing new over here.
[MAN GRUNTS]
[GUNSHOT]
[♪♪♪]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
OVER HEADPHONES]
[CAR WASH WHIRRING]
How's Junior?
Exactly what I expected.
He hasn't said a word to me
since we told him
it was going back.
I, um, spoke to the dealership,
they didn't wanna take it.
What?
It's in perfect condition.
It's... It's got 17 miles
on the odometer.
SKYLER: I know. I spent
the better part of an hour
sweet-talking the manager
down to a restocking fee.
Eight hundred dollars.
Eight hundred
dollars? For two days?
Well, the law says they
don't have to take it back at all.
All right, here's
the registration,
the window sticker, the receipt.
Oh, and make sure you
talk to the general manager.
His name is Glenn.
Glenn.
Call me if there's a problem.
And please just don't...
Don't tangle with anyone.
Fine.
Oh. Bueno, Martin. Muy bueno.
Walt.
[THE PRETENDERS' "BOOTS
OF CHINESE PLASTIC" PLAYING]
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
[TIRES SCREECHING]
♪ Nam Myoho Renge
Kyo Buddha Please ♪
♪ Can you help a little peasant
That's begging on her knees? ♪
♪ Illusion fills my head
Like an empty can ♪
♪ I spent a million lifetimes
Loving the same man ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
Whoo-hoo!
♪ Always makes it's way
Back to the heart again ♪
♪ And by the way
You look fantastic ♪
♪ In your boots Of
Chinese plastic ♪
[TIRES SQUEALING]
♪ Hare Krishna Hare Rama too ♪
♪ Govinda, I am
still In love with you ♪
♪ I see you in the
birds And in the trees ♪
♪ That's why they call
me Krishna Mayee ♪
[ENGINE REVVING]
Oh, shit.
♪ That run through The vein ♪
♪ Always makes it's way
back To the heart again ♪
♪ And by the way
You look fantastic ♪
♪ In your boots Of
Chinese plastic ♪
[SIGHS]
♪ Hofra told us We
should tolerate ♪
♪ The people and the things
That make me wanna hate ♪
♪ Oh, have a little
mixed mercy On me ♪
♪ This seasoned beauty
In this human pageantry ♪
♪ Jesus Christ came
down here As a living man ♪
♪ If he can live a life Of
virtue then I hope I can ♪
♪ Unto others As you
would have a turn ♪
♪ Back here and repeat
until You learn, learn, learn ♪
♪ Oh, every drop That
run through the vein ♪
♪ Always makes it's way
Back to the heart again ♪
♪ And every dog that
lived His life on a chain ♪
♪ Knows what it's like
Waiting for nothing ♪
♪ And by the way
You look fantastic ♪
♪ In your boots Of
Chinese plastic ♪
[SIGHS]
Yes, hello.
I need a cab.
Yes, thank you.
The name is White.
Uh, I am at the
Pavilion parking
lot on University.
Oh, yes, that's right.
Just south of the airport.
Oh, that would be
great, thank you.
Oh, how long do you
think that would take?
No, I'm sure he'll see me.
Thank you.
SAUL: Contrition?
Hey, there is total
contrition here.
There's mountains of contrition.
"Fan-tan-tastic." I will
messenger them over right away.
Oh, and, uh, ahem, about
that other thing unrelated,
yes, I can get you in.
But I gotta warn you,
the eighth hole is murder.
Oh, yeah. You wanna
make it interesting?
Great. Tee time is 7 a.m. sharp.
Prepare to have your
ass handed to you.
Okay. Bye.
[SIGHS]
He was headed for
destruction of property.
But since it's
your own property,
I sweated him down to
misdemeanor trash burning.
[LAUGHS]
Now, the only thing is,
it's... It's not gonna be free.
Uh, there's a 5 grand fine,
600 for towing and disposal,
another 3 grand to
steam-clean the blacktop.
So bottom line, your little
joyride's gonna set you back
about 52,000 bucks.
So was it worth it?
I don't need to hear
the blow-by-blow.
Just tell me it's done.
Oh, I'm sorry. Did I wake you?
I... I caught this thing
before it got into the system.
That means your
record stays clean,
the wife never finds out.
I've been working magic here.
I could at least
get an "attaboy."
[SIGHS]
Fine. Rebel without
a cause, give.
What is it? Fring?
WALT: He will see me dead.
And there's nothing
I can do about it.
All that's left is to wait.
And we're sure about this.
Because Pinkman says
he needs you too much.
"Pinkman says."
Oh, "Pinkman says."
Unless...
you could help me
find a third party.
What third party?
Someone who can
ameliorate the situation.
Let's ditch the
thesaurus, all right?
You talking about a hit man?
Assuming that's still
what they're called.
[IMITATING BUZZER]
Wrong answer.
That's what the
kids call "epic fail."
[SIGHS]
All I would need
is a phone number.
I'd do the rest.
Saul, there'd be a finder's fee.
A big one.
Look, if you held
my feet to the fire,
I... I could come up
with a couple names.
One or two guys west of
the Rockies who do this work.
But guess what. These guys,
they know Mike and
Mike knows them.
Are you telling me Mike
knows everyone who does this?
Who do you think
gave me their names?
Okay, plan B. Look, we
go outside my network.
Craigslist. Soldier of Fortune.
Let's say we get lucky.
I mean, incredibly lucky,
and find a guy who's
not an undercover cop
or some kind of
survivalist nut-job wannabe.
You gotta ask yourself:
How good is good enough?
Because whatever goombah we buy
at some point is gonna
come head-to-head with Mike.
And Gus Fring?
Hey, just winging that guy
is not gonna
"ameliorate" your situation.
Not by a damn sight.
I tried to solve this myself,
but I can't get
anywhere near him.
You can't get near him?
Why don't you ask your partner?
Yeah, I saw him.
And you tell Saul
before you tell me?
Look, he's my
lawyer, same as yours.
Every time I go over there,
Saul hassles me about Mike.
He's still scared the dude's
gonna come break his legs.
So I give him the latest.
What happened exactly?
I was at a diner with Mike
and he just shows up.
They send me outside
and the two of them talk.
That's it.
So this is, like,
a regular thing?
[SCOFFS]
How close were you to him?
Close.
I mean, closer than
you and me right now.
Did he speak to you?
It was over in 10 seconds.
Would you just answer?
He said he sees
things in people.
What things?
What people?
Me.
He said he sees something in me.
A month ago, Gus was
trying to kill both of us.
And now he pulls
you out of the lab
and employs you as what?
An assistant gunman?
A tough guy?
Does that make any sense to you?
He says he sees
something in you.
What kind of game is he playing?
Does he think you're that naive?
He can't truly think
that you'd forget...
Well, let alone Gale,
let alone Victor...
and all the horror that
goes along with all of that.
What about this
girlfriend of yours
and her little brother?
I mean, the man looked
you straight in the eye
and told you, "No
more children."
But that very
night, that little boy,
he just...
He winds up...
I mean, Gus can't possibly
think that you'd forget that.
Okay.
I mean, all I'm
saying is that...
Is it possible that
he would think
that you're that weak-willed?
Drop the sales pitch.
I'll do it.
You'll do what?
I'll kill him.
First chance I get.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Piña colada? More
like stale bubblegum.
Does anyone actually
want their car to smell
like the bottom of a
6th-grader's desk?
Okay. Hemp? Really?
Yeah, I know. But you
know what they say.
"The customer's always right."
Ooh, speaking of customer,
it's not too late to
have a grand opening.
I was thinking
huge party, balloons,
bouncy house for the kids.
You know, make a
splash, get on TV.
Let people know they're
not gonna have to face
the eyebrows of doom
when they come in.
Marie, how's Hank doing?
You know what?
He's doing better.
Is he? Yeah. He...
Lately, his mood's improved
and he's like a
maniac with his PT.
That's fantastic.
Yeah, don't get me wrong,
he's got a long
way to go, but he...
Yeah. Oh, hey.
Hey.
Hi, Walt. It's good to see you.
Hey. You too.
Hey, your cashier here
is quite the salesperson.
She just talked
me into something
called the Orbital
Paste Wax Buff.
Oh, yeah, it's very important
to maintain your clear coat.
Boy, once that's goes...
Oh, yeah.
Um, hi.
Hi.
SKYLER: Bogdan was
averaging 19 cars during rush hour,
and we are already up to
22. Twenty-two actual cars.
Last night, I deposited $3800.
Jesus.
How much is that?
Two hundred seventy-four
thousand dollars, give or take.
Give or take? Yeah.
I haven't counted it.
Wait.
Two hundred and seventy-four...
And... And this is how often?
Every two weeks.
Thursdays good for a drop-off?
Wait, Walt,
are you telling me
you make $7,125,000 a year?
Seven and a half
even, before expenses.
But I can't...
Th... This is too much.
So it's more than you thought,
and this is somehow bad news?
No, that's... That's
not the point.
I mean, there's no
car wash in the world
that could do this
kind of business.
I mean, this is nine
month" work here, minimum.
Seven million? That...
That could take years.
So set some aside.
Save it for a rainy day.
Save it? Where? Save it where?
I can't go to the bank with it
and I sure can't leave it here.
Oye.
Wait a minute.
Is this all 50s?
Who pays for a
car wash with a 50?
Skyler, I didn't
ask you to do this.
I was under the impression
that you had this under control.
I just didn't expect
this amount of money.
The 50s are gonna be a problem.
Well, that's what this
is, problem solving.
Skyler, this is a
simple division of labor.
I bring in the money,
you launder the money.
This is what you wanted.
I never wanted any of this.
I've gotta go.
If you want out, just
say that you want out.
Okay, then.
[AIR WHOOSHING]
[AIR TURNED OFF]
[GASPING]
[WHIRRING]
You're telling me you
made this in the lab?
Why not?
Making it in his own
lab seemed appropriate.
There's not much of it.
We had more for Tuco.
It's enough.
This is still the best way.
You go after him with a gun,
you'll never get
out of it alive.
But with this,
you slip it into
his food or drink.
There shouldn't be
any taste or smell.
Thirty-six hours later...
A man his age, working
as hard as he does,
no one will be surprised.
What about Mike?
Mike can have his suspicions,
but that's all they'll be.
Please, one homicidal
maniac at a time.
[SIGHS]
I don't know when I'm
gonna see Gus again.
I mean, if ever.
[SNIFFS]
Keep it with you.
When you have the opportunity,
be ready.
What if they search me?
Will they do that?
It's the wrong way around.
It's my lucky cigarette.
Well,
whatever you do, don't smoke it.
WALT, JR.: You... You know
they have a drive-thru, right?
HANK: Nah, this is good.
Could use the exercise,
get the blood pumping.
Don't worry, you're not
gonna have to pick me up.
It might take me a
while, but I'll get there.
Jesus, ain't we a pair.
Hey, you must
really like chicken.
V-8, 470 horses,
20-inch rims, satellite
radio, Bluetooth.
Zero to 60 in 4.7 seconds.
Whoa, whoa, what do
you mean, on a lark?
Spur of the moment,
your dad ups and buys you
a brand-new Challenger?
Yeah. I barely got
it around the block,
and Mom said we couldn't
afford it, so they took it back.
Do you know how long
I had it? Fifteen hours.
Well, hey, buddy, let
me tell you something.
When I was your age,
I'd have given my left nut
to drive a car like
that for 15 minutes.
Seriously, how... How
does that happen?
Well, we were looking at
used cars and I kind of...
Ah, you guilted him into it.
Yeah, yeah, I know. I hear you.
You pulled the old, "Poor little
me and my troubles," am I right?
Maybe.
You flew too close
to the sun, my friend.
You'd have let him
buy you a clunker,
you'd be driving now instead
of borrowing mom's hooptie.
Agent Schrader.
Oh, hey, how are you
doing? Well, thank you.
Good to see you.
Walter, Jr., do you
remember Mr. Fring?
How are you? Well.
Nice to see you again.
It's a pleasure to see you.
You're looking very well.
Yeah, well, you know,
chalk it up to clean living
and, uh, vitamin pills.
[GUS LAUGHS]
I must apologize. If I
had seen you come in,
there would have
been no question
of accepting your money.
In the future, please
feel free to ask for me.
A DEA hero should never
have to pay for a meal
at Pollos Hermanos. No kidding?
I'll take you up
on that, for sure.
[LAUGHS]
And, uh, how are
your mother and father?
They're... They're good.
The chicken is great.
Thank you.
If ever you're interested in
rewarding part-time work,
perhaps something after
school, my door is always open.
Sounds good.
HANK: Oh, I don't
know about this one.
He might eat up
all your profits.
Well, I'll let you
finish your meal.
Can I get you anything else?
A refill, perhaps?
No, thank you. I'm good.
Sure. Take a Diet Coke,
thank you very much.
Of course.
So where are we going?
Oh, big doings today.
The order of the day is
eyes open, mouth shut.
[CHICKENS PEEPING]
What's up?
Test.
You got me?
Count off.
Let's go.
Right here. Leave
the wrap on, please.
You know how to make coffee?
Sure. There you go.
You want a rundown? Please.
Three guys up at the gate,
two visible, one in the blind.
We got five guys down here
with a backup out of sight.
I got Tyrus down in the
tree line with a Barrett .50.
Planted him there last night,
in case we had
any early arrivals.
[♪♪♪]
I don't have an extra holster.
You stick this in your
pocket. Keep it out of sight.
You're gonna be here today,
you're gonna have a gun.
It's loaded?
[SIGHS]
I don't wanna see
that in your hand
unless you see me
with mine, understood?
Emergency only.
First car is coming.
All right, what's the
order of the day?
Eyes open, mouth shut.
A lot of guns.
Nobody's asking
you to give up yours.
You wanna sweep the place
before you bring in your guys?
I am the guy.
All right, then.
[IN SPANISH] Welcome.
Where is the rest of your party?
[IN SPANISH] I am
the only one coming.
And why is that?
My employers feel
I can adequately
represent their interests.
Please, sit.
This is my offer.
In consideration of our
previous relationship...
I will make a one-time payment
of 50 million U.S. dollars.
In return, our
business is concluded.
No further payments.
No further contact.
An absolute severance.
You have no response?
This is my response:
Yes or no?
You know what the Cartel wants.
Anything else would
be a waste of time.
Is it to be yes...
or no?
A hard way to
begin a negotiation.
This is not a negotiation.
[ENGINE STARTING]
[CAR DOORS CLOSING]
MIKE: You got something of mine?
Glove box.
Figure I better teach
you how to shoot.
Could be things
are gonna get hairy.
What is this?
I mean, you're giving
me a gun, and...
And now I'm, like, part
of the team or whatever?
He said he sees something in me.
Like what?
If I had to put it in a word,
I'd guess loyalty.
Loyalty.
Only maybe you got
it for the wrong guy.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
Jesse?
Hey. Hey.
Long time, no see.
How you doing?
Yeah, you know, uh...
good. Good.
Good.
Okay, we're gonna get
started. You coming in?
So the truth is, we
can't change the past.
What's done is done.
We've gotta own our actions,
but putting ourselves on trial,
acting as our own judge,
jury and executioner,
it's not the answer.
Because a lot of the
time, all that judging does
is just ensure that we're
gonna repeat the cycle.
Right?
"I'm such an asshole.
"It's totally hopeless,
what's the point?
I think I'll have a hit."
Jesse,
what's going on
with you these days?
[SIGHS]
I, uh, went back to the crystal.
You sober now?
Yeah.
Four days. Big whoop, right?
GROUP LEADER: Hey, four
days is four days. You're here.
You still...
working at the laundry?
How are things there?
Sucks ass.
[CHUCKLES]
Anything you want to talk about?
Um...
A couple of weeks back...
I, uh,
killed a dog.
GROUP LEADER:
You hit it with your car?
No, I...
I put him down.
I watched him go.
I was looking him
straight in the eye.
You know, he didn't
know what was happening.
He didn't know why. He...
He was just scared.
And then...
he was gone.
He was suffering.
It was a kindness.
No, he wasn't sick.
No. He was just, like a...
I don't know, like, a...
problem dog.
What'd he do?
Bite someone?
No, this dog never...
Never bit anybody.
You pick up the rock, you
go right to the dark side.
Anything can happen.
It ain't no rock
that made me do it.
Well, what was the problem?
Why'd you have to kill him?
Watch the crosstalk, please.
Maybe it's not the
details that matter, right?
How'd you feel about
what you did, Jesse?
I don't know.
Who cares how you feel?
What kind of a person
kills a dog for no reason?
GROUP LEADER: Colleen.
COLLEEN: Put an ad in the paper,
you drop him off at a shelter.
Don't sit there and talk
about killing a helpless animal.
We're not here
to sit in judgment.
Why not?
Why not? Maybe she's right.
You know, maybe I
should've put it in the paper.
Maybe I... I should've
done something different.
The thing is,
if you just do stuff
and nothing happens...
what's it all mean?
What's the point?
Oh, right, this... This whole
thing is about self-acceptance.
Kicking the hell out of yourself
doesn't give
meaning to anything.
So I should stop judging...
and accept?
GROUP LEADER: It's a start.
So no matter what I do,
hooray for me because
I'm a great guy?
It's all good?
No matter how many dogs I kill,
I just, what, do an
inventory and accept?
[SNIFFLES]
I mean, you back your
truck over your own kid
and you, like, accept?
What a load of crap.
Hey, Jesse.
I know you're in pain.
No, you know what?
Why I'm here in
the first place...
is to sell you meth.
You're nothing to
me but customers!
I made you my bitch.
You okay with that?
Huh?
You accept?
No.
About time.
[STEAM HISSING]
[GRUNTS]
[COUGHS]
Jesse.
Bring your light
over here, will you?
Do you see any residue there?
Where?
Here. On the
bottom, right there.
[WHISPERING] It's been
a week. What's going on?
I haven't seen him.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
I didn't think so.
But I'll just give it
another shot anyway.
[GRUNTS]
[STEAM HISSING]
Hey. Hey, buddy. Look at that.
Graduated to doorman.
Finally found your calling.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, little whiskers, Marie.
What'd you do?
Show your barber a
picture of a dog's ass
and said, "I'll take that"?
[LAUGHS] Yeah,
charming as usual.
Welcome back.
Looking good, Marie.
Oh, thanks, Steve. Good
to see you. How you doing?
He's doing fine. We
can take it from here.
Right, Gomie? Yeah.
If you wanna hold his elbow.
No, no, no. You
keep your mitts off me.
I'm good. I'm good.
MARIE: Hey.
Good luck.
Let's go, we're
running late. Come on.
[SIGHS]
Hank, seeing you walk in here,
I can't tell you what that means
to all of us.
Your progress, it's incredible.
Yeah, well, chalk it up to
clean living and vitamin pills.
[LAUGHS]
Steve tell you his news? What?
Finally got your period?
I made GS-14.
Wow, that's all right, man.
Next stop: Washington,
D.C. Sitting behind a desk,
papers piled so high
you can't see over them.
Hey, better you than me, buddy.
Seriously,
congratulations, buddy.
Thanks.
Steve said you might
have something for us.
Yeah, maybe. You guys
are gonna have to tell me.
You remember my pal Tim Roberts?
APD detective?
Yeah, well, he's working
on a murder case.
The victim's a 34-year-old
male Caucasian
by the name of Gale Boetticher.
One night last month,
Boetticher opens the door
and, bam,
takes a bullet to the face from
a person or persons unknown.
Now, this Gale Boetticher is
a bona fide chemistry genius.
I mean, he's got degrees
up the wazoo, right?
And, well, as you might
expect, he's a nerd's nerd.
Vegan, sandals and
socks kind of guy.
As it turns out, he's also
an A-number-one meth cook.
And what caught my eye is
his specialty product's blue.
So, what are you thinking?
This is your Heisenberg?
No. What I think we
got here is, ahem,
Heisenberg's former cook,
and maybe a line on
Heisenberg himself.
Anyway, lo and behold,
amidst all the
hippie-dippy nonsense,
I find this.
Now, this here, I
do a little Google-fu,
and I realize it's
a parts number
specifically for this baby.
Now that there is a high-volume
HEPA industrial
air filtration system.
That's a $300,000 gadget.
Perfect for a pharmaceutical
plant or microchip factory,
or maybe the biggest
meth lab north of the border.
Okay.
So this little dingus
here is manufactured
by a big international concern:
Madrigal Electromotive.
I call their Houston office,
and eventually I get through
to the nicest little
20-year-old temp.
I use some of the
Schrader sweet-talk on her,
before you know
it, she's pulling files.
Turns out six months ago,
one of these systems was
shipped to a depot right here in ABQ.
Who signed for it?
Gale Boetticher.
So I asked my new
girlfriend, "Who paid for it?"
And she says, "Nobody."
[SCOFFS]
They have no record that
anybody actually paid for this thing.
So I go back and push
more and before you know it,
the temp's gone, there's
no forwarding address.
And I'm talking to
some snot-nose lawyer
who's asking me for
my badge number.
Brick wall.
So I take a peek into
Madrigal Electromotive.
Now, Madrigal is based
in Hanover, Germany,
but they're what they
call "highly diversified."
Industrial equipment,
global shipping,
major construction,
and a tiny little foothold
in American fast food,
specifically a local chain.
Pollos Hermanos.
Okay. So what, right?
Boetticher's dead.
I got no line on who's
been bankrolling him
or where his lab was.
The whole thing's
a snipe hunt, right?
But now I get this crazy idea,
and I can't shake it.
I mean, I... I stay up
nights staring at the ceiling
trying to make sense of it.
That napkin. Remember, I
told you Boetticher's a vegan.
I mean, we're talking
this guy makes his own
fermented lentil bread,
or whatever the hell that is.
What's a vegan doing
in a fried chicken joint?
Maybe he's meeting somebody.
Like who?
Well, like, maybe...
this guy.
I mean, what do we know
about Gustavo Fring, huh?
This whole
friend-of-law-enforcement thing?
Could be a case of,
"keep your friends close
but your enemies closer."
I mean, he's got the money
to finance this operation.
Maybe he's got the connections
too. Maybe, just maybe,
he's our guy.
Hank, no offense,
but I think you're
really reaching.
If your guy had
his meeting at KFC,
you wouldn't immediately assume
that he's sitting down
with Colonel Sanders.
You know, I... Ahem.
I couldn't agree more, guys.
[CHUCKLES]
Gustavo Fring,
blue meth, you know.
The whole thing
is off-the-map nuts.
I ought to be wearing
a tinfoil hat, you know?
Except...
I can't seem to wrap my
mind around this one little thing.
And that is,
what are Gustavo
Fring's fingerprints...
doing in Gale
Boetticher's apartment?
[♪♪♪]