[♪♪♪]
Let's get something straight.
This, the chemistry,
is my realm.
I am in charge of the cooking.
Out there on the street,
you deal with that.
[ALARM BLARING]
[PEOPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
As far as our customers go,
I don't want to know
anything about them.
I don't wanna see them,
I don't wanna hear them.
I want no interaction
with them whatsoever.
This operation is you and
me, and I'm the silent partner.
You got any issues with that?
Whatever, man.
No matter what happens,
no more bloodshed.
No violence.
[♪♪♪]
Walt? Hm?
You all right? Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I'm okay.
You know, honey, you...
You really don't have to...
Look, I like being
here with you.
Yeah.
I'm only saying that,
you know, I'd be okay.
That, really, if you wanna go...
You know, actually, it would
make me feel a little better
knowing that you were there
when Walter Jr. Gets
home from school.
Okay.
All right. So you'll call
me when you're finished?
Oh, yeah. Okay.
[GRUNTS]
Oh, and have you
been in touch with Elliot?
Because I haven't
seen a check from him.
Yes, I... I got it.
Really? It came, yeah. And I...
Yeah, it did. It came last week
and I put it right into
my credit union account.
So I'm taking care of it.
Good. Yeah.
So we're good. We're good.
Could you not deposit
this until Monday?
Thank you.
Call if the
discomfort's too much,
otherwise we'll
see you next week.
Yeah.
[♪♪♪]
Chemical reactions
involve change on two levels:
matter and energy.
When a reaction is gradual,
the change in energy is slight.
I mean, you...
You don't even notice
the reaction is happening.
For example, when rust
collects on the underside of a car.
Right?
[CLEARS THROAT]
But if a reaction
happens quickly,
otherwise harmless
substances can interact in a way
that generates enormous
bursts of energy.
All right.
Uh, who can give me
an example of rapid
chemical reaction?
Hint, hint. Right here.
Like, an explosion?
Yes, good. Explosions.
Explosions are the result
of chemical reactions
happening almost
instantaneously.
And the faster reactants,
i.e. explosives...
And fulminative mercury
is a prime example of that.
The faster they undergo change,
the more violent the explosion.
Explosions.
Okay, listen, why don't you
start reading on your own
from the top of chapter seven.
All right?
[VOMITING]
[GASPING]
HUGO: You okay?
I got it, Mr. White.
Don't worry.
You got kids to teach.
Thanks, Hugo.
[BEEPING]
SKLYER: He's
starting to lose weight
which is, um,
tough, to see that.
I can already
feel the difference
when I put my, uh,
arms around him.
Can I talk to...?
Of course.
Walt.
When you don't let
me in, when you don't
tell me what's going on...
I mean, it's like I feel like
you don't even want
me around sometimes.
No.
And... And... And
recently, these...
These afternoons when
you're coming home so late
and we're just left
wondering where you are.
WALT JR.: Yeah, Dad.
What's up with that?
Walt, is there anything else
you're holding back
from your family?
Now's the time to share.
Well, I...
I-I like to be alone,
I mean, at times.
And it's not about you, really.
It's just that sometimes
it feels better not to talk
at all, about anything,
to anyone.
Alone time can be
helpful. For some types.
Maybe knowing what
you do when you're alone
might make it easier
for your family to
be more accepting
of whatever it is you do alone.
[MOUTHS "YEAH"]
Well,
I like to go on walks.
A couple of times a week,
maybe more, after work.
And I-I really enjoy the nature.
You know, the cacti,
vegetation, that kind of thing.
It's really very,
very therapeutic.
[♪♪♪]
[COUGHING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Yo, God, are you okay?
Hey, you did that
shit? I'm dizzy. No.
I'm just dizzy. I need air.
God, I feel like I'm burning
up. Sit down, sit down.
I gotta... Take this off.
Sit down, get some air.
Oh, God.
Oh.
Here.
Better?
Yeah, that's better.
Oh.
When were you gonna tell me?
Tell you what?
Cancer.
You got it, right?
How did you know?
My aunt had one of those
dots on her
to target the radiation.
What, is it in your lung?
I'm your partner, man,
you should have told me.
God, that's not cool, okay?
Not at all.
[GRUNTS]
What stage are you?
Three-A.
Gone into your lymph nodes.
Your aunt.
How-how bad was she
when they caught it?
Bad enough, she
didn't last long.
How long?
Seven months.
God.
I get it now.
That's why you're
doing all this.
You want to make some cash
for your people
before you check out.
You got a problem with that?
You tell me.
You're the one that looks like
he just crawled
out of a microwave.
You gonna be able
to finish the batch?
Yes.
[COUGHING] All right.
[SIGHS]
No.
You do it.
Me?
Yeah.
What happened
to your mad skills?
[SIGHS]
Go on. Here.
You do it.
You can do it.
If you have any questions,
I'll be right out here.
The next time, put an ice pack
on your head during chemo.
My aunt said it helped
with the hair loss.
[♪♪♪]
What's this, Christmas?
This that one we found way out
in the boonies at the cook site?
Holy shit. What?
HANK: Lab says they
pulled up an imprint
of some old writing
used to be on the inside.
Magic Marker or something.
Yeah? What's it say?
"Property of J.P.
Winn Chemistry Lab."
That's Walt's school.
[♪♪♪]
♪ It is such a good
night To kiss ♪
night To dance ♪
♪ It is such a good night to ♪
♪ Scooby-dee-dooby-doo ♪
♪ Scooby-dee-dooby-doo-love ♪
♪ It is such a good
night To kiss ♪
night To dance ♪
♪ It is such a good night to ♪
♪ Scooby-dee-dooby-doo ♪
♪ Scooby-dee-dooby-doo-love ♪
We were supposed to start at 3.
Hey, I'm out there making
fat stacks, man. Chill.
Hey, prepaid cell phone. Use it.
How much is this?
Twenty-six big ones.
Is that all?
Twenty-six-thousand dollars?
Uh, no, that's 2600,
and your share is 13,
minus 25 bucks for that phone.
How much meth did you sell?
Nearly an ounce.
Last time I checked there
were 16 ounces to a pound.
What did you do with
the rest, smoke it?
Yo, I've been out all
night slinging crystal.
You think it's cake
moving a pound of meth
one teenth at a time?
Why are you selling it
in such small quantities?
Why don't you just sell
the whole pound at once?
To who? What do I
look like, Scarface?
This is unacceptable. I
am breaking the law here.
This return is too
little for the risk.
I thought you'd be ready
for another pound today.
You may know a lot
about chemistry, man,
but you don't know
jack about slinging dope.
Well, I'll tell you,
I know a lack of
motivation when I see it.
Oh, my...
Come on, you've gotta be more
imaginative, you know, just...
Just think outside the box here.
We have to move our
product in bulk, wholesale.
Now, how do we do that?
What, do you mean
to a distributor?
Yes. Yes, that's what we need.
We need a distributor.
Now, do you know
anyone like that?
Yeah, I mean, I used
to, until you killed him.
So who took Krazy-8's place?
Some guy named Tuco.
Badass, from what I hear.
Tuco, okay. So then
just go talk to Tuco.
Right. Like, "Hello, sir. Hey,
I know you don't know me,
"but would you be interested
in a felony quantity
of methamphetamine?"
Well, yes, but
maybe with a little
more salesmanship, perhaps?
You just don't get it,
man, okay? This guy's OG.
What... What does that mean?
Jesus, look, he's
off our level, man.
He's not gonna do business
with some dude he doesn't know.
You just don't understand
the way it works.
You can't just bum-rush
some high-level ice man
and start cutting deals.
Okay? It's risky.
You need an intro, you
need someone to vouch.
Well, who introduced
you to Krazy-8?
Emilio, and that's only because
I knew him from third grade,
and we can't talk
to Emilio, because...
All right, all right, all right.
Look, I'm telling
you, Mr. White,
it's too risky. Okay?
I mean, we're making money.
Why can't you be
satisfied with the way it is?
Oh, come on! Jesus!
Just grow some fucking balls!
[MOUTHS "WOW"]
[LAB EQUIPMENT BEEPING]
Wait till Monday again?
Yes, please. Thank you.
[VOMITING]
Oh, God.
[FLUSHES]
HUGO: Mr. White.
Thank you, Hugo.
Uh...
[SIGHS]
[COUGHING]
Knock, knock. Oh, hey.
How you feeling, Walt?
Good. Yeah.
Are you up for having a visitor?
Hey, buddy.
H-Hank.
Well, let me know if
you need anything.
I will. Thank you, Carmen.
Damn.
Chick's got an
ass like an onion,
makes me wanna cry.
So, what...? What
are you doing here?
Well, I had some questions
I wanted to run by
you, work-related. Oh.
You feeling okay? I-I
can come back later.
No, no, no, I'm fine.
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
What do you mean,
"work-related," though?
Do you recognise that?
No. No.
Well, that was
used to cook meth.
Found it out on some Indian
land about 40 miles from here.
Old label on the
inside used to say:
"J.P. Winn Chemistry Lab."
I don't understand how
that came from here.
Well, I was hoping you
could help me with that.
We found it near
an abandoned car
that belonged to
one of our snitches.
A snitch?
Yeah, one of our
confidential informants.
Went missing a while back.
No body yet,
but we're pretty sure, you know:
Probably chopped up into little
pieces and fed to the buzzards.
Ugh.
Anyway, you...
Any respirators like
that go missing lately?
Uh-uh.
No. No.
No, I mean, not that I know of.
I'll need to look
at that inventory.
Sure. Sure. I've got a
list hanging on the wall.
Do you mind if I take a
look at your storeroom?
Not at all. No.
Be my guest.
All right, so who's got
keys? [CLEARS THROAT]
The science faculty,
the staff, Carmen,
the vice-principal has
the master, and me.
How about students?
Uh, no, no. No
students have keys.
Shit, I should hope not.
My question is do
any of the little pissants
know where you keep 'em?
Uh, I don't... I
don't think so, no.
I mean, besides,
I keep them right here in
my pocket anyway, so...
Walt, look, I know
they're your students,
but do not underestimate
them. Big mistake.
Are there any other respirators?
Um, no.
Because I'm counting six,
uh, inventory says eight.
Hm. [PHONE RINGING]
Glassware looking
a little sparse.
Yeah. You're missing a couple
of Erlenmeyer flasks, at least.
Oh, yeah.
A 5000 millilitre round-bottom.
Meth heads love
to brew in this baby.
You gonna answer that?
Oh, no, it's
just... No, I don't...
Maybe it's Skyler, she's
in trouble or something.
Shit, don't ignore
it on my account.
Answer it. Come
on, I got stuff to do.
Jeez. Okay.
Hello?
JESSE [ON PHONE]:
Yo, what's up, Mr. W?
Uh, speaking.
Bad time to talk?
WALT [ON PHONE]: Absolutely.
All right, so just listen.
So you know that guy we
were talking about, Tuco?
Turns out my boy, Skinny Pete,
was in the same
cell block with him
So we got our in. We're hauling
a pound to the dude right now.
Okay, then. Well, thank you.
Thank you very much for calling.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Ha. My, uh, doctor
is very solicitous.
Hey, look, buddy.
The last thing I wanna
do is get you in hot water,
but some meth-monkey had
a feeding frenzy in here, okay?
You gotta keep better
watch over your turf.
I will.
We don't want people to start
wondering about you, right?
[CHUCKLES]
[SNORTS]
Right. No. Right.
Absolutely not.
[RAP SONG PLAYING ON STEREO]
[DOORS SHUT]
So you're sure you're
tight with this guy?
Two nuts in a ball sack, yo.
[RAPPING IN FOREIGN DIALECT]
Yo, man, I'm Skinny Pete.
Maybe this isn't such a
good idea, yo. Come on.
[DOOR BUZZES]
Yeah, man, that's
what's happening.
Yo, Tuco's expecting us.
No need, man. Me
and Tuco go back.
Tuco, what's
happening, my brother?
Sick crib, yo.
You've been keeping it
real since you been sprung.
What's it been, like, a year?
This your boy?
Yeah, Jesse. Dude with the
glass I was telling you about.
Hey, man, yeah. I've
heard a lot about you.
Break out the ice.
Take a bump.
No worries, man, I'm no cop.
I said, hit it.
All right.
[CHUCKLES]
Booyah!
Whoo!
This kicks like a mule with
his balls wrapped in duct tape.
Whoo!
Where'd you get it?
I cooked it.
[CHUCKLES]
Bullshit.
Who you working for?
No one, man.
I mean, I have a partner
that I cook with, but that's it.
All right.
Aw.
We got a deal.
See, I told you Tuco
would hook you up.
Cool. I haven't said how much.
TUCO: Aw.
All right. How much?
Thirty-five large for the pound.
Well, you're a
little light, ese.
[CHUCKLES]
It's all right, don't
sweat it. It's all good.
It's good. Go on,
get out of here.
What about the money?
You'll get it.
This is a consignment operation.
You want me to float 35 G's?
You don't trust me?
Hey, no, no, hey.
It's not that, man.
It's just, you know, I don't...
I don't do business that way.
Tough shit, the deal is done.
You said this was cool, okay?
Money for meth, cash up front.
Don't front, dude,
Tuco's good for it.
I don't need your punk
ass to vouch for me.
Come on.
Oh, come on.
TUCO: All right.
You brought me some
really clean crystal. Whoo!
You really want
your money up front?
Up front.
[MAN LAUGHS]
Nobody moves crystal
in the South
Valley but me, bitch.
Morning, Hugo.
You don't mind if I
call you Hugo, Hugo?
GIRL: We've never had a
problem with Hugo, ever.
Is that Uncle Hank?
Right, what do you got
there? All right. Book him.
Uncle Hank's
arresting Mr. Archilleya.
CARMEN: This doesn't
make any sense at all.
I don't understand.
HANK: I got two words for you:
background check.
How about that?
JESSE [ON MACHINE]: Yo, yo, yo.
1-4-8, 3-to-the-3,
to-the-6, to-the-9.
Representing the
ABQ. What up, biatch?
Leave it at the tone.
[BEEPS]
Where the hell are
you? Call me back.
MARIE: Hey, Walt?
Yeah?
Uh, Hank's about to deal.
Okay, I'll, uh...
I'll be right there.
[COUGHING]
HANK: All right, let's see
what the turn brings us.
You're looking good,
Walt. Your color's better.
Yeah? Thanks.
SKYLER: He's actually on
the pretty strong stuff now.
Dr. Delcavoli's trying to
talk him into taking some time
off from work, but...
Well, actually, I just
talked to Carmen
this morning and they're getting
a substitute for a few weeks.
Oh. Good for you.
I didn't have a
chance to tell you.
Sorry.
Your bet, tough guy.
Check.
Uh, yeah, check.
Check's in the mail.
Ten million.
Well, then, 25 million,
because that's how I roll.
WALT JR.: Hey, Uncle Hank,
I heard you arrested
Mr. Archilleya the other day.
He's a pretty cool guy.
Well, turns out he has a record.
Yeah, a couple of
possession beefs.
We figured he was the
guy that was stealing your...
Your school's chemistry gear.
I mean, you know, he
had a key, fit the profile.
And when we searched his
truck, we found a big old fat blunt.
Which goes to prove old
huge Hugo ain't so cool after all.
It's... It's to you, Walt.
Yeah, I'll call.
You know, I can't
believe the school system
didn't know about
this guy's record.
I mean, that's pretty scary.
How could something like that
slip through the cracks?
WALT: I don't know.
I mean, for what it's worth,
Hugo just doesn't
strike me as a thief.
Yeah, well, nothing
personal, Walt,
but you wouldn't know a criminal
if he was close enough
to check you for a hernia.
[CHUCKLES]
That said,
we got a search warrant,
and we tore old
Hugo's house apart.
Turns out he's a
major-league pothead,
but, uh... But he didn't
raid your chemistry set.
You hiding something?
I'm in.
And the river card.
Yeah, I got nothing, I'm out.
I'm out.
Yowza.
When old
holes-in-her-purse bails,
you know you're in deep.
Looks like it's you
and me, buddy.
What's gonna
happen to him? Hugo?
Oh, well, I mean, he's gonna
lose his job, like he should.
Probably spend a
couple months in county,
because it's not his first rap.
I'm waiting.
[CHUCKLES]
You gonna man up or
are you gonna puss out?
Hank.
Sorry.
WALT: I'm all in.
Mm.
Dude. You bad,
bad, bad, horrible liar.
What are you smoking there, huh?
You got a heart? You
got the flush, don't you?
Nope. Not falling
for it, buddy. I fold.
Talk about
anti-climactic. HANK: Hey.
Your cards couldn't have
been that bad, come on.
Oh, my God. You
threw away an ace?
HANK: What are you
doing? And a cowboy for...
Oh.
A handful of nothing.
[COUGHS]
[FRIDGE SHUTS]
[CAN OF SODA POP OPENS]
[PHONE BEEPS]
[PHONE RINGS]
[SIGHS]
[CLEARS THROAT]
MAN [ON PHONE]: Yeah, what up?
Who is this? I was
dialling Jesse Pinkman.
Hey, man, he's out.
Well, where is he, then?
You the guy?
Yeah, I'm the guy.
How is he?
Got some busted
ribs and like that.
Got messed up pretty good.
I was all, like, "Damn,
Tuco, chill, ese."
I don't know what
got into him. Seriously.
He's out, man. Way out.
They got him doped up big time.
So you're the cook, huh?
Yo, I didn't catch your name.
Tell me about this Tuco.
Tell me everything about him.
[TOILET FLUSHES]
[♪♪♪]
[BUZZING]
Morning.
Could you pass
the butter, please?
Badass, Dad.
[RAP SONG PLAYING ON STEREO]
[MAN RAPPING INDISTINCTLY]
MAN: Hey, cue
ball. Need directions?
You Tuco?
I want to talk to Tuco, and
I'm not leaving until I do.
[SNIFFS]
What's your name?
Heisenberg.
Heisenberg. Okay.
Have a seat, Heisenberg.
I don't imagine I'll
be here very long.
No?
[CHUCKLES]
All right.
Be that way.
It's your meeting.
Why don't you start talking
and tell me what you want?
Fifty thousand dollars.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, man. Fifty G's?
How you figure that?
Thirty-five for the
pound of meth you stole
and another 15 for my
partner's pain and suffering.
Partner.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, yeah, I remember
that little bitch.
So you must be daddy.
Let me get this straight.
[CHUCKLES]
I steal your dope.
Hm?
I beat the piss out
of your mule boy,
and then you walk in here
and you bring me more meth?
[LAUGHING]
Whoo!
That's a brilliant plan, ese.
Brilliant.
You got one part of that wrong.
This is not meth.
[MEN SHOUTING]
Are you fucking nuts?
You wanna find out?
No, no, Gonzo, calma. Calma.
Calma.
You got balls,
I'll give you that.
All right, all right. I'll
give you your money.
That crystal that your
partner brought me,
it sold faster
than 10-dollar ass in TJ.
Let's say you bring me
another pound next week.
Money up front.
All right.
Sometimes you gotta
rob to keep your riches.
Just as long as we
got an understanding.
One pound is not gonna
cut it. You have to take two.
[LAUGHS]
[COUGHING]
Oh, really?
Hey.
What is that shit?
Fulminated mercury and
a little tweak of chemistry.
[CHUCKLES]
[MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[GROWLING]
[COUGHING]
[SILVER SEAS' "CATCH
YER OWN TRAIN" PLAYING]
♪ I wish I was strong ♪
♪ Good enough from the start ♪
[ENGINE STARTS]
♪ Instead of waiting so long ♪
♪ To reveal what's behind ♪
[SIRENS BLARING]
♪ There's no use in talking ♪
♪ You made up your mind ♪
♪ Baby, you and I ♪
♪ Are not the same ♪
♪ You say you're like the sun ♪
♪ I'm like the rain ♪
♪ Say, before we go ♪
♪ Do it all again ♪
♪ You better catch
Your own train ♪
you Your own train ♪