In closing, I can tell you
we take this very seriously.
APD as well as the DEA.
Stopping the manufacture
and sale of methamphetamines
remains one of our
highest priorities.
The theft of lab
equipment from your school
is also receiving
our highest attention.
Rest assured, no
stone will go unturned
in our search for the person
or persons responsible for this.
If you have any questions,
now would be the time. Sir.
MAN: You're talking like you
haven't caught anybody yet.
What about the janitor
dealing drugs at school?
There is no indication that
this individual was selling drugs.
He was arrested for having
a small amount of marijuana
in his car, not in the school.
And he's since been fired.
MAN: I heard he had a record.
I'd like to know how he got
a job here in the first place.
Exactly. Why wasn't
there a background check?
WOMAN: There was one. We're
currently reviewing our hiring policies.
WOMAN 2: You
better be doing more.
This guy was arrested
right in front of my daughter.
MAN: This guy was
stealing lab equipment, right?
MAN 2: That's not
our thinking this time.
We're looking at
others who had access,
but not limited to
the maintenance staff.
WOMAN 2: Are you
saying there was a break-in?
Do we know when this happened?
I mean, could it have
been during school hours?
We haven't been able to
establish a date or time.
But there is no sign
of breaking or entering.
MAN: So whoever
took it had a key.
We're talking inside job?
Someone who's
still at the school?
MAN 2: Sir, at this time I'm not
able to discuss details with you,
but what I can tell you
is that we have good people
working very hard on this case.
MAN: I'm sorry, officer, but
that just sounds like double talk.
WOMAN: We're trying to
protect our children. Level with us.
WOMAN 2: Really, we're giving
you all the information we have.
MAN: You know what I'd like to
see in school? Drug-sniffing dogs.
WOMAN: Yeah. Dogs
and metal detectors
and locker searches
and strip-searches.
WOMAN 2: Our district
has strict policies...
WOMAN: I heard about
this school in Canada,
they arrested one of the
groundskeepers with drugs,
and the next day they
found out [♪♪♪]
over half the students
were high on LSD.
WOMAN 3: LSD? When were
you gonna tell us about the LSD?
WOMAN 2 [ECHOING]: No, please.
No one said anything about LSD.
MAN: What about the
equipment that's stolen?
WOMAN 2: The
equipment was taken from
our chemistry-department locker.
And tonight we're lucky
to have someone here
to give us some specifics.
Walt? [GASPS]
Yeah.
Mr. White is currently
on medical leave.
But as he's chair of
the science department,
he's made a very special
effort to be with us here.
And I'd like to take a
moment to thank him for that.
Could you please
tell us more about
the equipment that was taken?
Please. WALT: Yes.
Sorry.
And thank you.
[CLEARS THROAT]
The inventory list for the
missing labware is as follows:
One 5000 milliliter
round-bottom boiling flask.
One Kjeldahl-style
recovery flask, 800 milliliters.
Two full-face respirators.
Some CEP funnels, some
head with a thermometer holder.
[GROANING]
Ooh. Ow.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Where did that come from?
And why was it so damn good?
Because it was illegal.
[♪♪♪]
[DOOR OPENS]
The basement.
Unfinished, of course.
But just look at all this space.
You gotta think rec
room, media room.
Just imagine all the things
you could do down here.
Now remember, you're buying
for this fantastic neighborhood.
Big lawns and shade trees,
walking distance
to the country club.
[SQUISHING]
What happened there?
Bit of a fixer, but this
house has great bones.
WOMAN: Know
what? We're zeroing in.
I've got another listing,
brand new, around the corner.
Yeah? Yeah.
Hi. Hi.
It's by appointment only.
Oh, well, I'm here
to see the owner.
Oh.
He's in the, uh,
recreational vehicle. Ah.
[ENGINE STARTS]
Yo, it's appointment only.
How are you feeling?
About as good as you look.
Jeez, you look like Lex Luthor.
Listen, I visited
you in the hospital,
but you were asleep.
Yeah, Skinny Pete said
you wanted Tuco's address.
Acting like you're
all out for blood.
But you are alive.
Obviously you wised up.
No, I did go see him. Bullshit.
So, what, are you
selling your house?
I got two dudes that turned into
raspberry slushy and
flushed down my toilet.
I can't even take a
proper dump in there.
I mean, the whole damn house
has gotta be haunted by now.
You didn't actually go see Tuco.
Here.
That is 17,500. Your
half of the 35,000.
Plus, there's an
extra 15 in there.
It's all yours.
You've earned it.
You got this money
from Tuco? Yeah.
So Tuco gave you this,
is what you're saying.
Well, we made a deal.
You made a deal? That's right.
How...? Why would you
make a deal with that scumbag?
You see what he did
to me? Because I think
that we can do
business together.
We came to an understanding.
No way, man. Okay?
No understanding.
Take a look at the
money in your hand.
Now, just imagine
making that every week.
That's right. Two pounds
a week, 35,000 a pound.
Without even talking to me
you told this insane ass-clown,
dead-eyed killer that, uh...
That we would give
him 2 pounds a week.
We'll just scale
up our operation,
add a few more hours.
No, don't talk to
me about hours.
What about pseudo, man?
How are we gonna get that?
You think the meth fairy's
just gonna bring it to us?
God, it takes me a
week to get this stuff.
I'm driving all the
way to Las Cruces,
200 miles each way to
meet up with my smurfs.
Smurfs?
The dudes who
go to the drugstores
and get a couple boxes at a
time and then sell them to me.
That's maybe only good for,
like, maybe a half-pound worth.
See, that's the bottleneck in
your brilliant business plan.
All right. Of course,
you would've known that
if you would've just asked me.
MAN: Well, here we are again.
Here we are.
Skyler, you look
great. Thank you.
You must be, what,
six, seven months?
How goes it? It's great.
Other than waddling to the
bathroom every five minutes.
The baby shower is next week.
And it'll be good to...
It'll be good to have a
day that's just about Skyler.
Very nice.
Thank you. Thank you.
Walt, I see you
committed to the hair loss.
Mm. Yeah.
How do you feel? Uh, okay.
I... You know, pretty
decent, actually.
His color is better.
You know, his energy.
And, uh, he's even
more, um, physical.
More physical?
Uh, well,
sexual.
Frisky, actually.
[LAUGHS]
I mean, that's gotta
be a good sign, right?
Sure, I'll take
that. Right, Walt?
Right.
Couldn't that mean that
the chemo is working?
Well, realistically, it
may just mean that
we've got the
antiemetics tuned right.
Truth is, until Walt's
finished this round of chemo,
and we look at a new PET
scan, we just can't say for sure.
Well, isn't there anything
else we could be doing?
I've been wondering
about alternative medicine.
I mean, Eastern healing.
You know, holistic.
Well, I can't speak
to its efficacy,
but as long as it doesn't
interfere with our treatment,
anything that helps my
patient have a better outlook,
a better comfort, is fine by me.
So you're saying it's
just all psychological.
It doesn't make
any real difference.
Having a better outlook
can make a
tremendous difference.
But it's also important that
we manage our expectations.
[♪♪♪]
What?
A junkyard? Let me
guess, you, uh...?
You picked this place?
What's wrong
with it? It's private.
This is like a non-criminal's
idea of a drug meet.
This is, "Oh, I saw this in
a movie. Ooh. Look at me."
Yes. So where do you transact
your business? Enlighten me.
I don't know, how
about Taco Cabeza?
Half the deals I've ever done
went down at Taco Cabeza.
Nice and public.
Open 24 hours.
Nobody ever gets
shot at Taco Cabeza.
Hell, why not the mall?
You know, wait at the Gap.
"Hey, it's time for the meet."
You know, I'll put down
the flat-front khakis,
head on over, grab
an Orange Julius.
Skip the part where
psycho-lunatic Tuco, you know,
comes and steals my drugs
and leaves me bleeding to death.
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
Look, you don't have
to be here for this.
Okay? I mean, seriously.
I'm okay.
[RAP MUSIC PLAYS OVER STEREO]
No. I'm no pussy.
I'm good.
[CRACKS KNUCKLES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
Mr. Clean and his boy.
Now, I'm sorry that
I had to tune you up.
Respect, ése, you
gotta give it to get it.
Hey, what are we doing
way the hell out here?
What, they close the
mall or something?
Heisenberg, come
on, break it out.
That's it? That's all you got?
We had some production problems.
[SCALE BEEPS] 0.53.
[SIGHS]
I thought you was a player.
You told me 2 pounds,
and now you waste my
time with these Chiclets?
Seventeen and a half.
Minus the half for
wasting my time.
WALT: Hey, come on.
What, you gonna argue?
You got something to say?
You're doing business
like a couple little bitches.
I want all of it.
Seventy grand.
What did you say?
You like this product.
And you want more.
Consider it a
capital investment.
Look, old, bald motherfucker.
Fifty-two and a
half, 25 points vig.
Vig?
Interest, weekly.
Okay.
That's $65,625 with interest.
1.875 pounds.
No, 2 pounds.
Next Friday, and no
production problems.
Can you handle 4 pounds?
Listen, old man, talk is talk.
But owing me money, that's bad.
What did you just do?
Four pounds. Four pounds.
Two pounds wasn't bad enough.
We're talking 2, 300
boxes of sinus pills.
There ain't that many
smurfs in the world.
We're not gonna
need pseudoephedrine.
We're gonna make
phenylacetone in a tube furnace.
We're gonna use
reductive amination
to yield methamphetamine,
4 pounds.
So no pseudo? No pseudo.
So you do have a plan.
Yeah, Mr. White.
Yeah, science.
Okay.
What's this?
That is a shopping list.
Getting some of those
items may be challenging.
One autotransformer,
6 liters anhydrous methenamine.
Two 35 M and M tube furnaces.
It's mm, millimeter.
One 70 millimeter would be
fine, but they're hard to come by.
Forty grams thorium nitrate.
Yo, Mr. White, I can't even
pronounce half this shit.
No. Count me out. All right?
I'm leaving town. I'm moving
to, like, Oregon or something.
This is just...
Jesse, Jesse, Jesse.
Listen to me.
Today is the first day
of the rest of your life.
What are you doing?
The first day of
the rest of your life.
But what kind of
life will it be? Huh?
Will it be a life of fear,
of "Oh, no, no,
no. I can't do this."
Of never once
believing in yourself?
Hm?
I don't know. Listen.
These things? We
need them, all right?
And only you can
get them for us.
[SIGHS]
WALT JR.: Okay, it's
ready. Here you go.
Hi, baby. I'm your Aunt Marie.
Of course you already know
that because when you watch this,
20 years from now, I will look
exactly the same as I do now.
I know, it is amazing.
I have aged shockingly
well. Haven't I?
Anyway, welcome to your
baby shower, Esmeralda.
Esmeralda? Esmeralda.
That's your name and
you heard it here first.
Now, that is your wonderful,
handsome older brother.
Show her, older
brother, your face.
Okay, not right up
the nose. Don't...
Okay, not up it.
Back. Back to me.
Here's your mommy. Hello, Mom.
And look, there
you are, Esmeralda.
Wake up, baby. Time to party.
Easy, easy. Believe it or not,
Esmeralda, right
after the party,
your name was changed to Holly.
And I believe, Hank,
that was around the time
that we took Aunt Marie
to the insane asylum.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I
dropped her off at the curb.
Then I married Shania Twain
and lived happily ever after.
[LAUGHS]
There's Daddy. Speak, Daddy.
Say hello to your daughter.
Oh, uh...
Holly, I am very proud of you.
And I... I think about
you all the time.
ALL: Aww.
Wherever you go,
whatever you do in life,
always know that
you have a family
who loves you very, very much.
Cheers. Cheers.
SKYLER: Oh, my God, it's
so cute. Oh, Carmen. It's...
Oh, look. Look at
that. It's adorable.
I love it, Carmen. Thank you.
You're so welcome, honey.
SKYLER: Thank you.
Look at the little feet.
Okay. From me. And Hank.
Oh, what nice wrapping paper.
Marie always finds the
best wrapping paper.
I do. Okay.
Let's see. And...
Exciting.
Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy.
It's... It's a... A tiara.
Yes. Oh!
Marie, is this...?
White gold and several
carats worth of zircons.
Oh, Marie. You spent
too much on this.
You shouldn't have. You
really, really shouldn't.
But it's so...
It's really... It's...
It's sparkly.
[CROWD CHUCKLES]
Sparkly. I know.
SKYLER: Thank
you. Hey, listen, Walt.
You got anything
stronger than beer?
It's... It's great.
I love it. Yeah.
Thank you. Thank
you, sweetie, thank you.
HANK: Sorry, man. It's just,
you know, after 200 presents,
it just gets kind of old.
It's nice stuff.
It is, isn't it?
I got just the thing
to go with that.
I'm sorry, man,
I wasn't thinking.
No, no, no. It's okay.
You mind if I have one?
You think that's a good idea?
Hank, I've already
got lung cancer.
Okay. You got me there.
Thanks.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Cuban.
Hm.
[CHUCKLES]
I did a little favor
for an FBI guy.
Now, I was under the impression
[CLEARS THROAT]
that these were illegal.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, well, sometimes
forbidden fruit
tastes the sweetest, doesn't it?
It's funny, isn't it?
How we draw that line.
Yeah.
What line is that?
Well, what's
legal, what's illegal.
You know, Cuban cigars, alcohol.
You know, if we were
drinking this in 1930,
we'd be breaking the law.
Another year, we'd be okay.
Who knows what
will be legal next year.
You mean like pot?
Yeah. Like pot.
Or whatever.
Cocaine? Heroin?
I'm just saying it's arbitrary.
Well, you ought to visit lockup.
You hear a lot of
guys talking like that.
"Hey, man, what you busting
me with these 14 bales of ganja?
"It's all gonna
be legal next year
when Willie Nelson's president."
Say it, buddy.
It don't only go one way either.
Sometimes there's stuff
that's legal that shouldn't be.
I mean, frigging
meth used to be legal.
Used to sell it
over every counter
at every pharmacy
across America.
Thank God they came to
their senses on that one, huh?
Yeah.
Okay.
Nice party.
Mm.
A tiara.
A white-gold tiara
for a newborn baby.
Yeah. You know,
I think she got that
at Gertrude
Zachary's in Knob Hill.
I mean, that thing must've
cost, like, what, 5 or 600 dollars.
You know, I think
I'm gonna return it.
Are you sure? She's
bound to find out.
Well, maybe I can explain to
her that we need a Diaper Genie
more than a
white-gold baby tiara.
[CHUCKLES]
Hey. You know,
I've been thinking
about what you
said to Dr. Delcavoli
about alternative medicine.
No. Don't worry. I'm not
gonna mention that anymore.
No, no, no. What I mean is that
maybe there is something to it.
Look. They do this Navajo
sweat lodge up by Farmington.
Healing ceremony. It's supposed
to be good for your lungs.
I'm not saying
that I believe in it,
but it might be an experience.
Really.
Mm-hm.
You?
In a sweat lodge.
I was thinking about driving up
on Friday, coming back Sunday.
I mean, if you're okay with it.
Well, of course
I'm okay with that.
Okay.
Sweat lodge? Yeah.
I'm already sweating.
Help me out.
Okay.
Hey.
70 millimeter tube
furnace. Excellent.
This is excellent. Good
work. Damn straight.
Okay, hydrogen.
Electrolytically produced, yes?
Yeah, like you
asked. I mean, this...
This crap wasn't easy
to get. And it's expensive.
Methylamine. Where's
the methylamine?
I don't see the methylamine.
Yeah, well, that's where
I ran into some trouble.
What kind of trouble?
Well, half this crap I
could just buy, right?
But this methylamine...
Not so easy. I mean, they
got it locked down tight.
But I did find some pros
who will rip it off for us.
But they want 10 grand.
So, what's the problem?
You have the money.
No, had. I spent
almost the whole wad.
I mean, I got,
like, 2 grand left.
I told you, all this
crap was expensive.
So these thieves,
did they say where
they would be stealing it from?
A chemical supply
place, south of town.
They got guards and security
cameras. They got steel doors.
That's why these dudes
are charging so much.
What?
[♪♪♪]
Hm.
[RATTLING]
So why don't we
just steal it ourselves?
Yeah?
How we gonna do that?
With this.
So, what's this
stuff called again?
Thermite.
And that will cut
through a lock?
Because this is supposed
to be one big-ass lock.
In World War II,
the Germans had
an artillery piece...
It's the biggest in the world.
Called the Gustav Gun.
And it weighed a thousand tons.
And the Gustav was
capable of firing a 7-ton shell
and hitting a target,
accurately, 23 miles away.
I mean, you could drop bombs
on it every day for a month,
without ever disabling it.
But
drop a commando,
one man, with
just a bag of this,
and he could melt right
through 4 inches of solid steel
and destroy that gun forever.
Jeez.
[COUGHS]
So yes,
I think it will cut through
any lock we're likely to find.
MAN: You'd like to return this.
SKYLER: It's very nice, but yes.
Well, it... It is from
the store, isn't it?
Oh, yes, it's from this store.
Do you happen to have a receipt?
No, I don't. It was a gift.
A-ha. A gift. Mm-hm.
Mr. Wilson, could you
step over here, please?
Mr. Wilson, I'd like
you to watch this lady
while I phone the police.
Whoa, excuse me?
Ma'am, this item is stolen,
as I'm sure you know.
It... Come with me, please.
Oh, yes. I intend
to press charges.
Please do.
We'll be here.
Look, I... I've never
stolen anything in my life.
All right? I told you,
that tiara was a gift...
A baby-shower gift. So
who gave it to you, then?
[SIGHS]
I don't think I have
to tell you that.
Ma'am, you don't
have to tell me anything.
You can talk to the police.
I can tell them my
daughter-in-law remembers
showing this particular
item to a tall blond woman,
who, when her back was turned,
walked right out
the door with it.
So there. Oh, yeah?
Well, then, I can talk to
the Channel Three News.
Yeah, I can tell them how
you people, without a shred...
Without a modicum of
evidence, illegally detained
an innocent pregnant
woman in a dank storeroom.
This is my office. I feel
I'm being held hostage.
Furthermore, I'm not
getting enough air back here.
I don't think... I don't
think I can breathe.
Oh, my... Oh, my God. Oh, no.
I'm going into labor. Yes, I...
[GROANING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[OVER PHONE]: Hi, you've
reached Marie. Do the beep thing.
Marie, it's Skyler. I
just left Zachary's.
I need to talk to
you immediately.
WALT: Where is the guard?
He's supposed to be coming by.
Do you think he already passed?
JESSE: Look, I
don't... I don't know.
Okay. Wait, there
he is. There he is.
Yeah, I see him.
Wait... Wait till he passes.
Okay, it's clear.
Here.
What the hell is
this? It's all they had.
Then you go to another store.
If this is all they had,
you're in the wrong place.
Just put it on.
Should've... Of course.
[METAL SNAPPING]
Okay, okay.
Okay. This is it.
Oh, God.
Okay.
Oh!
Get... WALT: What?
Look. What?
Hey, Jimmy, I'm stopping...
WALT: He's not supposed to
come back. What's he doing?
Oh, my God.
MAN [OVER RADIO]: Hope
everything comes out all right.
He's going to the
crapper. Oh, God.
Okay. You coming, man?
Come on. What are you doing?
Okay, there it is.
Is this gonna be loud?
You'll find out in
about 10 seconds.
Stand back.
Jesus.
[ALARM BLARING]
Come on, come on.
[DOOR RATTLING]
Hey, what's going on?
[♪♪♪]
Where are the
gallon jugs? I don't...
God! What?
Let's just take this.
Come on, come on.
What the...?
Damn it.
What are you doing
opening the door?
How are we gonna
take this thing out?
Come on. Take that.
Lift.
God. Jeez.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Hey. Somebody?
MAN: Billy, you back
from the crapper yet?
Let me out of here. I'm
gonna kick somebody's ass.
The alarm's going
off. Check it out.
Billy? [BOTH GRUNTING]
Billy? Jimmy?
Help!
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
JESSE: Come on, let me try.
How is it gonna
be any different?
Can I just try it?
Fine, go ahead.
Jesus. Okay.
All right.
[SPUTTERING]
[ENGINE TURNS OVER]
Yeah, baby. See? Eat
it. Okay, I'm the king.
Yeah, okay. I'm the king.
[ENGINE FIZZLES]
Oh, no.
No, no. That didn't sound good.
Oh, God.
Well, this thing's
not going anywhere.
We're not cooking in my
damn driveway, I'll tell you that.
WALT: God.
What part of "slow it down"
did you not understand?
What are you talking...? I'm...
It's heavy, man. It
got away from me.
Okay. All right. Now,
that's good, that's good.
Now just bring
it up, bring it up.
Easy, easy, easy. Okay.
Your real estate agent, when
is she supposed to come back?
Oh, shit.
Yeah. I don't know.
I'll make damn sure she doesn't.
[DIALING PHONE]
Good call, yo.
[PHONE RINGING]
WALT: Keep the temperature
steady at 425 degrees.
We'll need to run
it two more hours
to have enough to
make 4.5 pounds.
Four and a half, not 4?
Two pounds pays, two go back.
Four and a half pounds
puts us $44,000 ahead.
Each. Right on, man.
[BANGS TABLE] Right on.
With the amount of
methylamine that we got last night,
we can make 4.5
pounds a week for,
well, for the
foreseeable future.
How long is, uh, that gonna be?
I mean, in your, uh, situation.
How much cash do you need?
[SIGHS]
More.
[MURMURING]
[GASPS] [MURMURING]
Someone's in the yard.
Sh.
MAN: Yeah, this
is definitely the one.
WOMAN: It's pretty.
Actually, I like it.
We could pull that
out and put in a closet.
Just a little... We'll
have to bring that down.
MAN: I thought you
didn't like that type of thing.
Oh, no. No, I don't.
Right, right.
[SHUSHING]
Was there, by any chance,
scheduled for this
afternoon, an open house?
I left her a message.
It's not my fault.
I don't care how you do it,
just keep them out of
here. Do you understand?
Yeah. All right, go.
[MUSIC PLAYS OVER STEREO]
WOMAN: Absolutely.
You know, you can't
duck me forever.
What?
Come on, I left you,
like, 15 messages.
When I went to your office,
you snuck out the back.
I didn't sneak. I
was going to lunch.
Skyler, what are you,
the paranoid police?
You know what, Marie?
Marie, I have never been
so humiliated in my life.
That...
[CLEARS THROAT]
That tiara.
They accused me, at
Zachary's, of shoplifting it.
What were you
doing at Zachary's?
[SIGHS]
I was returning it.
You were returning it.
Why would you return it?
It just wasn't...
Marie, what is wrong with you?
Can you please tell me that?
Can you tell me why
you'd do such a thing?
What does that mean? Does
that mean you don't know?
That means that I have no idea
what the hell you're
even talking about.
You have no idea
what I'm talking about.
The shop...
The shoplifting. No idea?
You're not going to
admit this, are you?
I can't really
admit to something
when I have no knowledge
of what it is that I'm admitting.
[SIGHS]
MAN: Would you
like that gift-wrapped?
WOMAN; Yes, actually.
Don't forget to sign in.
[SNIFFING]
Thank you. Thank you.
You're right.
Look at this wall here.
[KNOCKS]
MAN: Excuse me, I'd just
like to see the basement.
Yeah, well, it's occupied.
It's not a bathroom.
Hey!
I just wanna see the basement.
What's the big deal?
Yo, you ain't seeing
the basement, bitch.
You got that? Is that
sinking in? Now, beat it.
All you all, house
is not for sale.
Get the hell out.
[SIGHS]
Hey. Hey.
So how was it?
Was it, uh, an experience?
Yeah.
It was definitely an experience.
What's that smell?
Oh, yeah, it's
sacred Navajo herbs.
You know.
[GROANS]
[EXASPERATED SIGH]
Hey, everything okay?
No.
Not really.
Huh.
Actually, not at all.
[SIGHS]
You know that, uh,
tiara that Marie gave us?
Yeah. Well, she stole it. Yep.
I practically got arrested
trying to return
it at the store.
Oh, my God.
I mean, she refuses to admit
it. She refuses to apologize.
I don't know what to do.
Hm.
People sometimes do
things for their families.
things for their families?
And what, that
justifies stealing?
Well...
Wow. That must've
been some sweat lodge.
Are you even listening to the
words coming out of your mouth?
What would you do if it were me?
What do you
mean, if it were you?
If it were me, what would you
do? Would you divorce me?
Would you turn
me in to the police?
You don't want to find out.
[SIGHS]
You want something to eat?
Um, no, thanks.
What is this shit? This is blue.
We used a different
chemical process,
but it is every bit as pure.
It may be blue,
but it's the bomb.
Tight, tight, tight, yeah.
Blue, yellow, pink.
Whatever, man.
Just keep bringing me that.
[GROANS]
4.6.
Come on.
And what'd I say,
man? This guy can cook.
You're all right,
man. You're all right.
We're gonna make a
lot of money together.
Just remember who
you're working for.
What did you say?
I'm just saying, they gotta
know that they're working for you.
Like they don't
already know that?
Are you saying
that they're stupid?
No, I'm just... I'm just saying.
Okay, so you're not
saying that they're stupid.
So I don't understand. Are
you saying that I'm stupid?
No, come on, Tuco.
I'm just... I'm just saying.
No, you're just speaking for me!
Like I ain't got the goddamn
sense to speak for myself!
Is that it? Is that
what you're doing?
Tuco.
Hey, why don't we
all just relax, huh?
[LAUGHING]
Heisenberg says "relax."
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
I'm relaxed. I'm relaxed.
I'm relax...
Whoo!
Damn, man! Look at that! Look!
Whoo.
That is messed up.
Okay, Heisenberg.
Next week.
[LAUGHS]
[GNARLS BARKLEY'S "WHO'S
GONNA SAVE MY SOUL?" PLAYING]
♪ Got some bad
news This morning ♪
♪ Which in turn made my day ♪
♪ When there's someone
spoke I listened ♪
♪ All of a sudden Has
less and less to say ♪
♪ Oh, how could this be? ♪
♪ All this time I've
lived vicariously ♪
♪ Who's gonna
Save my soul now? ♪
♪ Oh, I know I'm
out of control now ♪
♪ Tired enough to
lay My soul down ♪