HANK: Operation Icebreaker.
How we liking that? We
never used that before, did we?
Isn't that the name
of a breath mint?
What? Ice Breakers, right?
Breath mint? HANK:
Nobody's gonna think that.
Gonna be thinking
about some ship
in the North Pole breaking ice.
Says you. I'm gonna be
thinking Operation Breath Mint.
I'm thinking
Operation Breath Mint
every time you and me
are on a stakeout together.
Your breath can knock a
buzzard off a shit wagon.
All right, Operation TBD.
Thanks for nothing, Gom.
Anyway, say hello to
Domingo Gallardo Molina.
A.k.a. Krazy-8. Way smarter
than your average cheese eater.
I turned him out
when he was street,
but this dude's
like The Jeffersons,
moving on up.
Every dealer he'd throw at us,
he'd end up snaking
their customers.
HANK: Now it turns
out he's missing,
presumed dead.
Found his car
out in the boonies.
Last guy he ratted out was
none other than his cousin,
Emilio Koyama.
You thinking the cousin
found out and took revenge?
HANK: Could be, turns
out he's missing too.
And normally I'd say
someone did the world a favor.
But our snitch's car, turns out
we find two grams of meth in it,
we take it to the
lab, they come back,
they tell us it is the
purest they've ever seen.
Ninety-nine-point-one
percent. [WHISTLES]
Our chemist is blown away.
Said he couldn't do better.
Worse yet, it didn't come out
of some super lab in Mexico,
we're thinking this was cooked
here in the Land of Enchantment.
Car was abandoned at what
appears to be a cook site.
This is the, uh, only
other thing left behind.
We're sending
it off to Quantico,
see if they can
pull something off it.
Meantime, our guys
swabbed the filter element
and found the same 99.1 meth.
So be on notice.
We got new players in town.
Now, we don't know who they
are, or where they come from,
but they possess an
extremely high skill set.
Me, personally,
I'm thinking Albuquerque
just might have a new kingpin.
[SPITS]
[♪♪♪]
[HISSING]
Jesus, Walt, you're
burning the shit out of 'em.
Oh. Damn it.
Hey, Sky, you got
any more chicken?
Emeril, here, is gonna
need a fresh pack.
Bam.
HANK: All right, looking good.
Is this low-fat mayonnaise
in the coleslaw?
Uh, I... I don't know,
it's store-bought.
Okay, uh, Hank,
you need another beer?
Does the pope shit in his hat?
Yeah, I don't think
that he does, Hank,
and I think
everybody would like it
if you'd stop saying that.
Marie, some more wine, maybe?
I'm all right, thanks.
All right. Hey, I want a beer.
Yeah, I want Shania
Twain to give me a tuggy.
Guess what. It ain't
happening either.
How about some more soda, hm?
Yeah, sure.
Honey, do you need anything?
Mm-mm. No, Walt, thank you.
Okay. Be right back.
[♪♪♪]
WALT JR.: No.
What, are you kidding me?
You look like a damn
movie star, man.
Girls gotta be lining
up left and right.
Tell him how good-looking he is.
He's adorable.
He doesn't wanna be fricking
adorable, he wants to be hot.
See what I'm talking about?
That's female perspective.
She's supposed to say that.
HANK: Look, a guy
doesn't gotta look like, uh,
you know, Charlton Heston...
I'm talking Moses days.
To get a girl, all right?
You just gotta have confidence.
Confidence and,
uh... And persistence.
Okay? That's what
I'm talking about.
I chased your aunt Marie,
here, all over creation.
I kept bugging her for a
date, she kept saying no.
What, I asked
you, like, 50 times?
Yeah, it was before they
tightened the stalking laws.
[CHUCKLES SARCASTICALLY]
Anyway, how about your dad
here? That there's a good story, Walt.
Tell him how you
met Skyler. Uh-huh.
WALT JR.: Mom was a waitress
in Los Alamos and Dad
said that thing to you.
Well, actually, your
mother wasn't a waitress,
it was a summer job, and,
um, she was the hostess
and she also worked
the cash register.
And I used to go in there a lot
because it was close
enough to the lab
where I could ride my bicycle.
And once I noticed her,
it got to be so that
I would only go in
when I knew she was working.
When it was slow, she
would lean against the counter,
doing her crossword puzzles,
uh, but kind of hiding it.
Right? Pretending that
she was still working,
and once I caught on to that,
I would do crossword puzzles
while I ate my
grilled-cheese sandwich.
It got so that every day at
lunch, we would both be doing
The New York Times
crossword puzzle
10 feet from each other.
And, uh... Heh-heh.
Eventually, I caught
her looking over at me,
so I began saying:
"Excuse me, um, 14 across,
"seven-letter word
for whatchamacallit,
"uh, may I ask what...?
What you wrote down?"
And, uh, well,
that got us talking,
and, uh, boy, I
tell you, I was...
I was terrible at those puzzles.
[CHUCKLES]
I don't think that I
finished even one of them.
But your mother
would do them in ink.
HANK: Very smooth.
[CHUCKLES]
I bet you didn't think your
old man had it in him, huh?
But that's what
I'm talking about,
that's persistence, you see?
Once you set your
cap for something
or somebody, you
gotta just, you know...
[SOBBING]
Whoa. Skyler.
Mom, a-are you all right?
MARIE: Hey, hey.
Shh. Honey, it's okay.
What's the matter?
[SOBBING]
MARIE: What is it?
[SNIFFLES]
Ask him.
[DOOR OPENS]
What's she talking about?
Walt?
Um...
I have cancer.
Lung cancer.
It's bad.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
SKYLER: Ask him
how long he's known.
I guess a month, maybe.
Oh, for God sakes, Walt.
We're just sitting out
there having a cookout
like nothing's going on.
He made me promise
not to tell anybody.
Christ, these last 48 hours.
And it's the weekend,
so I couldn't even get
his doctor on the phone.
Buddy, why...? I mean, why
wouldn't you wanna tell anybody?
SKYLER: Walt, don't you see
everybody just
wants to help you.
We're family. We get
through these things together.
HANK: And I don't get,
you know, lung cancer?
How can that happen?
You don't even smoke.
You know, I'm thinking that
this goes back 20 years, maybe,
to the applications lab,
all those chemicals they
had you working around.
We... We always took
the proper precautions.
One time you complained
that they didn't give you
the right kind of,
um, I don't know,
some kind of ventilation hood
or something, and... And...
And then the headaches.
Honey, it wasn't that.
How do they think they
can get away with this?
We should hire a lawyer.
Okay, so first
let's deal with this.
Okay, so, what's the
next step for Walt?
Certainly a second
opinion, right?
Right. Right, absolutely.
MARIE: Okay, so first thing
tomorrow, I talk to my radiologists,
we find you the best,
the oncology dream team.
That's good. That's good.
[CHUCKLES, SNIFFLES]
Yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah, okay. Okay.
Yeah.
[SNIFFLES]
I'm gonna go check on Walt Jr.
I, um... I'm gonna see
if I can talk him into, I
don't know, joining us.
I really didn't mean for
him to find out that way.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Walt, uh...
whatever happens...
I hope this goes without saying,
but, um, whatever happens,
I want you to know that, um,
I'll always take
care of your family.
[MOUTHING WORDS]
[THE PACK'S "FLY" PLAYING]
[TOILET FLUSHES]
♪ Fly ♪
♪ So high, yeah ♪
[MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
JESSE: Yo, check out
these, uh, fake Pop-Tarts.
These are mad tight,
yo. No, thanks, man, pass.
Your loss. These are from, like,
Canada, or something. Imported.
Hey, yo, what happened
to your hallway, man?
Did, like, the ceiling
fall down, or...?
Oh, yeah, uh, no, man,
I think the house
is just settling.
You know, it's been
caving in left and right.
Hit me in the eye. Heh-heh.
It's bananas.
Yo, my pops could fix you up,
he's, like, a contractor
or something.
Yeah? Yeah, right on, I
should grab that number.
Say, Jesse, you still
cook a little crystal?
Uh, could be, yeah. You
know, from time to time.
I heard you lost your partner.
Emilio.
Didn't he get locked
up? No, man, uh, he's out.
His cousin bailed him out.
I think he skipped
town or something.
I don't know about any
of that, I've just been
kind of doing my own
thing these days, so...
But you maybe got
some crystal, man?
'Cause I could seriously go
for a bowl right now, you know,
take the edge off.
Hell, yeah, Sunday
night bowl, yo.
All right.
Well, uh, maybe it just
so happens that, uh,
I just recently cooked
the best batch ever.
Yeah?
Oh, yeah. Came up with
this whole new recipe.
It's more like a formula.
It's, like, way, way
more chemically...
Shit, you know, it's...
It's just the bomb, so...
But, you know, I don't
know, I've been thinking lately
I'll just lay off
of it for a while,
'cause lately it's been kind
of making me paranoid, so...
You know, for, like,
health-wise, just lay off.
Yo, if you're, uh,
not into sharing, man,
just tell us to
piss off, it's cool.
We don't need no soap opera.
Yeah, man, whatever.
No, no, it's all good, you know.
I-I'm just saying, uh, hey,
I got... I got plenty of pot.
Yeah, I think I'll bounce, man.
Yeah, sounds about right.
Hey, yo, yo. Hey,
homes, I'm joking.
Okay, I'm totally
joking with you.
You kidding? Sit down.
Best scante ever.
Grab that pipe.
[CHUCKLES]
[CLEARS THROAT]
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪]
[BANGING ON DOOR]
[BELL RINGS]
[GASPS]
[♪♪♪]
[GASPING]
[GROANS]
Okay, there.
[SIGHS]
Shit.
[COUGHING]
SKYLER: Walt, do
you need some help?
[DOOR HANDLE RATTLES]
Oh, no, I'm... I'm fine, honey.
I'm fine. Just, uh, privacy.
Thanks.
[COUGHING]
SKYLER: I'm right
outside if you need me.
Okay.
[COUGHING]
Yeah, any time on
Friday is absolutely fine.
Thank you so much
for working us in.
Uh, can I just put
that on a credit card?
Great. Perfect.
Okay, so we will see you
at 10:45 on Friday morning.
Thank you so much.
Okay.
Oh, yes.
Honey, the best oncologist,
I mean, not even
just in New Mexico,
but one of the top
10 in the entire nation,
his name is, um, Dr. Delcavoli
and we see him on Friday.
[SKYLER SIGHS]
Ah.
I mean, Marie really
came through for us.
She had her boss call, and...
[SIGHS]
Okay, this is good.
From here on out, I
mean, things are gonna...
What's...? What's that
we're putting on a credit card?
Uh, it's just a
deposit kind of thing.
How much of a deposit?
It's $5000.
Five thousand?
Jesus.
What's that, just to start?
I mean, just to tell me
what I already know?
Walt, he's not in our HMO, okay?
So be it, we'll figure it out.
Come on, don't get
hung up on money here.
We can always borrow from Hank.
Absolutely not.
No, I just...
We're not gonna do that.
[SKYLER SIGHS]
Well, maybe we can ask your mom.
Have you even called her yet?
Walt, regardless, you're
gonna have to tell her about this.
I'm willing to do it,
but I... I'll call. I'll call.
Okay, look,
I don't even want us
thinking about money.
Money is not the issue here.
It's not. I know. I know.
It's not.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
I'll take care of the deposit.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I'll, uh...
I'll borrow it from my pension.
[DUCT CLANGS]
Oh, damn it!
Hey. Heh-heh.
Hey, pal, what's up?
Oh, uh, yeah, no, I
thought I heard mice.
Heh. Boy, that's...
That's all we need, huh?
[GRUNTS]
So, what's up, pal?
What the hell's wrong with you?
What?
You're... You're acting all...
You're... You...
You're all... W-why
are you acting so weird?
Son. You're...
You're acting like
nothing is going on.
[SCOFFS]
[SIGHS]
[SIREN WAILING DISTANTLY]
[WHISPERS] Oh, no,
please. Please, please, no.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[LAUGHS, COUGHS]
[SAY ANYTHING'S "BABY
GIRL, I'M A BLUR" PLAYING]
Hey, no, hey! [HORN HONKING]
Hey! Put that douche
bag on the phone.
WALT: Oh, come on.
Hey, am I...? Am I gonna
have to come down there
and whup your ass?
[MOUTHING WORDS]
And let me tell
you something else,
I'm not doing this
for charity, right?
I'm the best he's got.
He knows it, I know it
I expect to be paid to a
level commensurate with...
I said, "Dave, do you think
40 grand is a proper bonus?"
That's less than 10 percent
of what I booked this quarter.
I'm not gonna sit here
and be disrespect...
Oh, he's shitting bricks.
Oh, you know he is.
Yeah, that man lives in
fear. I'll go across town...
Hell, I could go anywhere.
Hoffman, Gordon
Bradley, or Sorcher.
Even Goldberg-Wayne.
They'd make me a partner
just for walking
in the damn door
that's how ecstatic they'd be.
WOMAN: Next customer.
[HIGH-PITCHED]
Hells, yes, brother man.
Dude, you should
check this chick out.
Who? No. Buddy, she's a cow.
Stacey's a cow.
We're talking major
barnyard boo-hog.
Roll her in flour and
look for the wet spot
before you hit that, man,
you know what I'm saying?
That kind of stink
does not wash off.
Sir?
MAN: Ha-ha-ha. Right.
Sir.
MAN: Oh, yeah?
Sorry. Hi. MAN:
Yeah. Oh, totally.
Hi. What can I do for you today?
MAN: Which dude?
Dude that looks like a
lizard? WOMAN: Next in line.
I, um... MAN: He
limps like some leper.
I-I'm sorry, I-I would like...
MAN: Grosses me out.
A cashier's check
in the full amount,
made out to Oncology
Partners of New Mexico, please.
Oh, that's O-N-C-O-L-O-G-Y.
Yeah, you got it.
MAN: I don't understand why
they're forcing you to choose
between piccolo and oboe.
You show so much
promise with both.
They can't have any
switching between woodwinds.
No matter how they divide it
up, someone would be left out.
Rules are rules, I guess.
MAN: Sure, rules are
rules. I'm all for that.
But I'm telling you, you
really shine on that oboe.
You have real talent,
and I'm not just saying that.
Thanks.
What about Mr. Pemberton?
Is he giving you enough
individual attention?
I'd say so. He tries to
talk to each one of us
at least once during
every practice.
That's good.
Feedback's important.
It's key, I think.
Hey, so how was soccer practice?
[METAL CLANGS]
I think that was
in our backyard.
[CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Who's there?
[SIGHS]
What the hell are
you doing out here?
Hey, Dad.
[CHUCKLES]
Hey, Mom.
Jake.
Got new patio furniture.
Right on.
[GRUNTS]
Hey. Heh-heh. My leg.
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪]
WOMAN: What do
you think it could be?
God knows I'm no expert.
I don't know. Uppers, downers?
Your guess is as good as mine.
I think we should check
his arms for needle marks.
[SIGHS]
Do we let him stay?
The Presbyterian Church
has those meetings.
So maybe on condition, you
know? If he agrees to attend.
I-I just don't know
what to tell Jake.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Hey.
Hey. Good evening.
Well? Sleep well?
What time's, uh...?
What time is dinner?
In about an hour.
You know, I could, uh,
wash those clothes if you like.
They look a little lived in.
Oh, um, no, that's
cool. Yeah, maybe later.
We are not doing this again.
Adam... No.
We said we'd lay down
the law, we lay down the law.
We just have to be
consistent about it.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Hey.
WALT: You're, uh...
You're not taking the bus?
Oh.
All right. Well, listen.
Um, give me maybe
another 20 minutes,
and we'll get out of here.
All right.
Yeah, good.
[COUGHS]
You know, I-I just
think that, uh...
things have a way of
working themselves out.
JESSE: Wow.
When did you, uh...?
When did you get this?
Last May at the
year-end assembly.
They gave me that one
too. The one on the end.
Environmental
Consciousness Award.
What's that mean? What,
you, like, recycle cans and shit?
I contacted The
Albuquerque Journal
and asked what kind of chemicals
they use to bleach their paper.
Wound up writing
an article about it.
Right on, little bro.
Making mad inroads with
the business community.
All right.
Now, hey, remember,
not all learning
comes out of books.
[CHUCKLES]
Look at you. Heh.
You know, we should... We
should hang out more often.
You know, just, uh...
Just kick back and chill.
I mean, if you ever, like, I
don't know, need advice.
Because, you know, I've been...
I've been through
it all. For real.
Yeah, man, you, uh...?
You play the flute?
It's a piccolo, actually.
Dude, play some, uh...
Play some Jethro Tull.
Hey, guys, how we doing in here?
We're, uh... We're good.
Jake?
Yeah. Fine, Mom.
Well, that's good.
That's... That's great.
You know, what the
hell? You see this?
What am I, some
criminal or something?
Whatever.
Whatever?
What, you...? You
think that's okay?
Like, "Oh, we can't
let that scumbag
warp the mind of
our favorite son."
I'm the favorite?
Yeah, right.
You're practically all
they ever talk about.
[♪♪♪]
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, snap.
Awesome.
[CHUCKLES]
[CELL PHONE VIBRATES]
[BEEPS]
[WHISPERS] Yeah?
MAN: Yo, man, it's me.
Hey, listen. You know
that, uh...? That product?
You got any more of that?
No, man, okay? I'm
done giving out freebies.
You want charity, go
ask the Salvation Army.
No, no charity. No.
I got this cousin, he's
got him some rich friends.
These dudes are in town,
they're looking to party.
And your stuff
is, like, so sweet.
So, what do you say?
You up for making
some fat stacks?
'Cause they'll buy
everything you got.
[METAL RATTLING]
[GRUNTS]
Yes. Yes. Okay.
[COUGHS] [DOORBELL RINGS]
Oh, you can't be serious.
What the hell are
you doing here?
Yo, I waited till
the ball buster left.
I mean, no offense.
Who sent you, huh? Huh?
You wearing a wire? Hey. Jesus.
You setting me up?
Homo. A wire? You want a wire?
I got a wire. Speak
into the mike, bitch.
What the hell's wrong with you?
A wire.
Jesus.
So who did you tell about...?
Nobody. What, are you nuts?
Then why are you here?
I don't know.
To, like, touch base.
Touch base?
Yeah, you know, um,
what they call a debrief.
Maybe we could, like...
Thought we could debrief.
Debrief?
Wow, that's...
That's what you think
we need, debrief?
[LAUGHS]
Yeah, a-after what happened,
it just seems like
the thing to do.
Kind of, you
know, talk about it.
I mean, we can't... We
can't talk to anybody else.
Anyway, th-that
and I wanted to, uh...
Wanted to, you know,
tell you how much everybody
digs that meth we cooked.
Everybody digs
the meth we cooked.
Seriously. I got dudes
that would give their left nut
for a little more.
Oh. Great.
I'm just saying, I
mean, if you ever,
you know, saw your way
clear to, um, you know,
you and I cooking
a little more...
Wow.
Get the hell off my property.
What? I'm just saying.
Go. And don't come back.
Now.
All right. All right,
you know what?
Four grand.
Your share from
selling that batch.
That's why I'm here.
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
Hey, I didn't smoke it all.
Non-small-cell adenocarcinoma.
Stage 3A,
which means it's spread from
the lung to the lymph nodes.
There's no denying
it's very serious.
But it... Is it...?
It is...
curable?
I prefer the word "treatable."
But the treatments
we have at our disposal
can be very effective.
Without making any promises,
I can tell you that
the specific course
of radiation and chemotherapy
I'm going to suggest
has been successful.
In certain cases, it's
prolonged a patient's life
and even resulted in remission.
Hmm. Um, w-what
about the side effects?
Well, they can be mild
to practically non-existent.
Or they can be
pretty darn awful.
It varies from
patient to patient.
Typically, there's hair loss,
which begins a couple of weeks
after the start of chemotherapy.
You may find yourself unusually
fatigued, not much energy.
You won't want
to get out of bed.
You may lose weight
due to reduced appetite
and certain intestinal issues.
Muscle aches and pains,
gums will get sore and bleed.
And, uh, of course, there's
the possibility of nausea,
although we'll
prescribe an antiemetic
and try to counteract that.
[FADING] Possible
kidney or bladder irritation.
You may wind up with
increased bruising and bleeding.
There are maybe sexual symptoms.
Your skin may become dry...
[SIGHS]
Got anything to say?
What do you know about that?
Nothing.
Well, that's not
gonna fly this time.
How many chances
have we given you?
How many times
have we sat right here
and had the same conversation
over and over again?
Where you look us in the
eye and you plead ignorance?
And you play on our emotions
and you tell us
anything and everything
you think we wanna hear,
just so we'll give
you another chance.
Mm-hm. And it makes
us feel like fools.
Every time.
Enough, Jesse.
Enough.
[SIGHS]
MAN: We are not going
to have this in our house.
We need you to leave.
[SCOFFS]
Thanks for not telling on me.
Uh, you think I
could have it back?
[LAUGHS]
It's skunk-weed anyway.
[INDISTINCT TV CHATTER]
MAN [ON TV]: The Air Force
is aware of the widely-held belief
that some of these could
be flying saucers from...
You know, this is
actually very hopeful.
Nothing conclusive
in the evidence,
but probing and digesting
of information about UFOs
continues unceasingly.
Did you hear me?
I said this is really
very, very hopeful.
Oh.
Defense Command in Colorado
Springs issued an order...
So can I call them and...?
And tell them you'll
start next week?
Uh...
Even as they did so, the
military wondered whether
their scientific know-how
and their best weapons
would be effective in any battle
of the Earth versus
the flying saucers.
I just think that we
need to discuss it
a little more, that's all.
What is there to discuss?
You're gonna get the best
treatment, and he's the best.
Well, there's the money
discussion. I think...
No, $90,000 out of pocket.
Maybe more. SKYLER:
There's a way, Walt.
There's financing, there's,
um, installment plans.
I-I-I could always
go back to work.
Walt, there's always a way.
All right.
Skyler, say that there is a way.
And we spend all
that money, and...
Am I supposed to leave
you with all that debt?
No.
Honey.
I just don't want
emotions ruling us.
Maybe treatment
isn't the way to go.
WALT JR.: Then
why don't you just
fucking die, already?
[GASPS]
Just give up and die.
[COUGHING]
[COUGHING VIOLENTLY]
[HORN HONKING]
Come on, move your ass.
MAN: Uh, name of
the guy? You'll like him.
Yeah, dude, I'm not worried.
I got the best
fricking attorney.
I would not want to be on
the other side of this one.
He's got this little
team of ninjas, too,
that go out and do
forward operations...
He's got crap on people.
[DARONDO'S "DIDN'T I" PLAYING]
[ALARM BLARING]
MAN: What the hell?
What?
ATTENDANT: Don't
go near it, buddy.
MAN: What...? What are
you doing? Call somebody.
Call the fire people.
ATTENDANT:
Yeah. I have a fire...
MAN: I don't believe this.
Do you know how
much I paid for that?
♪ Didn't I Do the
best I could? ♪
♪ Didn't I? ♪
[SHOUTS]
Why are you doing this?
♪ Didn't I? ♪
♪ I tried my best
Just to be a man ♪
♪ Didn't I? ♪
♪ Didn't I do it, baby? ♪
♪ I tried to bring
the truth To light ♪
♪ It's the mystery to me ♪
♪ That you won't talk to me ♪
♪ What could it...? ♪