[♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[GRUNTING]
Oh, my God. Christ!
Shit.
[DISTANT SIRENS WAILING]
Oh, God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my
God. Think, think, think.
[LIQUID SPLASHING]
Oh, my gosh.
[PANTING, GASPING]
[EXHALES, COUGHS]
Okay. Come on, come on, come on.
Come on.
My name is Walter
Hartwell White.
I live at 308 Negra Arroyo Lane,
Albuquerque, New Mexico, 87104.
To all law-enforcement entities,
this is not an
admission of guilt.
I am speaking to my family now.
Skyler.
You are the love of my life.
I hope you know that.
Walter Jr.
You're my big man.
There are... There are
going to be some things...
Things that you'll
come to learn about me
in the next few days.
I just want you to know that
no matter how it may look
I only had you in my heart.
Goodbye.
[SIRENS APPROACHING]
[♪♪♪]
[COUGHING]
WOMAN [ON TV]: Money
before the panel earlier.
Happy birthday.
Oh.
Look at that.
That is veggie bacon.
Believe it or not.
Zero cholesterol
and you won't even
taste the difference.
Mm.
What time do you
think you'll be home?
Same time.
I don't want him dicking
you around tonight.
You get paid till 5,
you work till 5. No later.
Ah-hah.
Hey.
Hey, happy birthday.
Well, thank you.
You're late again.
There was no hot water again.
I have an easy fix for that.
You wake up early,
and then you get to be the
first person in the shower. Hm.
WALT JR.: I have an idea.
How about buy a
new hot-water heater?
How's that idea? For
the million-billionth time.
[COUGHING]
Did you take your echinacea?
Yeah.
I think it's getting better.
What the hell is this?
Hey. It's veggie bacon.
We're watching our
cholesterol, I guess.
Not me. I want real
bacon. N-not this fake crap.
Too bad. Eat it.
Phew. This smells
like Band-Aids.
Eat it.
[SIGHS]
So how does it feel to be old?
How does it feel
to be a smart-ass?
Heh. Good.
Eat your veggie bacon.
You're all set? Yeah, I'm fine.
All right, see you at
home. Okay, see you.
[BELL RINGS]
Chemistry.
It is the study of what?
Anyone?
Ben.
Chemicals.
No.
Chemistry is...
Well, technically, chemistry
is the study of matter.
But I prefer to see it
as the study of change.
Now, just... Just
think about this.
Electrons.
They
change their energy levels.
Molecules.
Molecules change their bonds.
Elements. They combine
and change into compounds.
Well, that's... That's
all of life, right?
I mean, it's just... It's
the constant, it's the cycle.
It's solution, dissolution,
just over and over and over.
It is growth, then decay,
then transformation.
It is fascinating, really.
[INDISTINCT WHISPERING]
[GIRL GIGGLING]
Chad.
Is there something
wrong with your table?
Okay, ionic bonds.
[CLATTERING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Are you done?
Ionic bonds. Chapter six.
[EASY-LISTENING MUSIC PLAYING]
One, two, three makes
10, and 10 makes 20.
There's your receipt.
Just hand this disc to
your car-wash professional.
Thank you. Come again.
[MAN SPEAKING IN
FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
He's not coming.
He says he quits.
I'm gonna run the register.
Bogdan, no. We
talked about this.
I'm short-handed,
Walter. What am I to do?
Walter?
What am I to do?
[MAN WHISTLING]
[COUGHING]
CHAD: Hey, Mr. White.
Make those tires shine, huh?
Oh, my God.
You will not believe
who's cleaning Chad's car.
Mr. White.
From chemistry.
ALL: Surprise!
Happy birthday, Dad.
Happy birthday. Happy birthday.
Oh, you're so very late.
Really, I'm serious, Skyler.
I mean, you're flat
as a washboard.
Oh. You look awesome.
She's not showing
at all, is she?
She's showing a little.
Carmen, this is
my sister, Marie.
Nice to meet you. Hi.
Glock 22, that's my
daily carry, okay?
I mean, unless you're talking,
what, Plus P Plus loads,
you can forget
the 9 mil, all right?
Shit, I seen one of those
bounce off a windshield one time.
Yeah, with you shooting. Hey.
If you're gonna
bring a gun, baby,
you gotta bring enough gun.
Forty caliber.
Uh...
This is awesome. Nice, isn't it?
Yeah. Dad, come check this out.
Yeah, I see it.
Come on, take it.
Yeah. Check it out, Walt.
Ooh.
No, no, it's just heavy.
HANK: That's why they hire men.
[LAUGHTER]
Hey, it's not gonna bite you.
Looks like Keith Richards with
a glass of warm milk, doesn't he?
[LAUGHTER]
Hey, Walt. Everybody,
listen up, listen up, listen up.
I'm gonna give a toast,
a little toast to my
brother-in-law. Come here.
Walt, you got a brain
the size of Wisconsin
but we're not gonna
hold that against you.
But your heart's in
the right place, man.
Your heart's in the right place.
We love you, man. We love you.
Everybody, to Walt. Nostrovia.
ALL: Nostrovia.
Oh, shit. Turn on channel three.
At which point, we
apprehended three individuals
and placed them in custody.
I'm proud to say the
outstanding professionalism
of my fellow agents at the
Albuquerque District Office
resulted in a substantial
amount of methamphetamine
being taken off the streets.
WOMAN: Were any
shots fired? No, ma'am.
Our agents took the
suspects by surprise.
Damn. The TV does add 10 pounds.
Ten pounds?
Hey, sit and spin, both of you.
Hank. What?
Sorry. You didn't see that.
So charming.
Clearly an ongoing operation.
One which was well-organized...
Hank, how much money is
that? It's about 700 grand.
It was a pretty good haul.
It's a good day for the
citizens of Albuquerque
Wow.
When we can put this big a
dent in the local drug trade.
Well, that's unusual,
isn't it? That kind of cash?
Mm. Well, it's not
the most we ever took.
It's easy money,
till we catch you.
Heh-heh.
Walt, just say the word and
I'll take you on a ride-along.
You can watch us knock
down a meth lab, huh?
Get a little
excitement in your life.
Yeah, someday.
Which one's this?
Um, that faux-Lalique vase I
picked up at the Super-Swap.
Oh.
How's it doing?
Well, I met my reserve
and there's still two minutes.
Mm.
What's up?
You tell me, birthday boy.
Oh, hey, so, what's
up for Saturday?
Mm. Car wash. Bogdan
says he needs me.
Till what time? Noon, 1-ish?
Probably 2, more like it.
And then what after that?
Um, actually,
ahem, I was thinking of
driving up to Los Alamos.
They've got this...
The visitor center
has an exhibit on
that's really supposed to be...
You're not gonna
paint? No, I'll paint.
It's just that this...
You know, this exhibition
on the Mars-rover
photographs are...
I mean, the detail really is
just supposed to be amazing.
It's just that I really need
you to paint at some point.
The sooner that back
bedroom gets finished...
And I'd do it myself, except you
don't want me on the stepladder.
I will paint. Okay.
What is going on
down there? No, it's...
Is he asleep?
No...
No, it's nothing. He's just...
You know. Well, you gotta
be careful about the baby and...
Well, don't worry about
the baby. This is just for you.
We are just doing you tonight.
So just close your eyes,
relax, and let it...
Close your eyes. Oh, okay.
Okay.
There you go.
That's it.
Keep it going.
Keep... Yes! Fifty-six.
[EASY-LISTENING MUSIC PLAYING]
[♪♪♪]
[COUGHS]
[SIRENS WAILING]
This is so embarrassing.
I am fine, honestly.
It's just some bug going around.
First, my wife had it,
then my son, and now me.
It's just... It's just
like a chest cold.
Could be some low
blood sugar as well.
I didn't have the greatest
breakfast this morning.
Honestly, I didn't.
Hey, listen, can you do me
a favor? Can you just, uh,
drop me off at a
corner somewhere?
Uh, no, sorry.
It's just that I don't have
the greatest insurance.
Take a couple of
deep breaths for me.
[COUGHS]
Is there anybody you
want us to contact for you?
[SCOFFS] No. God, no.
Lean forward for me, would you?
Mr. White, are you a smoker?
No, never.
Why do you ask?
[LOW RUMBLING, CLICKING]
[MUFFLED SPEECH]
Mr. White?
Yes?
You understood what
I've just said to you?
Yes.
Lung cancer. Inoperable.
I'm sorry. I just
need to make sure
you fully understand.
Best-case scenario, with chemo,
I'll live maybe
another couple years.
It's just
you've got mustard on your...
Right there. You
got mustard there.
Right there.
So my records
show that I paid it
and I certainly don't feel
that we owe any late...
Yeah, all right.
Well, I'll check with the bank
and maybe the post office
if they lost it or something.
Yeah, let me look
into that. Okay.
Thank you.
Hey.
Um,
did you use the
MasterCard last month?
Uh, fifteen
eighty-eight at Staples?
Um...
Oh, we needed printer paper.
Walt, the MasterCard's
the one we don't use.
Okay.
So how was your day?
Oh, you know.
I don't know. It was, um,
fine.
[EASY-LISTENING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BOGDAN SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[DISTORTED SPEECH]
[COUGHS]
[HIGH-PITCHED BUZZING]
[DISTORTED] Hey, Walter.
Walter.
Walter. Tomorrow
night I'm shorthanded.
I need you outside
to do wipe downs.
Come on. What?
I said I need you outside
to do some wipe downs.
Are you here to work, or
to be staring at the skies?
Come on. Let's go.
Come on, man.
Fuck you, Bogdan.
What?
I said, "fuck you."
And your eyebrows.
[GRUNTING]
Wipe down this!
[♪♪♪]
[BUTTONS BEEPING]
[PHONE RINGING]
HANK: Yo.
Uh, Hank? Hank, it's Walt. Hey.
Oh, listen. I didn't
wake you, did I?
Oh, good, good.
Oh, no, no. Nothing's
wrong. I just...
I've been thinking about that offer
of that ride-along.
HANK: It's the last
house on the right. See it?
Not the two-story
one, the one next to it.
Kind of, uh, I don't know
what do you call that? Um,
green?
Sage.
"Sage?"
Do you work at the
fucking Pottery Barn? Jesus.
Sage. That's the word for it.
My fault the only word your
dumb-ass knows is "green"?
"Cheese-dick." I know
that one. How about that?
Anyway, it's the,
um, sage one. See it?
WALT: So, what tells
you it's a meth lab?
HANK: Just our snitch.
Says some dude who
goes by "Cap'n Cook"
lives up to his name in there.
Says he always adds a
dash of chili powder. Heh-heh.
Ah, you exuberant Mexicans.
Uh-uh. "Cap'n Cook?"
That's a white boy's name.
Dopey as hell too.
Yeah? I'll tell you what.
I got you 20 bucks
that says he's a beaner.
All right. You're on.
All right. Come on,
come on, come on.
[SIGHS]
All right. School bus is
clear. You got the green light.
MAN [ON RADIO]: Copy that.
[ENGINE STARTS]
Watch this. Makes them shit.
[HUMMING WAGNER'S
"RIDE OF THE VALKYRIES"]
Go, go, go, go!
HANK: Meth labs are
nasty on a good day.
You mix that shit wrong
and you got mustard gas.
Phosphine gas.
I think. Yeah, exactly.
One whiff will kill you.
That's why the respirators.
[HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING]
MAN [ON RADIO]: House is
clear. One suspect in custody.
Copy that. The suspect,
might he be of the
Latino persuasion?
Driver's license says
"Emilio Koyama."
Asian. Pay up, sucker.
Hey, hey. First name, Emilio.
That's at least half a beaner.
Tell you what, I'll
let you off for a 10.
Whoa.
Cheer up, Gomey.
You people still
got J. Lo. Hank.
Do you think I might
get to go inside?
See the actual lab?
Uh,
Yeah, I'll tell you what, we're
gonna go peek our heads in
check it out first.
Stay here a minute.
Let's go, Frank.
[GASPS]
Oh, God.
[♪♪♪]
Oh, my God.
Pinkman?
Hey. Uh, it's me. I'm alone.
How'd you find me?
You're still in
our filing system.
So your... Your aunt
owns this place, right?
I own it.
Look, no one's looking for you.
Why are you here?
I was curious.
Honestly, I never expected
you to amount to much...
but methamphetamine.
I...
I didn't picture that.
There's a lot of
money in it, huh?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
No? Not a clue.
Cap'n Cook?
That's not you?
Like I said, no one
is looking for you.
Look, I don't know what
you think you're doing here,
Mr. White.
I mean, if you're planning
on giving me some
bull-winder about getting right
with Jesus or turning myself in.
Not really. High school
was a long time ago.
You ain't Welcome Back,
Kotter, so step off. No speeches.
Short speech.
You lost your partner
today. What's-his-name.
Emilio?
Emilio is going to prison.
The DEA took all
your money, your lab.
You've got nothing.
Square one.
But you know the business
and I know the chemistry.
I'm thinking
maybe you and I
could partner up.
[SCOFFS]
You, uh... You wanna
cook crystal meth?
You.
You and, uh... And me.
That's right.
Wow.
Either that,
or I turn you in.
What the hell is this?
SKYLER: Damned if I know.
I described it as
mosaic folk art.
And somebody bought it?
Yeah, some guy in Minneapolis.
Fourteen dollars
plus shipping. Yes.
At this rate, in 50 or
60 years you'll be rich.
So how goes the novel?
It's not a novel,
actually, which I...
You're not writing a novel?
You told me you
were. No. Short stories.
I said that if eventually I
have enough good ones,
that maybe I'll try
and publish another collection.
Those really didn't sell.
I just thought a novel
would be easier to sell.
Yeah, well, maybe so.
Ever want me to read anything,
I could critique it for you.
Oh.
No.
I mean, I'm just not
at that stage where I...
No.
Open offer.
So, what's up with Walt lately?
What do you mean? He's fine.
He just seems
I don't know.
Quieter than usual.
Well, turning 50 is a big deal.
I mean, I'm sure as hell
not looking forward to 40.
You're gonna be a
complete basket-case.
[CHUCKLES]
So it's a mid-life crisis.
No. He's just quiet.
How's the sex?
Marie, Jesus.
I guess that answers that.
[♪♪♪]
You just gonna sit there?
[SIGHS]
Look at this. Look at this.
Kjeldahl-style recovery
flask, 800 milliliters. Very rare.
You got your usual
paraphernalia, Griffin beakers,
there's your Erlenmeyer flask.
But the pièce de résistance
a round bottom boiling
flask, 5000 milliliters.
Huh?
I cook in one of
those. A big one.
One of these?
No, this is an volumetric flask.
You wouldn't cook
in one of these.
Uh, yeah. I do.
Uh, no, you don't.
A volumetric flask is for
general mixing and titration.
You wouldn't apply
heat to a volumetric flask.
That's what a
boiling flask is for.
Did you not learn nothing
from my chemistry class?
No. You flunked me, remember?
No wonder. Prick.
And let me tell you something
else. This ain't chemistry.
Okay, this is art. [SCOFFS]
Cooking is art
and shit I cook is the
bomb, so don't be telling me.
Shit you cook is shit.
I saw your setup. Ridiculous.
You and I will not make garbage.
We will produce a chemically
pure and stable product
that performs as
advertised. No adulterants.
No baby formula.
No chili powder.
No, no. Chili P's my signature.
Not anymore.
Yeah, well, we'll
see about that.
What the hell is this?
Lab safety equipment.
We're also gonna have an
emergency eye wash station.
These chemicals and
their fumes are toxic.
In case you didn't
you know that.
Well, you can dress up like
a faggot if you want. Not me.
Listen, this stuff
doesn't stay more than a day.
What? I thought we
were gonna cook here.
No, we're not gonna cook here.
Okay, this is my house.
I don't shit where I eat.
Well, then where
are we gonna work?
You tell me. This
is your deal, man.
You wanna smoke it up,
smoke it up at your house.
No, I didn't think so. Oh, well.
Well,
what if we rented one of
those self-storage places?
You know, those little orange
garages? Worked out of there?
No, they're onto that. They've
got dogs that sniff around.
RV, that's what you want.
What, like a Winnebago?
Yeah.
I know a dude who
wants to sell his.
He just goes camping with it.
But a mobile meth
lab? That'd be the bomb.
I mean, you can drive
way out in the boonies.
Be all evasive.
[♪♪♪]
Dude, this isn't even
seven grand, all right?
My guy wants 85.
This is all the money
I have in the world.
You're a drug dealer. Negotiate.
[SCOFFS]
Y-you are not how I
remember you from class.
I mean, like, not at all.
Yeah, well, I gotta go.
Wait. Wait. Hold up.
Tell me why you're
doing this. Seriously.
Why do you do it?
Money, mainly.
There you go.
Nah, come on, man.
Some straight like you,
giant stick up his ass
all a sudden at age, what,
60, he's just gonna break bad?
I'm 50. It's weird, is all.
Okay, it doesn't
compute. Listen,
if you've gone
crazy or something,
I mean, if y... If you've
gone crazy, or depressed.
I'm... I'm just saying.
T... That's something
I need to know about.
Okay, I mean, that affects me.
I am awake.
[SCOFFS]
What?
Buy the RV.
We start tomorrow.
SKYLER: How's
it coming in there?
Fine.
Do you want me or your dad?
Dad.
SKYLER: So how are those feeling
in the waist? Are they too tight?
You don't want to get
them if they're too tight.
They're... They're
pretty shrunk.
Are you sure you don't want
the...? Like a different kind?
Like, you know,
the skinny jeans,
because those are in style.
The skaters wear them.
Do I look like a skater?
All right.
[IMITATING WALT JR.] Mom,
get them, my big boy pants.
Mommy, could you zip
up my big boy pants?
[BOYS LAUGHING]
Don't. What?
Don't.
Walt.
[BOYS LAUGHING]
Where...? I have no idea.
No, you know what?
Don't even look at them.
They're obviously
very stupid. Yep.
Yeah.
I think that, um... I think those
jeans look really good on you.
I think you should get
them if you like them, okay?
Why don't you hang out here
for a second. I'll be right back.
Fine.
Hey, Mommy, I
think I pinched a loaf
in my brand new big boy pants.
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
What's wrong, chief?
Having a little trouble walking?
Get off me! Get off me!
I'll mess you up, man.
You'll have one shot.
You'd better make it good.
You waiting for, your
girlfriends? You better go.
You'd better go. Take it.
Take your shot. Take it!
Come on.
Come on. Come on,
let's get out of here.
Let's go.
Psycho.
Yeah, nothing but cows.
Got some big cow house
way out that way, like two miles,
but I don't see nobody.
"Cow house"?
Yeah. Where they live.
The cows.
Whatever, man. Shit,
yeah. Let's cook here.
[COUGHS]
Cow house.
God help me.
Uh, what are you doing?
These are my good clothes.
You can't go home
smelling like a meth lab.
Uh, yeah, you can. I do.
Those?
Wow. Those, uh... You're
keeping those on, right?
[SIGHS]
Come on. Daylight's burning.
Oh, my God.
[CHUCKLING]
Wow, this is... This
is a good look for you.
I mean, you're maybe only the
world's second-biggest homo.
Would you shut up and help me?
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Work it. Baby, work it.
Turn that off.
[WORKING FOR A NUCLEAR FREE
CITY'S "DEAD FINGERS TALKING" PLAYING]
♪ Dead fingers talking ♪
This is glass-grade.
You got...
Jesus, you got crystals in here
two inches, three inches long.
This is pure glass.
You're a goddamn artist.
This... This is art, Mr. White.
Well, actually, it's
just basic chemistry,
but thank you, Jesse.
I'm glad it's acceptable.
Acceptable? You're
the goddamn Iron Chef.
Every jibhead from here to
Timbuktu's gonna want a taste.
Man, I... I gotta try this.
No. No.
No. We only sell
it. We don't use it.
Okay, since when?
Listen, you've been watching
way too much Miami Vice.
That ain't happening.
[SCOFFS]
So, what now?
How do we proceed?
We cook more tomorrow.
Meantime,
I know just the guy to talk to.
[DOG BARKING]
Get him. Come on.
[RAP MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, yo. Kraze, how
you doing, my man?
Hey, you got a new
dog. Right on, man.
What's his name?
Yeah, I had a
dog like that once,
except maybe like twice as big.
Super-purebred.
Now, me personally,
I would train him to go
straight for the nutsack.
Just shut your mouth
and show me your money.
I ain't buying, ese.
I'm selling.
[MUSIC STOPS]
Tell me that ain't the finest
scante you ever laid eyes on.
Go ahead. Try it.
Hey, poochie. How you doing?
[GROWLS, BARKS] Jesus Christ.
Yeah. Booya! See, what'd I say?
It's all right. It's all right?
It's all right?
Yeah, it's all right.
So what? You're
back in business?
Hell, yeah, I'm back.
With a vengeance. Vato
loco gotta make a living.
You know, with your
cousin gone away and all...
And listen, homes, about that...
Really broke me up about Emilio.
That dude is like my brother.
You okay? You talk to him?
Yeah, I talk to him.
Said when the feds came,
you were out sticking it
in some neighbor lady.
Hey, you know,
I got lucky twice.
I don't know, man.
Emilio,
he thinks maybe
you dimed on him.
Whoa, whoa, hey,
hey. That is bullshit.
That is bullshit, Krazy-8.
I should kick his punk
ass for even thinking that.
You know what? Next
time you talk to Emilio,
you tell him for me, all right?
Why don't you tell him
yourself? Made bail this morning.
Go ahead, pendejo. Kick my ass.
Hey, listen...
[BARKS]
Where did you get this?
Hm?
Because I know your
little punk ass didn't cook it.
[MUFFLED RAP MUSIC
PLAYING IN DISTANCE]
♪ First I hit the guards
Then I'm going for the safe ♪
♪ Then open the vault ♪
[MUSIC STOPS]
[SCOFFS]
Damn, man. What are
you, some kind of nudist?
Yeah, that's some
stone-fine tick-tick
you been cooking there, ese.
How about you come work for me?
I'd be willing to sell it to you
if... If the price is right.
Out here all by yourself, huh?
Hey, I know you. He was
there when I got busted.
He's with the DEA. No.
You rata snitch motherfucker.
Run, Mr. White! Run!
Ah.
[GUN COCKS]
I say we cap them both.
[CHUCKLES]
You really cook up that batch?
Yeah.
You an artist.
It's a damn shame. Wait.
Wait a minute.
Listen to me. I'll teach
you my recipe, huh?
What do you say? You
wanna cook like me?
[COUGHS]
You let us both live,
and I will teach you, huh?
[JESSE GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪]
Put the cigarette out.
Please...
Move it, homes. You got all day?
Okay.
[BOTH COUGHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[BOTH RETCHING]
[GASPING]
[CLATTERING]
[GASPING SUBSIDES]
[EXHALES]
[MOLOTOV'S
"APOCALYPSHIT" PLAYING]
[PANTING]
[DISTANT SIRENS WAILING]
Shit.
Shit!
[GRUNTS]
[GUN CLICKS]
[GRUNTING]
[MOLOTOV'S
"APOCALYPSHIT" PLAYING]
[HORN HONKS]
[HORN HONKING]
[SIRENS WAILING]
What happened?
Hey, what'd you do to them?
Red phosphorus in
the presence of moisture
and accelerated by heat
yields phosphorus hydride.
Phosphine gas.
One good whiff and...
[VOMITING]
We gotta...
We gotta clean this up.
[MICK HARVEY'S "OUT
OF TIME, MAN" PLAYING]
♪ I'm walking out for love ♪
♪ I'm walking out really
down Like a cool breeze ♪
♪ I'm gonna be late again ♪
♪ Driver, wait for me please ♪
♪ I'm running all in vain
Trying to catch this train ♪
♪ Time don't fool me no more ♪
♪ I throw my
watch To the floor ♪
♪ It's gone crazy ♪
Where were you?
Walt...
I don't know what's been
going on with you lately
but... Nothing, honey. I'm fine.
Whatever it is,
I'll tell you this.
I do not like it when
you don't talk to me.
The worst thing you
can do is shut me out.
♪ Time don't fool me no more ♪
♪ I throw my
watch To the floor ♪
♪ It's gone crazy ♪
♪ Time don't do it again Now
I'm stressed and strained ♪
♪ Anger and pain
And the subway train ♪
♪ Long gone the rendezvous ♪
♪ Time made a fool out of me ♪
♪ Baby, can't you see ♪
♪ It's a timing tragedy ♪
♪ I think it's 9 When
the clock says 10 ♪
♪ This girl won't wait for the
Out of Time, Out of Time Man ♪
[MOANS]
Walt...
Oh, Walt, is that you?
[GASPS]
[PANTING]
♪ Long gone the rendezvous ♪
♪ Time made a fool out of me ♪
♪ Baby, can't you see ♪
♪ It's a timing tragedy ♪
♪ Long gone the rendezvous ♪
♪ Time made a fool out of me ♪
♪ Baby, can't you see ♪
♪ It's a timing tragedy ♪
♪ I think it's 9 When
the clock says 10 ♪
♪ This girl won't wait for the
Out of Time, Out of Time Man ♪