[♪♪♪]
WALT: Let's break it down.
Hydrogen. What
does that give us?
By mole, we're
looking at 63 percent.
Sixty-three? Wow. Mm-hm.
That is a big bite.
My next step's gotta be
oxygen. Oxygen, 26 percent.
Twenty-six. There
you have your water.
Carbon, 9 percent. Carbon, 9.
For a total of 98
percent. Right.
WOMAN: Nitrogen, 1.25 percent.
WALTER: One-point-two-five.
WOMAN: That brings
you to 99 and a quarter.
Which only leaves you
with the trace elements
down where the magic happens.
Oh, wait a minute. What about
calcium? Calcium's not a trace.
WALTER: Got a whole
skeleton to account for.
WOMAN: You would
think, right? WALTER: Right.
WOMAN: Calcium.
Calcium's only 0.25 percent.
What? That low? Uh-huh. Mm-hm.
Seriously?
Damn, I never
would've thought that.
Okay, so where
does iron fit in? Iron.
WOMAN: Wow, okay,
0.00004 percent.
What? You can't have
hemoglobin without iron.
Apparently, it don't take
much. No doubt. Go figure.
WALTER: Ah, sodium.
WOMAN: Sodium, 0.04. [COUGHING]
WOMAN: Phosphorus, 0.19.
Point-one-nine.
There we go.
So the whole thing
adds up to...
99.888042 percent.
We are 0.111958 percent
shy.
Supposedly that's
everything. Yeah?
Mm-hm.
I don't know, it just...
It just...
It seems like something's
missing, doesn't it?
WALTER: There's got to be
more to a human being than that.
[COUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
I hate these shoes.
Shoes make me look like I
should be changing bedpans,
like I should be
squeaking around
bringing soup to some
disgusting old person,
then take the bus
home to my 16 cats.
Then why are you wearing them?
I like the support. My arches
happen to be extremely archy.
[PHONE RINGING]
Yo, what's up?
Hey, can you call me,
like, in two minutes?
Thanks, bye.
I gotta go take this.
Ooh. Female?
Louis.
Not like it's any of
your business, though.
Just be quick about it. No.
Oh, and, um, please
don't say, "Yo."
You can't know
how much I hate that.
You missed a spot, right there.
Should you be up on that ladder?
You're more than welcome
to take over for me up here.
I don't see why you
don't get Walt to do it.
Yeah, there's an idea.
So um, I'm, uh, I'm working
on this new short story
and there's this
stoner character in it
and I'm trying to... um...
Well, you know,
actually, let me back up.
Um, you, uh,
you smoked your fair share
of pot in college, didn't you?
I mean, you at least tried it.
Come on.
I perhaps tried it. Why?
Do you remember it having
an effect on your mood?
Like, changing it
in any major way?
It made me more serious.
Really?
Because I mostly remember
it made me lightheaded,
that's about it.
I was just wondering if...
If it maybe could, um...
Um, you know,
it's just a character thing
I'm stuck on. Never mind.
Walter Jr.'s on pot? What? No.
No. No.
What would make you
even...? Where's he getting it?
Marie.
Seriously. Is it
this Louis person?
What are you
gonna do about this?
Marie, you need to
look me in the eye.
I am strictly asking
about a story that
I'm writing, that's all.
Right hand to God,
Walter Jr. is not on pot,
certainly not as far as I know.
Not as far as you know?
Marie.
[♪♪♪]
[TOILET FLUSHES]
Hey, look at me.
Hey, turn around and look at me.
This... This here.
I wouldn't do this
to my worst enemy.
[COUGHS]
This is degrading.
I'm sorry.
You hope I'll make it easy
and just drop dead, don't you?
But I won't.
So either kill me, or let me go.
You don't have
it in you, Walter.
[COUGHING]
How do you know my name?
Jesse.
He told Emilio and me.
I came by to sell your meth.
So, what, did you
threaten him, huh?
Did you beat it out of
him? Not even close.
What else did he tell you?
Pretty much everything
he could think of.
You were his
high-school teacher.
One time you taught
about carbon dioxide
by making grape soda in class.
You have a son who's retarded,
or in a wheelchair or something.
It shouldn't come across
as some news flash.
That partner of yours,
he's got a big mouth.
Walter,
I don't know what you
think you're doing here,
but trust me
this line of work
doesn't suit you.
So I should just
let you go, then?
Just unlock you
and adiós, huh?
I don't see what
real choice you have.
If it's between that and
cold-blooded murder.
Besides...
your real problem's
sitting upstairs.
[♪♪♪]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Occupied.
Hey, yo, I'm trying to
pinch one off in here.
Just give me some
privacy, would you?
Okay. What the hell, man?
What are you doing, man?
You asshole. What...?
You told him my name.
Says who, him? My
name, where I work.
You told him about my
son. Hey, don't touch me.
Damn junkie. No, give
me that. That's mine.
This is going down
the toilet. Watch it go.
No, that's worth
40 grand, you...
It's worth nothing
when you smoke it all.
Get off the toilet.
Get off the toilet! No.
Stop it. [TOILET FLUSHING]
No. No way.
[COUGHING]
No.
No, no, no.
Jesse, where the hell
do you think you're going?
Back off, man. Jesus.
We've got work to do. No, no.
You... You got work
to do. I did my part.
You mean that obscenity I spent
the last two hours cleaning up?
That is your contribution?
Kiss my pink ass, man.
I didn't ask for any of this.
How am I supposed
to live here now, huh?
My whole house smells like
toe cheese and dry cleaning.
Because you didn't
follow my instructions.
Oh, well, Heil Hitler, bitch.
And let me tell
you something else.
We flipped a coin, okay?
You and me. You and me.
Coin flip is sacred.
Your job is waiting for
you in that basement
as per the coin.
Fucking do it, already.
That's what she said. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, I think
we have some of those.
Yeah, you'll have to try 'em on.
Hello? Seven and a half, maybe.
I don't know. Excuse me.
Do you have these in black?
Mm-mm.
Anyways, so like I was saying
I went to the party the other
night. Yeah, Tony was there.
[PHONE RINGING]
Whatever.
Hey, where have you been?
I called you two hours ago.
HANK: Sorry, baby, I'm, uh,
kind of busy here. What's up?
Well, kind of a lot, actually,
and it's a delicate subject.
So I need you to focus, and...
Hey, sit down! Sit down!
Damn it, Hank.
I'm sorry, babe, I'm just in
the middle of something here.
Get down. Get down.
Sit down! Sit your ass down,
comprende? You too, sit down!
[SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
Shit.
I'm back, babe. What's up?
Walter Jr. Yeah, what about him?
Marijuana. He's
smoking it. Bullshit.
Excuse me, his own
mother seems to think so.
Skyler told you
that? She inferred it.
She inferred it, huh?
She strongly inferred it.
Like, "Doctor, my friend
suffers from
erectile dysfunction."
Please, come on. All right.
I want you to talk to him.
Walt should talk to him.
Hell, Skyler, better
yet. She'll kick his butt.
I think it ought to be you.
You know, tell him
some horror stories.
Maybe show him
some autopsy pictures.
An autopsy of a pot
overdose? Come on.
I don't know, baby,
it's just that, you know,
I figure his dad should be the
one doing this, don't you think?
Hank, he respects you.
Yeah, all right.
Well, listen, I mean,
I'll swing by their
place after work.
Good. Scare him
straight. Yeah, yeah.
Hey, where's my sugar?
Hm. Muah.
SALESWOMAN: Excuse me, ma'am.
Ma'am, you need to be wearing
footies before you try those on.
I'm extremely clean.
Yeah, well, I'd
really appreciate it.
Hey, sorry about
that. Yeah, I'll check.
SALESWOMAN: You know, I hid
a pair for you last week, gray ones.
My manager found them and
we put them back on the floor.
I know.
[SASHA DOBSON'S
"WITHOUT YOU" PLAYING]
♪ I don't want to stay ♪
♪ Without you ♪
[SIREN WAILING]
[HORN HONKING]
Hey.
I'm going.
HANK: What do you think?
WALT JR.: About what?
This look like a nice place?
No, not really.
Think you'd like to live here?
No.
Sure about that?
Yeah, pretty sure.
I thought we were going
to Cold Stone Creamery.
Yeah, yeah, well,
we took a little detour.
Figure we'll come over and
check out how the other half lives.
This here is what we
call the Crystal Palace.
You know who lives in
the palace? Meth-heads.
Nasty, skeevy meth-heads
who'd sell their
grandma's coochie for a hit.
Oh, you think that's funny?
That's funny, huh? Yeah.
Let me tell you something.
Every one of these
miserable wastes of
skin got started how?
Hm?
How do you think they
started? I don't know.
What do you think they were
doing before they graduated
to shooting meth in their dicks?
A gateway drug.
That's what we call it.
Dollars to doughnuts,
and I shit you not,
that gateway drug was
marijuana, every time.
You understand? Um, yeah.
So why are you telling me this?
Because I love you,
you little bastard.
And, hey, I was
young once, you know.
The world's a messed-up
place, you know.
You know, just this,
uh, one time, you know...
Hey! Hey! Hey, you!
Yeah, you, princess.
Get over here.
[HORN HONKING]
Hey, don't make
me get out of the car.
Check this out.
See what I'm talking about.
Hey, I ain't holding, okay?
Did I say open your mouth?
And hands off the car.
Other side. Go around the
other side, talk to my friend here.
What's your name, sweetheart?
Wendy. HANK: Wendy, huh?
How much you charge
for a windy, Wendy?
I ain't doing him, he's a kid.
Jesus, was that my question?
Don't think so hard, it's
gonna hurt your brain.
Are you on the pipe
or on the needle?
Nothing. Neither.
HANK: Yeah, yeah.
Show us your teeth, huh?
Come on, Wendy, let's
see those pearly whites.
Oh, God. See
that? Pipe, definitely.
HANK: Bigtime,
bigtime on the pipe.
You got something
you wanna ask Wendy?
Um, no, not really.
HANK: You ever smoke
anything else, Wendy?
Sausages don't count.
[LAUGHS]
Seriously, tell my friend
here how you got started.
HANK: Probably used to
be, what? Like a Girl Scout,
or probably sang
in the church choir.
What are you, like, handicapped?
He broke his leg
playing football.
He's a qb. Got an
arm like a howitzer.
So tell me, Wendy,
you smoke pot?
Why, you got some?
All right, hoof it, get
lost. Get out of here.
Hey, fair warning, next
time I'm gonna bust you.
So, what do you think?
Cool.
JESSE: Shut the
door. Shut the door.
Lock it. Lock it, lock it.
Who the hell was that?
Cop and some football
player messing with me.
They ask about me, huh?
No, I think they
just wanted pot.
Right there.
Shit, I left my root beer.
[♪♪♪]
[BEEPING]
SKYLER: Hello?
Hey, sweetie, it's me.
Listen, I'm so sorry.
The time, it just, ha,
it just... It completely
got away from me.
I'm just, ha... uh...
My fault, my fault. Bogdan
just kept me here late,
you know, doing some inventory,
and I, um, I... I
should've just...
You know, you're right.
I-I gotta learn to
say, you know, "No."
But, um...
Sky? You there?
You're at the car wash?
Yeah.
I seriously doubt that,
since you quit two weeks ago.
I called Bogdan,
looking for you.
Quite an earful he gave me.
Listen...
Listen, I'll come home
and we'll talk about it.
I don't think so, Walt. Honey...
Wherever you are,
why don't you just
stay there tonight?
Skyler? Skyler?
Skyler?
MAN: Walter?
Hello?
Hey, I'm kind of
hungry down here.
[♪♪♪]
[COUGHING]
[WALTER COUGHING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Oh.
Come on.
[COUGHING]
Damn.
I didn't think you
were coming back.
[GROANS]
How long was I out?
Ten, 15 minutes?
I've never seen someone knock
themselves out just by coughing.
You breathe in the same
shit you used on me?
I've got lung cancer.
[COUGHING]
I'll go make you
another sandwich.
It's safe.
There's no poison.
Because that would
be the way to do it
if you're gonna do it.
I suppose it would.
I mean,
you being a chemist and all.
So that name...
Krazy-8.
Do I really have
to call you that?
I mean, no offense,
but don't you have a real name?
Domingo.
That's "Sunday," right?
I'd rather call you
that, if you don't mind.
Whatever.
I can't say I ever
liked it much.
[COUGHS]
So, Domingo,
you from around town
here or someplace else?
Hey, Walter? You
getting to know me
is not gonna make it
easier for you to kill me.
Not that I mind, you understand?
You know, you keep telling
me that I don't have it in me.
Well, maybe.
But maybe not.
I sure as hell am looking
for any reason not to.
I mean, any good reason at all.
Sell me.
Tell me what it is.
I guess I'd start off by
promising that if you let me go
I won't come after
you, that you'd be safe.
I guess I'd say what
happened between us
never happened.
And what's best for both
parties is we forget all about it.
But you know that
anybody in my situation
would make promises like that.
And, in my case,
they happen to be true.
You'll never know for sure.
So, what else can I tell you?
I don't know.
But you've gotta convince me.
And you're going
nowhere until you do.
Hey, yeah. Yeah.
I'm from here in town, man.
ABQ, born and bred.
Never left.
Studied Business
Administration over at UNM,
got my degree.
Really?
Does that, uh, come in
handy in the drug trade?
It doesn't hurt.
I was gonna study
music originally.
Maybe even try out
for Oberlin and Berklee.
My pops talked me out of it.
Said there was no money in it
unless I wind up
some bullshit rock star,
and I didn't have a
snowball chance of that.
What does your dad do?
He owns Tampico Furniture
over on Menaul.
Wait a minute, I
know that place.
Wait a minute. That's...
That's that... That, uh...
They used to have
those... Those late-night...
The stupid commercials.
That they had, yeah.
Yeah, that's him. Been
doing them for over 30 years.
Wait a minute. How
did it go? It was, uh...
Wait, wait, wait. It was...
Don't let shopping
Strain your brain-o
Just sing this short refrain-o
Our furniture is bueno
Tampico is the name-o
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[COUGHING]
Pretty moronic. But
what can you do?
Well, it did tend to
stick in your head.
Did you write that? Being
the musician in the family.
Hell, no, man. It was
my crazy uncle Alex.
He sings it at bars, trying
to pick up on women.
His mind, it's like saying,
"Hey, I wrote
'Stairway to Heaven.'"
Yeah, but at
Tampico Furniture, I...
I think when my son was born
that we bought
his bassinet there.
DOMINGO: Mm-mm. We
don't sell bassinets there.
It's more of a specialty item.
We did use to sell cribs.
A crib, then, okay. A crib.
Yeah. No, I remember that.
In fact, I remember
recognizing your dad
from those commercials.
Although he wasn't anywhere
near as friendly in real life.
Yeah. No shit.
Did he, uh, try selling you
that extended warranty?
Yeah, he probably did.
And I was probably
dumb enough to buy it.
Yeah, that was his big thing.
You ask him for
a glass of water,
he'd tell you you need an
extended warranty on the ice.
Did you work there
too? Only my whole life.
Up until the day I said,
"Fuck you," and quit.
So, uh...
16 years ago, how old
would you have been?
If it was after school,
trust me, I was there.
Might have even
helped ring you up.
You and your extended
warranty on the crib.
[COUGHING]
Small world.
It is.
The paths we take, huh?
[MUTTERS INDISTINCTLY]
Jesse know you've got cancer?
No one but you.
Not your family?
No.
Why not?
Not a conversation that I'm
even remotely ready to have.
That's why you're cooking meth?
DOMINGO: You wanna
leave money for your family.
Hell, I mean,
I'll write you a check
right now if you let me go.
Like I said, Walter,
if this line of work
doesn't suit you...
get out before it's too late.
I don't know what to do.
Yeah.
You do.
I'll get the key.
[♪♪♪]
No.
Oh, no, no, no.
No. No. No, don't do this.
Don't do this. Why
are you doing this?
Why are you doing this?
[GRUNTS]
You're doing the
right thing, Walter.
Yeah?
Do you wanna?
[COUGHING]
So you're not angry?
What do you mean?
Angry at you?
No.
Live and let live, man.
That's very understanding.
Whatever, man.
I just wanna go home.
Yeah.
Me too.
Unlock me, Walter.
The moment I do...
are you gonna stick me with
that broken piece of plate?
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[YELLING]
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm so
sorry, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
[♪♪♪]
Hello?
Anybody down here?
[♪♪♪]
[CHATTER]
Everybody,
I need you all to
take your seats.
Settle down, please. Thank you.
I understand that
Mr. White is feeling
a little under the
weather this morning.
So you folks
are going to have to be
making do with me today.
And we are going to be
watching a very interesting video
on carbon
Very important stuff.
So, what do you think?
Ah, it's a cook site. Gotta be.
Nobody came way the
hell out here just to buy.
Fire there could have
started by accident.
I don't think that was
meant to destroy evidence.
Got a couple of Dooley tracks
headed away, towards the road.
So, what, they're in some
sort of camper-slash-lab?
They accidentally start a
fire and everybody FOs?
Yeah. Why not?
So why did that little
hair-gelled shit leave his car?
Ay-yi-yi.
Gomey, it's a
culture in decline.
It's a rich and vibrant culture.
It's a car that
jumps up and down.
What the hell?
You people used to be
conquistadors, for chrissake.
Smells like a Drakkar
Noir factory in here.
I already searched it.
Yeah.
You're wasting your time.
Give it up. If this
here's a trap car,
it's gonna take more than
your dumb white ass to find it.
Oh, yeah? You are talking
to the trap-car master,
my friend.
I'm Rain Man
counting his toothpicks.
Yeah, you're like
Rain Man. Retarded.
[HANK LAUGHING]
Yeah, baby.
Hello, zippy. Asshole.
Sort of looks like
meth but it's, uh,
it's too damn white.
You know what I'm
thinking, Gomey?
Yep. Somebody
croaked our snitch.
MAN: Hey, agents.
You got something?
[♪♪♪]
WALTER: I don't know. It just...
It just... Doesn't it seem like
something's missing?
What about the soul?
The soul.
There's nothing
but chemistry here.
[MOTOR WHIRRING LOUDLY]
Skyler?
There's something
I have to tell you.
[♪♪♪]