Here is, uh... Here's my résumé.
Um, I mean, technically it
says, uh, "curriculum vitae,"
which I think is more
professional, but, uh, you know,
same thing, pretty much.
MAN: That's, uh... Wow, great.
This position truly is a
no-experience-necessary
kind of thing.
And, uh, it doesn't
really say it here,
but, um, I have a solid
background in, uh...
In sales.
I'm pretty much
a self-starter, so...
That's excellent,
but, um... Excellent.
I just...
I really feel I
could be a major,
major asset to your sales force.
Ah.
I'm thinking there's a
little misunderstanding.
This isn't actually a sales job.
I mean, I'd be happy to
consider you for a sales position,
but all our agents
need to be licensed,
have at least two years
on-the-job experience
and usually a college degree.
Wow.
What you'll be
doing is more like...
advertising.
Hey, Jesse.
Hey, man.
Yo, man.
What up? Badger?
Where you been keeping yourself?
Nice duds.
Yeah, you too.
Thanks.
JESSE: Yo, why would you
wanna do this lame-ass job, anyway?
I mean, no... No offense.
'Cause I'm on probation, yo.
I gotta prove to the
man I'm rehabilitated.
Upstanding
citizen, all that shit.
It's really good exercise too.
You can't just stand there,
you have to spin the arrow.
There's all these
moves you have to learn,
like "the helicopter."
[GRUNTING]
Wow. Yeah. See, yeah?
That one's a bitch.
I'm not very good at it yet.
You, uh, really opened
my eyes to the possibilities.
Yeah. Hey, anyways, um,
thanks for the toke. Any time.
Speaking of which,
you think you could maybe, uh,
hook me up with some crystal?
Uh, no, I've... I've been out
of the business for a while.
Actually, now
thinking about retiring.
What? No. Yeah.
That stuff you made
is unbelievable.
It was pretty awesome.
Retirement? Argh!
I can't be hearing this.
No, man, I-I had this, uh...
This partner who
was helping me cook.
I mean, I was doing
most of the work...
[SIGHS]
but he was an asshole, so.
Anyway, I mean, pseudo's
getting harder and harder
to come by and...
Yo, I can hook you
up with some pseudo.
Major pseudo.
I got channels, bro.
We could partner up.
Huh?
No pressure.
No pressure. Just
think about it, all right?
Oh, shit. I gotta go.
[SIGHS]
Yo, this way to savings.
Save your dollar bills, y'all.
[SIGHS]
♪ Big savings This
way and save ♪
[SIGHS] Come on!
Save some money.
[♪♪♪]
WALT: It's a stupid gift.
SKYLER: No, it
isn't. He'll love it.
I don't know what
I was thinking.
Didn't the invitation
even say "no gifts"?
Walt. What?
We have to go.
I know, I'm not complaining.
Yes, you are.
Look, we need this.
We've been through
a lot lately. Okay?
Mm-hm.
SKYLER: Jesus, guess we
didn't get the "beige" memo.
Ah, we're okay.
Yes, I... I look like I'm wearing
a prom dress from 1985.
Honey, you look fine.
Walt, this is the only
thing I could find that fit me.
God, would you look at that.
The invitation said "no gifts."
[WHISPERS] So? Come on.
Sir, I'll take that for you.
Thank you. You're welcome.
Oh, look, there's Elliott.
Oh, come on, let's go say hello.
Elliott. Ha!
Walt.
You made it. WALT: Ha-ha-ha!
Wouldn't miss it for the
world. Thank you. Skyler.
Hi. Oh. Oh, that's
right. Hee-hee-hee!
Great to see you. You
look beautiful, as always.
Well, these days a little
more big than beautiful, but...
Of course, congratulations.
That was such great news.
Thank you. Gretchen,
look who's here.
Oh. Oh.
It's been ages.
Oh, it's so good
to see you. Heh!
Ha-ha-ha! It's really good.
Skyler, welcome.
Congratulations.
Thank you. It's
really nice to be here.
When are you due? SKYLER:
In about 10 more weeks.
And actually, we recently
found out that it's a girl.
Oh, that's so wonderful. Yeah.
Yeah, we've been thinking
about it for ourselves.
Yeah, thinking about it.
[CHUCKLES]
Uh... Oh, hey, by the way,
uh, securing that
patent was just amazing.
I mean, the work that
your company is doing...
Congratulations to both of you.
Hard work and
a lot of luck. A lot.
Yeah. Oh, well, now.
MAN: Elliott.
Will you excuse
us? We gotta say hi.
Make yourselves at
home, we'll catch up later.
Sure, sure. Okay.
Okay. May I? So
glad you're here.
Thank you. Bye.
John, Missy. How are you?
Shall we?
MAN: Congratulations.
Happy birthday.
[MUSIC PLAYING IN DISTANCE]
Oh.
Whoa.
Hm.
[COUGHING]
[SIGHS]
[SNIFFS]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE SPEECH]
Walt?
I thought that was you.
Farley. Ha-ha-ha!
Long time no see.
This is Walter White. Oh. Hello.
Back at Caltech, he was...
You were just a master
of crystallography.
I remember this one time we
were stuck on this protein problem
for... For weeks.
You just breezed right in,
and... And you had
one word for us...
Synchrotrons. It was
synchrotrons, yeah.
They generate pure and
more complete patterns
than x-ray beams.
Data collection takes
a fraction of the time.
This is the White
in Gray Matter.
Tell 'em, Walt. Okay.
Uh, well, back when Elliott
and I were in grad school,
we came up with the name.
Ahem. Schwartz,
black. Walter White.
So together they became
Gray Matter Technologies.
Cute, huh?
So you run the
company with Elliott?
FARLEY: No. No, that's...
That's Gretchen and Elliott.
Yeah, yeah. You know, I... I
gravitated toward education.
Ah. What university?
Oh, wow, it's a Stratocaster.
Not... Not just any Strat.
That's one of Clapton's.
ELLIOTT: No way.
"To Elliott, sorry about the
buckle rash, Eric Clapton."
Thank you. This is beautiful.
Why is he doing this? Beautiful.
What is he, like, 8 years old?
Here, honey.
Thanks.
Oh, this is from Walt.
Oh, God. It's okay.
Hey.
Let's see what we got.
[CHUCKLES LIGHTLY]
Yum Good Ramen.
[CHUCKLING]
This is what Walt and I lived on
for, uh, 10 months straight
while we were
working on our thesis.
Sold them down at
Ralstow's in the hardware isle.
Right next to the...
The... What was it?
Sterno. Yeah. The Sterno.
Yeah, ten for a
dollar ninety-nine.
To this day, I am
convinced these noodles
were responsible
for our success.
This was our lifeblood.
Man, where'd you find these?
I thought they'd been
outlawed years ago.
[CROWD CHUCKLES]
I love it.
Thank you, Walt.
Well.
For the man who has everything.
ELLIOTT: No. WALT: It was.
No, you remember
the fat guy. Yes.
We used to call him Snot Trough.
He had that thing
under his nose.
What do you call that
thing? That was Dobkins.
That was the same guy who
always smelled like chocolate milk.
It was. No, no, no, no.
It... It wasn't
Dobkins, it was...
Anyway, I swear to Christ,
he used to iron those patches
onto the elbows of his...
His members-only jacket
because he thought it made
him look more distinguished.
Didn't it? I thought it... No.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Oh, God. Well,
here's to Snot Trough.
To Snot Trough.
Wherever you may be.
God bless him. Heh-heh-heh!
Hmmm.
Do you remember
the...? The professor
who used to hate
Robert Wilhelm Bunsen?
Yes. All you had to do was
mention the Bunsen burner
and he was off on a rant.
"Oh, he didn't invent it." Do
you remember the waving?
"He just improved it," you know.
Oh. It was easy
to kill 15 minutes.
Yeah.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Oh, God.
I miss this, Walt.
Yeah. Me too.
Listen, uh, we... We ought
to get together more often.
Skyler and I would love
to have you and Gretchen
over for dinner sometime.
Oh, sure, yeah, absolutely.
But, you know,
what I mean is that...
That you and I should
work together again.
[CHUCKLES]
Are you gonna teach high
school? No, no, no, seriously.
W-what's stopping us?
Wait a minute,
Elliott, what are you...?
Are you asking me to come
work for you at Gray Matter?
Yeah, why not?
You... You'd fit right in.
You're brilliant, you...
You got a ton of experience.
Well, I...
I wouldn't really
know where to begin.
I mean...
God, you have no idea.
I spend my days just drawing
out atoms on the chalkboard
and trying to get these kids
to learn the periodic table.
Look, I... I... I understand.
Y-you're a little rusty,
but you're not seeing
the upside here.
We... We could really benefit
from a... A new set of eyes.
You know when you've been
trying to crack some problem
for months on end,
you get tunnel vision.
One guy thinking
outside of the box,
you may be exactly what we need.
[CHUCKLES LIGHTLY]
Well, listen, Elliott, it...
The offer is very appealing,
it really is, I thank you.
But, uh, there's...
There's something
you should know.
I... I... I have some
personal issues.
Look, there's nothing
we can't work out.
Well, yeah...
but it's... It's complicated.
We can help you.
We... We have excellent
health insurance.
The best.
[INAUDIBLE SPEECH]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Um, hey, did you...? Did you
try those prosciutto-wrapped figs?
They were, like,
wow. They were just...
I must have had about
30 of those suckers.
Oh, and the seafood
table, did you see that?
They had lobster tail, they
had crab legs, like, shrimp.
They had...
[SIGHS]
Walt. What the hell
did you say to Elliott?
What? You told him
about the cancer,
didn't you? Didn't you?
I can't believe it.
Okay, we were talking, he
asked how you were doing,
and I am sorry, but I don't have
the best poker face these days
where that's concerned.
He knew something was wrong
with you, and he pressed me.
He pressed you? Come on.
Walt, when it came
right down to it,
I didn't know what else
to do but tell him the truth.
The truth? Well, how about
you just said, "He's fine," huh?
You could have said that. "He's
fine." It would have been done.
I don't like the
way you're talking.
I don't like the way you
talk about my private affairs
to people who are not
even in our lives anymore.
Well, what exactly
did he say to you?
He offered me a job. What?
Yes. Kind of like
some fig leaf, you know.
Some face-saving bullshit
that allowed me to
generously accept his charity.
And then when I turned
that down, he flat out
offered to pay for my treatment.
Which is exactly what you
expected him to do, didn't you?
Walt. Didn't you?
No. I did not put him up...
Please. Come on. Come on.
[COUGHING]
Okay, what did you say?
Walt?
What do you think I said?
Why? Walt.
[SIGHS]
[CAR DOOR SLAMS]
[CUTLERY CLATTERING]
[INDISTINCT SPEECH OVER TV]
Hm.
Ready to go? I'm taking the bus.
Okay.
Bye, honey.
[SIGHS]
[DISHES CLATTER]
Hey, dude. Are
these bullet holes?
Uh...
No, man. Those are
for, like, um, you know,
uh, ventilation.
Cool.
Woo.
Nice setup, huh? Ha-ha!
Man. This is nothing, man.
I used to have, like,
twice as much glassware
until my, um, dumb-ass
ex-partner drove us into a ditch
and wrecked most of it.
Big-ass beaker, huh?
Hey, wait, wait, no, that's...
Yeah, that's a boiling flask.
This is a beaker.
Here's a Griffin beaker.
Here's a, uh, volumetric beaker.
Here's, uh, an Erlenmeyer flask.
Um, you got... Wow.
You really know your shit.
It's just basic chemistry, yo.
So
You got something for me?
Aw, hells, yeah.
Okay.
We're in business.
Right on, Badger.
Dude, check this out.
Jesus.
What are you bringing
that for? Hunting.
We might see javelinas.
[FUJIYA & MIYAGI'S "UH" PLAYING]
♪ I guess I wasn't
feeling okay ♪
♪ I felt that space and time ♪
♪ Went back and
forth And sideways ♪
♪ I'm putting up fast ♪
♪ All over the place ♪
♪ I guess... ♪
[WHEEZING]
Are you gonna help me or what?
♪ Oh She made me go "uh" ♪
♪ Uh ♪
Hey.
♪ Uh, uh, uh ♪
♪ Up against and underly ♪
Badger!
♪ We are as prickly ♪
♪ As a couple of porcupines ♪
♪ I'm pulling up fast
All over the place ♪
[MUFFLED SPEECH]
Yeah, buddy. Huh? Yeah.
♪ Oh She made me go "uh" ♪
♪ Go "uh" ♪
♪ Uh, uh, uh ♪
♪ Oh, sock it to me ♪
♪ I'm pulling out fast
All over the place ♪
♪ I guess It knocked
me sideways ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ She made me go "uh" Go "uh" ♪
♪ Uh, uh, uh Uh, uh, uh, uh ♪
WALT JR.: Let's see the money.
Here.
I need five each.
Come on, two more.
Here.
What about him?
Are you kidding? He
looks younger than us.
Whatever.
What about that guy?
No, he looks like a businessman.
BOY: So what?
So businessmen
are always in a hurry.
They're always, like, going
to some meeting or something.
Seriously, he's
just gonna say no.
BOY: Hey, hey, this guy.
This is our guy.
You're up.
Wh-why do I have to do it?
Give me the crutches
and I'll go do it.
Shit.
Um, excuse me, hey, um,
we forgot our IDs,
and we were wondering
if you could do us a favor
and buy us a six-pack?
You know, what
you're asking is illegal.
Um...
No, it's not.
Yeah, it is.
Oh, shit.
MAN: Guess you win the jackpot.
This is not how I wanted
to spend my night off.
Consider this your
first and last warning.
Yes, sir.
You're lucky you
got a good dad, here.
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
The other guys had to run.
I... I couldn't talk
my way out of it.
Not cool, man. Not cool.
What, you never tried to buy
beer when you were my age?
I'm talking about you calling
me and not your father.
How do you think
that'd make him feel?
[SIGHS]
[CAR STARTS]
SKYLER: I don't even
know what to say to you.
Just go.
I'll deal with you later.
[EXHALES]
Where's Walt?
I haven't seen him
since this morning.
Your guess is as good as mine.
Listen, do me
a favor, all right?
Don't tell him about the kid.
He's just a teenager
trying to score some beer.
You know,
growing pains.
I mean, he finds
out his dad's sick,
he starts acting out, you know?
First the pot, then this.
The pot?
You told me the kid was smoking.
That's what Skyler told me.
I mean, you may as well have.
I wasn't talking
about Walter, Jr.
[WHISPERS] I was... I
was talking about Walt.
Excuse me?
He admitted it.
[WHISPERS] He said he liked it.
Walt?
Mm-hm.
[LAUGHS] Shit.
[LAUGHING]
I didn't think he had it in him.
It's like he's not
himself lately. Yeah.
I mean,
why would anyone
in their right mind
choose not to do treatment?
Especially when it's
completely paid for.
Why is he doing this?
You know what we need to do?
What we really need to
do is sit him down, all of us,
and... And get everything
out on the table.
Talk it all through.
You mean an in...?
Intervention? No, no.
Just a family meeting.
Where everyone can
voice their concerns
and be heard.
[WIND BLOWING]
BADGER: You are a genius, bro.
This cankenstein is unreal.
When we get back, I'm
gonna burn that dollar bill suit,
'cause we're gonna
make some mad dough.
[CHUCKLES]
It's not right.
What do you
mean, it's not right?
Tsk. It's... cloudy. It's
not supposed to be cloudy.
Okay, that last
time, it was glass.
So what? Cloudy, not cloudy?
It looks good enough to me.
Good enough.
Wait, wait. Yo,
what are you doing?
[DOOR CLOSES]
Argh! Are you out of your mind?
I totally would've smoked that.
Look, it's not for you,
it's for our customers.
They're gonna demand
a certain standard.
What? What...? What are you...?
What? We'll just do it again.
Until we get it right.
[BLOWING]
Walt.
Please have a seat and join us.
[SIGHS]
We can do better.
Don't you fucking
think about it!
Hey. Come on.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Three entire pounds
of pseudo wasted.
Do you know how long I
had to spin that stupid sign?
Get off me, psycho.
Helicopter, bitch!
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[GRUNTING]
God! Argh!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Asshole.
[♪♪♪]
Open the door.
[CAR STARTS]
[GRUNTING]
[ENGINE STALLING]
BADGER: Come
back here, you bitch!
I'm gonna mess you up!
This isn't funny!
[GRUNTS]
I really need to understand
your thought process,
because clearly I don't.
I feel that this
decision you've made
is not only not in
your best interest,
it's not in the best
interest of our entire family.
Look, Skyler... SKYLER:
Not yet, please. I...
I have the talking pillow.
Everybody gets to speak
their minds, remember?
And then you'll get your chance.
Money has always
been an issue for us,
I'll give you that.
But now that Elliott is
more than willing to pitch in...
I understand that it's
hard for you to accept help.
Maybe it's the way
you were raised.
But, honey,
it's okay to lean on
people now and again.
You need this treatment.
And nothing can
stop you from getting it
except you.
Am I allowed to respond?
SKYLER: In a minute.
I think we need to go
around the circle first.
Hank, would you like to start?
Uh, yeah. Okay, well...
What I would say is...
Take... Take the talking pillow.
All right, look, buddy, um...
I know I don't get to
tell you this enough,
but, uh, I care about you.
A hell of a lot.
And this cancer thing...
Let's just... Let's
face it, you know,
you were dealt a shit hand.
But, um,
sometimes your luck can change.
I mean...
I mean, I can't tell you
how many times I was...
You know, I started
with a shit hand,
and I ended up with a, you
know, a full house. Okay?
I mean, the key is,
you gotta hang in there.
Man, you gotta keep
placing your bets,
keep placing your bets. Boom.
Hank,
what the hell are you saying?
SKYLER: No, please,
Marie, let him talk.
That's what we're
here to do. Please.
Go on, Hank.
All right, l... Look
at it this way, okay?
It's the bottom of the
ninth, bases are loaded,
you're up.
But you got a bum arm, right?
There's no fricking way
you're gonna hit a homer, okay?
So you can either let the
pinch hitter take the bat,
or you can hold on to your
pride and lose the game.
You get what I'm saying?
No.
You got your pride,
man. I get it, okay? I get it.
But this Daddy Warbucks
wants to chip in, man.
I'm... I'm with your
old lady on this one.
[LAUGHS] I say take
the money and run, man.
[SNIFFS, SIGHS]
Somebody wanna
take this thing? Here.
Y-yes, Walter...
Walter, Jr., I'm... I'm sure
that you have about a
million things to say, probably.
And now is your chance.
Go ahead. Just let it all out.
This is bullshit.
All right, come on.
SKYLER: It's all right.
It...
[SIGHS]
Talk.
Tell your dad how you feel.
I'm pissed off. Tell him.
I-I'm pissed off.
'Cause you're
being... You're being...
Y-you're...
[SIGHS]
You're a pussy.
You're, like, ready to give up.
You're... God.
What if you gave up on me, huh?
This here,
all the stuff I've been through,
and y-you're scared of
a little chemotherapy?
Me, personally...
I think you should do
whatever you wanna do.
What?
You told us to be
honest about our feelings.
Walt's the one with
cancer, it's his decision.
It's not up to any of us.
Why in hell would
you do this? Hey, hey.
I wasn't planning on
agreeing with Walt.
But after sitting and listening
to you all talk about his future
like he has no say in it...
He's not gonna have a future
if he doesn't get treatment.
I am a medical
professional. Ugh.
I x-ray people in
treatment every day.
I see them every day.
And you know what?
Some of them are
absolutely miserable.
Marie... I'm
sorry, but it's true.
And some of them don't wanna
spend their last weeks or months
being picked at by doctors.
But they got talked
into it by their families.
Can I get the pillow back?
'Cause I agree with Marie.
Thank you. SKYLER: Hank...
What? Maybe Walt wants
to die like a man, all right?
I don't want him to die at all!
That's the whole point of
this. So either help or leave!
Skyler, I just wanted
to do you the courtesy
of giving you my honest opinion.
You know, Marie,
this is not debate club.
This is my husband's life... I
made one simple observation...
And it's like you... How dare
you... Okay, so we disagree...
Ladies! Marie! [WHISTLES]
This is so stupid.
All right, I've got the
talking pillow now.
Okay?
We all, in this room,
we love each other.
We want what's best for
each other, and I know that.
I am very thankful for that.
But what I want...
What I want, what I need...
is a choice.
What does that mean?
Sometimes I feel
like I never actually
make any of my own choices,
I mean.
My entire life...
it just seems I never...
you know, had a... Had
a real say about any of it.
Now, this last one, cancer...
all I have left is how I
choose to approach this.
SKYLER: Then make
the right choice, Walt.
You are not the
only one it affects.
What about your son?
Don't you wanna see your
daughter grow up? I just...
Of course I do.
Skyler, you've read
the statistics, you...
[SIGHS]
These doctors
talking about "surviving"
one year, two years,
like it's the only
thing that matters.
But what good
is it to just survive
if I am too sick to work?
To enjoy a meal?
To make love?
For what time I have left,
I wanna live in my own house.
I wanna sleep in my own bed.
I don't wanna choke down
30 or 40 pills every single day
and lose my hair
and lie around,
too tired to get up...
and so nauseated that I
can't even move my head.
And you.
Cleaning up after me.
And me? What...?
Some, uh...
Some dead man,
some artificially-alive...
Just marking time.
No. No.
And that's how you
would remember me.
That's the worst part.
So that is my thought
process, Skyler.
I'm sorry. I just...
I choose not to do it.
[♪♪♪]
All right.
"All right" what?
I'll do the treatment.
[PAN CLATTERS]
[SIGHS]
It's gonna be okay.
Okay.
[MUSIC PLAYING OVER PA]
[DOOR OPENS]
Um, the lady from
the billing office
said they usually bill the
insurance company directly.
But since our HMO's
not paying for it,
we can pay up front
with a credit card.
Oh, good.
Oh, and then Elliott
will send a check. Right.
I will take care of it.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Walter White?
Yes.
Okay. Heh-heh!
All right. Okay.
See you in a minute. WALT: Okay.
Okay.
[♪♪♪]
[MACHINERY WHIRRING]
[MACHINERY BEEPING]
[♪♪♪]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[CAR DOOR SLAMS]
[PHONE BEEPS]
Ha-ha! Elliott.
GRETCHEN: Walt, it's Gretchen.
Oh, hey.
Hey, Gretchen, how are you?
You know, it was...
It was really great
seeing you two the
other day, you know.
Wow, what a party.
Um, Elliott told me
about the cancer.
I-I-I'm... I'm so sorry.
Well, you know,
it is what it is, I guess.
I don't... I don't
know what to say.
Except, I'm always here for you.
Both of us are. We
wanted you to know that.
Yeah, well, thank you.
Walt, Elliott told me
that he'd offered to
pay for the treatment.
You have to accept.
That money, as far as
we're both concerned,
that... That belongs to you.
Even the name of our
company, it... It's... It's half yours.
Walt?
Is this about you and me?
Gretchen, I really
appreciate the offer.
I do. Um, but we're fine.
Uh...
As it turns out,
the insurance came
through after all.
So, um,
I am covered. And, uh...
Well, and, anyway,
I-I-I really appreciate
it, I really do.
Thank you.
Good. That's good news.
You know, that really
was a... A great party.
Keep in touch, okay?
Sure. Sure, and...
thank you for calling.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[SCOFFS]
Yo!
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Wanna cook?
[♪♪♪]