[CREAKING]
[SIRENS APPROACHING]
[♪♪♪]
[CLICKS]
[BUZZING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO]
[HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING]
[♪♪♪]
[BED CREAKING]
[JESSE GRUNTING]
JESSE: Come on.
Come on.
Come...
Come on. Come on, baby.
Please, please. Come
on, come on. Come on!
[SOBBING]
Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God.
[BEEPS]
Yeah.
Slow down. Slow... Slow down.
Now, just... Just
take a deep breath.
Do it.
All right.
Now, what happened?
All right. All right.
Now, listen... Listen to
me. Are you listening?
Everything is gonna
be okay. I promise.
No, no... Listen. Calm down.
Just...
Sit tight. I know who to call.
Saul Goodman sent me.
Come on. Inside.
Latch the door.
Where is she?
Any other drugs in the house?
Think hard. Your
freedom depends on it.
What about guns? You
got any guns in the house?
Here's your story.
You woke up. You found
her. That's all you know.
Say it.
Say it, please.
"I woke up. I found
her. That's all I know."
[SOBBING]
Say it. "I woke up. I found
her. That's all I know."
I woke up. I found
her. That's all I know.
Again.
I woke up. I found
her. That's all I know.
Again. Again.
I woke up. I found
her. That's all I know.
Once you call, the
people who show up
will be with the Office
of Medical Investigations.
That's primarily
who you'll talk to.
Police officers may
arrive, they may not.
Depends on how busy
a morning they're having.
Typically, ODs are
not a high-priority call.
There's nothing here
to incriminate you
so I'd be amazed if you
got placed under arrest.
However, if you
do, you say nothing.
You tell them you
just want your lawyer.
Then you call Saul Goodman.
And do I need to
state the obvious?
I was not here.
You put on a long-sleeved shirt
and cover those track
marks on your arm.
Count down from
20, and then you dial.
Hang tough. You're
in the home stretch.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR SHUTS]
WALT: Do you want
2-percent or skim?
Uh... Two. Two. Two. All right.
Thank you. Mm-hm.
Junior.
Flynn. What?
Flynn.
WALT JR.: I'll be
there in a minute.
You all right?
Flynn, get your butt in here.
WALT JR.: Oh, my God. Mom,
Dad, come here. You gotta see this.
Seriously.
What? Look right
there. Look at that.
Are those donations?
WALT JR.: Yes.
SKYLER: Actual
donations for your dad?
WALT JR.: Total
strangers gave us $490.
Twenty-six people.
Virginia, Minnesota, Montana.
Look at this one. Vancouver.
All the way up in Canada.
And... And... And it's
all real, actual money.
It's actually right-right
there in the PayPal account.
And-and look... Look
what they're saying:
"Hang in there,
Walt." "Good luck."
"Hang in there."
Is-Isn't this awesome?
That's... Wow,
that is something.
Walt, don't you think a
little thank-you is in order?
Yes, absolutely. Thank you, son.
Thank you. This is a
big... Big help. Heh-heh.
[BELL DINGS ON COMPUTER]
WALT JR.: Oh, look, 20 more
bucks from Thunder Bay, Ontario.
Damn. Five... Five
hundred and ten dollars.
[PHONE RINGING]
JANE [ON RECORDING]: Hey, if
you're trying to sell me something,
I've got four little
words for you:
"Do-not-call list."
However, if you're
cool, leave it at the beep.
How did I know you wouldn't
be answering your phone?
I'm on my way. I'm gonna
be there momentarily.
I expect you on the porch,
bag packed, ready to go.
No excuses.
Sir, you may not
wanna be here for this.
Um, I just, uh, woke
up and, uh, I found her.
That's all I know.
What's her date of birth?
Um...
[SNIFFLES]
INVESTIGATOR: Sir, your
daughter's date of birth?
DONALD: April...
April 4th, 1982. Okay.
And mother's maiden
name and place of birth.
My mother? Your
daughter's mother.
Uh, Bishop.
And place of birth? Phoenix.
INVESTIGATOR: Phoenix, Arizona?
This is our address.
Do you have someone
who can drive you?
I can drive.
Well, then if you'd
like to meet us there,
we can complete the
intake and take our samples,
and then you can make
your arrangements.
Okay?
Now, do you need a card?
Will you both be coming?
[DOOR OPENS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO]
[BELL DINGS ON COMPUTER]
I don't believe it. Walt,
you have to see this.
Forty from Te... Terre Haute.
Walt!
WALT: It's me.
Are you there? Hello.
I'm, um, just checking in.
Our friend says he thinks
everything went well.
Uh... That's... That's good.
So listen. Just
call me, all right?
SKYLER: Hey, Walt,
you've gotta come in here.
We just broke a
thousand dollars.
[FLUSHING]
Wow. All right.
I'm... I'm coming.
HANK: All right. Some of you
already know my brother-in-law.
He's a good man.
The doctors say this operation
has a real chance
of helping him.
Of course, they're also
saying they wanna be paid
in private islands so dig deep.
Biggest donation
gets a six-pack of my
very own Schraderbrau.
Home-brewed to silky perfection.
Smallest donation
gets two six-packs.
All right. All right.
Other than Gomie
here pees sitting down,
here's what we know.
Christian Ortega, a.k.a. Combo.
Shot dead by an unknown
assailant last month.
"Combo?" I hear you say.
"Why, I'm unfamiliar
with that name.
Was he a Nobel
laureate perchance?"
No. He was a dipshit
wannabe banger.
Now, no arrests, save
for stealing a baby Jesus
from a Knights of Columbus
manger back when he was 17.
This dude was so low-rep he
never showed up on our radar.
So why am I talking about him?
Anyone? Anyone?
Bueller?
He was dealing
Blue Sky. That's right.
Now, how is it that the
purest, most professional grade
of meth we've ever come across
is being slung by
the likes of that?
But wait. It gets better.
Since, oh-uh, baby-Jesus thief
there slowed a
bullet with his neck,
the blue stuff's vanished
from town, okay?
Not a speck to be
found in Albuquerque.
Now, why is that?
Well, because maybe
your Heisenberg's in prison.
So says A.P.D. They
think they got their man.
I know you don't buy
it, but maybe it's true.
James Edward Kilkelly, yeah.
A.P.D. thinks this
is our mastermind.
You believe that, I
got a bridge to sell you.
Hey, he copped to it, didn't he?
What, for an extra pudding cup
every night at Los Lunas, huh?
Maybe, uh, if you give
him a pack of cigarettes,
he'll tell you what he
did with Jimmy Hoffa.
No, no, no. No, no,
no. I've been thinking.
Top-shelf product like this?
It doesn't fall off the
face of the earth, okay?
The way I see it, raw talent's
bound to pop up somewhere.
It's like Whack-A-Mole. So
I've been making phone calls.
Local police departments,
small-town sheriffs.
Haven't had much luck inside
the Land of Enchantment.
But outside, I've got
reports of the blue stuff
making a scene here in Texas,
Arizona, Colorado, and Nevada.
In fact, everywhere but here.
Almost as if somebody wised
up, stopped shitting where they eat.
Now, I say Heisenberg's
still out there.
I say he's gone regional.
Only he's still
right here in town.
Come on, 2800.
Come on, big 28. You can do it.
Only 30 more
dollars. Thirty more.
[BELL DINGS ON COMPUTER] [GASPS]
Fo... Forty dollars!
Twenty-eight ten.
Yes! Yes! Ha-ha-ha.
SKYLER: Who's gonna be next?
WALT: Your guy found him?
Where is he?
Okay, listen.
No, no, I don't care.
You have your guy pick...
Saul. Just shut... Saul.
Saul, shut up and
give me the address.
MAN: I don't recommend it.
A.P.D.'s been known
to sit on this place,
keep an eye on the
comings and goings.
Are they here now?
Well, I don't see any
sign, but that's the point.
Police could be the least of it.
You could just get
mugged or shot.
How about you go
on home, Walter?
Let me handle this.
Yo.
[MAN COUGHING]
[MOANING]
Jesse.
Jesse. Jesse. Look at me, son.
Wake up. Wake up. Hey.
I ain't got nothing for
you, man. It's all gone.
Jesse, damn it, wake up. Just...
Jesse, Jesse. Jesse, it's me.
Okay, it's me.
It's Walt. It's Walt.
Jesse.
Yeah. Come on,
let's get out of here.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm good. Come
on. Help me out now.
I'm good. I'm good. Right
here, man. Right here.
Listen, Jesse, you
are not good right here.
You are not good
at all. You hear?
Now, you just put your
arms around me. Come on.
You're gonna stand up,
and we're gonna... We're
gonna walk out of here, okay?
We're gonna take you
someplace nice and safe.
That's it. Now, let's go.
Come on. Here we go.
[SOBBING]
WALT: Shh, shh, shh.
I killed her.
What? I killed her. It was me.
I killed her, man.
I killed her. No.
Jesse, look at me. Look at me.
You didn't kill anybody.
I loved her.
I loved her more than anything.
No, no. No.
[♪♪♪]
I haven't given much thought
to the programs, to be honest.
I guess they should be, uh...
I don't know. Just... Just
use your best judgment.
There's no yellow dress here.
It's all... It's all
black and gray.
When's the last time you saw
her ever wearing a yellow dress?
What about blue?
Blue's better than black, right?
No, no. Not dark
blue. More like...
Well, um... Not
super-bright, either.
I mean, blue is blue.
No. No cleavage.
Long sleeves.
Yeah. It's nice.
It's nice.
[YAWNS]
Oh, big, big yawn, Holly.
I know what you
feel like. I'm tired too.
Okay, sweetie. WALT JR.: Yes.
[BELL DINGS ON COMPUTER]
Yes.
Here we go.
Here we go. Yes.
[BELL DINGS ON COMPUTER]
Would you mind turning
that thing down or off?
Junior. Hey.
The dinging. Just
turn down the volume.
Dad, it... It's money.
Just please do it, okay.
The noise is
disturbing the baby.
SKYLER: Marie,
slow down. I can't...
Oh, my God. You are kidding me.
Sure. Of course.
Any day after school.
Okay, um. Wait. I'm gonna...
Let me tell him and
I'll call you right back.
Okay.
[BEEPS OFF]
Guess what. What?
You are gonna be
in the newspaper.
N-No way.
One of Aunt Marie's
patients works at the Journal,
when she told him about
the website and the donations,
he went to his editor,
and they're gonna
do a story about you.
For real? Yep.
They're coming to interview
you with a photo and everything.
WALT JR.: Awesome.
It'll mean more hits.
And more contributions.
Wow.
HANK: East of Scottsdale?
Let me guess. Not talking.
[SIGHS]
Nope. Not a one.
Somebody somewhere
is running one tight ship.
All right, chief.
Yeah. Thanks a lot.
Yeah. You too.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
ASAC: Agent Schrader,
can you spare a moment?
Yes, sir. Absolutely.
Gentlemen, this is Supervising
Agent Hank Schrader.
Agent Schrader,
I'd like you to meet
Andrew Coffman
of the Adobe Hotel.
Hey, nice to meet
you. Nice to meet you.
Paul Canterna of
Canterna Real Estate.
Hey, it's a pleasure.
Good to meet you.
And Gustavo Fring of
Los Pollos Hermanos.
Please, just Gus. Hi, Gus.
Gotta tell you, you guys
make some killer chicken.
Ha-ha, thank you very much.
These gentlemen are underwriting
this year's Fun
Run, and I thought
I would give them a tour.
Absolutely. Get to see
what you're supporting.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Can you tell us a little
about your work here?
Oh, yes, the Albuquerque office
covers everything from
drug-related money laundering
to interdiction of illicit
substances crossing the border.
Now, the group that I supervise
focuses on methamphetamine,
which is a growing problem
in the country, unfortunately.
Terrible. Yeah. It is indeed.
Now, we've had some
successes locally,
but overall the supply
seems to be growing.
I gotta tell you,
community outreach,
like this Fun Run,
one of the most powerful
weapons we have.
Anything we can do.
Thank you. Thank you, Hank.
Gentlemen. Thanks.
Sure. Thank you.
Is this one of your agents?
Oh, uh, yeah, no, no, that's...
That's my brother-in-law.
He's got a health issue.
We're... We're trying to...
Oh, I'm... I'm very sorry.
What...? What
sort of health issue?
Lung cancer. Oh,
that's a rough one.
Oh, hey, hey, you don't...
You don't have to do that.
Please. Please.
I'm... I'm happy to do it.
Thank you very
much. You're welcome.
[♪♪♪]
Uh, just so you know, I
won't be back for a while.
I'm gonna have my
surgery on Friday.
I'm hopeful it'll go well.
But if not, Saul will
take care of things.
He's got your money.
He's keeping it for you.
Look, Jesse, lingering on
things doesn't help, believe me.
Just try and focus on
getting better, okay?
I deserve this.
What?
What you said in the desert.
I get it, what you meant.
I deserve whatever happens.
Oh, shit.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Oh, oh. There he is.
[WHISPERING] Walt, they're
doing a feature on Walter Jr.
We called you about 50 times.
Marie, I thought we were just
talking about a newspaper story.
Yeah, yeah, I know, I know,
but I thought, you know,
if it's good enough
for the Journal,
then why not TV?
So I went for it.
This is him? Yes.
This is Dad. Great.
Let's get everyone
over here on the couch.
I'm thinking Walt
Jr. In the middle,
Mom and Dad on either side.
Mom and Dad?
How much money
have you raised so far?
Six thousand, three
hundred and sixty dollars,
but there's more
coming in all the time.
Wow, that's amazing.
SKYLER: We don't
even know what to say.
It's just... It's
been incredible.
Judging from the things you
and other folks have
written about him,
your dad must be quite a
guy. Yeah. He is. He's the best.
You don't wanna lose
him, do you, Walter?
WALT JR.: N-n-none of us do.
We love him.
REPORTER: He's
a good man, isn't he?
WALT JR.:
Absolutely. Ask anyone.
Anybody. He's a great
father, a great teacher.
He knows, like, everything
there is to know about chemistry.
He's patient with you, and
he's always there for you.
He's... He's just decent.
And he always
does the right thing.
And that's how he
teaches me to be.
REPORTER: Would
you say he's your hero?
WALT JR.: Oh, yeah.
Yes, ma'am. Totally.
M-My dad is my hero.
D-D-Does that put him to sleep?
This one just
relaxes him a little.
We're almost ready.
We'll be taking you
in in just a minute.
Okay. Thank you.
Well...
Here we are. Yeah.
R-R-Relax... Relaxed yet?
As a matter of fact...
Wow.
I don't know what this
stuff is, but it's pretty great.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Yeah, it looks like it.
[CHUCKLES]
We'll be here when you wake up.
Well, I'll be looking for you.
Oh, they'll probably want
me to take your glasses.
Mm. Yeah, you better.
Yeah, okay.
Okay. I got them.
[CHUCKLES]
Where's your phone?
Hm?
Your cell phone.
Did you bring it?
Which one?
I'm... I'm pret...
I'm pretty sure he didn't...
He didn't bring it, Mom.
Okay.
[♪♪♪]
♪ Oh, there's a receipt
Where my money goes ♪
♪ Who need some new food
And 10 pounds of clothes ♪
♪ Wrapped in a dare
President's wife ♪
♪ Scissors and rock
Paper and knife ♪
♪ It's big and it's
slow Roses in rain ♪
♪ Black in its good
light Pleasure and pain ♪
♪ It's life ♪
♪ Life ♪
DELCAVOLI: Well,
first things first.
How old is that baby now?
When do I get to meet her?
You know I was actually
thinking of bringing her today, but...
She's, um, seven weeks tomorrow.
Se... Seven, right? Yeah.
Yeah, oh, hey, I have a...
A picture here
somewhere. Ah. Heh.
Oh. She's beautiful. Thanks.
Always a relief to say
that and actually mean it.
[ALL CHUCKLE]
How's your pain level,
Walt? Uh, it's... It...
Very low, basically.
BRAVENEC: Shortness of breath?
A bit, but much better. Good.
Well, your margins look good.
Obviously, I can't
foresee the future,
but even
conservatively speaking,
I can say that you bought
yourself some real time here.
There's no reason
not to be optimistic.
That's great. Heh.
That is great.
Thank you, doctor.
So, um, when could he get
back to his normal routine?
He can ease into it now. Okay.
And, uh, can he go
back to work or..?
I'd give it a few more weeks.
Make sure you
avoid any heavy lifting
and continue to
get plenty of rest.
Um, but he can be on his own?
I mean, just more,
you know, independent.
Yes. Use your best judgment.
Okay. Well...
Now, that's good news
for you, huh, honey?
Heh. One less baby in the house.
Don, hey. Hey, Stew.
Hey, welcome back.
Thanks. It's good to be back.
Jesus. We... We were
all so sorry to hear.
Yes. Thanks.
Terrible thing. Just...
But you know, we've all been
thinking about you and, uh,
you been doing
okay? I'm doing okay.
After a certain point,
time off doesn't help
so I figured I'd rather be here.
Focus on work. Sure. Absolutely.
Yeah.
Well, see you inside.
MAN: Continue to
descend through 1500.
DONALD: Headed downwind
for a left base on Runway 17.
Number 26-Tango,
descend to maintain 13,000.
Truth or Consequences
altimeter, two-niner-niner-eight.
Pima-311, contact
Albuquerque Center 134.6.
Juliet-5-Bravo,
ident, say altitude.
Juliet-5-Bravo, roger.
Clear direct to Winslow.
I think I may just keep this.
Sky?
What do you think? Hm?
Doesn't look so bad, right?
What are you doing?
I'm going to Hank and
Marie's for the weekend.
Since when? I'm
taking the baby with me.
Marie will pick up
Walter Jr. from school.
You'll have the house
to yourself for two days.
I want you to pack
your things and leave.
Why would I do that?
Hank has offered to help
since you shouldn't be
doing any heavy lifting. Skyler.
I want you gone by
Monday morning, I want...
I want you gone.
Okay. Can you at
least tell me why?
Because you're a liar, Walt.
Two cell phones, after all.
What?
Right before your surgery,
I asked if you had
packed your cell phone,
and you said, "Which one?"
When?
Skyler, I was medicated.
I mean, I-I-I could have
said the world was flat.
You know what I think?
I think you accidentally
told the truth.
Honey, we have been over this.
Asked and answered, right?
Then it got me thinking again,
about all the strange behavior.
Not the least of which
was the disappearance.
Out of my mind with
worry, calling hospitals,
checking the morgue.
Your fugue state?
I had to believe that, didn't I?
I had to find a way.
I mean, who would
lie about such a thing?
You tell me, Skyler.
You tell me exactly what it
is you think I'm lying about.
[CHUCKLES]
What? An affair?
I'm having an affair.
Is that what you think?
That's what I was thinking.
Yeah. For the last few weeks.
With whom? Who am
I having an affair with?
Well, my guess was
Gretchen Schwartz.
Something was going on
between you. I just knew.
Jesus. Skyler.
Get me a Bible to swear
on, if that's what it takes.
I am not having an
affair with Gretchen.
Oh, I know. I know you're
not. Because I asked her.
It really took me forever
to get in touch with her.
She was ducking
my calls for weeks.
So I finally left a message:
"What exactly is going on
between you and my husband?"
I thought that'd get
her attention and it did.
So she called me back,
and she finally told me.
The money for your treatment,
Gretchen and Elliott
didn't give you a dime.
They paid for nothing.
You refused every
offer they made you.
But that didn't make sense,
because I checked with
Delcavoli and the hospital,
and-and not
including your surgery,
we're nearly paid up.
Over $100,000.
Out of where? Out of thin air?
But then,
[WHISPERING] I
called your mother.
Yeah. Oh.
Thanks for that too.
But I thought, you know,
maybe she has some money
that I don't know about.
Maybe she contributed.
[SIGHS]
It's possible.
It-It turns out that not only
is the money not
from your mother,
she didn't even know
that you have cancer.
You never went to see her.
I-I-I dropped
you at the airport.
I picked you up.
You were gone for four days,
and yet she swears
that you were never there.
Lies on top of
lies on top of lies.
Skyler.
Could you,
just once,
do me the courtesy
of not denying it?
Skyler.
Skyler, don't do this, please.
I... I...
Skyler, please don't go.
[PANTING]
If I tell you the
truth, will you stay?
Stay, and I will
tell you everything.
Whatever it is,
I'm afraid to know.
[ENGINE STARTS]
DONALD: Wayfarer-515,
radio check.
Wayfarer-515,
Albuquerque Center, roger.
Climb and maintain 13,000.
Juliet-Mike-21,
squawk 4201, ident.
climb and maintain 17,000.
Clear direct to
Albuquerque via the...
Aircraft calling,
please stand by.
Jane-Mike-21, turn,
heading... Disregard.
Aircraft calling, say again.
Lifeguard-46, clear
direct Albuquerque,
climb and maintain 17,000.
Juliet-Mike-21, turn
left, heading 115.
Wayfarer-515,
traffic 3 o'clock, KingAir,
turn left, heading 085.
Sierra-alpha-alpha,
contact Albuquerque
Center, 134.6.
Contact Albuquerque
[BEEPING] [HUMMING]
Wayfarer-515, descend to 10,000.
Juliet-Mike-21, do you have
that traffic at your 9 o'clock?
Wayfarer-515, do
you have that traffic?
[HUMMING]
[EXPLOSION]
[♪♪♪]