[WIND BLOWING]
[♪♪♪]
[BENNY MARDONES' "INTO THE
NIGHT" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Hey, Captain America.
What's up, brother? Hey, bro.
[POLICE RADIO SQUAWKING]
[DOOR CHIMES BEEP]
[SIGHS]
This is stupid.
WALT: You got a better idea?
Okay, fun. Whatever.
So when do we, you know?
WALT: We don't, for now.
No cooking until
things settle down.
Settle down? I
thought you're the one
that said nothing's changed.
Look, I just put my
family through an ordeal
that they're just now
starting to accept, okay?
I can't...
Uh. That's too expensive.
Look, I can't leave my house
for more than 20 minutes
without my wife worrying.
I need time to mend fences.
Okay, so while you're fixing
fences, what about me, huh?
Your A-hole brother-in-law
took all my money.
That's $600.
Okay, what about the rest?
Rest of what?
Half your money's mine.
Fifty-fifty partners.
That's our business motto.
Meaning what, exactly?
That I suffer for
your carelessness?
You're the one who wanted
to work with Tuco, okay?
If it weren't for that, none
of this would've happened.
[DOOR CHIME BEEPS]
Just be cool. We'll talk
about this later, okay?
As for now, no
contact. Understood?
Whoa, whoa. Where are you going?
I leave first.
[SIGHS]
Walt!
WALT: In the kitchen.
Hey.
Hey. I didn't know you were
allowed to touch the stove.
Hilarious, Groucho.
Go on, grab a seat.
Juice is on the table.
What?
SKYLER: Mm, oh,
good morning, honey.
Hey, Mom.
Dad's cooking breakfast.
But don't worry. I'm
also doing all the dishes.
Huh? Huh? Eh?
Nice? Follow me.
There's also orange
juice and grapefruit juice,
which, personally, as you
know, I've never been a fan of.
But considering
all the polyphenols
and the limonoids, can't hurt.
Walt, you didn't
have to do this.
I wanted to.
Grapefruit juice?
Yes, please. Thanks.
There you go. Honey?
Um, no, I'll stick with
orange, thank you.
All right, well, dig in, dig in.
Pancakes are not getting hotter.
Wow.
Yeah. [LAUGHS] There you go.
WALT: All right.
Got one. Steely Dan.
Uh, no. Yes, absolutely.
No, in terms of
pure musicianship,
I would put them up against
any current band you can name.
You wouldn't know
any current bands.
[CAR HORN HONKING]
That's besides the point.
Have a good day, honey.
You too.
Ah! Boz Scaggs.
There's another one.
Ugh! Boz Scaggs. Mm-hm.
Whoever they are.
Bye. Thanks for breakfast.
Bye. You're welcome.
Listen, tell Louis
to drive carefully.
All right.
[CHUCKLES] [DOOR CLOSES]
Our son doesn't know
who Boz Scaggs is.
We have failed as parents.
Come to think of it, I barely
know who Boz Scaggs is.
Stop it.
Give me your plate.
No, no. I'll get
it. I'll get it. Yeah.
Thank you. Mm-hm.
Hey, uh, listen,
in the calendar section
um, all week long
there's a fiction
writer's seminar at UNM.
And, you know, probably
talking about how to get published
and that sort of thing. Yeah?
Mm-hm. Hm.
Yeah, so, anyway, I
thought maybe you might...
I mean, I'll go
with you if you like.
Oh, and, uh,
you know, I was thinking about
what you asked
me the other night.
You know, you were wondering
if I had a second cell phone.
And, well, I've been
thinking about that a lot,
and I think what you heard
was my cell phone
alarm going off.
Yes.
I've been using it a lot
as a medication reminder
to, uh, well, remind me
to take my medication.
And, uh, well,
the weird thing is that
the alarm sound is
almost exactly the same
as the regular phone ring
which is really a poor design,
if you ask me. But I
think that was probably it.
I tried to go in and change
it to a different sound
other than the
phone ring, but...
They so overcomplicate
these things.
Anyway, it was, uh, probably
just as well that I lost it.
There's got to be a new
one on the market by now.
You know, if we do this thing at
UNM, maybe on the way home
we can stop by, and I
can get a new cell phone.
[DOOR SLAMS]
Skyler?
[CAR DOOR OPENS AND SLAMS]
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
Skyler?
[DIALING]
[LINE RINGING]
[BUZZING]
[SNIFFS]
Ready?
Yo, for what, might help.
[SIGHS]
Not another intervention.
GARDINER: Jesse Bruce Pinkman,
pursuant to Section 47-8-13
of the New Mexico
Real Property Code,
you are hereby
given notice to vacate
the premises listed
as 9809 Margo,
Albuquerque, 87104.
Wait. What? You're kicking
me out of my own house?
It's your aunt Ginny's
house. And she gave it to me.
She never gave it to you, Jesse.
GARDINER: You were allowed
residentiary privileges.
Your parents have always
been the property owners.
Look, we talked
about this, okay?
I'd sell the house,
we'd split it fifty-fifty.
That was the deal.
What the hell happened?
What happened is you're
a speed manufacturer.
No, I'm not. What?
MRS. PINKMAN: A DEA agent came
looking for you, Jesse.
He came to our front door.
Okay, because I've
actually been helping them,
which I could get into a
lot of trouble for telling you,
so you're welcome.
I saw your basement.
Oh, yeah.
I was worried, so I went
over there and I let myself in,
and I found your laboratory.
You guys have your own key?
[SCOFFS]
Manufacture of a Schedule
II controlled substance
is a second-degree felony.
Under federal asset seizure,
the government can
take the entire house.
It's not even there
anymore. I cleaned it all out.
Son, we can't stop you
from ruining your life,
but you will not drag
us down with you.
GARDINER: Vacate
the house in 72 hours.
Otherwise, your parents
have authorized me
to contact the authorities.
Is that clear?
Do you have any
questions for us?
Three days, Mr. Pinkman.
Come on.
[CAR APPROACHING]
[CAR DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
Hi. Hey.
Hey, I, uh, fixed
the garage door.
Great.
Yeah.
One track was bent.
That's why it was bouncing.
Okay.
Where were you today? Out.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, everything's fine.
Hey, you know,
for what it's worth,
I was thinking about going
back to those meetings,
the cancer support group.
I think that that's good.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, that's good.
Uh, you were... You were
right on the money about that.
Yeah, that's...
It's good to, you know,
talk about things.
I think that's great.
Yeah.
[WATER RUNNING]
MRS. PINKMAN: Jesse.
Jesse. Hey, Jesse.
[GASPS]
You don't answer your phone?
[SIGHS]
Yeah, no, I've just been
pretty busy. How'd you...?
Oh, right, you have that key.
Um, hey, listen. Um...
So I've been thinking a
lot about our conversation
we had the other day,
and I... I completely get
why Dad totally tweaked
off on me like that and...
It's not just your
father, Jesse.
No, I... I... I know.
I know. I know.
I'm just saying it was,
you know, a really,
really big wake-up
call for me, you know,
which is why I
wanted to talk to you.
You know, I've been
thinking real seriously
about business school, actually.
You can do the whole thing
from your computer now...
No, Mom, Mom.
Hey, hey, this is good.
You know, we're talking,
starting a dialogue.
The time for talking
has passed, Jesse.
Hey. Hey.
What the hell, yo?
I thought this was
just a wake-up call.
We are putting it in storage.
When you decide to grow
up, you can have it back.
Why don't you grow up, Mom?
Ginny wanted me here. All right?
I was the one who
took care of her.
I took her to her appointments
and made her lunch every day.
I earned this.
You did not make
her lunch every day.
What did you do, huh?
She's lying there dying,
and where the hell are you?
Don't start with me. Now what?
You've decided
to, oh, I don't know,
make your eldest son homeless?
Wow! Great family, Mom.
Why are you like this? Why?
You have two sets of keys
and the padlock to the garage.
Leave them on the kitchen
counter when you leave.
No, Mom, Mom, Mom.
Hey, where am I supposed to go?
I don't know, sweetheart.
But please turn
your life around.
Yeah, this is gonna help
big time with that. Bitch!
Jeez.
[SIZZLING]
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Oh, hey, Mr. White.
Hey, well, now, that's the way.
Don't just sit out
there honking.
Come in and say hello.
Hey, we've got omelets.
You want an omelet?
No, I'm good.
New Mexican Christmas
style, red and green chilies.
No. Thank you, though.
Flynn and me gotta get going.
Who's Flynn? Flynn.
He's your, uh...
Flynn? Yeah.
So?
So? Nothing.
You ready? Like it.
Bye, Mr. White. Okay.
Bye.
Flynn? You know
about this Flynn thing?
Mm-hm.
Huh?
Okay. Flynn. Yeah.
As in what, Errol?
I don't know. It's what he
likes to be called these days.
What's wrong with Walter Jr.?
Don't take it personally.
He wants his own identity.
You think he... He
told Louis about me?
About the blackout?
Louis is his friend, Walt,
and your
disappearance upset him.
Hey, I made omelets.
[PHONE RINGING]
I'm going out, but
thanks, though.
Where you going?
[PHONE RINGING]
Can you get the phone, please?
Yeah. Yeah. Absolutely.
White residence.
JESSE: Yo, it's me.
Is this a good time?
What part of "no contact"
didn't you understand?
I know, but there's a problem.
I don't care. We agreed.
No amount of
pay-per-view channels
is gonna make any difference.
Honey, we're happy with
our cable provider, right?
Yeah, we're happy.
Skyler? Sky?
Where are you going?
Can you at least tell me that?
Out. [PHONE RINGS]
Ooh. Should
probably get that, Walt.
I'll be back in a few hours.
Skyler.
[PHONE RINGING]
What? Yo, I get
I shouldn't call,
but I'm in a situation over
here and I need my money.
I just gave you $600.
Yeah, and thanks,
Daddy Warbucks,
but that was before
my housing situation
went completely
testicular on me, okay?
You smoked the
entire 600, didn't you?
What? No. Yes.
No. Look, Jesse,
your problems are just that:
Your problems.
No contact. Do
not call here ever.
When the moment
is right, I will call...
Mr. White, you're not listening.
They're kicking
me out of my house.
God! God!
[LINE RINGING]
[PHONE RINGS]
You son of a bitch.
Uh! Son of a bitch.
Oh, hey, thank you.
Thank you so much.
Thanks, man. Oh, hey, guy!
You forgot something! Yeah!
You forgot your ice trays!
You're gonna need the ice trays!
Hey, you forgot
something here! Take this!
[BASS GUITAR BEING PLAYED]
♪ Black is the color ♪
♪ But beauty is the game ♪
♪ The beasties come To get me ♪
♪ But I don't feel The pain ♪
♪ Fallacies, fallacies ♪
[MICROWAVE
BEEPING] Hold on, buddy.
Yo, we should get Twaughthammer
up and running again, yo.
I'm serious. I know.
That sounded tight.
Hey, thanks again, P.
I made sure this stucknut
exterminator, you know,
put me on his speed dial.
Two nights tops. Oh, no, hey,
you still staying at
your aunt's on Margo?
Yeah. I'm thinking of
moving. Nob Hill, probably.
Jess-a-matic. Living the dream.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
Okay, buddy. You're
gonna eat your carrots
like we talked about, right?
Too hot.
No, no, buddy. Remember. Okay?
Come on, yes.
Listen, hey, talk to me, man.
Are you still having
mad relations out there?
You can talk to me.
I won't hate a player.
I can't lie. It's pretty hectic
out there, female-wise.
[SIGHS]
Damn. I'm hating, man.
See, that's why we
need to get the Hammer
up and running, you know?
Get you out of the house.
How awesome would that be?
Come on. Look. What? Hm?
I cut all the green
parts off like you...
Just eat them. Please?
We... We should do this.
You know, track down Cheevo
and Anthony and demo up.
Get back in the scene.
I'm sorry, man. Just hold
on one second, all right?
Okay, listen. How about you
take a bite of your sandwich,
and then you take...
[DOOR OPENS]
Mommy's home.
Hi. Hello.
Hey, honey, you
remember Jesse Pinkman?
His house is getting bug bombed
and I said he could
crash a few nights.
Hey, Jesse. Hey.
Paul, could you help me
in the bedroom with these?
Sure. Yeah.
[SIGHS]
Yeah, I used to
not like carrots too.
SARA: Hey, Hen,
I think it's someone's nap time.
Come on.
[CHUCKLES]
Man, oh, dude, you're
gonna... You're gonna kill me.
I totally spaced
that the in-laws are
crashing this weekend.
You got other people to call?
Hey, no, that's... That's cool.
I got tons of people. Yeah.
Yeah? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yo, in-laws?
Sucks to be you, P.
Yeah. Yeah, I know, huh?
Here.
See you, man.
It's good to see you.
Look, I'm asking to crash
three, maybe four nights, and...
Look, I already called Badger,
all right? I called everyone.
I need a solid here, bro.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, whatever.
[SIGHS]
All right. All right.
Hey, how about this?
[SIGHS]
What if it's just for tonight?
[GRUNTS]
[MUMBLING]
[SIGHS]
Wait. No, you cannot be serious.
You cannot be serious!
Hey.
Someone took your bike, man.
Not cool.
[PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[YELLING AND GRUNTING]
[LIQUID SLOSHING]
[JESSE SCREAMING]
[COUGHING]
[GASPING]
[WHIMPERING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[CRIES]
[COUGHS]
[COUGHING]
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
Morning.
Oh, hey.
Morning. Um...
Where did...? Where did Mom go?
Out.
Um, where's breakfast?
Hey.
Let's go do something.
Uh, like what?
Something fun.
WALT: All right, ready?
Let's, uh, put it in gear.
Is your foot on the...?
Okay. Good. Yeah. I got it.
Good.
Yes. Nice and smooth.
Good. Just like that.
Good. I like the hands
at 10 and 2. Very nice.
Okay, let's slow down here
to a stop in preparation
for a left-hand turn. Okay.
All right. You might want
to go easier on the brake.
Sorry about that. That's okay.
All right. You're doing fine.
Much better than last time, huh?
Oh, yeah, Louis
has been helping me.
Has he?
Good. Good. Okay.
Don't forget the
turn indic... Good.
I'll stop talking. You
know what you're doing.
And let's make
that left-hand turn.
Nice and smooth. Very nice.
Right hand.
Good. Good. Okay.
Oh, are you using both feet?
Yeah.
No. Wait. Wait. No,
Walt. You can't do that.
You can't use one
foot on each pedal.
Why not? Because you can't.
Stop, Walt, okay?
Just stop, please.
Right. All right.
Dad, this is way easier.
Come on. There's the easy way,
and then there's
the right way, right?
So let's just try it
again, right foot only.
All right. Okay?
Okay, just... You don't have
to... Okay. All right. That's fine.
Just... That's okay. That's
okay. Just try it again.
Here we go. Let's
just, just try it again.
Okay. [TIRES SCREECH]
Don't... Just easy.
Okay, okay, good. Great.
That was better. See?
Right? Better? Right.
The gas, the brake,
the gas, the brake.
I can't do this.
My legs don't work that way.
Your legs are fine. You
just have to stick with it.
Don't set limits for yourself,
Walt. You're all right.
All right. We'll
get this. I promise.
Now let's just try
again, all right?
All right. Here we
go. Here we go.
Okay, well, you don't need
to, you know, just take off.
But all right, here we go.
Slow it down just a little bit.
All right, we have a
turn coming up here,
so prepare to apply the brakes.
Prepare, Walt, for the
brakes. Brakes, the brakes.
I'm braking. You're
using both feet again.
It's not stopping. That's
the gas. Use the brake.
The brake. Brake, brake, brake!
Okay.
That's one way to stop.
I told you.
Flynn.
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS]
[GUN COCKING]
MAN: Hands up, asshole!
Yo, yo, it's cool. So
help me, I will spread you.
No, please, no, all right?
It's me, okay? It's Jesse.
All right? Look, this is my RV.
You towed it. Your
cousin Badger, remember?
What the hell are
you doing here?
You smell like shit.
It's a long story.
So I fixed up your felonious
rolling laboratory here,
750 for the repair.
Make it a grand,
counting the toilet
plus the 500 you already owe me,
and you're good to
drive on out of here
to someplace far away. Upwind.
Okay, um...
Here's the thing.
I can't pay you today.
But I can pay you
this week, all right?
Seventeen fifty?
We'll make it 1750,
for, like, you know, interest.
I thought your
word was your bond.
No, it totally is.
Definitely. I just
don't have the money
at this particular moment.
But I will, soon.
Here's my counteroffer.
I kick you out. I take
payment from your inventory.
I know a guy that'll pay
premium for this kind of crap.
All right. Two grand. Okay?
Two days, 2 grand.
That's totally fair.
Just don't take my
cook stuff. All right?
That's all I got left.
Please, all right? I really...
God, I really need a break here.
Okay?
Clovis, come on.
I don't know. There's a
bunch of stuff in there.
There's something called
methylamine. Me... Meth...
However the hell
you pronounce it.
Methylamine.
I don't know. I banged on
it. It sounds pretty full to me.
Holy shit. How much?
[ENGINE STARTS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
Hey! Hey!
[SHOWER RUNNING]
WALT: Skyler.
Louis took Walt to school.
I was thinking maybe
this would be a
good time to talk.
I dreamt that I owned an
antique bicycle repair shop.
In Ireland.
Weird.
Sounds weird.
I wanted to apologize.
For everything.
My
Desire for privacy.
My emotional
unavailability.
Having cancer
doesn't excuse all that.
I haven't been a
good partner to you,
and for that,
I'm very sorry.
I love you.
And I love this family.
And I just
want to make sure that
we don't lose contact.
Thank you.
Okay.
I agree.
Is that it?
Oh, God.
God, how long are
you gonna do this?
Do what? This.
Not... Not talking to me.
Going out all day and...
And refusing to tell me where.
You are obviously angry
with me about something,
so let's talk about it.
Oh, God.
I feel like you're upset with me
because you think that
I'm up to something.
Like what? I have
no idea, Skyler.
What, that I'm having
an affair? Is that it?
Is that what you think?
Is that why you
asked me about the...
Some other phone?
Because you think
that I'm being unfaithful?
I don't know.
Okay.
So ask me.
Why?
Would you even tell me?
Yes. I would.
Of course I would.
And no. I'm not. I'm not
having an affair, okay?
Now, what do I do
to prove that to you?
Swear an oath? Okay.
My right hand to God.
I'm not having an affair.
I heard you, Walt.
You're not having an affair.
Congratulations.
No, you know what?
Congratulations to you, Skyler.
Great job. Mm-hm.
I mean, what is this?
What do I have to do?
I'm trying to talk
to you, and you...
Okay, so talk, Walt.
Shut up and say something
that isn't complete bullshit.
You want to know
what you have to do?
You have to tell me what's
really going on right now.
Today. No more excuses.
No more apologies.
No more of these...
These obvious,
desperate breakfasts.
You don't want to lose
contact with me, Walt?
Good.
Then tell me.
Now.
Tell you what?
Skyler.
What is it you want me
to tell you? I don't know.
We're not done here. Skyler.
Do you know what
I've done for this family?
[ENGINE STARTS]
What the...?
[TIRES SCREECH]
Yo, I'm really sorry, okay?
What is wrong with you?
Why are you blue?
Oh, Jesus. I'm sorry.
Let's just say it starts with
my parents being greedy,
kleptomaniac douche bags.
Are you actually this stupid?
No, look. I know
this isn't a optimal...
To come to my house
and park on my street,
driving this vehicle.
I mean, what the
hell is wrong with you?
I'm... I'm really asking.
Nothing. I'm sorry. I just...
What if Skyler
had seen you, huh?
What then? What was
the plan then, genius, huh?
I don't know. You don't know.
You know why you don't know?
Because you don't
think. That's why.
You don't think.
You never figured out
how to think, did you,
Pinkman? Hey, I said I was sorry.
I just need my half of
the money, and I will go.
Your half?
There is no your
half of the money.
There is only my all of
it. Do you understand?
Why...? Why should I be penalized
because of your sloppiness?
Look, that is completely
uncool, all right?
We agreed, fifty-fifty partners.
Partners in what? What
exactly do you do here?
I've been meaning to ask,
because I'm the producer, right?
I cook. But from
what I can tell,
you are just a drug addict.
You are a pathetic junkie,
too stupid to
understand and follow
simple rudimentary instructions.
Too stupid to re...
[GRUNTING]
[CHOKING] [GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
Do it.
[COUGHING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Try not to touch anything.
[♪♪♪]
Want some breakfast?
[DOOR CHIME BEEPS]
[SIGHS]
♪ And ever day is the same ♪
♪ Since I met you ♪
♪ It's such a pretty
world Today ♪
♪ Knowing that you're mine ♪
♪ Knowing you're mine ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ And happiness Is
being close to you ♪
♪ And though the rain May fall ♪
♪ Our skies are always blue ♪
♪ If I look close enough ♪
♪ The sun will come
Shining through ♪
♪ It's such a pretty
world Today ♪
♪ Look at the sunshine ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Today and every day ♪
♪ Since I met you ♪
[♪♪♪]