[SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE]
[DOGS BARKING]
[PEOPLE SHOUTING IN SPANISH]
[ROCK SONG PLAYING
ON CAR STEREO]
What's up? How's it going?
All right.
What you need?
Yo, you buying or you
just stopping to envy?
Yeah. Punk bitches.
DIGITAL VOICE [ON PHONE]: Please
leave your message for 505-127-5223.
Record your
message after the tone.
To send a numeric page...
Bounce, little man.
Yo, Skinny, I'm up
on 2nd and Hazeltine,
getting eyeballed hard.
I got a bad feeling, man.
I need some backup.
Get your ass up here now.
[BEEPS OFF]
What's that thing in your ear?
What did I say? Get out of here.
What are you waiting for? Go.
[HORN HONKS]
[GUN COCKS]
[GUNSHOT]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[GURGLES]
[♪♪♪]
DELCAVOLI: Well, Walt, we've made
such headway with your treatments
that now it's time we
talked about sealing the deal.
Absolutely.
As you know,
my initial diagnosis was that
your cancer was inoperable.
That may no longer be the case.
We think now that a lobectomy
may be a viable option.
Maybe a pretty good option.
Dr. Bravenec is one of the
few surgeons in the country
performing lobectomies
after full-dosage radiation.
He's got a good track record.
Pretty good.
It sounds...
aggressive.
Yes. Very much so.
Understand that if you
don't have this surgery,
you're just waiting for
the cancer to spread.
And it will.
Now, through the
treatment you've had already,
we've bought you some time.
Maybe a lot, probably a little,
but that's all.
In my opinion,
if you're willing
to take some risk,
then this offers
the best chance.
[CLEARS THROAT]
How much would it cost?
I mean, I'm not
on your insurance.
I'd say between 170
and 200,000, all in.
For my part, I'd be willing
to write off what I can,
but mine isn't even
the biggest expense.
This is obviously
a big decision,
and you folks are gonna wanna
take some time to discuss it.
No.
I'll do it.
[WHISPERING] Um, Walt,
don't you think we should
at least talk this
through first?
I just think it's the way to go.
DELCAVOLI: I, uh, have to say,
I think it's the right choice.
I recommend that we
let the pneumonitis heal
for another couple of weeks,
and then we'll have at it.
Um, that's tricky. I, uh...
Oh.
BRAVENEC: When's the due date?
It's the, uh, 21st.
So two weeks and change?
Okay. I'll book the surgery
for four weeks from now.
That way Walter
can be on his feet
for the birth of your daughter.
But I wouldn't wait any longer.
[QUIETLY] Yeah.
[LOCK CLICKS]
Fourteen messages.
God.
JESSE [ON PHONE]: Yeah. It's me.
Where the hell were
you? I called, like, 20 times.
Working.
What is it?
Combo's dead.
Shot.
Which one is he?
You did not just say that to me.
Jesse, listen... That figures.
[SIGHS]
What's the word on the street?
No one's dropping no names.
Combo rang me
before it went down,
said a couple of dudes
were mad-dogging him,
trying to run him
up off the corner.
That's all I know.
Why'd we have to go
pushing into new turf, yo?
I mean, what'd you expect?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Is that all you got?
I'll do right by Combo's people.
Make sure you bust up
your cell and toss it, all right?
We'll figure it out.
I appreciate what
you're saying and all,
but with Combo gone and
Badger laying low out in Cali...
I'm on probation, man.
Fast track to Los Lunas.
We're on the verge
of making some
serious coin, Skinny.
What, you're gonna...?
You're gonna jump ship now?
This game we playing?
We don't got the
street cred to survive it.
Back when everyone
thought you killed Spooge,
maybe we were doing okay,
but that whole
thing-to-the-head thing, the ATM?
Yeah?
His junkie bitch copped to it.
Whole town knows it wasn't you.
[SIGHS]
Everyone knows?
Why didn't you say
something? I don't know, man.
Because we like you and all.
I'm telling you, just sit tight.
We'll get by.
All right? We'll
make it. Sorry, Jesse.
I'm out.
[DOOR OPENS, SHUTS]
We have had a bit of a setback.
I'm sorry but that's an
accurate description.
What else do you
want me to call it?
How about "your
fault"? How about that?
No, no, don't lay that on me.
You are in charge
of distribution.
You said expand the territory.
That doesn't mean
you become careless.
Guys, guys! Hey!
Who do I look
like, Maury Povich?
I'm not your marriage counselor.
Now, you're
professionals. Act like it.
Now. Setback. Go.
One of our dealers was murdered.
It was some kind of turf dispute
and apparently we lost.
And then everyone quit on us.
I mean, we have
absolutely no distribution.
Is there any way any of this
can be traced back to you?
Now, the police,
I'm talking about.
Well, there's
your silver lining.
How about you? How's
the, uh, health situation?
It's, uh, better. Do you mind?
Better?
Yeah, it's, uh...
It's looking a little
more positive.
I may have more
time than I thought.
Outstanding.
Now, as to your dead guy:
uh, occupational hazard.
Drug dealer getting shot?
I'm gonna go out on a limb here
and say it's been
known to happen.
Now, what about product on
hand? How's your inventory?
Thirty-eight and change.
Thirty-eight ounces? Grams?
Pounds.
You did say make hay
while the sun is shining.
[LAUGHING] Guys.
Why the long faces here?
I mean, you're
sitting on a gold mine.
A gold mine we can't sell.
We need a proper infrastructure.
We need foot soldiers
and we need dealers
on a street level
that are rock solid.
We need muscle and
we need enforcers.
Payback. That's what we need.
God.
I mean, this entire
process has just been so...
It's always been one step
forward and two steps back.
We need your help.
Look, let's start with
some tough love, all right?
Ready for this? Here goes.
You two suck at
peddling meth. Period.
So give up on trying
to do it all yourselves.
Hell, I'm amazed
you got this far.
Look, we are not going to deal
with another
high-level distributor.
No, thank you. We have
been down that road.
What, some tattooed speed freak?
No. What you two need is an
honest-to-God businessman.
All right? Somebody
who treats your product
like the simple high-margin
commodity that it is.
Somebody who ships out
of town, deals only in bulk.
Someone who's been doing this
for 20 years and
never been caught.
You know someone like that?
Let's just say I know a
guy who knows a guy.
Who knows another guy.
Let me make some calls,
see if I can get you a meeting.
Well, what's his name?
I have no idea.
He's very low profile.
He's careful like that.
[SIGHS]
You know, from what
I do hear about him,
he sounds a little like you.
ANNOUNCER [ON TV]: And
McDonald tabletops it, lands it.
He's coming to the end
and he's got the big fist pump.
Now Mueller's coming. Oh,
a double! Here he comes.
And he's coming to the
end and he takes second.
I need you to leave.
[TV TURNS OFF]
Look, there's, uh,
some stuff about me
you don't know and...
Like you're a drug dealer?
I kind of got that.
You pay in cash and
you use an alias, so...
[SIGHS]
One of my guys,
a friend who worked for me,
got murdered.
It was my fault. I put
him on that corner.
I'm gonna smoke some crystal
and I just think you should go,
being that you're in a
program and all and...
You could come
with me to a meeting.
[CHUCKLES]
No.
No meetings.
We could just get out of here.
It won't help. Yeah, it will.
And I don't need you
telling me that it won't.
I just...
All right, I really
just need you to go.
[MAN SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Sir? Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
[BOTH CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
You're late.
Yeah.
We're, uh... We're
in the big time now.
So where's the kingpin?
Your guess is as good as mine.
So you get the dude's name?
Nope.
So let me get this straight.
He's, uh... He's allowed
to know our names,
what we look like, but
not the other way around?
Why don't you get
yourself some food?
So we won't both sit
here with our Happy Meals,
looking like a couple chumps?
Gentlemen, is everything
to your satisfaction?
Fine, thanks.
This is nothing
but an ankle-grab.
I don't get you, man.
A week ago you talked like
you were all ready to hang it up.
We've nearly got 40
pounds we still need to sell.
Yeah, what about after?
After you gonna make up
some new magic number?
Like, "I got bills. I got
bills. I gotta make more."
What do you want
me to say, Jesse?
Things have changed. Oh, I know.
We got a guy killed.
You know what?
This is bullshit.
I'm out of here. Hey.
SKYLER: Oh.
I think she's waking
up from a nap.
She is certainly gonna wanna
get out and stretch those legs soon.
Mm. We're gonna have to
keep an eye on your fluids.
You're on the
low side of normal.
What? How...? How low?
It's not a problem unless
we see a growth drop-off,
so we're good.
We'll have you in for
an ultrasound next week
and keep an eye on things.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Hey.
Oh, man, you would
not believe the traffic.
That's why I left
40 minutes early.
Sorry. Hi. Hi.
What did I miss?
For your refrigerator.
Oh, my God.
Look at her.
Look. Heh-heh. Yeah.
God. It's like
she's here already.
I was just telling Skyler
everything looks great.
Okay, we've been talking
about it for months now.
It's time to make a decision.
You know what I'm
gonna say, don't you?
The C-section? Mm-hm.
And if it's a yes, we
need to schedule it.
Well, my, uh... My last
labor was pretty tough, so...
For the baby, um, I say yes.
Well, I agree, considering that
your fluids are on the low side.
I think it's best we
take her a little early.
So why don't we schedule it
for... On a week from Friday?
Ooh. Isn't that a
Friday the 13th?
[CHUCKLES]
We have a birthday.
Mm. The 16th.
I like it. Yeah.
You know, uh,
speaking of birthdays,
I've got to run
back to the office,
so I will see you later?
Oh. It's an hour before closing.
You're supposed
to be taking it easy.
Well, we're having a little
get-together for Ted's birthday
and I've gotta pick up the cake.
Why you?
Because I said I would?
It is the least I can do.
Okay? Yeah, okay. Yeah.
Bye. Bye.
[OPENS DOOR]
Let's get out of here.
You know, go do something.
Seriously.
You know that museum in
Santa Fe we talked about?
Let's take a drive.
Sure.
No, I cannot return that stock.
It's already been
drilled, it's been cut.
We're halfway through the job.
WOMAN [ON PA]: Mr. Beneke to the
shop, please. Mr. Beneke to the shop.
All right. Um...
Just let me think
about it, okay?
I gotta go.
Dean, I got... I gotta go.
Okay, all right.
ALL: Happy birthday.
Happy birthday.
Oh, my God. This is...
This is beautiful, guys.
Thank you very much.
Hurry. These candles aren't
gonna hold out much longer.
Wait a minute. Are
you making a wish?
You gotta make a wish.
Okay. Hm. Well, let's see.
The economy's in the toilet.
China's undercutting
us at every turn.
I'm at a loss.
Wait. Skyler? Yes?
I wanna hear it first.
Absolutely not. No way.
Come on. You cannot deny
your employer his birthday wish.
Yes, I can. Watch me. Please.
If this is your birthday wish,
I feel very, very sorry for you.
Come on. It was so
good last time. Come on.
That... It was ages ago.
And I'm... I'm enormous now.
And I don't look
anything like her anymore.
Not that I ever did.
I mean, come on.
You guys, these candles are
getting wax all over the place.
Seriously. Yes, come on, Skyler.
ALL [CHANTING]:
Skyler, Skyler, Skyler...
It's obscene.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday Mr. President ♪
♪ Of Beneke
Fabricators Incorporated ♪
[ALL LAUGHING]
♪ Happy birthday ♪
♪ To you ♪
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
That was fantastic.
Isn't she great, huh?
Okay, here we go.
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
WALT: He wasn't there.
SAUL [ON PHONE]:
Oh, he was there, all right.
What are you talking about?
I sat there for two hours.
Nobody came.
All I know is my contact
said he was there.
Are you sure you were
at the right restaurant?
WALT [ON PHONE]:
Yes, I'm positive.
Where was he? Who knows?
Maybe he stayed
out in the parking lot,
checked you out
with a telephoto lens,
didn't like the cut of your jib.
Anyway, it doesn't matter now
because my contact
says it's a no-go.
What? What do you mean?
No deal. No dice.
Shot at and missed.
Shit on and hit.
Wa-Wait a minute.
How can he make that decision
without even meeting me?
I told you, he's very cautious
who he does
business with, all right?
He's skittish, like a deer.
Call him back.
I'm sorry. I can't do that.
Yes, you can. Call him, Saul.
Hey, first of all, I never
called him, all right?
I called a guy who called
a guy who called a guy.
Second of all, it's over.
Understand? With
this particular individual,
all you get is the one shot.
[SIGHS]
Look, I'll see if I can scrape
something else together,
but don't get your hopes up.
No one else handles
that kind of bulk.
Ah! Damn it.
[♪♪♪]
Lucy, you must remember to have
the salt and pepper
shakers wiped.
Can I help you, sir?
Diet Coke, please.
And five minutes of your time.
What can I do for
you? Have a seat.
Please.
I would like to know why you
wouldn't meet with me yesterday.
I'm sorry. I'm not following.
I sat here yesterday,
waiting to meet with someone.
I believe that person was you.
I think that you're confusing
me for someone else.
I don't think I am.
Sir, if you have a complaint,
I suggest you submit it
through our e-mail system.
I would be happy to
refer you to our website.
I was told that the man
I would be meeting
with is very careful.
A cautious man.
I believe we're
alike in that way.
If you are who I think you are,
you should give
me another chance.
I don't think we're
alike at all, Mr. White.
You are not a
cautious man at all.
Your partner was
late and he was high.
Yes. Yes, he was.
He's high often, isn't he?
You have poor judgment.
I can't work with someone
with poor judgment.
Are you familiar
with my product?
I've been told it's
excellent. It is impeccable.
It is the purest,
most chemically sound
product on the market anywhere.
That is not the only factor.
You could charge
twice the current rate
for what I provide,
and your customers would pay it.
Hands down.
Now, who I choose to do
business with on my end
is not your problem.
You won't see him.
You won't interact with him.
Forget he exists.
I have to ask.
Why?
Why him?
Because he does what I say.
Because I can trust him.
How much product
do you have on hand?
Thirty-eight pounds.
Ready to go at a
moment's notice.
Will I hear from you?
I have your numbers.
You can never
trust a drug addict.
Look, I mean,
it's all kind of little
dribs and drabs,
but right here, take
Keller, for instance.
A couple hundred dollars
here, a few thousand there.
Dribs and drabs. Huh.
Once you add it all
up, though, with Keller,
the revenues are
almost 10 percent less
than was actually received.
And this is every quarter
for the last two years.
I, um...
When I saw that, I got worried
so I checked Accounts Receivable
and their customers.
I found six other instances.
Revenues being under-reported.
And I've only just
started to look into it.
We have requirement contracts
with a lot of these companies.
They have to anticipate their
needs for the next quarter.
Now, most of the
time, they overestimate.
I let them roll their
overages into the next order,
and if I don't,
they'll go elsewhere.
Obviously, we forgot,
or didn't go back and
adjust the revenue entries.
I-I know it's wrong from
an accounting standpoint,
but as you can see,
the money's coming in
eventually, as you can see.
Right.
Right, but, um,
I got the old bills of sale
and order forms out
of storage, you know,
to try and sort
this out and, um...
Most of the time,
there's no backup for the
reported revenues at all.
In a few cases...
I found xeroxed copies
with the dates changed.
Ted.
Hm.
All right.
Heh. You got me.
We're talking nearly a million
dollars of undocumented revenue.
What are you
thinking? I'm thinking
about saving a company.
I'm thinking about
people's jobs,
about their mortgages
and pensions,
and their college
funds for their kids.
Not to mention my own.
It doesn't mean that
you have to break the law.
Yes, it does, Skyler.
It's right there in the
books. Business is terrible.
The bank is on my back,
the IRS is grinding
me down to a nub.
If I don't keep up... Ted.
People go to prison for this.
My dad built this
company from nothing.
We... We make things here.
The people who work
here are like family.
I can't let that all fall apart
because of a
couple of bad years.
Sky... don't report this.
Please.
I'm not gonna turn you in, Ted,
but I can't be a part of it.
I know.
I know. I just wish...
I'm sorry.
I don't want you to go.
[PHONE RINGING]
JESSE [ON RECORDING]: Yo,
if I know you, leave a message.
PETE [ON PHONE]: Yo, it's Skinny
Pete. Just checking in with you, man.
We missed you at
the funeral today.
The whole crew was representing.
Even Badger came
all the way from Fresno.
Combo's people, his
ma, grandma, cousins,
everyone was all
choked up and shit.
Man, it was, like, emotional.
And you should
have seen the coffin.
It was this shiny,
white pearlescent.
Like, I'm sure I've seen
the exact same paint job
on a Lexus, right?
So we're definitely
talking high-end.
Anyway, guess you had
something bigger going down.
Watch your back
out there, bro. Peace.
[LOCK CLICKS]
I like to mix some ice with it.
Hold that.
What's it feel like?
There's a chill.
Don't freak out. It passes.
And then...
You'll see.
I'll meet you there.
Take that off.
[THE PLATTERS'
"ENCHANTED" PLAYING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
♪ Living is a breeze ♪
♪ When you make it seem ♪
♪ Enchanted ♪
♪ Lovers take for granted ♪
♪ All the worlds below ♪
♪ They ought to know ♪
♪ When you touch a star ♪
♪ Then you really are ♪
♪ Enchanted ♪
♪ When you're
dreams Are slanted ♪
♪ Through a lover's eyes ♪
[VEHICLE APPROACHES]
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
Phones off, please.
Pipes, I guess.
All right, everyone.
Eyes on your paper.
[BEEPS]
Yes.
Excuse me, where's the manager?
I'm the manager. Can I help you?
Uh, no, no, no. I met
a man here last week.
He's a black gentleman.
He's thin. Glasses.
Yes, sir. That's the owner.
Oh, owner. Okay.
He owns 14 Los
Pollos restaurants
in between here and Nevada.
He could be at any one of them.
Is there a phone number
that I can get to...?
I'm sorry, sir. I
can't give that out.
Is this about a complaint?
I'd be happy to refer
you to our website.
No, no.
What's his name? Gustavo.
Gus.
Thank you.
Thirty-eight
pounds, $1.2 million.
Truck stop, two miles
south of Exit 13 on the 25.
One hour. What?
One hour. You in or out?
In. In. Absolutely.
But I just need
a little more time.
One hour. If you miss it,
don't ever show your
face in here again.
Exit 13 off the 25
South, to a truck.
Come on! Come on!
[JESSE ON RECORDING]: Yo,
if I know you, leave a message.
Jesse. Jesse, pick up the phone.
Pick up the phone.
[ENGINE STARTS]
I'm coming by. I
need the product.
I need the product now.
[GASPS]
Ooh.
Oh! Oh!
Ah! Ooh!
[PANTING]
Oh, God.
Jesse.
Jesse!
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
[COUGHS]
Jesse. Jesse.
Jesse.
[GRUNTING]
Jesse. Jesse, wake up.
Jesse.
Jesse. Jesse, wake up. Wake up.
Wake up!
Come on, damn it.
Where'd you put it?
Where's the
product? Get off of me.
Where is it? Where'd
you hide the meth?
In the kitchen. Where?
Under the sink.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[GRUNTING]
[CELL PHONE CHIMING] Ah.
No. No, no, no. Not
now, not now. Not now!
[GRUNTS]
[DOOR OPENS, SLAMS]
[♪♪♪]