[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING]
[TRAIN RUMBLING]
Yo. Yo.
What up?
Damn, bitch.
You got something for me?
Yeah. Yeah, I found them.
Is this a five or
an S? Five, yo.
No, wait. S.
No, no. Yeah, five. Yeah?
Jesus, how the hell do you spell
"street" wrong? S-T-R-E-A-T?
Hey, man.
I'm slinging mad volume
and fat stacking Benjies,
you know what I'm saying?
I can't be all about,
like, spelling and shit.
Hey.
So they got names?
Hers is, like, I don't know.
She's just his woman is all.
Him, they call Spooge.
Spooge? Not Mad Dog, not Diesel?
So let me get this
straight. You got jacked
by a guy named Spooge?
Yo, what's his name matter?
All's I saw was that
knife he stuck in my face,
like that big.
But, hey, you know, if
you're looking for a reason
not to go do this
thing... Did I say that?
Because I'll go do
it myself, all right?
It's just I'm on
probation and all.
Yeah.
So you gonna do it?
Good. Right on.
Because these two,
they need to get got.
[♪♪♪]
[SIGHING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[♪♪♪]
Where's my money,
bitch? Where's my money?
Where's my...?
Where's my money,
bitch? Huh, bitch?
bitch? Oh, that's good.
Where's my money?
Where's my money, bitch?
Bitch, where's my money?
Come on.
I will mess you up.
That how you wanna
play this? Huh? Your call.
Your funeral, jack.
Hey, do not mess with me.
I will bury you
because I'm crazy, yo.
Yeah, mucho loco.
Do not test me.
Good morning. Good morning.
Honey, you blocking the mailbox.
Oh.
Yeah, sorry. Sorry.
Looks like it's gonna
be a nice day, huh?
Yeah. Yeah. High 70s.
You have a great day.
Right on. You too.
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[GLASS CRUNCHING UNDERFOOT]
[GRUNTS]
God. Shit.
Yo, anybody home?
Hello?
[CREAKING]
MAN [ON TV]:
Tonight, you will receive
the ultimate mixture of cutlery
tonight in the steel knockout.
Every phone line jammed.
Eighty-nine dollars on flex pay.
That's 15 easy installments.
And, folks, the
knockout is only...
Hey, yo, is anybody else home?
Now, Terry put
this one together...
Where's your folks? They here?
And I'm here to tell you...
Yeah, guys, you might
wanna put up like a...
Already done it.
Tonight, folks...
Do you realize
how long it's been
since we've offered
this sword in any set?
Much less the watashi and
tanto as a bonus in the deal.
It's no wonder...
It is no wonder so many of
you are on the line right now...
What's your name?
I'm gonna count this as one.
Even though there are three...
My name's, uh, Diesel.
Eleven, 12, 13,
14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19...
Yo, don't you wanna watch
something other than this?
Like, I don't know,
Mister Rogers'?
Imagine displaying this
set in your own home.
Folks, custom pieces...
Well, needless to say, I've
made a pretty good mess,
but there's a reason for that.
Just because these are under
$10, don't let anybody kid you.
These knives
possess edges like...
So when are your, uh,
your folks coming home?
Your dad, Mr. Spooge?
When is he, uh, getting back?
I'm hungry.
[ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS]
WOMAN 1 [ON RECORDING]:
Hey there, you three.
Just wanted to wish
Walt a good first day back.
We'll be thinking about
you teaching valences
and covalences and...
Okay, that's all I officially
remembered. Good luck.
Skyler, give me a call
when you get a chance.
[BEEPS]
WOMAN 2: Hi, Walt and Skyler.
This is Gretchen Schwartz
calling to say hello.
I'm down from Santa Fe today
and I was just
thinking about you both,
hoping everything's well.
I tried Walt's cell,
and it said the number
had been disconnected,
so I'm just hoping
that everything's okay.
Call me if you can,
whenever's convenient.
Hello? SKYLER: Oh, hi, Gretchen.
This is Skyler White. Am I
catching you at a bad time?
No. No, not at all.
It's so good to hear from
you. How is everybody?
We're very well, thank you.
Um, Walt is actually
at work today.
It's his first day back at work
and he lost his cell
phone quite a while back.
And I hope we didn't worry you.
No, no. I'm just so glad to hear
that everybody's fine.
That's wonderful.
Gretchen, I'm so very, very
long overdue in telling you this
and I have to take
Walt at his word
that he's been
passing it along for me.
I mean, he's been so adamant
about wanting to handle
this whole thing by himself,
and, um...
But I have picked up the phone
about a hundred times. I just...
What? What is it?
I, um, I can't
begin to thank you and
Elliott for what you've done.
Um,
the money for Walt's
treatment, it's just...
It saved us.
I... I... I don't know if I...
Walt keeps saying,
"Don't bother them.
It's no big deal."
But it is a big deal. Yeah.
To me. And to all of us.
So I just
finally wanted to say thank you.
Anyway...
End of speech.
[LAUGHS] So I do...
I hope we get to see you soon.
Truly, um, anytime
you're in town,
anytime at all, is good for us.
How about this afternoon?
Yeah, okay.
WALT: Monoalkenes, diolefins,
trienes, polyenes.
I mean, the nomenclature alone
is enough to make
your head spin.
But when you start
to feel overwhelmed,
and you will,
just keep in mind
that one element,
carbon.
Carbon is at the
center of it all.
There is no life without carbon.
Nowhere that we
know of in the universe.
Everything that lives, lived,
will live, carbon.
Carmen is carbon.
Sorry. Assistant
Principal Carmen.
Did you, uh...?
[MOUTHING]
No. Okay.
I like to think of it, uh...
I like to think that the diamond
and the woman who
wears it on her finger
are both formed
from the same stuff.
Or, say, the diamond and
the man who invented it.
Ah. That got your
attention, right?
The man who invented
the diamond. All right.
H. Tracy Hall. Write
this name down.
Dr. Hall invented the
first reproducible process
for making synthetic diamonds.
I mean, this is way
back in the '50s.
Now, today, synthetic
diamonds are used in oil drilling,
electronics,
multi-billion-dollar industries.
Now, at the time, Dr. Hall
worked for General Electric.
And he made them a
fortune. I mean, incalculable.
You wanna know how
GE rewarded Dr. Hall?
A $10 U.S. Savings Bond.
Huh?
Anyway...
A savings bond printed
on carbon-based paper,
paid to a carbon-based man,
for something he
made out of carbon.
CARMEN: It's so nice to
have you back with us, Walt.
You're looking
great, by the way.
[WALT CHUCKLES]
A little skinnier, which
is definitely no tragedy.
And then there's the hair thing.
I actually like that.
That's a great look for you.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
But you're feeling good?
Oh, absolutely. Hundred percent.
Yeah.
It's, uh...
I'm glad to be back at work.
I'm glad to... You know,
I'm happy to be here. Really.
We're happy too.
And I just, uh...
Yeah. It's good. It's great.
Is everything okay?
Just please feel
comfortable coming to me
with any problems, any issues.
Anything at all.
You know,
completely confidential.
Okay?
See you tomorrow,
Flynn. See you, Jeffrey.
Oh, man.
Let me see it.
Dad, let me see it.
Don't worry about it.
[CAR DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
Hey, let's go.
[SIGHS]
MAN [ON TV]:
Forty-eight dollars,
that's the original price...
Hey.
Peekaboo.
No?
[LAUGHS]
Oh, man.
[SIGHS]
WOMAN: Oh, my
hand is cramping up!
JESSE [WHISPERING]:
Oh, my God. Here, here, here.
MAN: Now, I don't know, stupid.
If you want your
hand to stop aching,
I gave you advice,
take it or leave it.
Okay, you stay
right here, all right?
Okay? I mean it.
Hey. Shh.
[MAN AND WOMAN
SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
WOMAN: Shut up!
MAN: You shut up.
WOMAN: You shut up,
you... MAN: You shut up!
You're the one who dropped
it. WOMAN: I didn't drop it.
I didn't drop.
Shit! You dropped it.
Shut the hell up about it.
You shut up! MAN:
No, you shut up.
[GRUNTING AND YELLING]
[SCREAMING]
Get up.
Shut up. Shut up! Both of you.
You know who might have done it?
I have an idea.
Well, here's what I think.
You ID them, and then together,
you and I put a bag
over their heads,
we tie them up, drive
them way out into the desert,
strip them naked,
then bury them up to their necks
in a huge mound of fire ants.
Saw it in an old western.
You with me?
Scorpions?
Scorpions are good.
Yeah.
Whoa. Nice.
Damn, Dad. Check it out.
Who is this?
SKYLER: So this is Walter Jr.,
or, uh, Flynn.
He likes to go by
Flynn these days.
WALT JR.: Mom. SKYLER: What?
I'm just offering the choice.
This is Mrs. Schwartz, whom
you've heard so much about.
Very nice to meet you, Flynn.
WALT JR.: Nice to meet you too.
SKYLER: Oh, uh, Walt.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Look who's here. Whoa!
Gretchen. Hi.
Always nice to see you.
What a nice surprise.
Look at you.
You're looking good.
Though a bald head
is a bit of a shocker.
I know it was for me.
Oh, you have a good-shaped head.
[ALL CHUCKLE]
May I? Oh, sure.
For good luck, right?
Exactly. Here's hoping.
We could use some
of that, huh? Yeah.
Mrs. Schwartz, thank you so much
for what you've done for my dad.
It was a really good thing.
You're very welcome.
We're gonna find
a way to repay you.
GRETCHEN: No, no, no.
We don't wanna... We
don't wanna ever hear that.
You know, I... I hate to say it,
but I really need to get going.
Oh, that's too bad.
You can't stay for
dinner? I wish I could,
but unfortunately, I have
to try to beat the traffic.
Okay. Okay.
Well, I... I hope we
get a... A chance to...
To catch up real soon.
Yeah, hopefully.
Gretchen, your purse.
Oh!
Well, good to see you.
And you and Elliott are
welcome any time. Really.
Um...
And I, for one, am
gonna be much better
about keeping in touch.
It's so good to
see you. And you.
Nice meeting you.
Likewise.
Okay. Bye now.
Drive safely.
GRETCHEN: Okay.
You know, what am I thinking?
I should walk her
to her car. Really.
I'll be right back.
Gretchen.
Hey.
Hey. Hey yourself.
What did you...?
We need to talk.
Can you not do or say
anything to anyone until then?
[ENGINE STARTS]
Please. Please.
JESSE: Where's my money, bitch?
I ain't gonna keep asking nice!
Yo, all right? I want my
money and my dope. Come on!
I just... I just
wanna say, man...
What? What? What
do you wanna say?
I just wanna go on record, man.
You hit me really,
really hard, man.
You hit me hard. I
think I'm seeing double.
Maybe I need to go see
a hospital or something.
Shut up! Jesus.
Serious, man, I might
have a concussion.
Don't fall asleep, baby.
Subdural hematoma.
Don't fall asleep.
Shut up.
All right. Empty your pockets.
Turn them out,
everything on the table.
Do it!
All right, turn around.
Turn around.
Turn out your back
pockets. Come on.
All right. Shoes.
Give them here.
I told you, Diesel,
we ain't holding any...
We shot it all.
Yeah? Shot an ounce
in a day and a half?
Yeah. All right, tell you what.
Both of you
pull it out of your
butts right now
or I grab a flashlight
and some pliers
and go exploring.
What's it gonna be, yo? Come on.
There you go.
All right, come
on. On the table.
All right, so, what,
you hold the crystal and
she holds the H, huh?
Division of labor.
All right, there's
maybe an 8 ball here.
Where's the rest of my meth?
Yo, for real? She
up and lost it, yo.
You shut up. You shut up, skank.
Shut up! Shut up!
Stop it!
This really isn't
getting any better.
It's turning cranial.
Oh, yeah? You see this
gun? Huh? It's got five bullets.
One for each kneecap,
plus an extra round
for your cranial
for being such a pussy.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey. Hey, baby.
Oh.
Come here, baby.
All right.
You two are never
getting high again.
I will make it
my life's mission.
Not another needle,
not another ball,
not one toke,
not till I get what's mine.
Yeah, we got you
covered, man, sure.
It just so happens we got
your money, man, plus interest.
You're damn
right, plus interest.
Where? Backyard.
Yo, right hand to the man,
dog. Backyard. Go check it out.
Hurting. Painful.
JESSE: Hey, hey, hey.
Me and your old man, we're
just playing a game, all right?
Hey, don't move.
Come on.
Ah!
JESSE: Come on.
Huh? See?
Me and the slit just boosted
it, yo. She's like a ant, man.
She can lift a hundred times
her own weight. For real.
What the hell am I
supposed to do with this?
Help me break it open.
Take out the money, get paid.
Get high.
Yo, that's my bank.
So? It's FIDC insured, yo.
It's a victimless crime.
JESSE: Where the
hell did you get this?
SPOOGE: Bodega. Way across town.
In, out, like, bam.
Went smooth as silk, yo.
JESSE: What, nobody saw you?
What about witnesses, dumbass?
SPOOGE: Hey, we roll
like the breeze, for real.
All we did, we just
walked in all smooth-like.
Nobody even noticed.
JESSE: Nobody noticed?
For real?
SPOOGE: I'm telling you.
Victimless crime.
[SPOOGE GRUNTING]
[THUDDING]
Oh, my God.
Oh, Jesus. Come on already.
It's about to give,
man. I'm sensing it.
JESSE: You don't know
what the hell you're doing.
I thought you told me you
boosted, like, six of these.
Yeah. Boosted.
It's not like he
ever got one open.
At least I got persistence.
The law of averages,
lucky number seven.
Don't listen to that skank.
Ooh, stop calling me that.
I ain't no skank!
Skank, skank, skank...
Hey, hey, hey.
Sit, sit.
All right, I swear to God
I will shoot you
both in the face.
Now chill.
You, get that thing open.
You sit the hell down,
and no throwing things.
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
Where's the kid?
The kid. The little kid!
What are you asking me for?
Oh, my God.
SPOOGE: I got you now, bitch.
I got you now. [LOUD,
METALLIC THUD]
You didn't see that coming, huh?
What the hell kind
of mother are you?
Huh?
How about you feed the kid
a decent meal every
now and then, huh?
Give him a bath. Put
some baby powder on him.
Get him some decent TV to
watch. I mean, what is this shit?
Are you serious?
You give me one hit,
and I'll be any kind of
mother that you want.
Oh, my God.
SPOOGE: Yeah, Diesel,
this thing would go easier
if we all had a
little taste, man.
Get out of the way.
Get out of the way!
[GRUNTING]
WALT: So you didn't tell anyone.
You didn't tell Elliott.
GRETCHEN: Not yet.
[PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
WALT: Well, what does that mean?
GRETCHEN: That means
exactly what it means.
That's a determination
I have yet to make.
WALT: All right, fair enough.
I can appreciate that.
All right.
First let me say,
I very much regret
involving you in this.
This was...
[WALT SIGHS]
This entire thing
was unfortunate.
GRETCHEN: Unfortunate?
WALT: And I apologize deeply.
GRETCHEN: Thank you.
Now please tell
me why you did it.
That's not really at issue here.
Well, you told me your insurance
was covering it. Was that a lie?
If you won't take our money,
and your insurance
isn't covering it,
how are you paying for it?
This... This is not an issue
that concerns you,
Gretchen, okay?
[SCOFFS]
Excuse me, Walt.
It does concern me.
It concerns me greatly.
You... You tell
your wife and son
that I am paying for
your cancer treatment.
Why are you doing this?
I will clear this up with them.
Walt, the look on Skyler's face,
she's sitting there,
tears in her eyes,
thanking me for
saving your life.
Why would you do that to her?
As I said, I will clear this up.
Just please allow me to do this
in my own way, in my own time.
All right?
I will explain the
whole thing to them.
And while you're
at it, explain it to me.
I don't owe you an explanation.
I owe you an apology,
and I have apologized.
I am very sorry, Gretchen.
There. I've
apologized twice now.
I'm humbly sorry.
Three times.
Let me just get this straight.
Elliott and I offer to
pay for your treatment,
no strings attached.
An offer which still
stands, by the way.
And you turn us down
out of pride, whatever,
and then you tell
your wife that in fact
we are paying
for your treatment.
Without our knowledge,
against our will,
you involve us in your lie.
And you sit here and tell me
that that is none
of my business?
Yeah. That's pretty
much the size of it.
What happened to you?
Really, Walt.
What happened?
Because this isn't you.
What would you know
about me, Gretchen?
What would your presumption
about me be, exactly?
That I should go
begging for your charity?
And you waving your
checkbook around
like some magic wand
is gonna make me forget
how you and Elliott...
How you and Elliott cut me out?
What? That can't
be how you see it.
It was my hard
work, my research,
and you and Elliott
make millions off it.
That cannot be how
you see it. Oh, good.
That's beautifully
done. You left...
You are always the
picture of innocence.
You left me. The
Just sweetness and light.
You left me.
Newport, 4th of July weekend.
You and my father and my
brothers and I go up to our room
and you're packing
your bags, barely talking.
What? Did I dream all of that?
That's your excuse
to build your little
empire on my work?
How can you say that
to me? You walked away.
You abandoned us, me, Elliott.
Little rich girl just
adding to your millions.
I don't even know
what to say to you.
where to begin.
I feel so sorry for you, Walt.
Fuck you.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey.
Hey, little man, you hungry?
[GRUNTING]
[BODY THUDS]
[GROANING]
Man. No, no, what are you doing?
No, what are you doing?
Spooge, I got him, I got him.
Baby, get up and help me.
Call me a bad mother.
I'll show you a
bad mother, bitch.
Get up, damn it! Get our dope!
Bedtime.
[GROANS]
Here we go. Oh, yeah.
Who's the big tough guy
now, huh? Huh? Is that you?
Is that you? You're
the big man? Huh?
Try and hit me now,
bitch. Try and hit me now!
Try and hit me now, bitch.
Oh.
[SIGHS]
Oh, hey.
Should I ask where you've been?
Never mind.
We're long past that, I suppose.
Skyler.
Gretchen called
about an hour ago.
Walt.
We need to talk.
Just say it.
They're cutting off the money.
What did she say exactly?
Hm.
Not much. It was, uh...
abrupt.
She said something like:
[CLEARS THROAT]
"I'm sorry to have to do this,
"but Elliott and I can
no longer continue
"to pay for Walt's treatment.
I wish you the very best."
And that was it.
Huh.
Yeah.
I mean, she sounded
apologetic. I guess.
I mean, it was quick.
She got right off the phone.
I was... I was
so stunned, but...
I... I called her back,
and she didn't pick up.
So, what do you know about this?
I mean, she and I had
a perfectly nice
visit this afternoon,
and then you come home
and all of a sudden she's
in a big hurry to leave,
and then the two of you
are talking in the driveway.
Walt.
What do you know that I don't?
Where were you tonight?
I drove up to Santa Fe.
I was with Gretchen.
Well, Gretchen and Elliott.
No, she just...
She just couldn't bring
herself to tell you today.
I mean, she couldn't
tell me, either, really.
I mean, there was a lot
of hemming and hawing
and beating around the
bush from both of them...
Okay, what...? Tell us what?
Well...
There was a lot of
business phraseology
being tossed around.
You know, things like, uh,
"cash-poor" and "leveraged,"
"quarterly decline,"
yadda, yadda, yadda.
But what they were truly
saying, in my opinion...
[LAUGHS]
They're broke.
You are kidding me.
No.
I mean, the
economy's in the toilet.
We all know that.
And all these big banks
and Fannie Mae and...
Well, apparently, Gray Matter
is no more immune
than anyone else.
That is...
[CLEARS THROAT]
Jesus, that's...
[SIGHS]
Yeah.
You know, she could
have just told me herself.
Hm.
Well, they're prideful
people, you know.
Listen.
Not to sound selfish,
but as far as we go,
we'll get through this, okay?
I mean, they've already paid
for most of my treatment, right?
Hey.
We're gonna make it.
All right? I promise.
Okay.
And yet,
she still drives a Bentley.
[CHUCKLES]
Keeping up appearances.
I mean, who knows?
Hm.
[DRILL WHIRRING]
WOMAN: Baby, that
don't make any sense.
SPOOGE: Of course
it makes sense.
Every safe's got
its weak spot, right?
You're designing a safe,
where you gonna
put your weak spot?
Nowhere.
I'd make it, like, strong.
SPOOGE: Jesus. On the bottom,
that's where.
You put your weak
spot on the bottom.
Oh, baby, that H is
bringing me down.
SPOOGE: Yeah, you took too much.
I told you.
I need to... I need to even out.
Let me get a hit
of that crystal.
SPOOGE: Hell, no.
You lost your share.
Come on, baby.
It's all I need,
just a little hit.
SPOOGE: Shut the
hell up, you dumb skank.
I'm trying to concentrate.
I ain't no skank.
I would appreciate an apology.
[DRILL WHIRRING]
SPOOGE: Ow! What?
WOMAN: I am trying to take
the high road here.
Are you gonna do right?
Just listen to me, stupid.
I... I am in the middle of
some very important work.
I am on the verge
here, all right?
So shut your skank ass pie hole
and assist me and shut up.
I ain't no skank.
SPOOGE: Skank,
skank, skank ass skank.
Skank ass skank.
You listening to me, skank?
Huh? You hear me, skank?
You are a skank
ass skank. Skank.
Skank, skank, skank. Skank.
I ain't no skank.
No, no, no. Don't. No.
[DRILL WHIRRING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Ain't no skank.
[LINE RINGING]
WOMAN [OVER PHONE]: 911.
[GROANING]
Hey, hey.
Hey, you remember peekaboo? Huh?
Can you go peekaboo like this?
Can you keep your eyes closed?
You keep them
closed. That's good.
That's good. That's real good.
All right. You keep
them closed just like that.
It's a little game we're
gonna play, okay?
Here you go.
Hey. Hey, look at me.
You wait right here. Okay?
It's just part of the game.
You wait right here, and...
[PANTING]
Look, just... Just don't
go back inside. All right?
You stay right here. Okay?
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
You have a good
rest of your life, kid.
[♪♪♪]