[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
Skyler, I'm so...
Marie. Oh, Christ,
Marie. How...?
Oh, God. Oh, thank God.
Is she beautiful?
Yeah, I, uh... I'm...
I'm, uh, staring at
brake lights on the 40.
Some accident up ahead.
Ah. Christ. Today
of all days, huh?
No, no, no. Let... Let her rest.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
Marie. Thank you.
[GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪]
Excuse me. Skyler White?
Three-oh-seven. Thank you.
Skyler, I'm so
sorry. I'm just...
Shh. Are you okay?
[WHISPERS] Meet your daughter.
Hi there, girl. Hi there, Holly.
Congratulations, Walt.
Oh, Ted, I'm sorry, I
didn't... I didn't see you here.
SKYLER: Oh, Ted...
Ted drove me here. Thank God.
I mean, this, uh...
This little bundle
of joy of ours
was practically on rails.
I mean, halfway here I
thought he was gonna
have to pull over and
deliver her himself. Heh.
Oh. Well, that... I'm
glad it didn't come to that.
[FUSSING]
Yeah. Thanks, Ted.
No problem at all.
Well, let me get out of your
way here so you two can...
You three can be alone, okay?
Listen, take it easy, Sky.
I really... I can't
begin to thank you.
TED: Don't... Don't
think anything of it.
It's my pleasure, all right?
Congratulations again.
Thank you. She's beautiful.
Okay. I'll talk to you soon.
Okay. Take care.
Bye.
Oh.
[CRYING]
[SIGHS]
Are you okay?
Is everything okay?
Everything is okay.
I just... I just wish
you'd been here.
Where's everyone
else? Downstairs.
Hank and Marie
took Junior for dinner.
He has been such a trooper.
He even changed
his first diaper.
No. Yeah.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Did he?
Honey, is there anything
that I can do for you?
Anything at all? Actually, yes.
I, uh, left my overnight
bag at home this morning.
I just think you get it in your
head, C-section. You know?
But I'm just so glad,
the way it all worked out.
Oh. Doing it natural instead.
It just couldn't have
gone any better.
Good.
Let me go get your things.
And I'll get my
stuff too, okay? Shh.
I'll spend the night. Okay.
[♪♪♪]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Dad.
I was in the shower, hey.
I overslept.
I'm running late,
but I'll be there.
Yeah.
[SIGHS]
Baby, I gotta go.
[MOANS]
Okay.
Somebody broke in.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR SHUTS]
Oh, no. No, no, no!
Come on.
Damn.
[PANTING]
Oh, God.
Oh, Christ.
MAN: This week was tough.
Toughest yet.
You know why? I knew
this day was coming.
My birthday. Your re-birthday?
Yeah. As it got
closer, it got worse.
I was scared shitless
I wouldn't make it.
I really didn't think I would.
Called in sick
three days in a row.
I know my boss was pissed.
I don't really care. I just
didn't wanna see anybody.
You guys know how that is.
All it would take is one friend
and I'd be out ripping
and running again.
But I made it. I really made it.
I got one year clean to the day.
[ALL CHEERING]
[SIGHS]
You look tired. Your
eyes are kind of red.
You getting enough
sleep? Actually, no.
I'm working on this
really complex new tat.
Yeah?
Yeah, a guy wants
his whole back done up.
Him on his chopper with,
like, flames all around.
I keep showing him the design,
he keeps asking
for changes, like:
"Give me more muscles.
Give me more flames."
And I'm like, "A: This
ain't the Sistine Chapel
and B: I have enough trouble
working around your zits."
I really wish you wouldn't
work at that place.
You know you need to
avoid those type of people.
I know and I do.
It's mostly college kids
and airmen from Kirtland.
It's actually really corporate.
Thank you.
So how's your job?
Oh, you know.
Same old, same old.
Doing backup
training on my days off.
God, they're hiring anybody now.
I mean, no experience
at all. It's scary.
Wow.
You... You seeing anyone?
Um...
No.
You?
What about that guy next door?
What do you mean?
Well, he seemed to
have some expectation
of you introducing me to him.
He knows you own the place.
Yeah.
Dad, he's our tenant.
End of story.
Why would I get
involved with a tenant?
Okay.
WAITRESS: There you go.
Oh, yes.
Oh, isn't she beautiful?
I just think she's the
most beautiful baby ever.
WALT: Yeah. And why not?
Good stock.
[PHONE RINGING]
I'll get it.
Yeah. Yeah.
WALT JR.: Hello. Hello?
Nobody's there.
Ah. Oh, well.
[RINGS]
Oh! Beat you. Ha-ha-ha.
Hello. Hey, man.
WALT [ON PHONE]: Oh, hi, Carmen.
Just Carmen.
Come on. Hurry up.
So you heard, huh? Yes, yes.
Good news. Oh, she's
just so beautiful. Heh.
Well, Holly.
Seven pounds, 3 ounces.
Why, everybody is...
Everybody is doing just fine.
You junkie imbecile.
What the hell are you
calling this number for?
I am trying to tell you, man.
Last night somebody
broke in my place, yo.
I got robbed. What?
Yeah. Somebody, they got
all of our... Our stuff. Okay?
All of it.
[PANTING]
You get me, Mr. White? Huh?
The blue stuff.
It's, like, uncanny.
They knew exactly where to look.
I mean, say something,
man, all right?
Yell at me or
something! Come on!
Mr. White.
[BEEPS OFF]
God.
Oh, no.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
MARIE: Hank, come on. People
are starving to death out here.
HANK: All right. All right.
I just had to get a beer.
Finally.
All right, guys. Here we go.
We got mild, medium
and muy caliente.
WALT JR.: I got
dibs on the breast.
Los Pollos Hermanos?
HANK: Oh, yeah,
seriously. You gotta try it.
I think this joint gives
KFC a run for their money.
[BABY CRYING]
Uh-oh. That baby is hungry.
Give me that baby.
Oh, sweetie, yes.
WALT JR.: Do you have
any coleslaw in there?
HANK: Oh, no, no,
no. Come on. Jeez, Sky.
Not at the table. We're
eating. Hank, it's only a breast.
It's my sister-in-law's breast.
Oh, you are so provincial.
Hank, remember the day
when you were talking
to me about childproofing?
Yeah. Right?
Yeah, yeah. What
are you thinking?
A fence or-or-or a cover?
Yeah. No, well, actually,
I was... I was thinking
more of an alarm system.
They have got these...
Yeah, they have got
these new systems
that are now sonar
systems that would...
Anything falls into
it, it sets the alarm off.
Oh, nice. Yeah.
Wow, that sounds
expensive. Well, yeah.
But, uh, for the baby, I mean...
HANK: Well, why don't, uh...
Hey. Why don't you let Marie
and I get that for you, guys?
Absolutely. No, no. Thank you.
No, no, please. I'll
be back at work soon
and we'll take care of it.
"Back at work soon"?
SKYLER: Since, you know,
you're scheduled for surgery,
I just thought it
might be a good idea
to have some money coming in.
Well, uh,
Skyler, we need to think
about what's best for the baby.
And I think having
her mother around
for at least the
first few years...
Money-wise, we'll
manage. I promise you that.
What? You guys got, like,
a printing press in the
garage churning out 50s?
WALT JR.: I wish.
Mom's even talking
about me getting a job.
SKYLER: That's right.
Everybody pitches in.
MARIE: Why don't
we ever get Chinese?
[BABY CRYING]
[BOTH MOAN SOFTLY]
I'll get her.
[SIGHS]
Yes. Good girl.
That's a good girl.
My little girl, huh?
Hey.
[WHIMPERING]
Hey, do you wanna see something?
Come here.
Oh, I know, I know.
[♪♪♪]
Yeah.
Hey.
You wanna see what
your daddy did for you?
Let me show you.
Here. Come here.
[BABY WHIMPERS]
Shh, shh, shh.
Wanna see?
Uh-huh.
That's right. Daddy did that.
Daddy did that for you.
This place looks
exactly the same.
Why don't you have computers
and shit? It's the 20th century.
What the hell are
you doing here?
Get out... No.
You took the stash.
I heard all those
phone messages,
and I figured it out.
You figured it out, huh?
Well, congratulations, Einstein.
You left me to
freak out all day long
like I dropped the
ball or something,
and you were the
one who took it!
Shut up.
You lower your voice.
"Like you dropped the ball"?
When have you ever not
dropped the ball, Jesse?
Blasted out of your mind
on whatever the hell that was.
What was that, heroin?
Jesus.
I was on my day off, man.
What I do on my day off...
"Day off"? We were
on call, you junkie.
On call for the biggest
deal of our lives.
I managed to pull it off
by the skin of my teeth,
no thanks to you.
And you made me miss
the birth of my daughter.
Son of a bitch.
How much?
How much what?
How much did you
get for the deal?
One-point-two million.
Six hundred thousand each.
Four hundred and
eighty thousand.
Saul's cut is 20 percent.
All right.
So where's my money?
[LAUGHS]
What?
You are joking, right?
If I gave you that money,
you would be dead
inside of a week.
Yo, man, look,
I'm off the heroin.
I didn't even like it
anyway. It made me sick.
And the... And the meth.
You know, I could
take it or leave it.
I'm clean, Mr. White.
For real.
Prove it.
Pee in that.
How gay are you,
seriously? Pee in it.
They're selling testing
kits at the drugstores.
If you are clean, I will
give you every last dime.
No, huh?
Well, I guess, until then
you'll just have to depend
on the kindness of
strangers to get high.
That and your little
junkie girlfriend.
[GRUNTS]
[BABY WHIMPERING]
WALT: Shh, shh, shh.
MARIE: Not on her tummy, Walt.
WALT: I'm not putting
her on her tummy.
I'll put her on her side. Do
you wanna hold her back?
MARIE: Yeah. Right there.
Just in case she decides
to do a little spit up,
I'm gonna roll up a
nice clean towel like this
and put it under.
Hammacher Schlemmer
makes a proper one of those.
It's hypoallergenic. Oh, yeah?
Well, I think a towel will do.
MARIE: Skyler, what is it?
Your son.
He is just unbelievable.
Come see what he did.
[KNOCKING]
I told you it's not ready yet.
Honey, just show it to them.
Heh. My God, son.
That's wonderful.
Flynn.
This is beautiful.
SaveWalterWhite.com.
Well, I, for one, am
telling everybody.
Wait a minute. You're not
asking for money, are you, son?
Yeah. That's the whole idea.
Louis helped me set up a PayPal
account and-and everything.
WALT JR.: See. But
we can't ask for money.
No.
SKYLER: Walt.
Okay.
I appreciate it. I really do.
Show me what else you put on.
This was all his idea.
He worked so hard on it.
Just let him help. Skyler.
It's... You can't ask
him to take it down.
It'll crush him.
Skyler, it's charity.
Why do you say that like
it's some sort of dirty word?
[SCOFFS]
WALT: This is insane.
I have so much cash on hand
that I actually counted
by weighing it on
my bathroom scale,
and yet, I can't spend it.
I can't tell my family about it.
All of whom think that I am
right on the edge of bankruptcy.
I mean, it's...
It's insane.
Well, I guess that's
why gangsters had molls.
What?
Gun molls.
Haven't you ever
seen White Heat?
Yeah, I've seen White Heat,
but I don't see
how that pertains.
Maybe you need a moll
more than you need a wife
who you can't trust
with your secrets.
Just... What good is money
that doesn't spend? Huh?
The tree falls in the forest...
You know, you get the point.
So, uh, communicating is out?
Out. All right.
Let's see. What else is there?
There's always, uh, "Hey,
I found a big bag of money
down by the railroad tracks."
No? No? Works for me.
[SIGHS, SNAPS]
Uncle Murray.
Oh, yeah. Ha.
Yeah, "Oh, many
is the happy memory
"of Uncle Murray
bouncing me on his knee.
"We lost track of the
old pervert years ago,
what do you know, he
kicked it and left millions."
No, no.
It cannot be blind luck or some
imaginary relative who saves us.
No, I earned that money, me.
And now my son
created his own website,
SaveWalterWhite.com,
soliciting anonymous donations.
Do you... Do you have any
idea how that makes me feel?
[TYPING]
Yeah, look at that. It's
got PayPal and everything.
Cyber-begging.
That's all that is.
Just rattling a little tin
cup to the entire world.
Yeah, there's no
deep-seated issues there.
Walt, uh, I'm looking
at the answer right here.
It's staring me in the face.
Do I have to
spell it out for you?
I know. I know.
You're thinking that I should
be funneling my money
into my son's website,
but absolutely not. No.
I am not going to
have my family think
that some mystery
benefactor saved us.
Not some mystery
benefactor, singular.
That would raise
too many questions.
However... Stay with me here.
Zombies.
I got a guy, who knows this guy,
who knows this Rain Man -type.
He lives with his mother in her
basement in Belarus, all right?
So good luck extraditing
his fat Russian ass.
Wait. Whoa.
He's a hacker-cracker
extraordinaire.
This guy can hijack
random desktops
all around the world,
turn them into zombies
that do his bidding.
For instance, he can
make it so, uh, 20- or 30,000
little donations come in from
all over the U.S. and Canada.
Ten, 20, 50 bucks a pop,
all paid in full, nice and neat,
untraceable, from
the good-hearted
people of the world
to Mr. Walter H. White,
cancer saint.
I'm getting a warm and fuzzy
feeling just thinking about it.
JESSE: He's an asshole,
that's what. Always judging me.
JANE: Not too much.
I mean, like... Like,
who is he, right?
I mean, first off, I taught him.
Always acting like I'm
his indentured servant.
Now the cotton.
Needle?
JANE: I don't understand
why you need him anyway.
JESSE: Exactly.
My point exactly.
[GRUNTS]
Flat against your
skin so it doesn't
wiggle around too much.
How much does he
owe you, anyway?
Four hundred and eighty.
Oh, hell, I'd be mad too if
somebody owed me 500 bucks.
No, no.
Four hundred and
eighty thousand.
What?
Thousand.
Not on your back, baby,
in case you throw up.
On your side.
Sleep on your side.
MAN: And she's all like:
"Don't preach to me."
And I'm like, "Baby,
I'm not preaching to you.
"I'm talking about basic
survival, you know?
I'm conversing
about life and death."
I mean, this here,
what we've been doing,
hell, Becky knows.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Dad?
I overslept. I'm on my way.
Dad, wait.
Dad, it's not... It's
not what it looks like.
Dad.
Dad, will just wait? Let me...
Just talk to me for one second.
No, Dad.
Dad, come on.
Dad?
Dad, no. No, stop it!
Don't touch him, Dad!
Dad, stop. Dad, let
him go! Son of a bitch.
Dad, no. Let go!
Stop it! Stop it, Dad! Stop
it! I want you out of here!
Get away from me, man.
Back off. JANE: Jesse!
Jesse, no! Back off!
Okay, everybody just calm
down! What's with you, yo? Huh?
Because I'll
seriously bust you up.
You miserable little smackhead.
Get the hell out! Hey,
I pay my rent, bitch.
All right? I got civil rights.
Dad, no! Okay!
Jesse, come on.
Please, no. Come on.
I pay my rent.
You're going back
to rehab. Today. Now.
Look, as it so
happens, we were just...
We were just talking
about that now.
Yeah?
Yeah, I was gonna
tell you, okay?
If you would just let
me. Eighteen months.
You have been clean
for 18 months, Jane.
Why? Why do you do it?
I backslid, okay?
Like, what?
What, you think
I'm proud of this?
Like I do it on purpose?
Lying to me.
Shacking up and using with
this scumbag, this loser.
Hey, it takes one to know one.
His name is Jesse, Dad,
and you don't know
the first thing about him.
We talk about rehab
every night. It's his idea.
You talk about rehab? Well,
gee, isn't that wonderful?
Thank you for not being
judgmental 24 hours a day.
Because that's
exactly what I need,
to be judged all the time!
Okay.
You know what you need?
I'll tell you what you need.
What are you doing?
I am calling the police.
Dad. Dad, no, don't.
Come on. Come on!
Dad, no. Don't. I
have tried 10 years
of love and understanding.
Maybe what it takes is
you drying out in a jail cell.
JANE: Dad, no.
Yes, I would like to report
drug use in a
building that I own.
Dad. No. It's ongoing.
Daddy, no. It's
illegal activity.
I'd like to talk to
somebody. No.
Would you connect me,
please? Fine, we'll go to rehab.
I could care less about
him going to rehab.
I want you in rehab.
Okay. I'll go first
thing tomorrow.
Not tomorrow. Today.
I have to call into work. I
have to stop the newspaper.
The last time I went to
rehab, all my houseplants died
because you didn't
water them, so...
Daddy, please?
I'll go.
MAN [ON PHONE]: Albuquerque
Police. How may I direct your call?
Tomorrow.
Hello?
I'm sorry. I made a mistake.
[PHONE CLICKS OFF]
Tomorrow.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR SLAMS]
You meant all that?
I don't know.
I just think if we
had enough money,
nobody could make
us do anything.
[SKYLER SINGING SOFTLY]
[PHONE RINGING]
[GROANS]
Oh, just let it ring.
No, I'm gonna go see who it is.
Shh, shh, shh.
It's okay, Holly.
It's okay, sweetie.
Good luck with that,
but I'm sure he'd be glad
to, you know, write some...
You know, actually,
here he is right now.
So, um, hold on a second.
What? It's one of your, um...
One of your old students
wants a letter of recommendation.
Oh, okay. Thanks.
Oh, honey, I think the
baby is getting hungry.
Oh.
Uh, this is Walter White.
JANE [ON PHONE]:
Hello, Walter White.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm sorry. I'm... I'm having
a little trouble recalling...
It's Jane.
You know, of Jesse and Jane.
Jesse's "junkie girlfriend."
Oh, yes, yes. Of course. Wow.
It really has been a long time.
Jesus. Get somewhere
where you can talk.
Sure. Yes. I am... I am
looking into that as we speak.
How the hell did
you get this number?
Did Jesse give it to you?
All Jesse wants is
what's coming to him.
No more, no less.
WALT [ON PHONE]:
What are you talking about?
Four hundred and
eighty thousand.
He told you about the
money. He told me everything.
So, what is this? Hm?
What, some kind of
blackmail or something?
This is me telling you
to do right by Jesse.
And bring him what you owe him.
I don't call that blackmail.
I call that you
getting off your ass,
and being a decent human being.
Well, I call it blackmail.
Dialing my number.
Talking to my wife.
And what's your end of
this? How much heroin does
a half a million dollars buy?
For your information, I am
holding Jesse's money for him,
and he will receive
every last dollar of it.
He will, not you,
at a time when I see fit.
But I will not contribute
to his overdose.
Now, you tell him,
if he gets clean...
If you both get clean...
You know what?
I take that back.
This is blackmail.
Because what I know about you,
high-school teacher
turned drug dealer,
with a brother-in-law
in the DEA,
that would make
one hell of a story.
National news, I'll bet.
Do right by Jesse tonight or
I will burn you to the ground.
Shit.
He's a high-school teacher.
What's he gonna do,
give you a B-minus?
Send you outside
to clap the erasers?
You wouldn't really go
to the cops, would you?
We won't have to. He'll pay.
And what if he doesn't?
Jesse, it's your money.
You're in the right
here. He's in the wrong.
He's not stupid. He'll pay.
What is it, really?
You don't want your
half a million dollars?
You wanna renounce your earthly
possessions and become a monk?
No, it's just, I'm not the
kind of dude who rolls.
And by extension, you
know, neither are you.
I mean, he's my partner.
I'm your partner.
NARRATOR [ON TV]: The
largest land animal in all the planet
lives in a tightly knit
matriarchal society
led by the eldest
female in the herd.
[BABY CRYING ON MONITOR]
SKYLER [ON MONITOR]: Close
your eyes and go to sleep. Shh. Shh.
SKYLER: ♪ Hush little
baby Don't say a word ♪
♪ Mama's gonna buy
you A mockingbird ♪
♪ And if that
mockingbird Won't sing ♪
♪ Mama's gonna buy
you A diamond ring ♪
♪ And if that diamond
ring Turns brass ♪
♪ Mama's gonna buy
you A looking glass ♪
♪ So hush little
baby Don't you cry ♪
♪ Daddy loves you And so do I ♪
She is finally asleep.
Oh.
Ooh.
What you doing?
Learning about elephants?
Hm.
Oh, honey, uh,
we're out of diapers.
Would you mind going out?
Jesse.
Not you.
Nice job wearing the pants.
How do I know she'll keep quiet?
I guess you don't.
You'll never hear
from either of us again.
You're not seeing
straight, Jesse.
You are making a mistake.
Do you know what this is?
It's a whole lot of cheddar.
This is freedom.
This is saying, "I can
go anywhere I want.
I can be anybody."
Who do you wanna be?
Where do you wanna go?
South America?
Europe? Australia?
Is New Zealand
part of Australia?
New Zealand is New Zealand.
Right on.
New Zealand. That's
where they, uh...
That's where they
made Lord of the Rings.
I say we just move there, yo.
I mean, you can do your art.
Right? Like, you
can paint, like,
the local castles and shit.
And-And I can be a bush pilot.
Yeah. New Zealand.
I can get behind that.
But I guess I'm good anywhere
as long as it's the two of us.
[PANTING]
But first, we gotta get clean.
And not because
anybody is telling us to.
We do this for us, right?
Yeah. Absolutely. For us.
All this here, we're
not gonna just
shoot this up our arms, Jesse.
We're not.
Hell, no. No, no, no.
We're better than that.
We're way better
than that. I say...
I say we flush what we've
got left and we start tonight.
Yeah, we can do that.
Definitely.
[THE OUTLAWS' "GREEN
GRASS & HIGH TIDES" PLAYING]
Excuse me.
♪ Now, if I let you
See this place ♪
♪ Where stories all ring true ♪
♪ Will you let me
Past your face ♪
What can I get you?
Uh... Give me a Fat
Tire draft, please.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
♪ ...have to love
Believe and feel ♪
♪ Before the burst Of
tambourines take you there ♪
Damn it.
♪ Green grass and high... ♪
Hey, honey.
No. I-I don't know
what to tell you.
Three stores I've
been to so far,
and not one of
them have it in stock.
Well... Well, do they have
to be diapers for newborns?
What if we went up a
size and just kind of...
All right, all right.
No, I understand.
All right. No, I'll just...
I'll just keep looking.
I'm, uh... I'm pulling
into Wal-Mart now so...
Yeah. Okay.
Love you.
Thank you.
God.
Well played.
Mm.
[CHUCKLES]
They found water on Mars.
They have indeed.
DONALD: Don't exactly know
what to do with that information,
but, hey, God bless
them, they found it.
Oh, well, actually,
they theoretically can separate
the hydrogen from the oxygen
and process that into providing
fuel for man's space flights.
Ostensibly, turning Mars
into a giant gas station.
So it's a...
Yeah. We live in
an amazing time.
To water on Mars.
So, what did you
have? Girl or boy?
Oh.
Little girl. That's nice.
Thanks. Congratulations.
Thank you.
I have a daughter. Yeah?
How old?
Heh. Old enough to know better.
Twenty-seven next month.
Oh, wow.
You have other
kids? Just the one.
I've got a 16-year-old
boy. Well, he's almost 16.
Jeez. Oh, there's a spread, huh?
But he helps out, though.
He's even changing
some diapers now, so...
It's more than I managed
to do when I was his age.
Kids today grow
up faster, I think.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, maybe so.
So any advice?
Having a daughter. Any advice?
Oh. No, not really.
Just love them.
Just... Yeah.
I mean, they... They
are who they are.
Yeah.
I've got this... nephew.
[CHUCKLES]
This nephew who is...
I mean, he's an adult.
But you can't infantilize them,
you can't live
their life for them.
But still, I mean,
there is that frustration.
You know, that...
God, that frustration that
goes along with, you know:
"Yes, as a matter of fact,
I do know what is
best for you, so listen."
But of course, they don't.
I mean, what do you do
with someone like that?
Family?
Yeah. Family.
You can't give up
on them. Never.
I mean, what else is there?
Jesse, it's me.
Jesse, I just wanna talk.
[♪♪♪]
Jesus.
Jesse.
Jesse, wake up.
[COUGHING]
No, no, no.
[COUGHING AND CHOKING]
[SNIFFLING]
[♪♪♪]