[METAL THUMPING]
[♪♪♪]
HANK: All right,
everybody. Listen up.
Tuco Salamanca.
For those of you who were
not with us this morning
we raided his headquarters.
Also his last-known address.
Even the little den of iniquity
he keeps for his
meth-hag girlfriend.
We netted a bunch
of his lieutenants.
The big man himself
smelled us coming.
So study the
face. Study the file.
Get a big old raging hard-on
at the idea of catching
this piece of shit.
[PEOPLE CHUCKLE]
My apologies to
the H.R. department.
Grow tumescent
with anticipation.
All right.
On the hit parade, 1998.
Reputed to have whacked
one "Dog" Paulson
back when our homegrown
bandidos were wresting the crank trade
away from the So
Cal biker gangs.
Also, we're pretty
sure he knifed
a Mexican national in '03.
And for my money,
seeing how he
customarily deals with rivals,
I'd say he is a prime
suspect in the disappearance
of our dearly missed Krazy-8.
Hats over your
heart for that dirtball.
We hauled Tuco in for
questioning on that one
but as usual, we
couldn't make it stick.
Yeah, he runs a tight
ship. Smug bastard.
And even worse,
El Paso says he's got some
kind of cartel connection.
Yeah, yeah. I know it's...
We all know what's
going on down there.
We sure as hell don't
want it going on up here,
which brings us
to the good news.
We finally got some actual,
honest-to-God evidence.
This is one of Tuco's
henchmen. Street name: No-Doze.
Found him tucked in the junkyard
along with Tuco's
own brother-in-law,
a.k.a. Gonzo.
Gonzo, this rocket scientist,
was moving No-Doze's body...
Either hiding it
there or pulling it out.
We're still not sure.
When he got his
arm crushed clean off.
[CHUCKLES]
Anyone wanna see the
photos, they're on my website.
Hilarious.
Anyway. The upshot is
we got us a nice, big, juicy,
bloody fingerprint
which belongs to Señor Tuco.
Christmas came early to
the Schrader household.
That is, provided
we find this guy.
So to all present, I ask
you, you wanna find this guy?
ALL: Yes.
What the hell was that? Jesus.
Wanna try that again?
Do you wanna find this guy?
ALL: Yes!
Are we going to find
this guy? ALL: Yes!
Louder, damn it! ALL: Yes!
Give me a "hell,
yeah!" ALL: Hell, yeah!
Hell, yeah! ALL: Hell, yeah!
ALL [CHANTING]: Hell,
yeah. Hell, yeah. Hell, yeah.
They ain't gonna find him.
Guy is in México by now.
Appearances, Gomey. Tsk, tsk.
It's all about appearances.
Listen, I gotta take
some personal time.
Now, in the middle of a manhunt?
Skyler called last night.
It's Walt. He's missing.
Just disappeared from the house,
and no one's heard
from him since.
Damn. You don't think he...?
Holler if you need me.
All right. Thanks a lot,
man. Appreciate that.
[SNIFFS]
SKYLER: This is
the most recent photo.
We haven't taken
many lately, so...
Um, but that's what
he looks like now.
W-without the hair.
[DOOR OPENS]
HANK: Hey, it's, uh, me.
Hey, Tim.
Really appreciate you
sparing us your day off.
No worries. Happy to help.
Yeah, this is helpful. Good.
What about height and
weight? Five eleven,
most recently, about 170.
One sixty-five.
That's what I weigh.
I... I guess, uh,
he weighs a little less.
That's fine. That's
close enough. Good.
What about other
distinguishing features?
Tattoos or moles or scars?
Anything that might help us.
Um, tattoos? Um,
no. Not really. No.
That's fine.
Is that the list of
medications? Yes.
I wrote them all down.
And there's no
drug interactions.
None that are listed.
Um, I called his doctor, so, no.
Has he been depressed?
He's, um... He's
been withdrawn lately.
A little withdrawn.
Yeah.
Um, last night, he
was, uh, agitated.
Agitated?
Yeah. When he
came home last night,
he was, um, agitated, upset.
TIM: Upset in general
or upset because of
something particular?
Um...
When I asked him
what was wrong, he said:
"I don't know where to begin."
Um, then he just
walked out of the room...
Out of the bathroom.
I was in the tub, I
was taking a bath.
And when I came out about
10 minutes later, he was gone.
Nothing else missing?
His keys, wallet, cell
phone. Just what was on him.
But... What about
the phone call?
Uh, I'm looking into it.
What phone call?
Uh, Walt's cell phone rang.
He pulled it out, looked
at it and didn't answer it.
But then, a short time after,
he wandered out of the bathroom.
I mean,
couldn't that be, uh,
important, right?
Anything else you can think of?
[SIGHS]
Anything else. Um...
No. I called the
credit card providers,
and there's no report
of any recent activity.
I... Let's see.
I checked with every
hospital within 50 miles.
Every police station.
Every morgue.
So, no, I really don't... I
don't have anything else.
I was actually hoping that
you had something else,
being that you're the expert.
I'm... I'm sorry.
No worries.
I think this is good
enough to start.
Gives us plenty to work on.
Mrs. White.
Thank you.
Walter. Thank you.
So that cell-phone
call she's talking about?
I ran it.
And? Never happened.
No record of it.
Second cell phone.
Yeah. I'm thinking.
[THUMPING ON METAL]
[MAN GRUNTING]
[♪♪♪]
[COUGHING]
I understand.
Out.
JESSE: Get away from me!
[GRUNTING]
Settle down, bitch.
JESSE: You gonna shoot me, huh?
Shoot me in here!
I hope I bleed
like a mother too!
That way, you
have to clean it up!
[GASPING AND PANTING]
It's your ride, retard.
I ain't gotta clean
jack. Now get out.
[TRUNK SLAMS SHUT] [GASPS]
[COUGHS]
TUCO: Get up.
Get up.
[BOTH PANTING]
Oh, my God.
Don't... Don't do this, Tuco.
[GRUNTS]
[THE WALKMEN'S "RED MOON" PLAYS]
♪ I held up ♪
♪ A light to the smoke ♪
♪ But the wind blows ♪
♪ Blows it away ♪
♪ And the night is cold ♪
♪ And the clouds Go by ♪
♪ Tomorrow morning ♪
♪ I hope ♪
♪ To be home ♪
♪ By your side ♪
No more posters?
Walter Jr.'s making more.
Thank you, Marie.
I don't think
he'll hurt himself.
I mean, he just doesn't
strike me as the type.
He'll turn up.
[SIGHS]
Okay, the whole tiara thing,
I just find it
bewildering that...
Marie.
- -you didn't believe that...
Not now.
[MAN SPEAKING IN SPANISH ON TV]
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[COUGHS]
Empty your pockets.
Thought your name
was Heisenberg,
"Walter Hartwell White."
Heisenberg is kind
of a pseudonym.
You know, a business name.
Yeah.
[SIGHS]
I like doing business
with a family man.
There's always
a lot of collateral.
[TUCO LAUGHING]
[WALT GASPS]
Answer me one thing.
Can I trust you?
Yes. Yes, absolutely.
TUCO: Sit down.
DEA...
hit my place of
business this morning.
About a hundred
cops looking for me.
You two haven't
been talking, right?
No.
Picked up my whole
crew, top to bottom.
Everybody except Gonzo.
That's weird, right?
I mean, don't you
think that that's weird?
It's weird. Yes.
Unusual.
Last two days,
I couldn't get
Gonzo on the phone.
He's been acting all pouty
on account of No-Doze.
Explain to me.
How is it my fault
that that little bitch
did not know his place?
I saw this coming.
I can see the future, you know?
It's this gift that I have
deep inside my head.
I knew last night they were
gonna come try and bust me.
Gonzo.
He went and
snitched to the cops!
That lousy son of a bitch!
I trusted him like a brother!
I was good to him! I was good!
I see Gonzo, I'm gonna
gut him, I'm gonna skin him,
and I'm gonna stuff
his hide for a heavy bag,
and every time I hit him,
it's gonna be like
a lesson to myself!
You never, never trust
the people that you love!
So you plan to ice Gonzo,
like, future tense?
What?
You're... You're saying, Tuco...
You're saying that Gonzo
is currently operating
as a police informant
as far as you know?
I'm very sorry to hear that.
That's disappointing.
Yeah.
I'd waste him too, yo.
Shut up.
Okay.
They're out there
looking for me right now.
They... They got ghetto
birds and... And black ops.
I need to get high.
Oh, fu... I need to
get good and high.
[SNIFFS]
Ah!
What's with this gak? It
smells like headcheese.
No, it's, uh... It's killer.
Yeah, seriously.
So I was thinking last night.
I came up with this great idea.
México.
Mexico?
Ha-ha. We'll disappear
way out in the jungle.
We'll set you up in a superlab.
We'll do nothing but cook 24/7.
And no Federales
are gonna mess with us
because I got my people there.
Connections.
We are going to make beaucoup
bucks, Heisenberg, huh?
Tuco, I...
I have a wife and family.
So what? You'll get another one.
I don't want you to
take this the wrong way,
but I can't just
uproot my life like that.
Yeah, man. I mean, me neither.
Who's talking to you?
JESSE: You... You need me, man,
because I cooked that
scante in your hands.
Yeah.
I'll tell you something, yo.
You never tried nothing like it.
Stink or no stink,
one bump, you'll be
flying high for days.
It's a new product him
and I've been working up.
Careful when you hit it.
It kicks like a 12 gauge
when it comes on.
[LAUGHS]
It's got a secret ingredient.
What secret ingredient?
Chili powder.
I hate chili powder.
This blue magic, this is money.
You keep cooking
this, Heisenberg.
[SIGHS]
We're gonna rewrite
history with this.
[SNORTS]
[TUCO HOWLS AND LAUGHS]
All right. Time to
clean the menudo
out from between your ears.
No, no, no. No, I
need him, Tuco.
I need him very, very badly.
He's my partner.
And if he doesn't
go, I don't go.
TUCO: I'll tell you this.
My cousins are driving
up here right now
to smuggle us back down,
and they're gonna
be here by sunset
and you're gonna
be on that truck,
or you're gonna be dead!
And you...
You better hope they
got room in the trunk.
SKYLER: Where are you going?
Louis is taking me
to the train station.
We'll put these up.
No, no, honey. No, I'll do it.
He wants to help, let him help.
I mean, how long has it
been since you've slept?
Yeah, she's right, Sky.
Why don't you lay down a while?
For Christ sake, you
got a bun in the oven.
I got my cell if you need me.
Okay? SKYLER: Okay.
Bye, sweetie.
I'll see you later.
All right. Bye.
[DOOR OPENS]
Actually, I think the very fact
they haven't found him yet
bodes well.
Well, I mean, if he... You know.
Somebody would've
smelled something by now.
There's... There's
got to be something.
Some detail that we
haven't picked up on.
What about the
second cell phone?
Oh, Jesus.
What? We can't just
ignore a potential clue, Hank.
Okay. What...? What
are you talking about?
Uh, the call you said Walt
got before he disappeared?
There's no record of it
with the phone company.
Uh, no incoming, no
dropped calls, nothing.
But his phone rang. I heard it.
Um, all right.
Well, then if that's the case,
he must have a second phone.
Wh... Why? What... What
sense would there be in that?
Yeah. All right. Okay. I'm
not here to argue with you.
No, Hank.
You can't just bring up secret
cell phone and then drop it.
What...? What does it mean?
I don't know, Sky. What
do you want me to say?
It means Walt has a secret.
Everyone's got one from
somebody, big or little.
Okay. Oh, wow. Everyone. Okay.
Skyler, come on.
He kept cancer
from you for weeks.
Okay, then, let's assume
there's a second cell phone.
So what? What, is
he having an affair?
Walt? Please.
[SIGHS]
What about the marijuana?
He's not on pot anymore.
[LAUGHS]
Says who? Him?
Chemotherapy and
marijuana go together
like... Like apple
pie and Chevrolet.
Maybe he's addicted to the pot
and he owes his drug
dealer a lot of money.
Marie, you don't get
hooked on pot like that.
How do you know?
You didn't even know he
had a second cell phone.
Hank, you have to question
this drug-dealer person.
He may know something.
[HANK SIGHS]
Well, I'm telling you, we're
grasping at straws here.
Then grasp.
HANK: Excuse me, ma'am.
Hi, I'm looking for
Jesse. He around?
No. I'm afraid not.
Why? I'm sorry.
Hank Schrader.
Uh, I'm actually
hoping to talk to Jesse
about my brother-in-law,
Walter White.
He taught your son
chemistry in high school.
Oh, Mr. White. Yes,
I remember him.
That was a long time ago.
Yes, ma'am.
It's my understanding
that he and Jesse,
they've stayed in touch.
Really? Yeah.
Huh.
Mr. White must've seen
some potential in Jesse.
He really tried to motivate him.
He was one of the few
teachers who cared.
Yeah, Walt's that way.
He's... He's a good man.
I'm so sorry to hear
about his illness.
Please pass along
our best wishes.
I certainly will, as
soon as he turns up.
Um, he's missing, actually.
Just kind of walked off, or...
Anyway, which is
why I'm going around,
trying to think of anyone
who knows him, even slightly.
That's terrible.
Anything we can do to help.
Well, if you could put me
in touch with your son...
Like I said, we're kind
of desperate for leads.
Jesse's not answering either
phone number I have for him,
and no one seems to
be home at his house.
And why do you think my son
and Mr. White would be in touch?
I don't necessarily.
I just, um...
Are you with the police?
No, ma'am. Not at all.
I'm with the Drug
Enforcement Administration.
Oh, my God.
Is my son in trouble?
I have absolutely no
reason to think that, no.
Do I need to get a lawyer?
You know, you don't seem
very forthright about this,
coming here and asking
questions about my son and...
Mrs. Pinkman, I swear to you,
I'm not here on
official capacity.
I do not care what your son
may or may not have done wrong.
I just wanna find
my brother-in-law.
His wife is worried sick,
and she's got a baby on the way.
I'm sorry. I would
like to help you,
but I have not seen
my son in over a month.
I don't expect to see
him anytime soon.
Well, thanks for your time.
Oh, uh...
If you could tell
me one more thing.
Is Jesse still driving the
'89 Chevy Monte Carlo,
as far as you know?
[SIGHS]
If he had spent half as
much time and money
on his education
as he has on that
ridiculous bouncing car...
Low rider, huh?
Gomey, hey.
No, nothing yet. Hey, listen,
do me a solid and check out
a '89 Chevy Monte Carlo
registered to a
one Jesse Pinkman.
Specifically, I wanna know
if the car's got a LoJack.
It's one of those
jack-off low riders,
so I'm betting it's got a
good shot that there is.
If so, can you go ahead
and get me a fix on it?
Thanks, buddy.
[SIGHS]
[MAN AND WOMAN
SPEAKING IN SPANISH ON TV]
[SNIFFS]
[GRUNTING]
Oh!
Oh...
Chili powder.
Did I not already tell you
how moronic that was?
[SIGHS]
Whatever, man.
At least I tried something.
Hey, it almost worked too.
How's about you
leaving my gun, huh?
First you boost it, then
you leave it in your house.
My gun.
How was I supposed to know
you were chauffeuring
Tuco to my doorstep?
Well, at least he
wants you alive.
[NEWSCASTER SPEAKING
IN SPANISH ON TV]
[MAN SINGING AND
MUSIC PLAYING ON TV]
Hey, I don't get it.
If Tuco didn't kill
Gonzo, then who did?
I don't know.
Does it really matter?
If he finds out
that Gonzo is dead
and not a police informant,
who does he automatically blame?
Us.
We need a plan.
Think, think.
Let's just bum-rush him, man.
You know, you crack him
over the head with something,
and I'll go for his gun.
[THUD]
Crack him over the
head with something?
Hey, you got the
C-bomb, man, all right?
You're as good as
checked out already.
Okay? You should
be, like, all sacrificial,
jumping on a grenade, yo.
Just...
Oh, so my life is
not the priority here
because I'm gonna
be dead soon anyway.
That's your point?
Uh, yeah.
[SCOFFS]
[PAN SIZZLING]
We gotta get him to take this.
Well, he don't much
like the taste of chili P.
That much has been established.
So unless you can
convince him to booty bump...
Eat. We got a long
ride ahead of us.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Go on, sit.
You're looking a little
weak, Heisenberg.
I don't want you to go
belly up before we get there.
[DINGS]
TUCO: Take it easy, Tio.
I will feed you. I eat
first. That's the deal.
[DINGING]
What?
[LAUGHING]
Oh, I get it, I
get it, I get it.
Oh, you greedy old bastard.
I tell you, Heisenberg.
Old people.
You feed them, huh?
You put them in a really
nice crib in the country,
and yet they gotta steal
the food off your plate.
You better eat
every bite of that.
TUCO: Oh, God!
What'd you do that for?
God!
[TUCO SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[WOMAN SPEAKING SPANISH OVER TV]
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
[DINGS]
[LAUGHS] Hey, look. Look.
There's nothing left.
[BELL DINGING]
[DINGING]
[SNIFFS]
Oh!
What?
What do you want?
No.
Don't even tell me
that you're hungry.
Don't go there.
[BELL DINGING] [GROWLS]
[LAUGHS]
Are you mad-dogging them, Tio?
What, you don't like them?
One ding.
That means yes.
Tio don't like you.
Why don't you like them, Tio?
You don't trust them?
[BELL DINGS ONCE]
Why don't you trust them, Tio?
Tuco, come on. He's...
There clearly some
dementia. He's not lucid.
Shh.
Did they do
something to you, Tio?
Something that you don't like?
[BELL DINGS ONCE]
What did they do to you?
What did you do to my tio?
Nothing. Nothing.
Bullshit! My tio does not lie!
I don't know. I swear.
I don't know. I...
No, I... Maybe it was...
I... I did change the
channel on his TV, but...
Yeah, yeah, that's it.
While you were cooking,
you know, he was
watching one of those, um...
Those, uh... The
telenovels, you know,
with all those
ripe honeys on it?
He was really into it.
I told you not to change
the channel, man.
You know, dude needs
his eye candy. That's it.
[LAUGHING]
Tio.
Is that it, Tio?
Did they change your mamitas?
What are you telling me, Tio?
Huh?
Are they punking me?
[BELL DINGS ONCE]
JESSE: Hey. No.
No, man. No.
Come here! Aah! Don't shoot.
No, no, Tuco.
[GRUNTING]
Tuco, no. Tuco.
Tuco. Shut up!
[COUGHING]
No. Please, no. God. Please, no.
No, God. I don't wanna die.
Tell me what you did, Walter!
JESSE [SOBBING]:
Jesus, I don't wanna die.
No!
Tell me what you did!
We tried to poison you.
Because you're an insane,
degenerate piece of filth,
and you deserve to die.
[HOWLS]
[GRUNTING]
[GUNSHOT] [SCREAMS]
Who's the bitch now?
[GROANING]
[CRYING]
Let him bleed.
[COUGHING]
Oh, the keys.
Tuco.
Oh, my God.
WALT: The cousins?
[♪♪♪]
[TUCO GRUNTING]
JESSE: What the
hell is going on?
Jesse Pinkman.
You're a hard man to find.
Oh, shit.
Easy.
[♪♪♪]
[BOTH PANTING]
[METAL THUMPING]
Oh, my God.
Oh, God. Hank.
Who? Hank.
What?
Oh, my God. What?
Oh, my God. Stay.
What are you doing?
[BELL DINGING]
[♪♪♪]