[SIRENS WAILING DISTANTLY]
[♪♪♪]
TUCO: Ha-ha-ha. What is this?
It's blue.
WALT: We used a
different chemical process,
but it is every bit as pure.
It may be blue,
but it's the bomb.
[SNIFFS]
[COUGHS]
Tight, tight, tight. Yeah.
[SNIFFS]
Oh, blue, yellow,
pink, whatever, man.
Just keep bringing me that.
Oh!
You're all right. We're gonna
make a lot of money together.
Just remember who
you're working for.
What did you say?
I'm just saying, they gotta
know that they're working for you.
TUCO: Like they don't
already know that?
Are you saying
that they're stupid?
No, I'm just... I'm just saying.
Okay, so you're not
saying that they're stupid?
So I don't understand. Are
you saying that I'm stupid?
Is that it?
Is that what you're doing?
WALT: Tuco. Tuco.
Hey, why don't we
all just, uh, relax, huh?
[LAUGHING]
Heisenberg says relax.
[TUCO EXHALES]
I'm relaxed. I'm relaxed.
I'm rela...
Whoo!
Damn, man! Look at that! Look!
[TUCO SIGHS]
Yeah, that's messed up.
Okay, Heisenberg. Next week.
[LAUGHS]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[CAR IGNITION STARTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Adjusting for inflation
Good state college,
adjusting for inflation,
say, $45,000 a year.
Two kids, four years of college,
$360,000.
Remaining mortgage
on the home, 107,000.
Home equity line,
30,000. That's 137,000.
Cost of living, food,
clothing, utilities,
say, 2 grand a month.
I mean, that... That should
put a dent in it, anyway.
Twenty-four K a year,
provide for, say, 10 years.
That's $240,000.
Plus 360, plus 137.
Seven thirty-seven.
Seven hundred and thirty-seven
thousand. That's what I need.
That is what I need.
You and I both clear
about 70 grand a week.
That's only 10 and half
more weeks. Call it 11.
Eleven more drug deals,
and always in a public
place from now on.
It's doable. It's
definitely doable.
[SIGHS]
[CAR IGNITION STARTS]
JESSE: Whoa. No, no.
Slow, slow. Stop, stop.
[WHIMPERING] Heisenberg!
What the hell?
What's wrong with him?
What's the matter with you?
You can't take an
ass-beating, bitch?
Oh, damn, Tuco. Shut up!
There's... There's
no, uh, pulse.
Do something. Do something?
He... He needs an ambulance.
He... He needs a hospital.
Do something!
You're smart, right?
Do that... Do that thing.
No, there's not...
There's nothing.
Breathe into his mouth.
No, they don't teach that
anymore. It doesn't work.
You, come here.
Breathe into his mouth.
No.
[GRUNTING]
TUCO: Get rid of him.
Look, Tuco, we can't
do him like that, man.
Buzzards and rats and all that.
I'm just saying, you know?
It's not very Christian.
That sounds like arguing.
[CLANKING]
[TUCO WHISTLES]
TUCO: Gonzo, hurry up.
What's the big hurry?
Oh, I... I just think
we're done here.
Oh, yeah?
You're done.
Huh? Huh?
[GRUNTS]
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
[METAL SQUEALING]
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
Hey, I'm back here.
Hello?
MAN [ON TV]: Are
already married...
Hello?
[INDISTINCT DIALOGUE ON TV]
WOMAN [ON TV]:
Thank you to our viewers...
[SIGHS] Hey.
MAN: The crash happened as
rush hour began around 8 a.m.
Walt?
Didn't you hear me?
Walt.
Hey. Hey yourself.
What, you can't answer
when I'm calling you?
Are you okay?
Great.
New hat?
Yeah.
[SIGHS]
Well, I got some grilled
chicken at Albertson's.
Do you want me to
heat some up for you?
WOMAN: But they can
occasionally adapt to other local areas
like airports, golf courses...
[TV TURNS OFF]
Where've you been?
[SIGHS]
[SOBBING]
Oh.
What is...?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Oh.
[LAUGHS] What are you doing?
Okay. Um...
Do you know what? I've
got all this crap on my face.
Let me clean up first, okay?
You know, Walter Junior's
gonna be home any minute, so...
Okay. Um... Yeah, just...
Okay. Hold... Enough.
Hold up. Stop it.
Ow! Stop it!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[♪♪♪]
[SIGHS]
I know you're scared
and you're angry
and you're frustrated.
And I know none of this is fair.
But you cannot
take it out on me.
WALT JR.: Hey, I'm home.
[♪♪♪]
JESSE: Oh, we are dead.
Dead, man.
Ruto or rute or
however the hell you...
This is conjecture.
This is conjecture?
Yes. And conjecture
isn't helping.
State the facts. My
conjecture isn't helping?
Okay, fine. Facts, then. Fact A:
My phone rang
eight times last night.
Dead air, hang ups every time.
Second fact: Like
3 in the morning,
I saw that black Caddy of
his cruising my neighborhood.
No headlights. If
he wanted to kill us,
he would've done
it at the junkyard.
What is that, conjecture?
Are you basing that on
that he's got, like, a normal,
healthy brain or something?
Did you not see him beat a
dude to death for, like, nothing?
And that way... That way
he just kept staring at us,
saying, "You're done."
"You're done"?
You want to know
what that means?
I will tell you what that means.
That means exactly
how it sounds, yo.
All right. We are witnesses.
We are loose ends.
Right now, Tuco's
thinking, "Yeah, hey,
they cook good meth,
but can I trust them?"
What happens when
he decides "no"?
No.
It is him or us. You understand?
It is him or us!
How would you do it?
What do you mean,
how would I do it?
Specifically, how would
you do it? Step by step.
All right.
Say we set up one last sale.
This is providing
he doesn't decide
to waste us before then.
Now, every time we
bring in a new batch,
he always tests
the product, right?
So as his head is
down, you know,
giving it a snort,
just: Pop, pop, pop!
Pop, pop, pop. So three shots?
Yeah, three shots
or, I don't know, two.
No, wait. Is it
two, or is it three?
Two would probably
work, I guess.
Yeah. Okay, two shots.
Two in the chest?
Two in the face?
Man, come on.
I'm just trying to
understand how this works.
Okay. All right, we'll...
We'll put a pin in that.
But by now, the big guy, Gonzo,
he's probably
coming at you, right?
Yeah. Right.
So you turn toward him.
Yeah, just wheel on him...
How many shots for him?
I mean, he's a big guy.
How many shots does that take?
I don't know. Three
shots. Okay, three shots.
Okay, Tuco and
Gonzo. Two men down.
Now, is there anyone else there?
I mean, Tuco is usually
with someone else, right?
Maybe even a couple of guys.
His... His dealers, his posse.
All right.
So we'll put a
pin in that one too.
Now at this point, how
many shots have been fired?
I mean, you've gotta
be running low, right?
How many bullets
does that gun even take?
Well, let me see.
It's not...
[GRUNTING]
How can you suggest
that we kill a man
and you can't even open the gun?
It's not that easy, is it?
Hey, man, Walt, you did it.
Yeah.
[♪♪♪]
MARIE: Call Skyler.
[DIALING]
[LINE RINGING]
SKYLER [ON RECORDING]: Hey, there.
You've reached Walt, Skyler and Walter, Jr.
We can't come to
the phone right now,
so please leave us a message.
Well, aren't you early
bird, up and out already?
Listen, the big lug
and I are gonna go try
that new restaurant
over by UNM tonight,
so let me know if
you guys wanna hang.
Listen to me. "Hang."
Walt Jr. will be
proud. I know the lingo.
I'm still hip.
It's Chinese. The restaurant.
I don't know, I just
feel like Chinese.
Do you think that
people in China
ever just feel like American?
You know, and they go out
and get little takeout boxes
with mashed
potatoes and meat loaf
and try and figure out how to
use the little knives and forks?
I wonder if that ever happens.
All right, I'll let
you go. So call me.
[PHONE BEEPS]
Skyler didn't pick up?
Obviously, she's not home.
HANK: Baby. Baby, wait up.
Hey, what was that about,
uh...? About Chinese?
Dinner tonight. That new place.
How late they serve?
I don't know.
You got Dave at 8.
Not tonight.
Yeah, yeah. You do. Remember?
No, that's Thursday.
No.
Yeah, I'm pretty
sure that's Thursday.
Remember the last minute
they changed it around for you?
They were gonna
charge us a penalty.
Look, baby, you only
got six more sessions.
Yeah, and I'm doing them, Hank.
I said I would do them,
and I'm doing them.
I can't help it if you got
your days of the week wrong.
BOY: Look out.
Sorry, Mr. Schrader.
[SIGHS]
Look, it's... You
know, it's just...
Oh, boy. I...
I think Dave is, um,
really helping you.
Yeah. [CAR ENGINE STARTS]
[SOFT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC
PLAYING ON CAR STEREO]
Yeah.
[TIRES SCREECH]
Sorry about that.
She's, uh...
MAN: Hey! Hey, where's
my phone call? Ow!
Hits two in the sand,
two in the forest.
And then he says,
"Give me a four."
HANK: Gomez.
Gomez? What do you got for me?
Come on. Chop-chop.
Good morning to you too.
GOMEZ: A.P.D. sent this over.
This was about
eight or 10 days ago.
You know Southwest
Aniline, right?
Yeah, off the 25?
The place smells like feet.
This is them. Check this out.
Holy shit. What was that?
Thermite. So they tell me.
Burns about 5000 degrees.
Kind of stuff you see
on a James Bond movie.
Nice.
Guys who know their trade.
Ah, wait. I take that back.
[CHUCKLES]
What, they didn't think
about stealing a hand truck?
Hey, try rolling it,
morons. It's a barrel.
It rolls. Jesus.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
HANK: So, what'd they get?
GOMEZ: Methylamine, 30 gallons.
P2P?
They're cooking
old-school biker meth.
Who the hell still does that?
All the old-timers I know
are either dead or in prison.
Pseudo's in short supply,
so these two make do by
changing up the formula.
That and the thermite,
I'd say these two
know their chemistry.
But ranking them
as burglars? Shit.
I wouldn't trust these two
to break into the
Special Olympics.
They got book learning
but no street skills.
Maybe they're college kids.
Chem students trying
to make a big score.
Yeah, maybe.
I tell you, 30 gallons
of precursor...
That big a score, they're gonna
wind up stepping on some toes.
Tell you what,
they better pray it's us
who catches up to them
and not those boys from Juarez.
[CHUCKLES]
[CAR ENGINE STARTING]
[GASPS]
[SIGHS]
Your daughter wants out.
[LAUGHS]
[PHONE RINGING] Oh!
SKYLER [ON RECORDING]: Hey, there.
You've reached Walt, Skyler and Walter, Jr.
We can't come to
the phone right now,
so please leave us a message.
[ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS]
MARIE: Hey, it's me.
Thought I'd try
you earlier this time,
before you go out and,
you know, face the day.
I'm realizing now
it probably takes you a little
longer to get to the phone,
owing to the extra
baby weight...
[ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS]
Hey, sweetie.
[SIGHS]
Walt, did you spend
the entire night out here?
No.
Uh, no, no. Well, not all of it.
I mean, I did have a touch of...
My stomach, you know. And, uh...
I knew I was gonna
be up and down,
so I just didn't wanna wake you.
WALT: How would
he know where I live?
You sure it was Tuco?
Well, who else could it be?
Did you ever tell
him my name? No.
Did you ever tell him
where I live or anything?
No. What about Gonzo,
or the... Or the dead one?
Did you tell them anything?
I didn't say jack, man.
Okay, Tuco must've put
out, like, you know, feelers.
He's got his ways and
means, yo. Sources, all right?
He's closing in.
And what happens
when he finds out
that my brother-in-law
is a DEA agent?
Oh, God. What happens then?
[SIGHS]
Look, it's got five bullets.
I finally figured out how to...
Look, I just finally...
I figured it out.
I say we get a second
gun, right? For you.
I mean, don't we, like,
double our chances?
I mean, mathematically.
I've got a better idea.
[SIGHS]
Thank God.
All right.
What is it, Mr. White?
Lay it on me.
Beans.
Beans?
They're castor beans.
So, what are we
gonna do with them?
Are we just gonna grow
a magic beanstalk? Huh?
Climb it and escape?
We are going to
process them into ricin.
Rice and beans?
Ricin.
It's an extremely
effective poison.
It's toxic in small doses.
Also fairly easy to
overlook during an autopsy.
All right.
All right. So...
Don't touch them.
Seriously, you can get
poisoned from beans?
Yes.
Back in the late '70s,
ricin was used to assassinate
a Bulgarian journalist.
The KGB modified
the tip of an umbrella
to inject a tiny pellet
into the man's leg.
And we're talking about
an amount not much bigger
than the head of a pin.
But it... It killed him?
Oh, yes.
Now we just need to
figure out a delivery device,
and then no more Tuco.
Oh...
[KNOCKING ON WINDOW] [GASPS]
Hey, Sky.
Hey, Hank.
How you doing?
Is this, uh...? This a bad time?
Um... No, come on in.
Uh...
[DOOR CLOSES]
I, uh...
I should've called
first. I'm sorry.
[CHUCKLES]
What can I do for you?
Maybe, um, we ought...
You wanna...? You
wanna sit down first?
I don't know, Hank.
Depends on whether or not
this is gonna be about Marie.
Did she send you?
Hell, no.
She's barely even talking to me.
That's why I'm here, okay?
Self-preservation. Big time.
[LAUGHS]
Look, uh,
I know you gals have
your ups and downs.
I get it. Gals.
And I need to get involved
like I need a second
hole in my ass.
[LAUGHS] Uh-huh.
But if you could do
me this huge favor
and just return her phone calls.
I don't, ahem, think I'm
quite ready to do that yet.
Communication.
Communication, right?
Back and forth. Come on.
Sky, do this for me,
please. You can yell at her.
Just... Just...
Just call her back.
[SIGHS]
Marie is a shoplifter, Hank.
That's right.
That baby tiara she
gave me at the shower?
She stole it from
Gertrude Zachary's. Yeah.
I almost got arrested
when I went back to return it.
And Marie won't admit
it. She won't apologize.
[SIGHS]
Yeah.
If I thought you
were gonna return it,
I would have never, you know...
You knew about this.
We're... We're working on it.
I mean, she... She's
got this therapist, Dave.
And I mean, Dave is really good.
Dave's good, yeah.
But it's... It's an
ongoing process, Sky,
and we... We have gotta
be understanding, you know?
I mean, we gotta, you know.
We gotta support
the shit out of her.
Oh.
Do we?
Yeah.
I need support.
Me.
The almost-40-year-old
pregnant woman
with the surprise
baby on the way.
And the husband
with the lung cancer
who disappears for hours on end,
and I don't know where he goes.
And he barely even
speaks to me anymore.
With the moody son
who does the same thing.
And the overdrawn
checking account.
And the lukewarm water heater
that leaks rusty-looking crap
and is rotting out the
floor of the utility closet
and we can't
even afford to fix it.
But, oh, I see.
Now I'm supposed
to go, "Hank, please,
"what can I possibly
do to further benefit
"my spoiled,
kleptomaniac, bitch sister,
who somehow always manages
to be the center of attention?"
Because God knows she's the one
with the really
important problems.
[SOBBING]
Want me to take a
look at that utility closet?
[♪♪♪]
JESSE: That's all it takes?
WALT: That's all it takes.
JESSE: So now what?
WALT: Now we
arrange our next meet.
In a public place this
time. Nice and safe.
Business as usual.
And, uh, after we sell
him our usual four pounds,
then we'll pull this out.
"By the way, Tuco,
"this is a new meth formula
we've been working on.
Would you care to try it?"
Okay, well, what's new about it?
I mean, just in case he
asks. What do we say?
I don't know. Whatever you want.
It gets the user insanely high.
I mean, how much
salesmanship do we really need?
That degenerate snorts
anything he gets his hands on.
Okay, well, we'll just
put a pin in that, then.
Anyway, within
the next 48 hours,
maybe 72,
it'll look like natural causes.
What, like a heart attack?
Yeah.
Or the flu, maybe.
His associates won't
know any differently,
and we'll be in the clear.
Not if Tuco kills us first.
[PHONE RINGING]
Ah...
[PHONE CONTINUES RINGING]
Just keep it down.
Hey, Hank. What's up?
HANK: Oh, hey, uh, buddy.
Uh, you been home yet?
No. Why?
Well, uh...
Because I really
screwed up, man.
I apologize in
advance for the earful
you're gonna hear from Skyler.
I was trying to get her
and Marie talking again.
Big mistake.
I should have
just kept out of it.
Yeah, well, okay.
[SIGHS]
Me and my big mouth, I guess.
Yeah, well, that...
You know, it happens.
It's no problem. No worries.
Yeah, well, thanks,
man. I appreciate that.
Jesus, the wives, huh?
Hank, unfortunately, I really...
Oh, yeah. Hey, man,
don't let me keep you.
Actually, I'm at
work, so... Oh, hey.
[LAUGHING]
You wanna see
something really freaky?
Well, I would, but...
Seriously, Walt, this is...
[LAUGHS]
You gotta check out this crime
scene me and Gomie are at.
Just a second.
[CAMERA CLICKS]
[LAUGHING]
Hank. Hang on, hang on.
It should be coming
through right now.
[PHONE BEEPS]
Guess it could be worse, huh?
Could be having a
day like these two.
Couple of local bulletheads.
Guess they pissed
off the wrong guy.
Walt, you there?
Hey, Walt?
I'm taking this.
No. It's my gun. I need it!
No, you don't. Not
if you leave town.
Get out of here.
Tuco killing Gonzo means
he's coming after us next.
Now, I've... I've gotta
get home. My family.
[♪♪♪]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[COUGHS]
Skyler?
WALT: Walter, Jr.?
[CLANKING]
[COUGHING]
Hey.
Where's Walter, Jr.?
Having dinner at Louis'
house. Supposedly.
Yep.
All day, I've had the
whole house to myself.
So where have
you been this time?
SKYLER: Walt?
Walt?
Walt, will you come in
here and talk to me please?
Walt!
I'll be right there.
HANK: Yeah, I recognize
these two knobjobs.
Known associates of
a psychotic piece of shit
named Tuco Salamanca.
Guess he got
tired of associating.
Yeah. Hey, do you
mind if I get in there?
No, go ahead.
Thanks.
The big one smells fresher.
You guys find a death wound?
No?
I see, uh... I see lots of
blood, but no, uh, bullet holes.
DETECTIVE: Yeah.
You done taking pictures?
All right. Let's
lay them out flat.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Let me get out of
your way here, man.
[RIPPING]
Oh, snap.
Damn, Ricky. Leave
something for the coroner.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, this is beautiful.
Hey, someone call Jay Leno.
We got the world's
dumbest criminal.
This guy wasn't murdered.
Look.
Big stuff here was
moving this guy's body
when the stack
must have shifted.
Crushed his arm,
pinned him here,
and he, uh, bled out.
Poetic justice. Oh, I love it.
Don't you just?
Hey, hey, get a photo of
me with this guy, all right?
Old stumpy, here. Make
sure you get the stump in there.
[CAMERA SNAPS] [LAUGHS]
Walt, would you
talk to me, please?
I... I don't know
where to begin.
[PHONE RINGING]
What the hell are
you doing here?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Get in.
TUCO: Get in.
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
TUCO: Let's go.
[METAL SQUEALING]
[♪♪♪]