[COUGHING]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANING]
[CAR APPROACHING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING
FROM POLICE RADIO]
Just get me home.
I'll do the rest.
[CAR DEPARTS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[MARTY ROBBINS' "EL PASO"
PLAYING ON CAR STEREO]
♪ I saddled up
And away I did go ♪
♪ Riding alone In the dark ♪
♪ Maybe tomorrow
A bullet may find me ♪
♪ Tonight nothing's worse
Than this pain in my heart ♪
♪ And at last, here I
am On the hill of the... ♪
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
[COUGHING]
Yes, hello, this is David Linn
from The New York Times.
May I speak with Susan,
please? Thank you.
Hi, Susan, it's David again.
I was just calling to
see if we can set...
Well, yes. Well, I figured
we'd have to do the
interview by phone,
since they've
already left New York.
But what we'd really love to get
is a photo of Mr. and
Mrs. Schwartz
to go along with the article.
When are they
scheduled to get home?
Oh, so they'll be
home tonight. Gotcha.
Now, the address I have on
them is Upper Canyon Road.
Is that still...?
No, it isn't. They've...
Oh, let me get a pen.
Where do they...?
Tesuque. I see.
And the address?
Is that up near the opera
house? I hear that's nice.
No?
Well, I'll be in contact
with my photographer
to check on his schedule.
No, no, it's their call.
I know how busy
Mr. and Mrs. Schwartz are.
Thank you.
This should make
one hell of a story.
Goodbye.
ELLIOTT: I'm just saying,
it's apples and oranges.
Listen, I maintain,
if I want pizza,
I go to a pizza place. Yeah.
If I want Thai, I
go to a Thai place.
What is the point in
comparing Did I marry you?
Pizza to Thai?
What has happened?
GRETCHEN: This is different.
ELLIOTT: They're completely...
GRETCHEN: Oh, come on,
are you the man I married?
I am the guy who wants to
end this ridiculous conversation,
kick off my shoes,
and have a very
large glass of wine.
Well, I'm gonna tell
you to be my guest.
[ALARM BEEPING]
All right, wait.
The answer is 21.
No. Yes.
Yes, because it has history.
Come on.
Prohibition.
The Sweet Smell of Success.
ELLIOTT: And Per
Se has Thomas Keller.
Game, set, and match.
GRETCHEN: The whole
vibe is so Yountville.
You transplant
it to Manhattan...
ELLIOTT: Transplant it to
Islamabad, I would still eat there.
GRETCHEN: Oh,
there's a good thought.
ELLIOTT: What, Islamabad?
GRETCHEN: No, Napa.
We have to go to Napa.
ELLIOTT: Oh, my
God, all this talk of food.
Do you think Juana
left us anything?
[GOUNOD'S "BALLET MUSIC NO. 1
ALLEGRETTO" PLAYING ON SPEAKERS]
GRETCHEN: She doesn't
think we're back until Wednesday.
Unless you told her.
ELLIOTT: No, I haven't.
Oh, look, here.
Just a pear, that'll be perfect.
GRETCHEN: Yeah.
ELLIOTT: You wanna
get us a nice bottle of wine?
GRETCHEN: Mm-hm.
ELLIOTT: Do you think
we have any of those...?
What are those crackers
with, like, the sun-dried tomato,
and they were slightly
peppery, but not too peppery.
GRETCHEN: We don't have them?
ELLIOTT: No.
GRETCHEN: Ask Juana.
ELLIOTT: We haven't
had them in forever.
I don't know why
she doesn't get those.
GRETCHEN: Why
don't you talk to her?
ELLIOTT: She's got that
thing with her daughter.
Anyway, Napa? Yeah.
How long since we've
been? Two years.
Jesus, that's two years.
Yeah, too long,
right? Is this okay?
Oh, that looks perfecto.
You wanna get the fireplace?
Is it good? Mm-hm.
Is it ripe? Mm-hm.
ELLIOTT: Yeah.
GRETCHEN: We could
invite George and Delores.
They could come up from Marin.
And Bill and Miriam Cohen.
We could have a
little spa action, right?
And then we could do
some sort of wine, and then...
[SCREAMS]
Hello, Gretchen.
Elliott.
I really like your new house.
Walt.
This...
Are we looking east?
Oh...
My God, you must
have one great view
of the Sangre de Cristos.
Walt, w-what are you doing here?
WALT: I saw you on Charlie Rose.
You looked great.
You both did. If
you are here to...
To hurt us...
Walt, whatever it
is you're planning...
Actually, I'm here to
give you something.
It's out in my car.
How about the three
of us take a walk to it?
It's just parked down the road.
I couldn't get it
past your gate.
Elliott,
if we're gonna go that way,
you'll need a bigger knife.
[KNIFE CLATTERS ON FLOOR]
WALT: Keep
stacking. It'll all fit.
[COUGHING]
That's all right.
Yeah, just throw it on top.
Gretchen, would you mind?
We don't want to lose
any under the furniture.
All right.
That is $9,720,000.
Where did it come
from? And why is it here?
I earned it, and you're
going to give it to my children.
What? Why?
Walt, I don't think we...
On my son's 18th birthday,
which is 10 months
and two days from today,
you will give him this money
in the form of an
irrevocable trust.
You will tell him that it is
his to do with as he sees fit,
but with the hope
that he uses it
for his college education.
And for the
betterment of his family.
Walt, I'm not sure
that we follow.
W-Why...?
Uh, I mean, why, in
particular, would we...?
If you wanna give your kids
drug money, go do it yourself.
I can't.
My wife and son hate me.
They won't take my money.
Even if they did,
the federal government
wouldn't let them.
But two rich benefactors
who are known for their
charitable endeavors,
who would think nothing of,
for instance, writing
a $28 million check,
to help victims of
methamphetamine abuse?
I have to think that your
money would be very welcome.
It wouldn't make any
sense coming from us.
It certainly would.
My children are
blameless victims
of their monstrous father.
A man who you
once knew quite well.
Call it a beau geste,
call it liberal guilt,
call it whatever
you want, but do it.
And you are not to spend
a single dime of your own money.
If there are taxes or
lawyers' fees owed,
you will take it
right from here.
They use my money, never yours.
ELLIOTT: O-Okay, Walt, sure.
That sounds reasonable.
So, what happens next?
I guess we shake
on it, and I leave.
I can trust you to do this.
Yes.
Absolutely, you can.
[SCREAMS]
Don't move. Don't...
Don't dare move a muscle.
You don't want them to think
that you're trying to get away.
Just breathe.
Just this afternoon, I
had an extra $200,000
that I would have loved dearly
to leave on top of this table.
[♪♪♪]
Instead, I gave it
to the two best hit men
west of the Mississippi.
Now...
Whatever happens to me tomorrow,
they'll still be out there.
Keeping tabs.
And if,
for any reason,
that my children do
not get this money,
a kind of countdown will begin.
Maybe a day or so later,
maybe a week, a year,
when you're going for a
walk in Santa Fe or Manhattan
or Prague, wherever,
and you're talking
about your stock prices
without a worry in the world.
And then suddenly,
you'll hear the scrape
of a footstep behind you,
but before you can
even turn around:
Pop!
[WHIMPERS]
Darkness.
Cheer up, beautiful people.
This is where you
get to make it right.
[♪♪♪]
[CRYING]
[SNAPS FINGERS]
Oh, yeah, right.
You know, I don't exactly
know how to feel about all this.
PETE: For real, yo.
Whole thing felt kind of shady,
you know, like, morality-wise?
BADGER: Totally.
How do you feel now?
Better. Yeah,
definitely improving.
What's this I hear about
blue meth still being out there?
What do you mean?
Have you heard anything?
Is it still being sold?
Yeah.
By whom?
It's you, right?
I mean, aren't
you still cooking?
PETE: Damn, man.
We were sure it was you,
because that shit is choice, yo.
Better than ever.
I mean, um, you know.
Jesse. BADGER: Seriously?
You said he moved to
Alaska. That's what I heard.
Right on, Jesse.
Passing the torch.
BADGER: Damn, man, couldn't
he at least throw a brother a bone?
[♪♪♪]
[BLOWS]
[INHALES]
[METAL CLANKS]
[JAVAROO'S "LOVE IS RUNNING
THROUGH ME" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
♪ My heart keeps calling
to you Baby, why? ♪
Whoa, what happened there?
It's my birthday.
Yeah? Well, happy birthday.
HANK: It's easy
money. Till we catch you.
Say the word, I'll take
you on a ride-along.
You can watch us
knock down a meth lab.
Get a little excitement
in your life. Heh, heh.
Yeah, someday.
[SOFT JAZZ MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Welcome. Would you like
a menu? No, thank you.
Chamomile tea
with soy milk, please.
All right, you got it.
Hey, how you doing?
Good.
How's things?
Hey, I like your...
Shirt.
My blouse? Nice.
Yeah, I like the color.
That's a nice color on you.
It's kind of a...
I don't know exactly
what you'd call it.
It's kind of a cornflower blue.
Before you say or do
anything, just hear me out.
Todd.
Nobody knows I'm here.
Just listen for two minutes,
and then I'll leave. Please.
No. Please.
Just two minutes of
your time. That's all I ask.
Please.
You're running out of
methylamine, aren't you?
I can do the math.
You've been at it long enough.
You must be running low.
I have a new method
that requires no methylamine.
It's easy, and it will
keep you in business.
And, Todd, I could
teach it to you.
How did you know
to find us here?
Ten a.m.
Every Tuesday morning,
you and I met here.
You're rather
schedule-oriented, I guess.
[COUGHING]
Sorry.
I need the money.
I've spent almost
all of mine already,
just trying to stay one
step ahead of the police.
Mr. White, I don't
think there's...
How much would it cost us?
Nothing short of a million.
And believe me, for this,
that is giving it away.
I think Jack should hear this.
Yeah, I don't know.
Now, listen, I can come up
there tonight and talk to him.
He'd get it.
This is a win-win situation.
Hi, what can I get for you two?
He's just leaving.
Good seeing you
again. Take care.
For you?
I'm good.
And I need more stevia.
Okay, no disrespect to the
man, but doing business with him?
Right now, that's not...
Of course we're not
doing business with him.
Todd, please.
Don't make me
walk you through this.
Jesus. Did you look at him?
You'd be doing him a favor.
[WALT COUGHS]
[WALT HUMMING MARTY
ROBBINS' "EL PASO"]
♪ Mexico ♪
♪ Out through the back
door Of Rosa's I ran ♪
[COUGHING]
♪ Out where the
horses Were tied ♪
♪ I caught a good one
Looked like it could run ♪
[SIGHS]
♪ As fast as I could ♪
[REMOTE BEEPS]
♪ From the west
Texas town Of El Paso ♪
[HUMMING]
[GROANS]
[REMOTE BEEPS]
[PHONE RINGING]
ANSWERING MACHINE:
Hello, please record after the tone.
[ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS]
MARIE [OVER
PHONE]: Truce, all right?
Skyler, I have news about
Walt, and you need to hear it,
so if you're there, pick up.
Skyler...
Hey.
What's up?
Walt's in town.
Yeah?
That car they thought he
stole in New Hampshire,
they found it in a Denny's
parking lot right on Central.
And your next-door
neighbor, on the right...
What's her name, Becky?
Becky's on the left.
Carol's on the right.
Becky, Carol, whatever.
She saw him at your old house.
Just this morning, plain as day.
He's there, walking
out of your house,
and he calls her by name.
He didn't hurt her,
did he? He didn't...?
No, he's just
like, "Hey, Becky!"
Or Carol, whatever.
She said he looked
exactly like the Unabomber.
But she's positive it was him.
They're getting calls
from all over town.
He's here, he's there, he's
going to blow up city hall.
He has some sort of manifesto.
He wants to be on the news.
Who's making these calls? Him?
There are two or three voices.
They're not sure if
they're crank calls
or people he's put up to it,
or if they're actual
anonymous tips.
It's stretching them thin,
which is maybe the point.
As far as I'm concerned,
there are three places
that he would go:
To you, to me, or Flynn.
Right.
They're watching
the high school.
They're probably
watching your place too.
I mean,
I know that's what
Hank would do.
There is no way
Walt's getting to you.
They are absolutely
going to catch him.
No doubt about it.
That arrogant asshole thinks
he's some criminal mastermind,
but he's not.
But on the off chance...
Yeah.
On the million-to-one chance,
you be on the lookout, okay?
Thanks.
You got it.
Five minutes.
WALT: Five minutes.
You didn't kill anybody
sneaking in here, did you?
You didn't hurt anybody? No.
Didn't have to.
You look terrible.
Yeah.
But I feel good.
So talk.
Why are you here?
It's over.
And I needed a proper goodbye.
Not our last phone call.
So you're going to the police?
They'll be coming to me.
If you're in custody,
what stops those
people from coming back?
When...
When I still had the house,
three men came in
the middle of the night,
wearing masks,
threatening Holly
and Flynn and me.
They told me not to talk about
that woman at the car wash,
and if you're in custody...
They're not coming
back. Not after tonight.
What's tonight?
We don't want your money, Walt.
I thought Flynn made that clear.
He did.
And I don't have
any to give you.
I spent the last
of it getting here.
All I have to give you
is this.
Call the DEA once I leave.
Tell them I was here.
That I forced my way in.
Tell them...
Tell them I wanted bacon
and eggs on my birthday,
and that I gave you that ticket.
Those numbers are
GPS coordinates.
For what?
A burial site.
That's where they'll find
Hank and Steve Gomez.
[CRYING]
It's where I buried our money.
And the men who
stole it from us,
the men who still have it,
they murdered Hank and Steve
and put them in that hole.
Now, you trade that
for a deal with the prosecutor.
You get yourself out of this.
Skyler.
All the things that I did,
you need to understand...
If I have to hear
one more time
that you did this
for the family...
I did it for me.
I liked it.
I was good at it.
And...
I was...
really...
I was alive.
[SIGHS]
Flynn will be home soon.
Before I go,
may I see her?
Whoo.
Damn, man, this
thing's a classic.
What block you got in it?
The 500 or the 425?
Couldn't tell you.
Well...
Five hundred.
That's the one you want.
No replacement for displacement.
Where to?
To the clubhouse.
Go ahead, just park it
right in front over here.
No, no, no, just
straight in, man. Just...
What are...?
All right, fine, here, whatever.
[WALT COUGHS]
Hey, how you doing?
Turn around, put
your arms out like this.
[TRAIN HORN BLARES IN DISTANCE]
While you're at it,
why don't you
lift your shirt up,
give us a spin?
Christ, I'm not wearing a wire.
Okay?
My wallet and keys?
Yeah, you'll get
them back. Just relax.
[WHISTLES]
Stay here.
Keep your eyes open.
Jesus, look at you with
that head of hair. Is that real?
Yes.
That's not a wig? Seriously?
No.
What were you doing
before, shaving it?
Yes.
Christ, that is one
fine head of hair.
I mean, otherwise,
you look like shit, but...
Hello to you too, Jack.
Now, can we talk business?
I don't think so, no.
Did Todd tell you
what I'm offering?
Yeah, he told me.
The thing is, we're
not really in the market.
You're low on methylamine.
What happens then?
No, we'll get more.
That Quayle woman's
got her own setup.
The heat's off her.
She can break loose a barrel.
It ain't broke, so why fix it?
Todd, please, would you
explain things to your uncle?
Explain to him the
benefit of what I'm offering.
You really shouldn't have
come back, Mr. White.
I'm sorry.
Wait. Jack. Where
do you want it?
I don't know, anywhere
but my living room?
Take him out back.
Jack, look, you owe me.
You owe me. Hey, hey, hey.
MAN: Let's go. I
owe you, what for?
Jesse Pinkman.
You promised you would
kill him, and you didn't.
Instead, you partnered with him.
MAN: All right. WALT:
You're his partner now...
Whoa, stop.
Partners? What are
you talking about?
He's alive, isn't he?
He's cooking for you.
What, are you gonna lie?
Him being alive is not
him and me being partners.
Not by a damn sight.
What, you think I'd
partner with a rat?
Where is that
little piece of shit?
He's finishing up a batch.
Go get him. Bring him here.
Uncle Jack... No. No, no, no.
This one here,
calling me a liar?
He just insulted you,
he insulted me, all of us.
Jesus. Hustle it up. Come
on. Let's get this over with.
I'm gonna show you
just how wrong you are.
Then I'm putting that
bullet in your head myself.
[DOOR OPENS]
Yeah, you see what I'm
talking about, you son of a bitch?
Now, does this look
like a partner to you?
Come here. Take a look.
Come here!
Take a look at him.
Have a gander.
This is my partner.
Right, partner? Right, buddy?
Hardworking, good
partner. Fifty-fifty partner.
Can you hurry this shit up?
Make it quick?
[YELLS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Toddy, get him off, would you?
Yeah, Toddy, get them both off.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[REMOTE BEEPS]
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
TODD: Uncle Jack.
Jesus.
Mr. White.
[♪♪♪]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GAGGING]
[♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
Wait. Wait.
You want your money, right?
You wanna know where it is?
You pull that
trigger, you'll never...
Come on.
Do it.
You want this.
Say the words.
Say you want this!
Nothing happens
until I hear you say it.
I want this.
Then do it yourself.
[GROUCHO MARX'S "LYDIA, THE
TATTOOED LADY" PLAYS AS RINGTONE]
♪ Lydia, oh, Lydia Say,
have you met Lydia? ♪
♪ Lydia The tattooed lady ♪
♪ Lydia, oh, Lydia Say,
have you met Lydia? ♪
♪ Lydia The tattooed lady ♪
♪ Lydia, oh, Lydia Say,
have you met Lydia? ♪
♪ Lydia The tattooed lady ♪
Pick up the phone.
[LINE RINGING]
WALT [ON PHONE]: Hello?
Is it done?
Is he gone?
Yeah, it's done.
He's gone.
They're all gone.
Todd? Who is this?
It's Walt.
How are you feeling?
Kind of under the weather?
Like you've got the flu?
That would be
the ricin I gave you.
I slipped it into
that stevia crap
that you're always
putting in your tea.
Oh, my God.
Well...
Goodbye, Lydia.
[CELL PHONE CLATTERS]
[LAUGHING]
[SCREAMS]
[COUGHS]
[POLICE SIRENS WAILING]
[BADFINGER'S
"BABY BLUE" PLAYING]
♪ Guess I got What I deserved ♪
♪ Kept you waiting
there Too long, my love ♪
♪ All that time Without a word ♪
♪ Didn't know you'd
think That I'd forget ♪
♪ Or I'd regret ♪
♪ The special
love I had for you ♪
♪ My baby blue ♪
♪ All the days Became so long ♪
♪ Did you really think
I'd do you wrong? ♪
♪ Dixie When I let you go ♪
♪ Thought you'd realize
That I would know ♪
♪ I would show ♪
♪ The special
love I had for you ♪
♪ My baby blue ♪
[♪♪♪]