JESSE: There.
That's them.
[SIGHS] Your play, Walter.
You're on your own.
Looks like you're about
1,000 gallons light here, Mike.
Where's the juice?
The methylamine isn't coming.
Why is that?
And who the hell are you?
I'm the man who's keeping it.
What the hell's this?
We had an agreement,
right? We got our deal.
So where's the tank, Mike?
Mike doesn't know where it is.
Only I do. And you're
dealing with me now, not him.
Why don't you just cut
to what it is you want,
or what you think is gonna
happen here, all right?
'Cause we're gonna
get what we came for.
That 1,000 gallons of methylamine
is worth more in my hands
than it is in yours or
anyone else's, for that matter.
But I need distribution.
[CHUCKLES] Distribution.
That's right.
So if you agree to
give up your cook
and sell my product instead,
I'll give you 35
percent of the take.
35 percent? Wow.
Are you kidding me? 35...
Mike, please tell me this is a joke.
You know how far we had to stick our
necks out to get our hands on this cash?
And why the hell
would we want you?
You realize we have
our own operation, right?
I know all about your operation.
My partners here tell me
that you produce a meth
that's 70 percent
pure, if you're lucky.
What I produce is
99.1 percent pure.
So?
So... it's grade school t-ball
versus the New York Yankees.
Yours is, uh, just some tepid,
off-brand, generic cola.
What I'm making is classic coke.
All right. Okay.
So, um... [CLEARS THROAT]
If we just waste you
right here, right now,
and leave you in the desert,
then there is no more
coke on the market, right?
See how that works?
There's only us.
Do you really wanna live in
a world without coca cola?
My partner tells
me that your crew
switched to a P2Pcook
because of our success.
You dye your meth
with food coloring
to make it look like mine.
You already ape my
product at every turn.
But now...
You have the opportunity
to sell it yourself.
I need you to listen to me.
We're not gonna
give up this deal
to be your errand boys,
do you understand?
For what?
To watch a bunch of
junkies get a better high?
A better high means
customers pay more.
A higher purity
means a greater yield.
That's 130 million
dollars a profit
that isn't being pissed away
by some substandard cook.
Now you listen to me.
You've got the
greatest meth cook in a,
no, the two
greatest meth cooks
in America right here,
and with our skills,
you'll earn more
from that 35 percent
than you ever would on your own.
Yeah. So you say.
Just wondering
why we're so lucky.
Why cut us in?
Mike is retiring from our crew,
so his share of the
partnership is available,
if you can handle
his end... Distribution.
And if you give him
five million dollars
of the 15 million that
you brought today.
Just think of it
as a finder's fee
for bringing us together.
We have 40 pounds
of product ready to ship,
ready to go.
Are you ready?
[CHUCKLES]
Who the hell are ya?
You know.
You all know exactly who I am.
Say my name.
Do what? I don't...
I don't have a damn
clue who the hell you are.
Yeah, you do. I'm the cook.
I'm the man who
killed Gus Fring.
Bullshit. Cartel got Fring.
Are you sure?
That's right.
Now, say my name.
Heisenberg.
You're goddamn right.
I gotta hand it to you, Walter.
Hey.
I appreciate the kind words,
but I'm out too, remember?
I know. We'll talk.
Maybe we should talk
about how and when
I'm gonna get my
five million dollars.
And we will do that.
Absolutely.
It's just, you know...
Jesse, just give me
some time here, okay?
I'll need a little help getting things
up and running during this transition.
You can at least
do that for me, right?
Huh? Come on. Don't worry.
We'll figure it out.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[TRUNK SLAMS SHUT]
Well, I guess that's it.
Parting thoughts,
of which I have two:
First, as I said,
I'll handle the legacy
costs out of my end
so you won't have to worry
about my guys anymore.
Second, the bug.
The DEA will do a sweep.
Can't say when.
Could be anytime.
But you need to
get it outta there,
sooner rather than later.
All right.
That's it?
No "thanks for the
five million dollars,"
no "sorry for chaining
you to a radiator"?
Just get the bug, Walter.
So, hey.
I guess, uh...
I guess I'll see you around.
No. Don't think so.
When I'm out, I'm out.
Well, I'm out, too, Mike.
Kid...
Just look out for yourself.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[KNOCKING CONTINUES]
Are we good?
You tell me.
Okay, Jesse. Back it up.
You're good.
Keep it coming. Straight back.
Slow it down.
All right. That's good.
Hey, Mrs. White.
[TRUCK DOOR OPENS]
Vamonos.
I wish.
All right. Let's get
this thing hooked up.
[CLEARS THROAT] Walt...
What is this?
Do you really wanna know?
Why are you hiding it here?
Don't worry about it.
Who are you hiding it from?
I said, "Don't worry about it."
From the police?
Or someone else?
Someone who would kill for it?
Why don't you go
back in the office?
back in the office
and let us do this?
We'll get it out of your hair.
[CLACKING]
[RATTLING]
Oh! What'd you
bring me this time?
They're bacon banana cookies.
Is there bacon in
these? Oh, my God!
Just bits. Just
little bits of bacon.
Just enough to make
those suckers really pop.
Dan, this is too much.
I'm not sharing those.
Bad office etiquette?
I don't give a crap.
They're mine. Well, they're
yours to do with as you please.
Good, 'cause my husband's
not getting any either.
How is Mickey?
Don't get me started.
He wants to buy a boat.
I can't even get him
to start the lawnmower,
and he wants to buy a boat.
Oh, I don't know. A
boat might be nice.
A little one, maybe.
Oh, please. Where would
you even take a boat?
All the way down
to Elephant Butte?
Or Caballo. It's
beautiful down there.
You can even
leave it at the lake
if you don't want
to haul it every time.
We are not buying a boat.
I'll tell you that right now.
And the last one is 545.569.
Aw, dang it.
I almost got them all
that time. Very good.
But actually, I've got an
extra one for you this week...
603.
603. Where is that?
Right down there. Ah.
All right. I'll let
you get to it.
Thanks, dot.
Young Kaylee's gonna need
a second safety deposit box
if you decide to leave
one more dollar to her.
Mm.
How's the rest of it?
Oh, it's empty, as usual.
The families are pretty
reliable with the pickups.
Nobody complaining
about wanting it all at once?
Nah, they get it. Slow
and steady wins the race.
So I guess this
is it for a while?
Mm.
Don't worry about the families.
They'll keep getting
their deliveries.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[HANK ON SPEAKER DEVICE] I know
times are tight, but it's for the kids,
and your sponsorship
would sure be appreciated.
Yeah. We have
a, um, silver level,
but the gold and platinum levels
really get your name out there
on the banners and t-shirts.
Sure. No. No,
that's not a problem.
No, you call me
directly if things change,
you hear? [CLICK]
[SIGHS] Gomie, take
a brick to my head
if I ever have to make
another fun run call.
I'm done.
What's up? Why you smiling?
GOMEZ: 'Cause the
Ehrmantraut warrant just came in.
Oh, baby, now we're talking.
How quick can you
get your group together?
Two, three hours. Make it two.
We're gonna nail
that son of a bi...
[WATER SPLASHES]
[WATER SPLASHING]
[WHISTLES]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
MAN: Police! Search warrant!
[SIGHS]
[KNOCKING]
Police! Search warrant!
MIKE: Coming. Hold your horses.
[LOCK CLICKS]
Search warrant.
Police! Search warrant!
How's that restraining
order working out for you?
Uh, if you want me to read that,
I'm gonna need my glasses.
MAN: Too bad you had to make the
trip out from headquarters, Sergeant.
MAN 2: From out
of bed, you mean.
When a cop kills himself,
they want a full report.
[MAN CONTINUES FAINTLY]
MAN 3: A single contact wound.
Powder burn on his
temple and right hand.
Suicide, I think.
Tell the wagon boys
they can have him. Yes.
WOMAN: [CRYING]
When I found him,
he... he was dead.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey! Perfect timing.
Just about to get started.
Uh, you know,
if you can get going
on that settling tank,
that would be a huge help.
We left that stuff in there
too long after the last cook.
Mr. White... I
mean way too long.
Now we have a tremendous
amount of residue.
You know what we need to
invest in is a power washer.
Mr. White, can we
just take a second
and talk about all this?
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Yeah.
Um... Uh, look, you know what
I think we need to talk about?
Is doubling down.
Doubling down? Mm-hmm.
Cooking 100 pounds
a week, not 50.
As in starting a new lab,
a lab that you'll run.
A cook all of your own.
Why not? You deserve it.
You're every bit as good as me.
Well, what do you think?
Mr. White, uh,
I think that nothing
has changed for me.
I just wanna get my
money and, and get out.
Jesse, this...
What we do...
Being the best at something
is a very rare thing.
You don't just toss
something like that away.
And what, you wanna
squander that potential?
Your potential? Why?
To do what?
I don't know.
Well, think.
To do what, Jesse?
Well, I'll figure
it out, all right?
Look at you.
What have you
got in your life, huh?
Nothing. Nobody.
Oh, wait. Yes.
Video games and
go-carts. Mr. White...
And when you get tired
of that, what then? Huh?
And how soon will
you start using again?
Look...
Look, I know how upset you are
about what happened to this boy.
I am just as upset as you are.
Are you? Really?
How can you say
that to me? Jesus!
I mean, I'm the one
who's the father here.
What, do I have to curl up in
a ball in tears in front of you?
Do I have to lock
myself away in a room
and get high to prove it to you?
What happened to
that boy is a tragedy,
and it tears me up inside!
But because it happened, what,
am I supposed to just
lie down and die with him?
It's done!
It makes me sick
that it happened,
just like everyone else
who has died in our wake.
What Todd did...
You and I have done
things that are just as bad.
Yeah.
All the people
that we've killed...
Gale and the rest...
If you believe
that there's a hell...
I don't know if you're
into that. But we're...
We're already pretty
much going there, right?
But I'm not gonna lie
down until I get there.
What, just because I don't
wanna cook meth anymore,
I'm lying down?
How many more people
are gonna die 'cause of us?
No one. None.
Now that we're in control,
no one else gets hurt.
You keep saying that,
and it's bullshit every time!
No. Always! You know what?
I'm done, okay?
You just give me my
money, and you and I,
we're done.
Hmm. Okay.
Why?
Why do you want this money?
Because it's mine. It's my cut.
But isn't it filthy blood money?
I mean, you're so pure. You
have such emotional depth.
No, no, no, no. You shouldn't
touch that dirty money.
I'll save you from that, Jesse.
Come on.
You want it.
You want it just as
much as I want it.
And it's not wrong
to want it. Okay?
So stay and work with me,
and you can make
ten, 20 times as much.
Whatever, man.
You don't wanna
pay me, I don't care.
Yes, you do.
It's on you, all right?
I'm done. No, you're not.
You're not done.
You're not leaving,
because if you
leave, you get nothing!
Do you understand me? Nothing!
Jesse!
Budget for the current fiscal
year for electronic surveillance
is 1.5 million,
on par with ATF and
the Marshal Service,
but still just a
fraction of FBI totals.
We're lobbying congress
for an additional 1.41,
but we're waiting
on action reports
[FADING OUT] to demonstrate
we're actually getting worthwhile results.
Our undercover operations
reap the most successful
actionable intelligence,
if you refer to the
chart in appendix four.
If ASAC Schrader can tell us
about the surveillance man-hours...
Hank?
Hank!
I think we're going
to wrap this up.
If ASAC Schrader can stay behind
while everyone else clears out.
Thank you, everybody.
You know no one wants
to see you succeed at
this more than me, right?
Yes, sir. I know
how good you are.
I wouldn't have stuck my neck
out to get you here if I didn't.
But you're not knocking
down doors anymore, bubba.
You're in charge of
an entire district office,
and that comes
with responsibilities.
I mean, Hank, basic reports
aren't being filed
in a timely manner.
I'll work on it.
It'll get better.
Yeah, it will, because way
too much time and money
is being spent
on the Fring case,
a case which is
essentially over.
All this overtime to surveil
Michael Ehrmantraut?
That's just money that could
be better spent elsewhere.
I understand,
but I'm not making
these choices lightly.
We've got increased reports
of blue meth on the street,
Fring's gang is still operational,
and Ehrmantraut is involved.
It's that simple.
I believe you. But so what?
It's one case out of dozens,
and you don't play favorites with
it just because it used to be yours.
I really think that... Don't
play favorites with it, Hank.
You got a bigger job than that.
I mean, forget
the financial cost.
I hear you're personally serving
search warrants out in the field?
That was an error in judgment.
Won't happen again.
You're damn right it won't.
I'm just gonna
bottom line this for you.
The surveillance budget
for Ehrmantraut is now zero.
We clear?
Sure. Thank you.
Clear. Good.
We'll be in touch.
[KNOCKING] Yeah?
Hey.
So, Ramey wanted
to catch up with you?
Talk sports and stuff, I guess?
Yeah. Something like that.
No more following Ehrmantraut.
Not worth the
financial investment.
Well, it's not like the
guy's going anywhere.
He's not even bothering
to throw our tails anymore.
He's just living a
boring old-man life
like he has
nothing left to hide.
And none of Fring's
crew is talking?
Not giving an inch.
You sweeten the pot enough?
Zero jail time and an
all-expense-paid trip to Maui?
[CHUCKLES] Not that, but
close. Nobody wants to bite.
Christ!
They're either the most
loyal crew in history,
or someone's still
paying them off.
You still checking bank records?
No one living
beyond their means.
Nine perps...
All being represented
by one lawyer.
Not unusual in a case like this.
Yeah, this guy, what's his name?
Daniel Wachsberger?
He represents every one of these
douche-bags except for Ehrmantraut.
Can we find out more
about the lawyer?
You want me to
start tailing a lawyer?
Like the shit ain't deep
enough for you already?
Hey, Ramey said we
couldn't follow Ehrmantraut.
He didn't say anything
about anybody else.
Do it.
You're the boss.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SIGHS]
All right. Shall we get started?
Now, I know that most of this,
or all of this, is
gonna be new to you.
But, uh, did you take
chemistry in high school?
Just basic?
No.
Okay. That's all right.
As we go, I'll be as
detailed as possible
without being overwhelming.
Yes, sir.
Look, Todd, I don't need
you to be Antoine Lavoisier.
Uh, what I do need
is your full effort
and attention.
Listen and apply yourself.
If you do that, then
we just might have
a fighting chance here, okay?
Okay. Okay.
Well, here we go.
[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHATTERING]
Slowly. Steady.
[MUFFLED CHATTERING]
[MUFFLED CHATTERING CONTINUES]
The aluminum helps speed up
the delivery of hydrogen chloride.
Gently pour it in. No spilling.
[MUFFLED CHATTERING]
You're gonna like
the little Schticky,
but you're gonna
love the big Schticky.
For bigger messes like
dust bunnies under the bed
or picking up after...
Now...
The CO2 freezes the liquid,
crystallizing it,
which gives us our
finished methamphetamine.
[SIGHS]
Now all that's left
is to break it up, weigh
it, and we're done.
Wow. This is, um...
This is complicated. It's
gonna take me a few more times
to get a grasp on it.
Oh, yeah.
It'll take a few more times.
I do all right?
You did fine, Todd.
You applied yourself.
That's as much as I can ask.
Now all that's left, I
guess, is to talk money.
We can talk money
once I get this right.
[ZIPPER UNZIPPING] Hmm.
Morning. Guess what I have.
Cake pops. They're
balls of cake on a stick.
Very nice. Thank you, Dan.
See? I put little faces on them.
Hey.
[MICROWAVE OVEN WHIRRING]
[MICROWAVE BEEPS]
All right.
[SIGHING]
[HUMS]
Mm.
I'm, uh... I'm working
with a new guy now.
And I think that it...
I think it could
possibly work out,
because...
I'm trying, Hank. I
really am. I'm trying,
but there's this... [SNIFFLING]
I mean, it's like I
don't even exist to her.
Well, yeah... [STAMMERING]
I mean, I know she's struggling.
I know, but I... I...
I just don't know what to do.
I mean, what can I do?
Such a mess. [STAMMERS]
[SIGHS]
I mean, we...
Both of us... We...
We just have screwed up so much.
I'm just... [SNIFFLES]
I'm sorry. I don't...
Um, do you, do you have
any coffee? Maybe I could...
Coffee? You bet. Yeah. You bet.
What, you take,
uh, cream, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
[SIGHS]
[IMITATES GUNSHOT]
[DOOR OPENS]
All right. Here you go, buddy.
Oh, thank you, Hank. Yeah.
Look, I'm sorry to waste
your time with all this.
Ah, no. [STAMMERING]
It's really...
It's... you know.
You know. Yeah.
Yeah.
Hey. Oh, hey.
Hey, could you excuse me?
Oh, yeah, yeah. Sure, sure.
Tell me something
good. You tell me.
I sweated the guy for 14 hours.
That should be
some kind of record.
Quit your bragging.
What'd you get?
He's gonna do
it. He's gonna flip.
He's willing to give
us Ehrmantraut?
[CHUCKLING]
What are you
wasting your time for?
Go throw a net around
that son of a bitch.
All right.
[SWING CREAKING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Yeah? DAN: Mike, hey, it's me.
Can you talk? I can.
Great. Look, there's a small
situation with the money.
I don't want to do
this on the phone.
Are you available?
I can come by in a few hours.
That's not good for
me. Where are you now?
I'm at the park with
my granddaughter.
Where exactly?
Palomita.
Oh, you know what? I'm not far.
I'll come to you.
You just hang tight.
[CLICK]
[RINGING]
[GROANS] Yeah?
WALTER: Mike, they're coming
for you. Right now. They're coming.
Slow down, Walter. Who? The DEA.
The DE... Somebody flipped.
They have, uh, some...
Some kind of bank surveillance.
And something about some lawyer.
Someone is talking, Mike, and
they're coming for you right now.
[CAR APPROACHING]
[SWING CONTINUES CREAKING]
[EXHALES]
SAUL: How could Mike
use that clown of a lawyer?
Dan Wachsberger. [CHUCKLES]
He would've had better luck with
the law firm of Moe, Larry and Shemp.
Always consult with me
before using outside counsel.
All right, Saul. Enough, please.
Instead of just sitting
around here, what can we do?
Besides pray that he gets
away? I'm open to ideas.
Because if the DEA
catches up with him,
and he flips, it's
good night, John-boy.
No. No way Mike
would ever flip, okay?
No way. [SIGHS] Yeah, yeah.
Never say never.
This is the second time the
DEA has confiscated his bankroll.
[CHUCKLES] You know?
Jesus, fool me once, right?
Look, he won't flip.
But his nine guys will.
[PHONE HUMMING]
[SIGHS]
[HUMMING CONTINUES]
[DRAWER CLOSES]
Hey. Whoa, whoa. It's him.
[SIGHS] Uh, Mike,
uh, I got you on speaker
phone with the brain trust.
The what? The, uh...
[SNAPS FINGERS]
Walt and Jesse are here.
I don't want Walt
and Jesse, Saul.
I want you. I need your
help. What do you need?
I got a go-bag at the airport...
Passports, money, but
there are eyes everywhere.
I can't get close.
I need you to pick up that bag
and get it to me as
soon as possible.
Do you know how thick the crap
storm is out there because of this?
I told you not to use
that lawyer. He's a hack!
Shut up, Saul, and get
the bag. JESSE: Hey, Mike,
I can get it to you, all
right? Just tell me what to do.
No, kid. Not you.
I'm paying Saul. He
can do the job just fine.
Yeah, you're paying me, and
the DEA knows I represent you,
so they're probably
sitting on my car right now,
hoping I do something stupid.
Mike, I can do it,
okay? It's not a problem.
No, Jesse.
Jesus, I'll do it. Besides,
you're out, remember?
Mike, tell me where
to get this bag.
[WATER SPLASHES]
[CAR APPROACHING]
Hello, Walter.
Before I hand this over,
I need something from you.
And what's that?
The names of your nine men.
[SCOFFS] Why?
You're never gonna pay
them off. What's the point?
The point is,
Mike, it affects me.
It affects Jesse, too,
and we deserve to know.
The only thing left to do now
is leave town. You understand?
"Leave town." Wow.
Yeah, I just can't up
and leave, like you, Mike.
I've got a family. I've got
people who depend on me.
Yeah.
Goodbye, Walter.
You're welcome!
[SCOFFS]
I'm sorry, what?
I want those names, Mike.
You owe me that much.
I don't owe you a damn thing.
All of this, falling apart
like this, is on you.
Wow.
[LAUGHS] Wow!
Oh, that's some kind
of logic right there, Mike.
You screw up, get yourself
followed by the DEA,
and now, suddenly,
this is all my fault?
Why don't you walk
me through this, Mike?
We had a good thing,
you stupid son of a bitch!
We had Fring. We had a lab.
We had everything we needed,
and it all ran like clockwork.
Oh, my God. You
could've shut your mouth,
cooked, and made as much
money as you ever needed.
It was perfect. But, no,
you just had to blow it up.
You and your pride and your ego!
You just had to be the man.
If you'd done your
job, known your place,
we'd all be fine right now!
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[QUIVERING BREATHS]
I just...
I just realized that
Lydia has the names.
I can get them from her.
I'm sorry, Mike.
This... This whole thing
could've been avoided.
Shut the [INAUDIBLE] up.
Let me die in peace.
[SOFT THUD]