MAN: Honey mustard.
[SPEAKING GERMAN]
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[SPEAKING GERMAN]
[PEOPLE TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
[BEEPING]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[MS. TROMEL SPEAKING]
[KNOCKING]
[KNOCKING LOUDLY]
[MAN SPEAKING GERMAN]
[DOOR THUDDING]
[BANGING ON DOOR]
[WHIRRING]
[ELECTRICAL ARC]
[FLUSHING] [BANGING
ON DOOR CONTINUES]
JESSE: [ON PHONE] Honest to
God, it's starting to drive me crazy.
WALTER: Well, don't. It
keeps me awake at night.
I lay there thinking, "Where
is it? Where did it go?"
And I just... You
know, I can't even...
I have no idea.
Jesse... Jesse, look.
Doesn't it make sense
that it wound up in the lab?
I thought about that a lot.
But I just don't see how.
Well, look. You had the pack
in your pocket of
your jacket, right?
Yeah. Your jacket
was in your locker.
So maybe the cigarette
just fell out of the pocket
and wound up in the locker,
and now it's all burned up.
It's gone. Yeah.
But I don't know that, you know?
I can't ever know for sure.
[SIGHS]
Well, look, did you
check your house?
Did you... Maybe it's
somewhere in your house.
No, man. I've looked
everywhere, okay?
Did you check
your car? No, no...
Thoroughly? Yes, of course.
Look, it's not in my house.
It's not in my car. And
the more I think about it,
there's no way it
fell out in my locker.
And I keep thinking
somebody's gonna find this thing
on the street or something.
You don't know that.
Somewhere where
I dropped it. No.
Some innocent person,
some kid maybe, even.
No. No. come on.
And they're gonna pick
it up, and it's gonna...
You're working yourself
all up. Oh, my God!
Jesse, listen.
You've gotta get
ahold of yourself here.
All right? I'll tell you
what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna come over there.
And together, we're
gonna look for this thing.
All right?
Yeah.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
Ohh.
[WHIRRING]
What the hell is that?
My Roomba.
I already checked it.
When?
Like, a week ago.
Oh, God.
Oh, Jesus.
Okay. Easy, easy. Take it...
Careful. Let me see.
Is it still intact?
Yeah. Good.
Good. No worries.
Let me get rid of this.
What luck.
Whoo.
[TOILET FLUSHES]
Well, I don't know about you,
but I, for one,
could use a beer.
You have any?
Jesse?
[SOBBING]
I almost shot you.
Hey, hey, now...
I almost killed
you all because...
Listen.
It was just a... A
misunderstanding, that's all.
No. No, no, no, no.
I don't know what's
wrong with me, Mr. White.
I... Hey.
[CRYING]
I don't know how I
could be so stupid.
Stop that now. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
I'm so sorry.
Shh. Shh.
It's okay.
[CONTINUES CRYING]
Listen to me.
What happened,
happened for the best,
you hear me?
And I wouldn't change a thing.
You and I working together,
having each other's back.
It's what saved our lives.
I...
I want you to think about
that as we go forward.
Go forward where?
[CHATTER ON TV]
MAN: [ON TV] Stillwell,
steady as she goes.
Ohh.
Willie, note the time.
Whoo.
Ohh. Captain, I'm sorry,
but you're a sick man. Mmm.
I'm relieving you as
captain of the ship
under article 184.
Oh, God. CAPTAIN: I don't
know what you're talking about.
Helmsman, left 180. Ohh.
Mr. Keith, what do I do?
You're the officer on the
deck. [KNOCKING ON DOOR]
I told you to come left.
Now come left, and fast.
MAN 1: I'm sorry, sir,
but you're not issuing
orders on this bridge anymore.
[KNOCKING CONTINUES]
I've relieved you.
I take full responsibil...
[TURNS OFF TV]
WALTER: Thanks for seeing us.
WALTER: We're here
to talk partnership.
Partnership.
Yes. Equal. Three ways.
You, Jesse and me.
Partnership in what?
Well, we figure we're
gonna start cooking again.
You know, we figure, why not?
There's no denying the
popularity of our product.
There's a market to be filled,
and currently no one to fill it.
JESSE: A lot of
money to be made.
And obviously, Jesse and I
have manufacture covered.
But there's still distribution,
support, logistics,
that sort of thing.
For instance, we'll need a
steady supply of precursor.
With your experience
and connections,
you would be a great help.
Mmm.
Granted, there's a
lot of work ahead.
There's a lot of rebuilding.
And, no doubt, our
profits will be smaller.
At least at first.
But each of us will
receive a larger cut.
Owners, not employees.
Thanks, but no, thanks.
Mike,
I know you don't care for me.
We've had our issues, you and I.
But I would suggest
that you leave emotion
out of this decision.
I am.
You
are trouble.
I'm sorry the kid
here doesn't see it,
but I sure as hell do.
You are a time bomb
tick, tick, ticking,
and I have no intention of
being around for the boom.
Well, sleep on it.
Maybe you'll reconsider.
In the meantime,
we're pressing on.
Morning.
Hey, why aren't you upstairs?
I came to see if you
needed any help.
Yeah, well, I don't.
Well, I can see that,
man. It's outstanding.
Yeah. I'm working on it here.
Not exactly running
marathons here, you know.
Yeah, well, when did
your couch-shaped ass
ever run any marathons?
I'm proud of you,
brother. Yeah, yeah.
So how many Krauts we got?
Enough to invade Poland.
Came in their own
G5, just like Oprah has.
G5, yeah? Mmm-hmm.
Is that one where the...
Where the wings go up like that?
I think they all do that.
They all have that?
Anyway, we got two U.S.
Attorneys in the house.
Big doings. Your
name keeps coming up.
Yeah? Hey, give me a
hand here, would you?
Just... Just a little
bit there. Thanks.
HERZOG: I hired
Peter Schuler in 1992.
Almost single-handedly,
he grew our little
restaurant division
into an industry leader
and a source of
great personal pride.
I am shocked and
saddened by his death
and outraged by the damage
his actions have wrought
upon my grandfather's company.
[SPEAKS GERMAN]
Alleged actions.
An innocent man
does not kill himself.
My people and I
are here to help.
To your investigation,
I pledge Madrigal's
full cooperation
and transparency.
I confess I have
my selfish reasons.
I believe Peter Schuler
was a lone anomaly.
But if that is not the case,
I want to know it,
just as you do.
So when you gonna announce it?
I don't know.
As I'm walking out the door
with my big cardboard box.
Can't do that.
You know damn well we're
gonna throw you a big party.
Damn straight. We're
talking a blowout.
Outstanding police work, Hank.
If only I'd listened.
But I guess the damage was done.
It's not right, them
putting this on you.
Somebody's gotta
go under the bus.
Ramey's a good man.
He'll do right by you.
Besides, this office
practically runs itself.
Bullshit it does.
Sir.
What's with that APD
thing? The electromagnets?
They're thinking it's
about Fring's laptop.
Turns out a couple of
days before it happened,
desk sergeant gets this phone
call from a "postal inspector,"
quote, unquote,
wanting to know where
they keep the thing.
And he told them? Jesus.
Anything left of the laptop?
[SCOFFS] Do we look that lucky?
You know, I sneaked a peek
before APD took it out of Fring's office.
The whole thing was encrypted.
They wouldn't have got
anything anyway, but...
So Hector
Salamanca killed Fring.
But who gave Salamanca the bomb?
[SIGHS] Whole lot of questions
and not much in
the way of answers.
Yet.
The APD did find some
of Fring's financials.
That just might
lead to something.
I had him out to my house.
4th of July.
We cooked out in the backyard.
My son shucked the corn.
My daughter cut up potatoes.
Fring brought sea bass.
Every time I grill it now,
I make a little foil pouch,
just like he showed me.
That whole night,
we were laughing,
telling stories, drinking wine.
And he's somebody
else completely.
Right in front of me.
Right under my nose.
Hi. What can I get you?
Just tea, please. Chamomile.
Oh, sorry. We don't
have chamomile tea.
Then some sort of bergamot,
provided it's not Earl Grey.
I like soy milk
instead of dairy.
We don't have soy milk
or any sort of bergamot.
Wow. You're really running
me through my paces here.
Uh-huh.
Well, English
Breakfast, I guess.
We have Lipton's.
That's pretty much all we have.
I would like a cup
of hot water, filtered,
if possible, and a
single slice of lemon.
And I'm assuming
you don't have Stevia?
Never mind. I brought my own.
You coming to me,
or am I coming to you?
Face forward.
We'll talk like this.
I guess I'm coming to you.
Ohh.
Mmm.
Take a breath, will you?
This place is safe. No
one's gonna see you here.
My God!
Duane, this is so... Thank you.
How did I not see
you sitting back there?
So weird. [CHUCKLES]
You want anything else, Mike?
No.
I'm good, Fran. Thanks.
Now,
how about we lose
the sunglasses?
I feel like I'm talking
to Jackie Onassis here.
There you go.
Breathe in, breathe out.
Drink your whatever.
Who killed Gus?
Haven't I told you not
to worry about that?
Now, what do you want from
me, and why is it so important?
What's this?
A list of 11 names.
Okay.
You know them all.
I do.
Those 11 men... And I
think you know this, Mike.
Those 11 could sink
us, you and me both.
Where are we going
with this, Lydia?
No specific. I'm just
pointing out facts.
These men... Your
men... Yours and Gus's...
These men were on
the payroll, very publicly.
They trace back to
Pollos and the laundry.
They trace back to Madrigal, and
they're gonna get picked up by the police.
And when they do,
when they get picked up
and threatened with prosecution,
and there's only one way
out for them, they're gonna...
And I'm not saying
all of them, okay?
All it's gonna take is
two or three, or even one.
But there's always a
weak link somewhere.
But they're gonna talk. At least
one of them's gonna talk about you,
about me, and that's
all it's gonna take.
These are the 11 I know
of, but I'd love your input.
I never met your
chemist, for instance.
I'd love your input.
You want me to kill
every man on that list?
Wow. That's a leap,
what you just, uh...
No, I didn't say that.
But if you think
that'd be wise...
[SIGHS]
You're scared, aren't you?
Yeah.
You're very upset,
which I'm gonna factor
into my response here.
These are my guys,
and they are solid.
Understand? What about
Chow at the warehouse?
Didn't one time you have to
shoot him through the hand?
You think that didn't
stick in his memory?
What about Dennis
at the laundry?
They're sure to pick him up.
They already have. They
picked him up last night.
My guys are solid.
I vetted them with great care,
and Fring made sure they
were well compensated
in the event of a
situation such as this.
They're paid to
stand up to the heat,
keep their mouths
shut, no matter what.
And they will.
Now, I don't know what kind of
movies you've been watching,
but here in the real world,
we don't kill 11 people
as some kind of
prophylactic measure.
Look at me
and say you understand.
I understand.
I get it.
So we're off that
very silly idea?
Good.
Drink your hot water.
I gotta go.
Did you have enough?
Yeah. I'm good.
Okay.
[QUIETLY] Bye-bye.
Bye. Bye.
Bye, big brother. [CHUCKLES]
Say bye to Mom for me.
I will. Have a good day.
You, too.
[DOOR OPENS]
[SIGHS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[QUIETLY] Skyler. Mmm...
Hey.
The car wash
opens in 15 minutes.
Mariano can open for me today.
Hey, how about you get up, huh?
Come on.
A shower will feel good.
Hey, Chow.
How you holding up?
Okay.
You know, they... They...
They talked to me.
You can't smoke in here, Chow.
HANK: Thanks for coming down.
Have a seat, Mr.,
uh, Ehrmantraut.
Am I, uh, saying that right?
Close enough.
So, once more, you're waiving your
right to have an attorney present?
Correct.
Could you state that
to the camera, please?
I'm waiving my right to
have an attorney present.
Uh, okay, then. We just
have a few questions.
You're currently employed
by the Pollos Hermanos chain.
Is that correct? Yes, I am.
And what do you do there?
Corporate security.
Corporate security. Yeah.
What's that? Like, uh,
guarding the special sauce?
I conduct employee
background checks.
I oversee loss prevention.
At a fast-food restaurant,
that's a full-time job?
We have 14 locations.
So, yes, it's a full-time job.
Yeah, well, [CHUCKLES]
If I were you, I'd start
sending out those resumes.
It says here you're a
private investigator?
Where you licensed?
New Mexico, Arizona, Utah.
Every state where we operate.
Colorado? You have some
restaurants there, right?
Colorado doesn't
require licensure.
You licensed to carry a firearm?
Concealed carry? Yes, I am.
Which states?
It'd be quicker to mention
the states in which I'm not.
And if we pulled your C.C.P.'s,
everything would be in order?
I'm guessing you've already
done that, so you tell me.
You strike me as a former cop.
Am I right?
Where at?
Philadelphia.
Philly. [CHUCKLES]
The city of brotherly love.
Turns out we, uh, we
know some folks there,
and they told us that your
tenure as a police officer
ended somewhat,
uh, dramatically?
You wanna talk about that?
Not particularly.
Yeah, me neither.
See, I'm more interested
in why Gus Fring
decided to put a guy like you
in charge of his
corporate security.
I mean, given your history
doing background checks
on pimple-faced fry cooks.
Seems like overkill.
What else you do for Fring?
He must've needed help running
that drug empire of his, no?
Drug empire?
First I'm hearing about that.
I don't know
anything about that.
Hey, man, we have a guy that
could put you in that underground lab,
and he'll testify to it.
So from here on out,
this can go hard or easy.
So what's it gonna be?
Forget your handcuffs?
I'm confused.
Am I under arrest
here, or am I not?
You wanna state
that for the camera?
You are not under
arrest, currently.
Agents, do you have any
more questions for me?
Because you've got
me very stirred up
with all these
false accusations.
If I'm not under arrest,
I'd prefer to leave.
Oh, well...
Uh-huh.
And I suppose we could talk
about the two million dollars
in your granddaughter's name.
Yeah. It seems, uh,
Fring had all these
secret offshore accounts
that he would
deposit money into.
Like, uh, well, an
even dozen of them.
And they're all in the names
of certain people
on his payroll.
There was the, uh, the
manager of the laundry,
um, a couple guys from
the Pollos distribution center.
There was the owner of a chemical
warehouse, a bunch of others.
You know, guys that must've
been getting paid off the books.
Anyway, one of the names
was Kaylee Ehrmantraut.
Ten years old and
just cute as a button.
Yeah. Two million and change
we found on deposit for her.
Way more than anybody else.
Now, my partner here,
he took one look at
that and said, "Shit, man.
"This fifth-grade girl is the muscle
behind Fring's entire operation."
I said, "Whoa, whoa. Hey,
partner, slow down there.
"Maybe it was actually
"her dear old granddaddy."
Impressive, no? That...
[CLICKS TONGUE]
level of insight?
He's not impressed, Gomie.
Perhaps he's picturing all
that money going bye-bye.
Yeah, well, I mean,
the government's gonna
take every last dollar, unless...
Well, here's the thing,
Mike... Or Michael?
Mr. Ehrmantraut.
Here's the thing, Mike.
Lucky for you, you
didn't touch that money.
I cannot say the same
for the other 11 on the list.
One of your guys
is gonna roll on you,
and then we'll definitely
remember the handcuffs.
Now, before that day comes,
you can do yourself a solid.
You can tell us what you know,
you can tell us
who's still out there,
and if we like your story,
good things can happen.
Kaylee might be able to
keep some of that money.
Maybe.
HANK: So what do you say?
I don't know anything
about any money.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
WALTER: First order of business
is to find a new place to cook.
Before anyone says
it, no more RV's.
I don't know. The crystal
ship did pretty good for us.
The "crystal ship"?
Yeah. That's what I called it.
Well, I'll admit, it held
its own as a starter lab,
but it was too dark, too small,
not to mention it could've
broken down at any moment.
Saul, find us someplace
safe from prying eyes.
Security against
detection is paramount.
But I don't wanna drive too far.
No more 50-mile treks to
some Indian reservation.
In town is trickier.
I mean, you got a lot
more of your prying eyes.
If Gus can manage
it, then so can we.
Precursor. Where
are we with that?
Uh, we're good on everything
except, uh, methylamine.
No surprise.
It's dry as hell out there.
What if we switched
back to a pseudo cook?
Absolutely out of the question.
Jesse, there is methylamine
out there. I know it.
Yeah, but what if there's not?
Because there isn't.
I mean, really.
There is.
Have faith.
Can I... Can I offer a thought?
Uh...
Say a guy wins the lottery.
Ten million bucks.
The very next day, what's
the one thing he does not do?
He does not go buy
another lottery ticket, right?
He counts his lucky stars,
and he sails off into the sunset,
which, seems to me,
and all due respect,
some advice you two might take.
What lottery did I win exactly?
Hey, you're alive.
I mean, as far as I'm concerned,
that's the Irish sweepstakes.
I'm alive, and I'm broke.
Counting the money
that I owe Jesse,
I'm about 40 grand in the hole.
Does that seem
like an acceptable
stopping point to you? [SIGHS]
There is gold in the streets,
just waiting for someone
to come and scoop it up.
But me, I should quit now.
Jesse, too, I suppose, huh?
Wow.
I got you this time, kid.
And how come you get
two, and I only get one?
Hmm?
Oh, no, you don't.
That one's mine!
[MUTTERS]
No. [GROANS]
[PHONE BUZZING]
Oh!
[BUZZING CONTINUES]
I give up, baby.
You're too good.
Yeah?
CHOW: It's me. You got a minute?
Yeah. A minute. What's up, Chow?
The DEA, they call
me to come back.
Say they want to talk more.
I'm sure they do.
Did you call your lawyer?
Yeah, but, Mike, the
DEA take all my money.
I need it.
I need my money.
You understand.
What do you want
me to do about it?
I don't know.
I don't know. We gotta talk.
Not on the phone.
Can you come to my house?
All right.
Give me two hours.
[BEEPS]
[WHIRRING]
[SOFT THUDDING]
[THUDDING CONTINUES]
MIKE: Chris.
I'd like you to drop your
gun where you stand,
and then turn
around very slowly.
[GUN CLATTERS]
[SIGHS]
Come on over and
sit next to Chow.
[GRUNTS]
[EXHALES FORCEFULLY]
How much was she gonna pay you?
Ten thousand a name.
How far did you
get down the list?
Just Chow.
I figured I'd start with you.
For you, she was
gonna pay 30,000.
I'm really sorry
about this, Mike,
but I needed the money.
Those feds, they
took it all, man.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
I know.
Are you ready?
Listen, Mike... [GUN FIRING]
[SHELLS CLATTER]
[EXHALES]
DELORES: Kiira, come
and have some cookies.
KIIRA: It's a cookie!
It's a cookie, yes!
Let's go. Uh-huh.
[SPEAKS SPANISH] Let's count.
BOTH: Uno. Dos. Tres.
Cuatro. Mmm-hmm.
Cinco.
Seis. Seis. Muy bien.
Siete. Siete.
BOTH: Ocho.
Nueve. Diez.
[NANNY SPEAKING SPANISH]
Amarillo. Amarillo.
Rosado. Rosado.
Azul. Azul.
Verde. Verde.
[CONTINUES SPEAKING
SPANISH] [DOOR OPENS]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Well, look at this.
What are you doing?
Hey, Mommy! What
are you doing still up?
Hey, yourself. Give me a kiss.
She said she
wanted to wait for you.
She does, huh?
Well, who's the
adult here, Delores?
Tell me she ate
her dinner, at least.
DELORES: Oh, yes,
she ate everything.
She ate her peas,
she ate her carrots.
[WHISPERING]
Do whatever it takes
to keep them out
of here, or they die.
She ate a whole lot
of carrots. Understand?
KIIRA: Yep. DELORES:
That's right, my girl.
Delores, I'm gonna take a bath.
Put Kiira to bed and then go
on home. I'll see you tomorrow.
Really? You don't
want me to wait for you?
No, you go home. Thank you.
Si, Miss Lydia. Buenas noches.
Mommy, you gonna
come say good night to me?
Yeah, honey. After
Mommy takes a bath.
Okay.
Love you.
DELORES: Mommy's
very tired, so let's go to bed.
[GASPS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Don't hurt my daughter.
I won't have to
unless you scream.
You know why I'm here?
What are you waiting for?
The nanny to leave.
If you have anything
to say to me,
now's the time.
[SCOFFS]
Two good men
died because of you.
Don't shoot me in the face.
Please.
I don't want my daughter
seeing me like that.
Your daughter won't see you.
Yes, she will. She'll find me.
She never once
sleeps through the night.
Nobody's gonna find you, Lydia.
Wait. What?
No.
No. No.
No! She has to find me.
Lower your voice.
[WHISPERING] She has to find me.
She has to find me. I... I...
You want your
five-year-old daughter
stumbling across your dead body?
I can't just disappear. She
has to know I didn't leave her.
She has to know that!
Keep your voice down.
I don't care what you do.
I'll scream, and
I'll keep screaming.
My daughter's not
thinking I abandoned her!
Shut up and calm down.
I don't care. You
have to promise.
You have to promise
me... [BEEPS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Promise I don't disappear.
[SIGHS]
Can you still get your
hands on methylamine?
Methylamine, Lydia.
Can you still get it?
Maybe.
Why?
[DOOR CLOSES]
[BEEPS]
[PHONE BUZZING]
[BUZZING CONTINUES]
Yes?
MIKE: You still plan
to move forward?
Yes, we do.
I've reconsidered. I'm in.
Good.
[GRUNTING]
Well, you missed a good meal.
The lasagna came out very well,
if I do say so myself.
I wrapped some up for
you if you'd like some later.
[GRUNTS]
[EXHALES FORCEFULLY]
You know, it gets easier.
I promise you that it does.
What you're feeling right now,
about, uh, Ted...
Everything.
It'll pass.
[SIGHS]
When we do
what we do for good reasons,
then we've got
nothing to worry about.
And there's no better reason
than family.