Gotta say, when you
first brought her in,
I had my doubts.
But your little
darling's got nine lives.
Rear-wheel assembly
took the brunt of the impact.
So, uh...
Yeah.
C.V. shaft, boots,
joints, axle...
Replaced all of it.
No way around it.
I went after-market on
most of the parts here.
You want me to swap in
factory parts, that's fine.
But using after-market's the only
way we'll keep it under blue book
and on the insurance
company's dime, okay?
Nothing beats free.
Uh, swapped out your air filter,
topped off your fluids.
Didn't have to replace
the windshield this time.
I know, right?
Oh, and I noticed you had
some sort of gunky buildup
in the front end here.
First, I had no idea
what I was looking at.
Then I remembered
that you had me replace
that front fender
a few months back
when you ran over that deer.
We went at it with
the steam hose,
cleaned it up for you.
Hardest part was the paint.
Fern green. Interesting tint.
Anything else?
That's it. Zero
balance, like I said.
Sign here, you're good to go.
People like to joke,
but I really,
really like this car.
She's sturdy as all hell.
I'm betting you get another
200,000 miles out of her.
Hey, Benny.
What would you give me for it?
What's the blue book, you mean?
No. I mean, what will
you pay me for this car?
Well, I'm not
really looking for...
$100?
Fifty?
Insurance company just shelled
out 1,900 for the parts alone.
Then it's a bargain.
You give me 50 bucks,
and she's all yours.
You sure about this?
Sure as shooting.
I'll check the register.
Dad?
Fifty bucks? Are you crazy?
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINE REVS]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[REVVING INTENSIFIES]
[REVVING CONTINUES]
[WOMAN SPEAKING
GERMAN ON SPEAKERPHONE]
[MAN SPEAKING GERMAN
ON SPEAKERPHONE]
Gotta be kidding me.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[SPEAKING GERMAN]
[MAN CONTINUES IN GERMAN]
[SIGHS]
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
Oh, Christ.
I'm at work right now.
MIKE: Yeah, I know.
This is a heads-up.
You got visitors.
Visitors? What...
You mean today?
I mean 30 seconds.
[MAN CONTINUES IN GERMAN]
Come in.
Ms. Rodarte-Quayle?
Agent Hank Schrader,
agent Steve Gomez, D.E.A.
We met briefly in,
uh... in Albuquerque.
Uh, yes, we did.
What can I do for you?
There. The foreman.
Navy plants, powder-blue shirt.
Hey, buddy.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
[MAN CONTINUES IN GERMAN]
[MUFFLED SCREAM]
MIKE: Yeah? They got Ron.
Ron's done.
Okay.
No. No.
Not okay, Mike.
Not okay. The...
The look he just gave me
was the very antithesis
of "okay," okay?
Breathe, Lydia.
No one's talking to the police.
I just had, like,
14 D.E.A. agents
barge into my office,
screaming and yelling at me,
and they were swarming all
over the warehouse, okay?
The warehouse!
Besides, Ron was my guy.
Remember? I don't
have a guy anymore.
Ron fixed security and pulled
the barrels and drove the truck.
You can't expect
me to do that stuff.
I mean, let's be realistic.
Mike, this is crazy.
I'll send a new guy.
[CLICK]
WALTER, JR.: You're
crazy. [WALT LAUGHING]
My car almost has
500 horsepower.
It would totally smoke...
Horsepower isn't everything.
Don't you know that?
You have to factor in drag
and torque and suspension
and weight of the car.
And listen, one more factor
that you're not thinking about...
The experience of the driver.
And I totally got you
there. Please. Please.
I got you. You
drive like a geezer.
Really? I drive like a gee...
Tell me, can a geezer
do donuts? I don't think so.
Bullshit you ever did donuts.
Whoa. Watch your language.
And, yes, I did. Seriously?
Yes, seriously.
And if you show me
just a modicum of respect,
maybe I'll teach you.
Yeah? Yes? No.
No, I won't. I take that
back. Yes. Yes. No...
Just a joke. I'm just...
You're saying yes.
No! No, no. That was kidding.
We didn't shake
on it. No. Yes. Yes.
We are now. That doesn't count!
WALT: I know you don't approve.
But mine...
We'll call a birthday
present to myself.
And Junior's...
People will just chalk that up
as me being a softy.
And besides,
I didn't actually
buy either one.
They're both leases.
So it all fits our story.
Okay?
Oh.
We can afford it now. Hmm?
You're back at it?
Well, yeah.
We have to make up
that 600,000 we lost.
What do you think
about boarding school?
Boarding school?
For who... For Junior?
Yeah. There's this
place in Northern Arizona,
and it's supposed to be one
of the top ten in the country.
He's a year away from college.
Why on earth would we do that?
I... I don't know. I just...
Just thinking about the kids.
Mmm. Holly, too?
Where are we sending
our eight-month-old?
Peace corps?
[CHUCKLES]
No. I just...
A new environment
might be good for them.
What does that mean?
What's wrong with
their environment?
Skyler...
What's wrong with
their environment?
Nothing.
Hey.
Listen, I know these last
few weeks have been rough.
The threat to Hank
and this whole
thing with Beneke.
But there's absolutely nothing
for you to be afraid
of anymore, okay?
I mean, clear sailing
from here on out.
I promise.
You know, I want us to try
and start looking
forward to things again.
Speaking of which, my birthday.
Hmm?
I don't know...
I don't know what
you have planned,
and with everything
that's been going on lately,
I'd understand if you haven't
even given it a thought.
But I think...
A little celebration
might be good.
For all of us.
You know, a birthday party.
What do you think?
Hmm?
Yeah?
Okay.
And maybe, if I may be so bold,
chocolate cake
with chocolate icing?
Life is good, Skyler.
Oh...
WALT: Mmm. Thank you.
Hey, Mom, you forgot something.
Hmm? Dad's bacon.
That's okay. I can do it.
No. Mom has to.
Well, it is sort of a tradition.
Watch this, Holly. [CHUCKLING]
Watch what she does with bacon.
Watch it. Watch it.
What is she doing?
That's a pretty small "1."
Kind of is.
Just a little. [CHUCKLING]
Ah, now you're talking.
No. No. Good move.
No. No, no, no. It's good.
Very good. Family teamwork.
Making sacrifices.
Very important.
Happy birthday, Dad.
Thank you, buddy.
[HOLLY COOING] You want some?
HANK: Guy's some
piece of work, isn't he?
Six feet under
and half a face...
He's still screwing with us.
So, what's next?
Oh, I don't know.
This madrigal thing seems
hinky, though, you know?
We got Burgermeister
Meisterburger over here in Germany,
and 5,000 miles
away, you got this guy.
There's gotta be someone
in the middle, you know?
Someone we're missing.
What about that, uh,
Lydia what's-her-name?
You know, Lady Banjo
Eyes at the warehouse?
In this world? No way.
Too uptight. Too together.
Maybe.
She was wearing
mismatched shoes.
How together can she be?
[EXHALES FORCEFULLY]
Gentlemen, how
goes it with Fring?
You know, just, uh,
working through the grief.
How soon before
you submit a final?
Well, we've been kicking
around some ideas.
Had you asked me that
a couple of weeks ago,
I'd have said this was just
a mop-up job, but... But?
Well, no one on Fring's
crew is talking to us.
I mean, not a peep, no
matter how hard we squeeze.
Which makes it likely there's
somebody out there keeping them in line.
Our money is on this
guy, Michael Ehrmantraut.
He's Fring's head of
"corporate" security.
He's a definite hard case.
Now, we're gonna stay on him.
We're putting together a
surveillance team as we speak.
Okay? The other thing is...
This may be unrelated,
but the blue meth is
making a bit of a comeback.
Tell him, Gomie. Yeah. Some
small amounts on the street-side pulls.
Lab's telling us
it's the same stuff.
I mean, it could be old
inventory leaking out,
or it could be
somebody's rebooting,
using Fring's former cooks
to set up a new operation.
I thought we had
Fring's cooks...
The unsubs in the lab fire.
Thought maybe one of
them was your Heisenberg.
Yeah. Maybe. I don't know.
Like I said, there's
still a lot of questions.
Agent Gomez, could
you give us a moment?
Hank, I gotta say,
your work here has been stellar.
Really first rate.
Thank you, sir.
So much so that I'm wondering
if it's time you made a change.
You know, I have to
get back to El Paso.
This office needs an A.S.A.C.,
and I'm thinking we should
be promoting from within.
If you were to put
in an application,
and I recommend that
you do, you will get the job.
I have no doubt this D.O. would
be well served with you at the helm.
Wow. That's, uh...
I'm not sure what to say.
It's a big step up.
It's not without its headaches.
The politics may take
some getting used to.
Plus, you'd be overseeing
every case in the office,
so you'd need to reassign
all your day-to-days,
Fring included.
Much as I hate losing
a good field man,
that's the job, and you
need to be okay with it.
What do you say, Hank?
You want it?
Well, considering my wife
would murder me if I said "no"...
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah. I want it.
Congratulations. Thank you.
Can you, uh, finish up for me?
It's... It's my birthday.
Oh, yeah? Yeah.
I probably have a birthday party
waiting for me, you know, so...
Uh, yeah. Cool.
Yeah, no problem.
Hey, uh, happy birthday.
Thanks. Thanks.
[MEN CRYING OUT ON T.V.]
WALTER, JR.: Hey, Dad.
Hey.
[CHANGES CHANNEL]
Where's your mom?
Uh, kitchen.
[CHANGING CHANNELS]
Hey.
Oh, hey.
[MAN SPEAKING ON TV]
So, what's the plan?
Um, Hank and Marie
are on their way,
roast chicken and
potatoes for dinner,
rocky road for dessert,
and, uh, chocolate
cake, as requested.
What's up?
Me?
Nothing.
Thought you'd be more
jazzed about the new job.
No! What... No! I am!
Baby, I'm so proud of
you. Yeah, yeah. Okay.
Sorry, sorry. I believe
you. Just don't kill us here.
[SIGHS]
Look, Marie, you've been
moping around the last few days.
Marie?
What's up?
Marie, come on. I'm sorry. I...
I made a promise to someone.
To who?
Who? Your brother-in-law.
Are you gonna give
me a hint at least?
It involves infidelity.
That's all I'm gonna say.
Oh, shit. I knew it.
Knew what? What did
you... What did you know?
Well, I mean, I didn't know it,
but I've been, you
know, saying it forever.
Walt's second cell
phone, you know?
Sorry, babe, but I was way
ahead of you on this one.
Way ahead of me. Oh.
Well, it wasn't Walt.
Skyler?
No way.
[DOORBELL RINGS] Hey.
Hey! There she is! Hey! Hi!
Hey! Hey!
Hey, pal. Welcome. Welcome.
Come on in.
Happy birthday! Hi!
I'm in the center
lane going about 60.
I had no choice but to
just tear butt out of there.
Just bwaaa! So sweet.
Yeah, highway patrol's
gonna be sweet on it too.
Gonna get their
ticket quota in a month.
You'll help me out,
right, Uncle Hank,
now that you run the D.E.A.?
Oh, yeah. For my spoiled brat
car wash millionaire nephew?
Sure. I'll make sure
you get a cell with a view.
[LAUGHTER]
All right.
Well, I'm outta here.
Okay.
Happy birthday.
Thank you, buddy.
Congratulations
again, Uncle Hank.
Thanks.
I'll see y'all later.
WALT: All right.
All right. Have
fun. Bye. Be safe.
Drive safely, okay? I do.
HANK: Slow down. Never.
Hmm.
A hell of a couple
cars there, Walt.
Honey, for my next birthday,
I'm gonna take a
page here from Walt
and buy myself a jet plane.
WALT: Well, maybe
I overdid it a little.
But with these
new lease rates...
I mean, they're
mighty attractive.
Yeah.
Great dinner, Skyler.
Those were some bad-ass
whipped potatoes, I tell you.
You have to tell me how
you get all the lumps out.
How do you do that?
A potato ricer.
A ricer? You don't hand mash?
No.
Well, uh... Boy, it has...
It has been quite a
year, huh? [CHUCKLES]
Do you know that, uh,
it's almost exactly a year ago
that I got my diagnosis?
Jesus. Yeah, right? Yeah.
Seems like longer, doesn't
it? Yeah. No. it's, uh...
One year ago tomorrow.
The day after my 50th.
Honestly never thought
I'd make it this far.
The cancer and surgery
and Hank being shot...
It just...
So many dark days.
Well... [CHUCKLES]
There's Marie's talking pillow.
Remember that? [CHUCKLING]
It was... [MUTTERS]
Boy, I did not want
to get any treatment.
I think I was too scared
or too angry or...
I don't know. I
just wanted to quit.
But you guys... You got
me through it somehow.
Kept me going.
And that happened
again and again and again.
I mean, there were times
when I was sure I was done for.
But then someone or something
would come through for me.
God. And Skyler... I can't...
Honey, remember that
first week of chemotherapy?
That night on the
bathroom floor?
What you said to me?
I was so sick.
It was rough going at first.
But Skyler...
She was right there, of course,
putting wet washcloths
on my forehead.
And she's singing to me.
And this would go on and on,
day after day.
And I remember I was lying
on the floor of the bathroom,
because the tile felt
nice and cool, you know?
And my head was in Skyler's lap,
and I was just asking her
if this could all be over.
It was too hard. It was...
I just wanted it stopped...
Skyler, isn't that freezing?
HANK: Whoa. Hey-o. Pool party.
What are you doing,
Skyler? [CHUCKLES]
What is she doing? Walt?
Hey, uh, Sky, maybe
it's time to get out now.
What do you think?
Skyler, Hank asked
you a question.
You need to get out... Skyler!
She's gonna come up, right?
She has to.
[MUFFLED] Skyler,
you need to get out.
[WATER SPLASHES]
Oh, my God.
Wha... Okay.
Okay. It's gotta be...
Nope.
[BEEP]
[SWITCH CLICKS]
Come on! How am I supposed to...
Hey.
Wait.
Wait, wait. Who are you?
I'm the... I'm the
guy. So where's the...
Hold on. Hold on.
Who sent you?
Who sent me? Who do you think?
No. I'm asking you.
Mike.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
And this Mike person...
What's his last name?
Lady, I just got off a
plane from New Mexico,
and I got a 900-mile drive back.
That's 14 hours if I don't stop.
So the sooner we do
this, the sooner it's done.
Uh, Ehrmantraut.
Okay? Satisfied?
Sorry, but I'm not gonna
apologize for being careful.
With all that's been happening
around here, for all I knew,
you were one of those undercover
people they send into high schools.
So, yeah, I'll take
paranoid any day
over getting gang
raped by prison guards.
Oh, no doubt.
So, uh, where's the...
Up there. Number 22356.
That's the one I erased
from the inventory,
so it has to be that one.
Can you reach it?
Yeah, with, like, a forklift.
You got one?
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait! Stop!
[LIQUID SLOSHES]
Oh, my God. Oh,
my God. Oh, my God.
What?
Please tell me that's
not what I think it is.
Has anything like this
ever happened before?
No. No, of course not.
[SIGHS] No, no.
I just...
She and I have been
having some issues.
Yeah, yeah. I, uh... I might've
heard a little bit about that.
I mean, hey, look,
Marie didn't go into detail.
She just, you know, said that,
you know, you guys were...
having some issues.
So, uh, what's the next move?
Might be good to have
her talk to someone.
Oh, I agree. Yeah.
Well, I'm gonna
get on that first thing.
Yeah.
There's Marie's guy, Dave.
She seems really happy with him.
Not that Marie's
an advertisement
for advanced mental
health or anything.
You know...
I just had no idea she
was taking it this hard.
Some birthday, huh?
She's gonna try
and get some sleep.
Oh, okay.
What was that?
I don't know.
I mean, was she trying...
No, not in a swimming pool. No.
With all of us there?
No, I don't think so.
[SNIFFLING]
But, uh, we both, uh,
think that...
She should talk to someone.
I'm gonna get you Dave's number.
Okay.
Listen, Walt, I...
I can't help but sense
that there may be some issues
between you and Skyler.
None of our business, of course.
And, Hank, I don't know if you
picked up on any
of... He knows...
He knows I know.
These things
happen in a marriage,
but it isn't unfixable.
I think what
would be great is if
you two had some space
to work through this stuff.
So...
And keep an open mind here.
What if we took
the kids for a while?
Took the kids? Absolutely.
We'll look after them for a
day or two, or however long,
and leave you and Skyler
to look after each other.
Uh, that's very
generous of you, Marie,
but I... I just don't see
how that's a solution.
And... I mean...
Besides, Junior and
Holly... That's a lot of work.
No, it isn't.
Junior's independent,
and my niece is
only the easiest,
most delicious baby
that was ever born.
It'll be fun, right?
Yeah. Yeah. No, yeah.
Yeah.
Absolutely. Yeah.
It's a good idea.
I think it's a great idea.
Just the thing for both of you.
Marie, this idea...
Was it yours?
Actually, it was Skyler's.
Uh-huh.
She really needs this, Walt.
Yep.
I gave Marie bottles.
They'll stop and pick
up diapers along the way.
I spoke with Junior
on the phone,
and after much discussion,
he agreed to swing by
tomorrow, pick up some clothes.
And so, voila,
the kids are out of
this environment.
What a coincidence.
I know you're awake.
What was that about?
Can you explain it?
I don't want the
children here anymore.
It isn't safe.
Skyler, we have talked
about this repeatedly.
It has never been more safe.
"Never been"?
A couple weeks ago, a
man was coming to this house
to kill us, to murder
your entire family.
You were in the
crawlspace, screaming.
And I dealt with him. It's over.
It is not.
You're right back in
the meth business again.
This is different. Now
I'm running things.
So wait. Now that
you're in charge,
it's what... It's gonna be
smooth sailing from here on out?
I don't see why not.
I keep the work at work, Skyler,
and nothing will ever
impact you or the kids.
You don't know that. You
can't make that promise, Walt.
I can promise you
that Gus Fring is dead.
And he was the threat.
He was the danger.
I thought you were the danger.
Is that what your
pool stunt was about?
Trying to protect
my children from me?
Not just...
There's blood on my hands too.
What blood? Beneke?
He's in the hospital
because of me.
No. Because of what I did.
Skyler, you can't beat
yourself up over this thing.
Please. You didn't
set out to hurt anybody.
You made a mistake, and
things got out of control,
but you did what you had
to do to protect your family.
And I'm sorry. That doesn't
make you a bad person,
it makes you a human being.
Stop it, Walt. Just stop.
I don't need to hear any
of your bullshit rationales.
I'm in it now.
I'm compromised. But I won't...
I will not have my
children living in a house
where dealing drugs and
hurting people and killing people
is shrugged off
as "shit happens."
We're back at it? Fine.
But the kids stay
away, and that's that.
"That's that"? That's what?
I got them out of this house.
To a sleepover at
their aunt and uncle's?
They spend a day or two,
Junior stays up late watching
movies, and then what happens?
We'll see. No, I'll tell
you what happens.
They come home to this house,
to their parents who love them.
No. I will not let our
business endanger them.
How many times do I have
to say that they are not in...
I said no.
I swear to God, I won't
have them back here.
What are you
gonna do to stop it?
Whatever it takes.
Everything in my power.
Like what? I mean, specifically.
What is your next move?
My next move is
maybe I hurt myself.
Make it clear we need more time.
Let Hank and Marie
see we're still struggling.
No, more like
you're still struggling.
So maybe next time,
I have you committed.
Put you in some
inpatient facility
while I take care
of the kids myself.
Is that what you want?
So then maybe I show
up with bruises on my neck,
give myself a black eye,
say that you beat me
when you found
out about my lover.
I see.
So you want to involve Ted?
Oh, well, that'll be fun,
bringing the police up
to speed on all of that.
But not as much fun as
telling your 16-year-old son
that his father
is a wife-beater.
Also not a very good
plan. What else you got?
I could send Junior
away to school.
Oh. Now here's
the conversation...
"So, honey, I know you've only
got one year left in high school,
"but I would love it so much
if you would drop everything,
"leave all your friends behind,
"and go to boarding
school in Arizona."
You have any other ideas?
Because I'm not hearing
a solution to your problem.
How are you going
to save our kids
from this terrible environment?
I don't... What
are you gonna do?
Are you gonna run off to France?
Are you gonna close the
curtains, change the locks?
This is a joke. Come on, Skyler.
You wanna take me on? You
wanna take away my children?
What's the plan? I don't know!
This is the best I could
come up with, okay?
I... I will count every minute
that the kids are
away from here,
away from you, as a victory.
But you're right.
It's a bad plan.
I don't have any
of your magic, Walt.
I don't know what to do.
I'm a coward.
I... I can't go to the police.
I can't stop
laundering your money.
I can't keep you
out of this house.
I can't even keep
you out of my bed.
All I can do is wait.
That's it. That's the
only good option.
Hold on,
bide my time,
and wait.
Wait for what? What
are you waiting for?
For the cancer to come back.
[BUZZING]
Yeah?
Okay. Okay.
Just relax. I'm coming.
JESSE: You tell me
what that looks like.
If the D.E.A.'s
tracking her barrels,
there goes our
precursor connection.
That's done. And I'm
telling you, these days,
chances of getting a new
methylamine hook-up is rare, man.
It's like Bigfoot.
Like unicorn-rare.
Kid, it's just... You're
giving me heartburn here.
G.P.S. on the
bottom of the barrel.
Why didn't they put it inside
where nobody would see it?
Look, it's inside, it gets wet.
They made these
things to put under cars.
They can get wet.
Huh.
Even by cop
standards this is sloppy.
And the other barrels...
They have trackers
on the outside too?
I don't know. Probably.
You didn't check any
of the other barrels? No.
But that's the only one we
could've taken, according to her.
Once we spotted
it, she freaked out,
I put the barrel
back, and we F.O.'d.
Let me ask you something.
The person who spotted this...
Was it you or was it her?
Lydia. She saw it first.
Okay.
She's dead.
Wait, wait, wait. What?
Lydia planted this
thing, not the cops.
She's thinking if
she makes it look
like her inventory's
being watched
that we'll leave her alone and
take our business elsewhere.
And she's right.
We will be taking our
business elsewhere,
right after I leave
her alone in a ditch.
But wait, hey, if the
D.E.A.'s not tracking her stuff,
that's a good thing, right?
I mean, all we
gotta do is tell her to,
you know, cut the crap and
keep the methylamine coming.
You don't know
this woman like I do.
I had a chance to deal with this
before, and I gave her a pass.
That's what I get
for being sexist.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
Mike, you can't just...
Look, that's our
precursor. We need her.
Kid, if we have to ramp
down for a while, so be it.
It beats working with a lunatic
who's gonna get
us arrested or killed.
Look, she didn't seem
crazy to me, you know?
She just seemed, like, uptight.
And now you're being sexist.
Trust me, this
woman deserves to die
as much as any
man I've ever met.
No. Wait!
Just wait.
What if this really was
the cops, you know?
And what if you're wrong
about her? I'm not wrong.
But what if you are?
Jesse, your misgivings
have been duly noted.
Now move away from me.
No. This is a voting thing.
I don't think so. I
vote it's a voting thing.
Mr. White, weigh
in here, would you?
What do you think?
Mr. White?
The methylamine keeps
flowing, no matter what.
We are not ramping down.
We're just getting started.
Nothing stops this train.
Nothing.
Hey, yo, Mr. White. Hold up.
I just wanted to
say I liked your idea.
You know, it's pretty, uh...
I think it's the way to go.
Oh, hey, um,
you said it was your...
your birthday, so...
I left the receipt in the box
in case you wanna exchange it.
Anyway, hey, happy birthday.
Hi.
I, uh, stopped by
Hank and Marie's.
Junior is still asking,
"What is going on?"
Nonstop, very
insistently. [CHUCKLES]
But everything's okay.
They're watching Ratatouille.
It's very sweet.
How are you?
There's gonna be some
more money coming in soon.
Is that okay?
Fine.
Good.
So...
Coming to bed?
I wanna show you something.
See that watch?
It's a birthday present.
The person who
gave me this present
wanted me dead too.
Not that long ago,
he pointed a gun
right between my eyes,
right here,
and he threatened to kill me.
He changed his
mind about me, Skyler,
and so will you.
[TICKING]
[TICKING LOUDLY]
[CLICKS]