[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[ENGINE IDLING]
[METAL CREAKING]
[♪♪♪]
[GARAGE DOOR WHIRRING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[CELL PHONE DIALING]
Mariano, it's me.
I need you to get
Skyler on the line.
No, no, I need you to get
her on the phone right now.
Tell her it's urgent.
No... What do you mean
she won't get off the phone?
I am giving you
permission, Mariano.
You make her get off the phone.
[GARAGE DOOR WHIRRING]
Mariano, who is Skyler
on the phone with?
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Yeah.
Okay.
[VIBRATING]
Where is she? Where's
Skyler? She just kind of left.
She didn't say
where she was going.
[COUNTRY MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Skyler, my... My
head is spinning.
And yours, I...
I can't even imagine.
So much makes sense to me now.
You jumping in the pool,
you sending us your kids,
I get it.
I just wished I'd
seen it sooner.
He's a monster.
He's a...
Look, I don't know
what he did to you
to force you to
keep his secrets.
If he threatened you,
or whatever mind
games he played...
I don't know if there was abuse.
But I want you to know that
you can be open with me.
Don't hold anything back, okay?
I mean, I don't even understand
if you know the
full extent of this,
what he's done.
Not just the meth cooking,
but the lives he's destroyed.
But, look, that's all
behind you, starting now.
You're done being his victim.
Because here's
what we're gonna do.
Sky, here's what we're gonna do.
You and the kids will
move back to our house,
where you'll be safe,
where he can't get to you.
Hank, does Marie...?
No. We'll get to
that soon enough.
It's just you and
me right now, okay?
Okay.
Before we, um...
Before we get you
back to the house, I...
I'm gonna ask you to tell
me everything you can.
Um, take as long as you like.
Just start from the beginning
when you first became
aware of Walt's activities
and just try to be as
detailed as you can.
What, right... Right here?
Right now? Sure. Why not?
While it's still
fresh, you know?
And just remember
to state your name and
the date before you start.
Hank, do...?
Do we have to do this right now?
No, we don't have to
do this right now, no.
Here's the thing,
I need something solid
that I can bring to my people.
A statement, on the record.
So you testifying to
Walt's criminal activity,
whatever you know,
goes a long, long way here.
Okay? I mean, you see,
building a case this big,
gathering evidence,
enough to get a conviction,
we're talking a
long-haul proposition.
I don't want that bastard
running out the clock.
But with your testimony...
What do you mean,
running out the clock?
His cancer. His cancer is back.
So he says.
He didn't tell you?
Who's to say it's even
true? Lying piece of shit.
Look, regardless, I
mean, we'll just assume.
Fine. Okay?
That son of a bitch
looks me in the eye
and he says if what
I know is true... "If."
he'll be dead
before I can prove it.
The balls on that son of a...
I got all these little pieces.
They're all part of the story.
They don't mean
much on their own,
but when you tell
me what you know,
we start filling in the gaps,
I'll have him in lockup
before the sun goes down.
Hank, I...
I think maybe...
Maybe I need a lawyer.
What?
No, no, no, you don't.
Yeah, I think maybe I do.
Skyler, understand, I
am here to help you.
But to do that, I
need your help.
We start bringing in lawyers,
and they start
putting up roadblocks
where they don't need to be
and my ability to control
this situation diminishes.
Just for my own
protection, and just...
You know, it seems to make sense
that I should have
someone to talk to.
Skyler, I'm your
biggest advocate here,
and I'm telling you,
for your own good,
you need to get out
ahead of this thing.
I mean, you start, you
know, getting defensive...
I'm not saying it's right,
but I'll tell you it's a fact,
the DA will look
at you differently.
But you don't know
that. Skyler, yes, I do.
I've been around
long enough to know.
It's in your best interest
to get out there
and show the world
you have nothing to hide.
Look,
no one in the world is
more important to me
than your sister.
So believe me when I tell you
that your best interests
and mine are the same.
But, Hank, you telling
me not to talk to a lawyer
doesn't sound like that at all.
It sounds like what you want...
What you want is to get Walt
at all costs.
Okay.
Okay, let's just...
slow down. Slow down.
You can...
You can talk to a lawyer later.
But right now,
what we need to do,
we need to go get the kids.
We need to bring them to
my house so that they're safe,
and then we need
to help each other
put that animal away, okay?
Come on. Hank.
Let's go to the house,
and we'll deal with it there.
Am I under arrest?
What? Am I under arrest?
Skyler, I... You're not
thinking straight about this.
You have to listen to me.
I... Skyler. Skyler. Skyler.
Am I under arrest? No.
Am I under arrest? No. Sky...
Hank, are you
arresting me? Sky...
[SHOUTING] Am I under arrest?
[SOBBING]
[SIGHS]
Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
I gotta do it, man.
KUBY: Dude. Mm.
What are you doing? Huell.
Hey, quit screwing around. Mm.
We are here to do a job,
not channel Scrooge McDuck.
You hearing me?
I hear you.
KUBY: Dude.
[HUELL GRUNTING]
Aw, screw it.
Mexico.
All's I'm saying.
[CHUCKLES]
Guy hit 10 guys in jail
within a two-minute window.
All's I'm saying.
SAUL: Yeah, it's me again.
Listen, you've got to hide those bags.
The monkey is in the
banana patch, capiche?
So call me.
That's the third message.
Where the hell is that kid?
[PHONE RINGING]
That's her. SAUL: Don't.
I have to talk to her.
SAUL: You don't.
Answer that phone and
Schrader's on the line with a wiretap
recording everything. You're
not doing anybody any favors.
Why do you still have a
battery in that thing? Take it out.
They might be trying to
triangulate your movements.
I'm not being paranoid. Do it.
I can't believe she went to
him. SAUL: She just panicked.
She went right to him
without even talking to me.
I'm not saying it's not bad.
It's bad, but it could be worse.
Really? How much
worse could it be, exactly,
in your estimation?
What does she actually
know? What has she seen? Hm?
Nothing. It's hearsay.
It's all he said, she said.
The only real evidence
that she can lead them to
is your money. Once
we take care of that,
well, yeah, then
they got nothing.
Nothing? Hank knows.
That's not nothing.
Yeah. I can't exactly see
him turning the other cheek.
Of course there's always, um...
Always what?
Have you given
any thought to, um,
sending him on a trip to Belize?
Belize? Yeah, Belize.
You know, where, uh...
Where Mike went to,
off on a trip to, uh, Belize.
Saul, you better not be saying
what I think you're saying.
It's just conjecture on
my part. Hank is family.
Okay, it's an option that...
You understand that?
It's an option that has
worked well for you in the past.
Jesus. What is wrong with you?
My mistake. Family,
off limits, of course.
I'm just throwing
thoughts out there.
This is a safe room, right?
Jesus. Send him to Belize.
I'll send you to Belize.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Finally.
It's about time. Have
you two been followed?
Are you sure?
If they had, we'd all be
in handcuffs right now.
I took the tops off.
Figured you'd wanna check
to make sure it's all there.
You figured right.
Close enough.
If you need any help
on the other end...
These things are
a bitch to move.
I'll manage.
HUELL: And we
don't mind overtime.
Ain't no thing.
Pay Huell and Kuby
and take your cut.
The rest is mine.
Insurance in case I need you.
In case you need me?
I'm thinking the
probability is high.
Just find Jesse.
Keys.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[GRUNTING]
[HOLLY BABBLING]
Saul Goodman,
please. Skyler White.
No, no, please don't
tell me he isn't there.
I know he's been
avoiding my calls.
All right, well, has my
husband been there?
What do you mean,
you don't know?
Either he has or
he hasn't. I don't...
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Sweetie.
MARIE: Sky?
[KNOCKING CONTINUES]
Sky, I know you're home.
Let me in. Let me talk to you.
I'm just gonna wait here
until you open the door.
So let me in now or
three hours from now,
but I'm not leaving
until I see you.
Skyler, please.
Just you.
Not Hank.
MARIE: Tell me Hank is crazy.
Tell me he doesn't know
what he's talking about.
You gotta give me
something, Skyler.
Anything to help me understand.
It can't be true.
Oh, my God.
How long have you known?
Hank said that when
you walked into the pool,
that's when you knew.
When you had your...
But not then.
Before that.
Since Gus Fring?
The money.
All that money that Walt made
when you bought your car wash.
And your whole gambling story.
That was a lie. I...
Did you know then?
You had to.
Skyler...
Did you know since
before Hank was shot?
Skyler?
Marie.
I am so sorry.
You're sorry.
You're...
I'm sick of...
[GASPING]
You won't talk.
You won't talk to Hank
because you think that Walt
is going to get away with this.
[CRYING]
Oh, God.
[HOLLY WHIMPERING]
[MARIE MURMURING]
MARIE: Come on, baby. Come on.
Let's go. Marie. Marie. Hey.
What are you doing?
Hey, what are you doing?
She's coming with
us. No, she is not.
Give her back to me. Marie.
[HOLLY CRYING]
Hank. Hank, help! Hank!
You are not leaving this
house with my daughter.
Give her back to me.
Marie, give her
back to me. Stop it.
You're scaring her.
Give her back. I'm
trying to protect her.
I'm her mother.
She's not gonna
live in this madhouse!
You don't know what you're
talking about. Give her back.
HANK: Marie. Listen,
I will call the police.
You call them. You
call them, Skyler.
I will. Give me my baby.
Marie, put her down. SKYLER:
You can't take her away.
HANK: Marie. Give me my baby.
We are not leaving without her.
Give me my baby now! Marie!
HANK: Do it now.
Give her back.
[HOLLY WAILING]
SKYLER: That's
right. It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay. I got you.
[♪♪♪]
Okay, Mama has you now.
Mama has you now.
Mama has you. Shh.
It's okay. It's okay.
Shh.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
[HOLLY CONTINUES WAILING]
You have to get him.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[WALT GRUNTING]
[JOSÉ LARRALDE'S
"QUIMEY NEUQUÉN" PLAYS]
[COUGHING]
Thirty-four, 59,
20, 106, 36, 52.
[GRUNTING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[WHISPERING] Walt.
Where have you been?
Oh, my God.
What happened?
[IN NORMAL VOICE] You
moved the money, didn't you?
You buried it somewhere.
Did you get my messages?
I told Hank nothing.
Walt, I swear I didn't.
Say something.
Please.
Oh, my God.
Walt. Walt.
Hey.
[GROANING]
How...? How long was I out?
Four or five hours. Oh.
How are you feeling?
It's true.
The cancer is back.
Is this it?
Does that make you happy?
I can't remember the
last time I was happy.
Just tell me.
I know you talked with Hank.
I know you made a deal.
Skyler, I'll make this easy.
I'll give myself up if you
promise me one thing.
You keep the money.
Never speak of it.
Never give it up.
You pass it on to our children.
Give them everything.
Would you do that?
Please.
Please don't let me have
done all this for nothing.
How did Hank find out?
Did somebody talk?
No, no one talked.
It was me.
I screwed up.
The way Hank talks,
he's got his suspicions.
Not much else.
You can't give yourself up
without giving up the money.
It's the way this works, Walt.
So maybe our best move here...
is to stay quiet.
Okay, you can take it off now.
All right, what's so important
you had to come way out here?
LYDIA: The amount of
money I'm bringing in,
I deserve to see why
it's all going wrong.
You an expert on meth labs now?
You gonna tell us how
to fix our operation?
And what if I can help?
What will it hurt to show me?
I don't like my
time being wasted.
Well, I'm here, and 10
minutes is a small sacrifice
when we're talking about
a $50 million shortfall.
So?
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[ENGINE STARTS]
Safe to come down?
MAN: Yeah. You're good.
Ladies first.
Okay, now you've seen
it. Yeah, now I've seen it.
What?
Well, how about we
start with it's filthy.
What are you, my mother?
What filthy?
It's just dimly lit.
LYDIA: Do you seriously think
this is up to the standards
of your predecessor?
Because it's not.
Not even close.
DECLAN: Well, the product
we're making, it's selling just fine.
Heisenberg's standards
don't matter anymore.
To whom? A bunch of
scabby Arizona tweakers?
They matter to my buyer
in the Czech Republic,
therefore, they matter to me.
Look, I cannot move
what this person is making
if it's substandard.
And it is. It just
is. No offense.
If you can do better, do better.
I don't know what to tell you.
You tried to get
the man back, right?
He said no, so... I mean,
what do you want me to do?
Todd. Use Todd again.
Look, he learned
from him, all right?
At least Todd's first two
cooks were at 74 percent.
On his third cook,
he started a fire.
Look, I tried Heisenberg's
way. It didn't work out.
I wanna cook in my territory.
I wanna use guys that I trust,
not Todd, who I don't.
And that's the end
of the conversation
as far as I'm concerned.
I really wish you'd have
given him a chance.
Hey. We have a problem.
DECLAN: You stay here.
[HATCH CLOSES]
[PHONE BEEPS OFF]
[MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[GUNSHOTS]
MAN 1: Get down!
[MACHINE GUN FIRING]
[CLATTERING]
[GUNSHOTS CONTINUE]
[GUNSHOTS STOP]
[HATCH OPENS]
MAN 2: Hello? Ma'am, you okay?
Hello?
Safe to come up
whenever you want.
I...
I don't want to see.
Okay.
Cool, so I guess maybe, um...
Maybe just close your eyes.
Okay.
This way.
To the right.
Ha-ha. Are you
kidding me with this?
Heh. Uncle Jack.
[GRUNTING]
Fire in the hole.
[GUNSHOT]
It's okay. Sorry about that.
It's cool, lady.
Okay, boys, let's take it
all. Let's get everything.
Hey.
You...
going into work today?
You're kidding, right?
What about you?
Are you going to the office?
You have to tell them, Hank.
Today.
Marie, I just... I
just don't have it yet.
The piece I need to
prove it all, it's just not here.
Then let them help you.
Tell Steve, tell Ramey.
You've got enough to get them
to believe your story at least.
Put the whole DEA on it.
That's how this is
supposed to work, right?
No.
No?
What no? What are you,
Lone Wolf McQuade?
Look, baby...
You've gotta go
in with this, Hank.
Look, the day I
go in with this...
that's the last day of
my career, all right?
I'm going to have
to walk in there,
look those people in the eye
and admit that the person
I've been chasing the past year
is my own brother-in-law.
It's over for me.
Ten seconds after I tell
this story, I'm a civilian.
And then how can we help
Skyler if she comes to her senses?
When I go in there...
I'm bringing proof,
not suspicions.
I can be the man who
caught him, at least.
What if you wait
and they catch Walt without you?
If they find out that you
knew and you said nothing?
Hank, wouldn't
you go to jail too?
[CHATTERING]
[♪♪♪]
Hey, Hank. Welcome back.
Morning.
Hey. Hey, boss.
MAN: How you doing, Hank? Hey.
Hey. Look who's back.
I had to see it
with my own eyes.
How you doing? Good.
Yeah, yeah. You miss me?
Miss you? Like my balls
miss jock itch, maybe.
Yeah? I didn't
know you had balls.
All right, don't make me
sorry I stopped by here.
Anyway, you got a
budget meeting in an hour,
then a meet-and-greet
with the new prescription
task force guys.
All right. Hey,
you know, listen.
Let's see if we can get
that budget meeting pushed
and instead see
if you could set up
a conference call with Ramey.
What for?
Just a "getting back up
to speed" thing, you know,
for me.
All right. You got it.
Oh, hey. Did you hear
about that money thing?
No, what money thing?
Oh, you're gonna love this.
It involves your old
pal Jesse Pinkman.
Pinkman?
MAN: I'll give you this.
Jesse, you're never boring.
Not boring at all.
So come on,
buddy, share with us.
Why were you tossing millions
of dollars all over Albuquerque?
KALANCHOE: I promise you we
can hold out just as long as you can.
That's a fact. I got a bladder
the size of a hot water bottle.
Man, all that cash.
I wouldn't be able to
stop talking about it.
I know. But I don't think I'd
be tossing it out my car window.
KALANCHOE: Heh-heh. Yeah.
My take-home doesn't allow
for that whole Robin Hood thing.
But apparently
Jesse is raking it in.
MUNN: Yes, indeed.
I'm sure he's got a perfectly
reasonable explanation
for where he got it.
Sure. He found it.
Or won it in a card game, maybe.
That's it. Won it
in a card game.
Lucky night at the casino.
KALANCHOE: Jesse,
did you have a lucky night?
Okay. Jesse, we're gonna
let you gather your thoughts
so we can continue this
stimulating conversation.
Can we get you
anything? Coffee? A soda?
Right.
Yeah. Thought not.
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
I have a history
with Jesse Pinkman,
and I think he can
be helpful to me
on another active investigation.
Look, I'm only asking
for a couple minutes here.
You said he wasn't talking?
Let me tell you, that
kid hates my guts.
Despises me, okay?
Maybe I can get him cranked
up enough that he starts yapping.
Then you guys go in,
get what you need
from the little shit-stain,
finish him off.
Gives me anything
useful while he's with me,
I'll share it, 100 percent.
I could use a smoke break.
Yeah. How about you?
Yeah. Maybe you could keep
an eye on our suspect for us,
just for a few minutes.
Absolutely. I can do that.
Okay.
All right, guys.
[♪♪♪]