[FLY BUZZING]
[BUZZING]
Mr. White?
Hello?
[BUZZING]
Mr. White, the, uh,
car's been dealt with, sir.
No one tailed you?
No. I stayed off
the main streets
and kept checking, so...
Joe ask any questions?
I told him RV job,
just like you said,
and he totally knew.
It's pretty cool the
way they do that,
turn a car into a cube.
So, should we deal
with this other thing now?
[BUZZING]
[SIGHS]
Yeah.
Sure.
[CAR ALARM CHIRPS]
I don't want to talk about this.
Okay.
It had to be done.
All right.
I need to talk to you.
In private.
So what's the story?
You get to Mike?
Mmm-hmm.
He get out safe?
He's gone.
[SIGHS] All right.
Well, what about
those nine guys in jail?
They got no reason
not to talk now.
So what do we do?
"We"? Who's "we"?
There is no "we," Jesse.
I'm the only vote left,
and I'll handle it.
[DOOR CLOSING]
My client will supply
vital information
relating to the organization,
distribution, and production
of Fring's
methamphetamine enterprise.
In exchange, we expect
all charges to be dropped,
and Dennis not only walks
out of here a free man,
but also receives
blanket immunity.
[SCOFFS]
For what he's gonna be
furnishing, this deal is plenty fair.
[SCOFFS]
Best I'd be willing to do is queen
for a day and reduced charges.
All charges dropped.
Queen for a day and a five-k.
That's the best
you're gonna get.
No way. Guys, come on.
You can be a fairy
princess, for all I care.
Where you going?
I'm going shopping for someone
who can tell me something
I don't already know.
Hey, hey.
I got plenty you don't know.
You seem a little confused.
This here is a buyer's market.
I got eight other
assholes just like you,
four of them within
100 feet from here.
I also got Dan the
douche bag lawyer
who's gonna give me the
money and Ehrmantraut.
So settle in, Dennis.
Enjoy your new home.
I'm gonna go rattle some cages.
[DOOR OPENS]
[CLOSES]
So?
Maybe you should
order something.
Do you want a
coffee or something?
Not just now.
I think this would play better
if you ordered something.
I think this will play just
fine, and I'm not thirsty.
So let's take a
look at the list.
Lydia, you've come all this way.
You do have the
list? Yes, I have it.
Good.
It's just not written down.
And why is that?
It's in my head. Safer there.
I see.
Then I suggest
you pick up a pen.
Not just yet.
It was my understanding
that attending to
these nine names
was precisely what you wanted.
Ten names now. Ten,
counting the lawyer.
Yes. Ten, counting the lawyer.
So, what,
am I not tying up loose
ends for our mutual benefit?
You're tying up loose ends,
and I don't wanna be one of them.
Once I give you that list,
I've served my purpose,
and then maybe I'm just one
more person who knows too much.
So, you put that
list in my hands,
and in your mind,
I immediately just murder you,
just right here in
this restaurant? No.
Right here in this public place,
immediately? Not right here.
That is not what
I... Listen, Lydia.
You made me promise
on my children's lives
that I guaranteed your safety.
From Mike.
You guaranteed I'd
be safe from Mike.
There's no way
he'd ever go for this,
you getting rid of his guys.
You wouldn't be
doing this, the names,
if Mike were still a factor.
Yeah. That's what I thought.
What do you want, exactly?
Because if you don't
want to give me that list,
then I've truly
got no use for you.
I can grow your
business exponentially.
Just give me the list.
I can do that by
helping you expand
into a larger, highly active,
highly profitable marketplace.
What do you know about
the Czech Republic?
The Czech Republic?
Did you know there's a
higher demand for meth there
than anywhere else in Europe?
Five percent of its
10 million people,
which is roughly the
population of the southwest
from Western Texas to Phoenix,
are using meth.
You keep your market here,
but by adding overseas sales,
you can more than
double your current profits.
And I checked.
The average purity is
only about 60 percent.
They've never seen
anything like your product.
You'll blow their hair back.
Shipping internationally
seems like courting disaster.
Not if you're madrigal. Madrigal
is under investigation
by the DEA.
The restaurant division, mostly.
We've got 46,000 employees
spread across 14 divisions.
And once Mike's people
are no longer a factor,
things should tidy up nicely.
This is what I do,
you understand?
I move things from point A
to point B all over the globe.
1.2 million metric tons a month,
and all of it right
at my fingertips,
a laptop click away.
The Czech Republic...
Who's there on the other end?
People I ship to regularly.
People I've worked
with for years.
They're professional
and very amenable.
I'm very careful
who I work with.
And if this is such a slam dunk,
then why didn't
you pitch it to Fring?
I did. He said yes.
We were in the final
stages of working it out
when somebody killed him.
You don't think Gus Fring
built his distribution
network all by himself?
There are considerable
advantages
to diversification
of distribution,
like putting 6,000 miles
between you and your product.
At 25 pounds a week,
I'm estimating you'll
gross about two million.
Give me ten pounds to start,
and we'll see how it goes.
All right.
Now, with Fring,
my end was gonna be 30 percent,
which I believe is
more than fair. Okay.
Trust me, if you do this...
Lydia, learn to take
yes for an answer.
Now, first things first.
Shake on it?
We're going to make
a lot of money together.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[BEEPS]
Todd, I think it's time
I meet your uncle.
MAN: No iron pile.
There's too many
muscle-heads flexing their shit
Too many eyes.
MAN 2: Okay, so
no chow line, no yard.
Gonna keep it simple.
Pass-byes.
Yeah. Hallways,
shower room, cells.
The easy stuff.
MAN 3: I say we go with a riot.
Our boys get it done in a riot.
No, no, no. No chaos.
I don't want the goon squad
rolling in and stealing our shot,
you know?
This has gotta
be fast and quiet.
Just boom, boom, boom.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Surgical.
Surgical. That's
what it's gotta be.
So how many guys we got at MDC?
Three, counting Shaddock.
And he makes the schedule now,
so we can put who we
need where we need them.
All right. So MDC's
covered. What about the rest?
We need G block
in Valencia, right?
Our guy's on the night shift.
Have him pull a double. Nah.
His supervisor's got
some hard-on about OT.
Have him switch with somebody.
I don't know. Just get it done.
Regardless, you know, we got
enough guys in Valencia right now?
Might have to hire out.
You high? Mix
blood with chuntaros?
No way. Well...
There's no need. We got enough.
Hitters ain't the problem.
It's that short walking window
after lunch. Mmm-hmm.
Yeah.
It's gonna be tight.
Real tight.
You know, I gotta be
straight with you, man.
Taking out all
these guys is doable.
But hitting them in three separate
jails all within two minutes?
Whacking Bin Laden
wasn't this complicated.
[CHUCKLING]
Where do you suppose
these come from?
I've seen this one before.
I wonder,
are they all
In some giant
warehouse someplace?
Hey.
It can be done, just
not the way you want it.
It can be done
exactly how I want it.
The only question is,
are you the man to do it?
Figure it out.
That's what I'm paying you for.
[CHUCKLING]
[SIGHS]
[TICKING]
[LOUNGE MUSIC PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE]
[CRYING OUT]
[DOOR RATTLES]
[BLOWS LANDING]
Aah!
[MEN GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING]
[TICKING CONTINUES]
[ALARM BLARING]
[MEN GRUNTING]
[THUD]
[ALARM CONTINUES]
[MUFFLED YELLING]
What's happening?
Oh! Oh!
What are you doing,
man? Don't do this, please!
No, man! Help me!
Help me! Help!
Help me!
[TICKING STOPS]
[GIRLS LAUGHING]
Excuse me a second.
Grab more photos, will you?
[INAUDIBLE]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Yes?
MAN: It's done.
New details have emerged
in the spate of jail deaths that rocked
central New Mexico three days ago.
As of yet, no names of victims have
been released, but authorities continue
to investigate
what appears to be
a carefully coordinated
sequence of attacks
that occurred within minutes of
one another Giddyap! Giddyap!
In three different
correctional facilities...
Ooh!
Is it okay if I turn
this off? Oh, sure.
I don't want the
news on right now.
Hank just pulled up, and
he's not in the best mood.
Oh, all right. Well,
I'll get out of your hair.
Okay.
Hi, honey.
Dinner will be in about an hour.
And I thought we could
have that chicken that you like.
Or we could order Chinese?
Sure. There you go.
There you are.
Wanna play with your toys?
I'll see you in
a little bit, okay?
See you in a little bit.
Hey, Hank. I was just
getting ready to leave.
Want a drink?
Um, yeah, sure. Thanks.
Perfect.
Rocks, right? Rocks, yes.
[HOLLY COOING]
[SIGHS]
Been thinking about this
summer job I used to have.
Oh, yeah?
Back in college,
I'd spend my days
marking trees in
the woods with this...
this orange spray can.
Marking trees?
Yeah. Crews would come in later
and find the trees I
tagged and cut them down.
First, you go in, and
you mark locations
for skid trails and landings.
Then you choose specific trees
all within a selected grid.
[SIGHS]
Every day,
I'd go back,
hike in,
pick up where I left off.
Oh. Sounds nice,
being out in the woods all day.
Nah, it wasn't so great.
I got sunburned.
There were mosquitoes.
I just wanted to
make a few bucks.
Buy beer.
Been thinking about that
job more and more lately.
Maybe I should've
enjoyed it more.
Tagging trees is a lot
better than chasing monsters.
I used to love to go camping.
[POP ROCK PLAYING]
[SONG CONTINUES]
[SONG FADES OUT]
This way. Here, baby girl.
Come see your brother.
There you go,
sweetie. That's it.
Oh, my God! Look at her go!
Good job!
WALTER, JR.: Peekaboo. This way.
Here. Let's go see your
brother. Let's get him.
Get him! Where'd you go?
I can't see you. Where'd you go?
There you are!
[CHUCKLING] [LAUGHING]
You're really good
with her. [COUGHING]
Come here, my baby girl.
You're gonna be a
handful, aren't you? Yeah.
Mama's gonna get
her exercise. Aw.
[SIGHS]
Hey, do you, uh... You wanna
watch a movie? [PHONE RINGING]
Hey, Louis.
Uh... [CLEARS THROAT]
One moment.
Uh, nothing.
[CHUCKLES] What's up?
[SIGHS]
Oh, well.
[CHUCKLES]
It's nice to see
you smile again.
I mean, you seem good.
Yeah. I'm hanging in there.
To see you laugh
like that just now...
It's such an improvement,
don't you think?
I don't... I don't really...
[STAMMERS]
We've been thinking,
Hank and I, that
it may be time to
take the kids home.
It's been almost
three months, right?
Almost three?
Um...
Does Hank not want...
Oh, no, no, no. Oh, god. No. No.
Hank's crazy for these
kids. You know that.
It goes without saying,
we love having them.
And we're always here for you
and wanna help you
any way that we can.
But...
We're starting to worry
that maybe...
Maybe we're enabling you.
Sweetie, you've had
a lot on your plate,
and you and Walt
have had a lot...
So much to contend with.
And I'm so proud of you for going to
therapy, by the way. You know that, right?
It can be so helpful,
such a good tool.
And I'm very, very proud of you,
but I...
We...
Maybe at this point,
the best way
to help repair the family
would be to repair the family,
you know?
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[WATER LAPPING SOFTLY]
Take a drive with me.
Walt.
This is it.
This is what you've
been working for.
I rented this place, and
I started bringing it here,
because...
I didn't know what else to do.
I gave up counting
it. I mean, I had to.
It was just so much, so fast.
I tried weighing it.
I figured one bill
of any denomination
weighs a gram.
There are 454 grams to a pound,
but... [EXHALES]
There's a variety of
denominations, so...
How much is this?
I have no earthly idea.
I truly don't.
I just stack it up, keep it dry,
spray it for silverfish.
There is more money here
than we could
spend in ten lifetimes.
I certainly can't launder it,
not with 100 car washes.
Walt...
I want my kids back.
I want my life back.
Please tell me...
How much is enough?
How big does this
pile have to be?
[SOFT WHIRRING]
[CLICK]
[MECHANICAL HUMMING]
[DOOR OPENS]
Ow!
Aw, shit!
[SIGHS] [KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[KNOCKING]
Hi.
Hey.
Um, I...
I hope I'm not disturbing
you or anything.
I tried calling, but, uh...
Yeah. No, I, uh,
tossed all my burners.
Oh. And you didn't
answer your home line, so...
It's disconnected.
Oh, um, unplugged, I mean.
Did you leave a message, or...
Uh, no.
So, what's up?
I was just in the neighborhood,
so I thought I'd drop
by and say hello.
You, uh, wanna come in, or...
Uh, sure.
Thanks.
You know, I'd offer you a...
A beer or something, but...
No, no. No, I'm... I'm...
I'm fine, thanks.
You, uh, didn't wind
up moving, I see.
Didn't have to.
Saul told me what you did.
Anyways, uh, I'm not in jail.
You aren't either,
so there you go.
There was no
other option, Jesse.
It had to be done.
I'm not coming back.
I know.
So why are you here,
exactly?
[CHUCKLES]
It's funny. I...
I saw a bounder the other day.
Bounder? Yeah.
Our RV? A bounder?
Oh. Oh.
Oh, you saw the
same one as ours?
Yeah. Well, within a
couple years, I guess.
Early '80s.
It was certainly in
a lot better shape
than our old hunk of junk.
A much nicer paint job.
No bullet holes in the door.
Yeah. That thing
was a nightmare, huh?
Oh, it was primitive.
You know, whenever
I hit a red light,
I used to pray
it wouldn't crap out on me.
Yeah.
And then, suddenly, it
would sometimes have that...
That screeching sound
that just... Out of the blue,
like we hit a pack of cats.
Power steering belt.
That's what that was.
I always had this...
This whole system...
Strategy to not
let it idle too low.
Remember that time we ran out
of gas coming back from a cook?
Ah, the gauge. The gauge
always said half-full, so...
Yeah, you had to walk
three miles with a jerry can
while I waited on
the side of the road,
praying the whole time
that no cop would show up,
no good samaritan.
God.
We had money.
Why'd we keep it?
Why did we have to have
the world's shittiest RV?
Inertia? Yeah.
Yeah.
Inertia.
So, hey, um, you
know, I gotta get going.
Yeah. No, me too. I'm just
meeting up with some friends, and...
I gotta get going as well.
I left something for you.
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[CAR DEPARTING]
[PANTING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Hey.
I'm out.
MARIE: With some big
earrings, it could be really nice.
Perhaps some big
hoops. I feel like I just want
to mix it up with
my hair this summer.
You know, like color...
HANK: Yeah. I don't know.
WALT: Did you have a
coin collection? I had coins.
Have the time to do hobbies.
Coins and baseball cards.
Those were the ones.
You can play around with
it and take them in and out...
Not enough hours
in the day, right?
Not enough hours...
MARIE: My hairstylist told me
to take prenatal vitamins.
For your hair?
He said they work,
so I figure why not?
Oh, uh, Flynn,
could you put some
more sunscreen on Holly?
Yeah. Is it over there?
Yeah, it's right here. Okay.
For a home brew, though.
Papa-free. That's good.
Although I don't know why it would
be bad. Yeah. I know. Me neither.
Oh, do you...
I used to squeeze
lemon juice in my hair.
You remember that?
You wanted to be a
beach bum so badly.
I did. Ohh.
You and your stiff
hair. [GROANING]
Stiff what? Hey, hey.
I was interested to
see you get into that.
Borage oil is supposed to
be good. It's like chemistry.
Is it really? Better than
flaxseed? I don't know.
That's cool. I like your style.
There is no Christmas.
Maybe I should brew up a batch.
What do you think?
Ooh, schraderbrau?
Yeah. I vote yes.
I second that.
Well, there you
go. It's unanimous.
Well, who am I to fly
in the face of public
demand, right?
[CHUCKLING]
All right. Hold on. [GRUNTS]
Anybody, uh... Anybody
want anything? Want anything?
No, I'm good. I'm
good, thank you.
All right.
Does it look glossier?
Do I have a halo? I don't know.
How's she doing? She's good.
Try not to put any of that
sunscreen on her fingers.
HANK: "To WW, my star,
my perfect silence." [CHUCKLES]
WW.
I mean, who do you
figure that is, you know?
Woodrow Wilson?
Willy Wonka?
Walter White?
[CHUCKLES]
You got me.