[♪♪♪]
[LIQUID SQUISHING]
WALT: Jesse?
Jesse!
Show yourself right now!
[♪♪♪]
[CAR ENGINE RUNNING]
[IGNITION BEEPING]
[BICYCLES APPROACHING]
[♪♪♪]
[WHIRRING]
[MOTOR WHIRRING]
I'll be in touch.
Okay. Hey, Huell.
Listen, I want you to
swing by the high school
on your way to Saul's.
I can't believe he would
go after my son, but...
You got it.
And Kuby's at the
car wash, right?
Parked right across the street.
All's quiet. No Pinkman.
Okay. Just find him.
[ENGINE STARTS
AND CAR PULLS AWAY]
[PHONE KEYPAD BEEPING]
[LINE RINGS]
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Please leave a message.
Jesse, listen.
I mean, obviously, you've
changed your mind here,
and so thank you for that.
And I know you're angry.
I wanna fix this, okay?
Whatever it takes, all right?
We'll talk, and
we will fix this.
Until then, just...
Just sleep it off, okay?
And then call me.
Be safe.
How's it coming?
I replaced the doorjamb
and the striker plate.
Switch this out,
we'll be good to go.
Good. Do you want separate keys
for the different locks or do
you want one working both?
No, no, no. No re-key.
Same exact keys as before.
Usually with a break-in,
people like to get new keys.
No, same keys, same locks.
The old keys have
to work here, okay?
Okay. All right.
[WHIRRING]
Good.
Good. Good, good, good.
[SNIFFS]
Oh, no, no. Hey,
guys, guys, guys.
Cut that. Yeah, this...
That area's still
pretty bad. Right.
We'll have to go
over this a lot more.
We've made three passes already.
Like I say, gasoline's tricky.
No, no, no. The smell has
got to be gone completely.
My wife is coming home,
and I can't have
any odor, any stain,
any sign that anything
happened here.
Understand?
I... I know. This
is short notice,
and I really appreciate it.
Sir, we'd love to take
more of your money,
but you've got gas soaked
through to your subfloor.
Until you pull this up
and get new carpet,
new padding,
this is as good as it gets.
[♪♪♪]
Is that gasoline?
Ask Dad. Hey. Over here.
What happened?
What happened is that
I should sue someone.
That's what happened.
So I'm on my way
to the drugstore,
and I have to stop
to get some gas
and there is this total
pump malfunction.
You know what? She
shouldn't be in this room.
I mean, this is
supposedly green,
but you know how it is.
You can close the
windows in the nursery
because it's really
only out here.
This is as good as it gets.
So, uh,
pump malfunction?
Yeah. I'm standing there
filling up like I've done
a thousand times before
and I hear a chunk. You
know, the pump's nozzle.
The metal thing. The
thing you squeeze?
I hear a chunk. So I
suppose, in my naiveté,
I took to understand
that gas is no longer
coming out of the nozzle
so I pull out the hose to
put it back and whoosh!
Yeah, I am suddenly
soaked in gasoline.
I mean, on my arms
and my legs and my groin.
So now I am in a panic.
I race home, I run
inside the house,
and I'm stripping off my
clothes as fast as I can.
I jump in the shower.
It's not until after I
get out of the shower
that I realize my
gas-covered clothes
have been soaking
in the living room rug
this entire time.
I mean, it's... It's...
The whole thing
is just so stupid.
I could have rinsed
off at the station.
Halfway home, I
started to realize,
wait a minute,
there's a water hose
right there next
to the air pump.
You know, for tires.
Anyway, so that was my day.
How was yours?
WALT JR.: Dad? Yeah.
Please, can you
just tell the truth?
Tell... What do you mean?
You fainted, didn't you?
Because you're sick again?
You were pumping
gas, and the fumes,
they made you pass out again.
Just... Just admit it.
No, the... No.
It was the pump.
[SCOFFS]
All right, I...
Maybe I did get a little
swimmy at one point,
but I did not faint. Okay?
I'm fine, and that's the truth.
However, in the best interest
of all of our
continued good health,
I don't think we can stay here.
I mean, not until
we get new carpet.
Yeah.
Uncle Hank and Aunt Marie,
they got plenty of space.
Hey, what about a hotel?
A hotel. That could be sweet.
A good one.
I like the way
you're thinking. Yes.
Could be a little
family vacation.
Might be fun. What do you say?
Why don't you put
some clothes together?
Yeah. All right.
I'm sorry. It's not
my finest hour.
I'll go pack a bag.
Okay. Okay.
Think this'll leave a scar?
I never should have let my
dojo membership run out.
Jesus. Jesse did that?
Yeah, but you gotta understand,
deep down he loves me.
So, where is he?
Still looking. WALT:
Where have you looked?
His place, his folk's place,
this Brock kid's place.
Crack shacks at Siesta Hills,
the Indigo, the Crystal Palace,
go-kart joint on Copper Ave,
AA meeting off the 40.
His buddies, Beaver
and what's-his-name?
Badger and Skinny Pete.
Yeah, no, he's not with them.
WALT: They could
be covering for him.
I posed as a meter reader.
I put a bug on the
tall kid's mom's place.
For three hours straight,
all he talked about was
something called Babylon 5.
I checked with my gal at A.P.D.
She said Pinkman's
not in their system
so the cops don't have him. Yet.
Maybe he changed
his mind about leaving,
called your guy back.
Somebody misses their
first chance with my guy,
there's no second.
Well, keep looking.
What then?
What do you mean?
I mean, Pinkman's
like a bad penny.
Sooner or later, he'll turn up.
I'm wondering what you
wanna do when he does.
Jesse is upset about the boy.
I just need to explain to
him why that had to happen.
Okay, but say, you know,
just for the sake of argument,
the kid's not in the mood
for a nuanced discussion
of the virtues of
child poisoning.
His plans are running more
towards stabbing you to death
with a pointed stick. In
that scenario, then what?
You have a suggestion?
We were wondering if maybe
this isn't an Old
Yeller type situation.
Old Yeller?
Yeah, Old Yeller was the best,
most loyal dog there ever was.
I mean, everybody
loved that mutt
but one day, he showed up rabid,
and little Timmy, for
Old Yeller's own sake,
had to, uh...
Oh, you... You saw the movie.
You're full of colorful
metaphors, aren't you, Saul?
Belize, Old Yeller...
Just brimming with advice.
Do not float that idea again.
Find him.
WALT: Sorry. Ah. Sorry.
Room key wouldn't
let me into the ice room
so I had to go down
to the front desk.
But here we are.
Checked in on Junior.
Heh. Pay-per-view
and room service.
He's in heaven.
Hey, I thought you
were gonna take a bath.
How's Saul doing?
Saul? Goodman?
No idea.
No?
You were just out talking
to him in the parking lot.
I'm sorry. Were
you spying on me?
Yes.
And I feel just
awful about it too.
You know, I played along
with your pump
malfunction bullshit
because Junior was
standing right there,
but now I would like to
know what's going on.
First of all, it's no big deal.
Coming here is just me
being overly cautious.
Jesse Pinkman, you know?
He came over to our house
that time for dinner, remember?
Well, he... He got
upset over this...
Something he thinks I did.
I did do it.
But I did it for
very good reasons.
And it's just...
It's complicated.
Wait, are you...?
Are you telling
me that he tried to
burn our house down?
That was...
probably, for a brief
moment, his intention,
but, obviously, he
changed his mind.
And how does that work?
Him...? Him changing his mind?
Ah, God.
Look...
You've got to understand
that with Jesse,
there are emotional
issues, personal issues,
some drug abuse.
But he has always been
more of a danger to
himself than anyone else.
He has a tendency to fly
off the handle, that's all.
So he has never hurt anybody?
No.
I can't believe you
got her down so fast.
So...
what's your course
of action here?
Saul's guy, Kuby,
tracks him down,
which shouldn't take long,
and when he does, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna talk to him.
Make him see reason.
Talk to him?
Make him see reason?
So I'm clear,
these are just euphemisms
you're using here, right?
No.
What?
Wh...? What does that mean?
My God. I knew this
was going to happen.
I knew it. I told
you that someday,
someone was going to come
to our door and try to hurt us.
And now here we are.
No.
Jesse didn't go
there to hurt anyone.
He poured gasoline
all over our house, Walt.
He tried to set
our house on fire.
He changed his mind.
He didn't do it, did he?
What if he changes it back?
[HOLLY BABBLING]
Walt, you need
to deal with this.
How much have you
had to drink? Heh, heh.
Not nearly enough.
I don't know how we got off
on whatever it is we're
talking about here...
but, clearly, I haven't
explained the situation
well enough because
this is a big overreaction.
We all need to just take a
deep breath and calm down
because Jesse isn't just some...
Some... Some rabid dog.
This is a person. A person
that is a threat to us.
I mean, my God, where we
are now with Hank and Marie
and that awful tape we made.
After everything we've done,
you can't just
talk to this person.
You're saying...
that I just...
What...? What
exactly are you saying?
We've come this far.
For us.
What's one more?
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[SNIFFS]
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTING]
Jesse!
Stop what you're doing
and turn and face me!
[SNIFFLING]
You wanna...? You
wanna know what he did?
You wanna hear about it?
Jesse, put out the lighter.
He poisoned a little kid.
An 8-year-old boy.
Just because, you know...
Just as a move!
Walt's a bastard. Secret's out.
We'll talk about it.
But I need you to put
out the lighter, okay?
Look, Jesse...
Jesse, I don't wanna kill you.
And you don't wanna be killed.
So put it out.
He can't keep
getting away with it!
He won't.
You really wanna burn him down?
Let's do it together.
[CAR IGNITION BEEPING]
[ENGINE STARTS]
You were following me?
Yeah. Since Goodman's.
Where we going now?
DEA. Downtown.
What, I'm, like, arrested?
Yeah, you know how this works.
Be a good witness for me,
it'll go better for you.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, sitting around MDC,
waiting to be a witness
against Mr. White.
It's... Heh.
It's gonna go great for me.
So...
you're angry.
I can't sleep. I'm not eating.
Last night, I was
online for six hours
looking up untraceable poisons.
This close family friend
had been keeping a
secret from you and Hank,
and somehow this person's
secret became known,
and now you're sad
and hurt and angry.
I'm...? I'm in the ballpark?
To be this wrong about someone.
This off.
We all lead double lives
to some extent, don't we?
We all have our secrets.
Yeah. Not like this.
Not like him.
Marie, I think it's
time you filled me in
on some more details here.
Who and what are
we talking about?
I said I can't do that.
It'd be bad for Hank.
Our friend made that
clear in his little movie.
Those kids...
under his roof. That baby.
I'm sick just thinking about it.
How could I have not seen this?
If I weren't being such a...
idiotic... Stupid
idiot, I could've...
We could have...
Blackjack winnings.
Nothing suspicious
about that at all.
Tell me about this movie.
Dave, can we simply
just focus on my feelings here?
The details don't
really matter, do they?
There's nothing
to be done, okay?
He screwed us and he won.
Can we just...?
Can we talk about
something else, please?
Yes?
How's work?
Last week, you were upset
about the new parking rules.
Marie?
Saxitoxin.
Derived from shellfish.
Produces a flaccid paralysis
that leaves the victim
conscious through a
progression of symptoms.
Death occurs from
respiratory failure.
That is definitely a contender.
Marie,
you're not ready
to fill me in here,
that's fine.
But I want you to listen.
There is no problem,
no matter how difficult
or painful or
seemingly unsolvable,
that violence won't make worse.
I know, I...
Don't worry. I
wouldn't hurt anybody.
I just...
It just feels good
to think about it.
[DOOR OPENS]
HANK: Hey, babe.
What's the story here?
Oh, well, something's come up.
I thought you might
wanna get out of the house
for a day or two.
You thought I'd pack up and
move out of my own house.
Why? What's going on?
Look, I don't wanna
get into it now.
But you know that
thing with Walt, there's...
There's been a development.
What happened?
Are you in danger?
No, no, no, not at all.
Just... It's a fluid situation.
I think it might go a little
smoother if you're not here.
So I... It's gonna
be great, you know?
I booked you a spa
package at La Posada.
You can do that
river-stones thing.
Hank, what the hell is going on?
Hank?
We have a guest.
[SNORING]
HANK: He was a little keyed up.
Gave him a couple
sleeping pills.
Okay. Okay, so listen.
I bring that kid in,
put him in the system,
Walt's gonna find out five
minutes later. You know?
My last 10 witnesses
died in jail, remember?
And I can't use a DEA safe
house without writing him up.
I can't risk a motel.
I know it sounds crazy,
but this is the best place.
For now. Just a
day or two, tops...
Okay, just answer
me this one question:
Is this bad for Walt?
Yeah. Very.
Good. I'm staying.
I'll heat up lasagna.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Phone's ringing.
[CHIMING]
AUTOMATED VOICE:
You have one new message.
WALT [ON RECORDING]:
Jesse, listen. Uh...
I mean, obviously, you've
changed your mind here
and so thank you for that.
And I know you're angry.
I wanna fix this, okay?
Whatever it takes, all right?
We'll talk, and
we will fix this.
Until then, just...
Just sleep it off, okay?
And then call me.
Be safe.
[PHONE BEEPS]
Hey.
What are you still doing up?
Couldn't sleep.
Ah. You and me both.
Here. Have a seat.
[SIGHS]
Everything okay? Oh, yeah.
Just business stuff.
Going over some options.
You guys still think you
might buy another car wash?
Oh, uh... Yeah. Well, maybe.
See how it goes.
How it goes now that...
Now that you're...
You're sick again, right?
No. That's not what I mean.
Hey. Told you not
to worry, remember?
How...? How can I not worry?
Come on. You think
I came all this way
just to let something as silly
as lung cancer take me down?
Not a chance.
I'm not going anywhere.
Should've brought
our suits, huh?
It's okay.
It's all right.
[WALT JR. CRYING]
I'll be up in a minute.
Okay.
See you in the morning.
[PHONE KEYPAD BEEPING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Would you like some coffee?
[SNIFFS THEN SIGHS]
Morning. You want some coffee?
No. The lady, um...
I think your wife...
MARIE: You take cream and sugar?
Uh... Black's... Black's good.
Thanks.
This is probably
gonna take a while.
Oh. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll run some errands. Okay.
MARIE: All right.
Uh... You remember Agent Gomez?
How you feeling?
Your head clear?
Yeah.
This... This can't
be what you mean
by burning him to
the ground, right?
I got stories that'll
make your toes curl,
but, you know, it's just
"my word against his word"
kind of stuff.
So, you know, I
don't really have any,
like, proof or anything.
Gomey, can you grab
the curtains over there?
There's a glare
thing happening here.
You know he's
retired, right? He's...
He's not even in the
business anymore.
So you're never gonna
catch him with a camcorder.
HANK: We're gonna catch him.
We gotta do this
first, okay? Come on.
Just tell us everything
you remember.
Any business dealings,
any personal dealings,
any criminal activity you
were a witness or a party to.
Anything and everything.
Just tell us your story, okay?
[CAMCORDER BEEPS]
Start from the beginning.
When did you first
meet Walter White?
Right. Okay, uh...
I first met Mr. White...
Walter White.
In junior year chemistry.
He was my teacher.
[DOOR CLOSES]
You believe him?
Yeah. I do, unfortunately.
And I hate to admit it,
but I think the kid is right.
There is no physical
evidence, not that I heard.
Yeah, well, no weapons,
no bodies, no working lab.
Just the word of one
nut-job meth-head
against
Mr. Rogers-Has-a-Lung-Tumor.
So do we take a run at
Lydia Rodarte-Quayle?
Vamonos Pest?
Follow up with the
Drew Sharp killing?
Where do we start?
I say we start with this.
WALT [ON RECORDING]: Jesse...
I'm gonna be at Civic
Plaza tomorrow at noon.
I hope you'll give me the
chance to explain myself
and talk through
everything once and for all.
I'll be alone and unarmed.
So if you wanna come
and shoot me in the head,
that's up to you.
Either way...
I'm in your hands.
[PHONE BEEPS]
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Go and talk to that asshole?
You can't be serious.
Go and listen. He
wants to explain himself.
We put a wire on you
and let him explain.
So your plan is to do his plan?
You seriously
think that this...?
This whole "once and
for all in the plaza" thing
is so he can talk to me?
Why not?
I... I... I can't
believe you two.
The dude wanted me out of town
before I came to
burn his house down,
and now I'm more
of a threat to him.
And he's got a zero-tolerance
policy on threats, you know?
If I go to this plaza, I'm
a dead man, is why not.
Hey, Walt's ruthless.
He'll do just about anything
to protect his interests.
I agree.
Except when it comes to you.
He cares about you. Heh.
HANK: Can't you see?
Oh, yeah. You mean,
when he's not ripping me off
or calling me an idiot
or poisoning people
that I care about?
Yeah, no, Mr. White's gay
for me. Everyone knows that.
No, I mean it. Based
on everything you told us.
Uh, he paid for your rehab,
ran over those two
drug dealers with his car.
Sounds like he saved your life.
Made you a 50-50 partner.
He didn't need to do that.
Yeah, he sort of did.
I'm the only one
near as good as him.
I don't know.
The way you tell it,
sounds like he's manipulating
you to stick around.
Like he doesn't wanna lose you.
All those numbers he runs on you
over and over, helping
you find the ricin cigarette.
Look how far he'll
go to show you...
To convince you that
he's not such a bad guy.
That's what this is.
What if it's about, um,
killing me, you know?
You know, getting
me out in the open,
hire some, uh...
Some clock-tower guy
or have me sit on a poisoned
needle or something, you know?
Nothing's gonna happen to you.
The plaza's one of the
most wide-open public places
in all of Albuquerque.
It's the middle of the day.
And Agent Gomez and I
will be right there with you.
Look, you two guys
are just guys, okay?
Mr. White, he's the devil.
You know, he is. He
is smarter than you,
he is luckier than you.
Whatever... Whatever you
think is supposed to happen,
I'm telling you, the exact
reverse opposite of that
is gonna happen, okay?
Jesse, Jesse, we're
not brainstorming here.
This is not asking.
Unless you know
another way to get the man
or you wanna take your chances
with the banger boys
over in MDC, then this is it.
This is what's happening.
I gotta piss. Can I piss?
HANK: Yeah. Down to the left.
You got another SD card?
[SIGHS]
What? What if the kid's right?
What if it's a trap?
The kid?
Oh, you mean the junkie murderer
that's dribbling all over
my guest bathroom floor?
Well, then, he's right.
Pinkman gets killed,
and we get it all on tape.
HANK: Remember,
you're hurt, angry,
but you're here
for answers, okay?
But don't... Don't
push the questions.
Okay? Let's not get
him suspicious, all right?
You let him do
the talking, right?
Just relax. That's
what matters most.
Don't cross your
arms, if you can help it.
Pancho Villa, Salma Hayek.
[OVER RADIO] Pancho Villa,
Salma Hayek. You getting that?
Loud and clear, idiota. HANK:
How's it looking, Gomey?
GOMEZ: No change.
He's just sitting there.
Are we doing this, or what?
Ready to kick some ass, partner?
All right. Time to go.
Okay.
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪]
[CHATTERING]
[BOTTLES RATTLING]
[GASPS]
[♪♪♪]
GOMEZ: Hey, Hank, you got
eyes on this? What's with the kid?
He's just standing there.
What the hell is he doing?
[♪♪♪]
He's on the move
now. He's taking off.
I think he's running.
Oh, no, no, no, kid.
Come on.
[♪♪♪]
GOMEZ: You got him?
He's at the pay phone.
Who the hell is he calling?
Oh, no, no, no. Come on, kid.
No. Come on.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Nice try, asshole.
WALT: Jesse, where are you?
I just wanna talk to you.
No. I'm not doing what you
want anymore. Okay, asshole?
[OVER SPEAKER]
This is just a heads-up
to let you know
I'm coming for you.
See, I decided that burning
down your house is nothing.
Next time, I'm gonna get
you where you really live.
WALT: Jesse, listen.
Jesse? Jesse?
[CHURCH BELL TOLLING]
GIRL: Daddy! Daddy! Hey!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
HANK: Get in.
Son of a bitch!
Stupid, high little...
What the hell
was that all about?
What were you thinking?
Thinking there's
another way. What?
To get him. There's another way.
A better way.
[SIGHS]
[PHONE KEYPAD BEEPING]
[COUGHING]
Hey.
It's Walt.
I'm okay.
I, uh...
Todd,
I think I might have
another job for your uncle.
[♪♪♪]