[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[PHONE DIALING]
Hey, Mr. White. It's me. Um...
I know you're probably
real busy with retirement,
but I got some news I think
you should maybe know about.
Me and Declan had some
differences of opinion,
and it got a little messy. Um...
It's all straightened out now,
but just a heads-up,
there's been a kind of
change in management.
Anyway, just thought
you should know.
Feel free to give me a
call if you want the details,
but, you know, it's
cool, so whatever.
Okay, then. Thanks. Bye.
TODD: Right, so there I
am, I'm on top of the train,
pumping the water in,
he's watching to
make sure we put in
exactly what he'd calculated.
We gotta be real precise
because water and
methylene weigh different,
and he figured it all
out to, like, milliliter.
I'm up there with my hose.
We're going as fast as we
can. We only got a few minutes.
At the crossing, we got this guy
who's smooth-talking
the engineer.
And it's all just going great
until this other dude shows
up in this monster truck,
so we're pretty much screwed,
because he can just push
the entire dump
truck off the tracks,
which, you know,
is what he does.
Wait. What's your guy
doing? You can't stop him?
Yeah, but what's he gonna say?
"Thanks anyway, sir,
but my friends are still
stealing cargo back there."
So I'm looking all around,
because I know we're not done,
but the gallons are
slowly ticking away.
And finally Mr. White
tells me to cut it.
So I fling the hose,
I'm grabbing the cap,
I'm screwing in the bolts.
Just, like, busting
ass, you know?
And then I feel the train
start moving and I'm...
You're... I'm on top.
Did you piss your
pants? Yeah, right?
So the thing starts speeding
up, so I jump off the moving train.
Like, total stuntman stuff.
It's like Hooper. You
ever see Hooper?
Oh, hey, man, Burt
Reynolds. Good movie.
He jumped out of a
helicopter, not a train.
Whatever, man.
It's a good movie.
This guy Jesse, he's underneath,
and the train just
drives right over him.
And luckily he's
this skinny little guy.
Damn. That's a tight operation.
It was perfect.
No one even knew
they got robbed,
just like we planned.
Mr. White told me it was,
like, the biggest train heist ever,
like, potential money-wise.
So that's how that
happened. Ha, ha.
[MACK SELF'S "EVERYDAY"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
WAITRESS: Can I
get you anything else?
Nope. Thanks, darling.
I'm ready for the check.
JACK: You feeling
good about cooking?
Yeah.
You'll be able to
run your own lab?
Do it up right? Yeah.
For sure. I got this.
All right.
Let's make some money,
then. I gotta hit the head.
JACK: Ever been on a
plane and find yourself
looking down at the
armrest next to you,
looking at the little plug
where the ashtray used to go?
I look at that and I say,
"What the hell happened
to this country?"
Nanny state.
I see a kid with a
bicycle helmet on,
I wanna smack
the shit out of him,
like, for his own good.
[TOILET FLUSHES]
[SLIM RHODES' "GONNA ROMP AND
STOMP" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
♪ Gonna romp, stomp
Swing with you, baby ♪
Sway with you, baby ♪
♪ Gonna romp, stomp
Rock with you, baby ♪
Roll with you, baby ♪
♪ Gonna romp, stomp
Romp and stomp tonight ♪
[♪♪♪]
[INDISTINCT OVERLAPPING VOICES]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[CAMCORDER BEEPS
AND POWERS DOWN]
Mr. Pinkman.
How are you today?
Not so good, huh?
Of course, I might be
able to help you out.
I wanna talk to you about
your partner, Heisenberg.
See, I know he's my
brother-in-law, Walt.
Oh, yeah. That's the look.
Lucky for you, I'm
more interested in him.
So I got an offer.
If you help me out here,
tell me all about you and him
and your little meth business,
maybe I talk to my
friends at the A.P.D.
and make all this go away.
I know he's the mastermind here.
Plus, I'm thinking,
based on your recent activities,
that maybe there's a
little trouble in paradise?
Maybe you guys aren't
getting along so good?
I'm right, aren't I?
Eat me.
Sure that's how you
want to play this?
Why don't you try
and beat it out of me?
That's your thing, right?
He really did a number
on you, didn't he?
I don't know, but...
happy people usually
don't go around
throwing millions
of dollars away.
I don't think...
Walt's gonna be patting
you on the back for that.
But maybe that's the point.
But, you see, I get that.
My own brother-in-law,
lying to me for over a year.
Using me.
Maybe you
understand that feeling.
Help me out here, Jesse,
and we can put him away.
I know you want that.
I think you wanna talk.
Not to you.
Agent Schrader, beat
any good suspects lately?
Tall and taller, ask him
about his history with my client.
He knocked the
poor kid unconscious
last time they were
alone. So, what'll it be,
a civil rights lawsuit
the size of Montana?
Because I'll oblige you.
Oh. So long, Rocky.
Keep your left up.
Detectives, I'm
inviting you to leave.
I'm gonna try to remain calm,
but will you do me a favor
and tell me what is up with you?
My guys are busting their asses
trying to hide Walt's
money from the feds,
and you're tossing
yours out a window?
And I have to hear about
your little act of philanthropy
on the news?
Did you hit your
head or something?
Why didn't you call me the
second you got arrested?
What did you say to Schrader?
Nothing. Jesus. Just chill out.
Chill out? No. No, I
don't chill out right now,
because things
have gone nuclear.
I imagine Schrader shared
with you his recent discovery.
Okay, well, then you get
my complete lack of chill.
[SIGHS]
Just use the money
that I gave you.
No, Saul. Saul,
I... Stop... Saul.
Stop talking. I don't care.
Just... Just make it
happen. Work your magic.
And call me when he's out.
WALT JR.: Hey, Dad, I'm home.
Oh, okay. I'll be right out.
Hey, you going to work today?
You were out late last night.
Huh? I... Well, I, uh...
Yeah, I guess I just
lost track of time.
[PHONE RINGING]
WALT JR.: Dad. Huh?
I'm gonna head out, okay?
Where you going? Uh,
Aunt Marie just called.
She wants me to help her
with some computer thing
and asked me to stay for dinner.
That cool?
Uh, I guess that...
Cool. All right, see you later.
Wait, uh, son?
Junior. Hang on a second. Yeah?
Oh, good. Come on back
inside. What happened?
Oh, this? Nothing.
No, I'm fine. It's fine.
Really. I do wanna
talk to you, though.
Okay. Are you okay?
Yeah. Here. Sit down a second.
I just don't wanna keep
things from you, okay?
I mean, you deserve to
know what's happening.
[SIGHS]
Yesterday, I passed out.
Briefly. Very, very briefly.
And I did this.
Why did you pass out?
Well, my latest scans
show a little shadow on my lung.
But my doctor put me right
on a new round of chemo,
which is why I've
been so tired lately.
But I was pushing
myself too hard.
I know it. I just don't
want you to worry.
I learned my lesson.
Well, um, what's the...?
What now?
What now is that we go
on, like always. Right?
Hey, don't worry
about this, okay?
I know that's hard,
but I beat this once.
There's no reason
to think I won't again.
And my doctor
says I'm doing great.
I'm responding really
well to the treatment.
And I'm feeling very...
Very good about this, all right?
And what would
really help me out
is if we all stayed positive.
Can we do that?
Yeah?
Hm? Okay.
So why don't you go
and help your Aunt Marie,
and we'll talk about this later?
No. No. No way.
I'm staying. I'm not leaving.
[DOOR OPENS]
Flynn is not with
you, is he? No.
No. Why would he be?
How'd it go?
That bad, huh?
How bad are we talking, Hank?
I didn't tell them.
Why not?
It's just not time yet.
No, it's past time.
Way past time. We
talked about this.
You've got to tell them
now. It's gonna be worse
if they find out that
you've kept this from them.
Look, it's just I've got some
things I gotta chase down.
What? What things?
Leads, you know.
What leads? What? Something new?
I'm not keeping anything from
anybody, Marie, okay? Jesus.
Don't tell me how to do my job.
SKYLER: Walt.
Are you sure about this?
It's the only way.
Okay.
[SIGHS]
I'm ready.
[CAMCORDER BEEPS]
My name is Walter
Hartwell White.
I live at 308 Negra Arroyo Lane,
Albuquerque, New Mexico, 87104.
This is my confession.
[CHATTERING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
They're here.
Thank you for coming.
Okay, I'll start.
Skyler and I... WAITER:
Welcome to Garduño's.
My name is Trent. I'll
be taking care of you.
Can I start anybody off with
some beverages? Margarita?
How about some of our
tableside guacamole?
I think we're fine.
We need some time with the menu.
No worries. Be right
back with some water.
So you here to confess?
[SIGHS]
There's nothing to confess.
We're here to talk
about Walter, Jr.
Flynn and Holly should be
living with us. End of story.
And while we
respect your opinion,
we think that your
concern is misplaced.
Skyler and I feel,
due to Marie's attempt
to lure him to your house...
I wasn't trying to lure him.
Regardless of what
you might call it,
Skyler and I would
like to ask you
to please leave our
children out of this.
Junior has been through
a lot already this year.
You are just...
This investigation, Hank,
do you realize what
this will do to him?
Hearing these things?
He's gonna hear it
when I kick in your
front door and arrest you.
If that day ever
comes, so be it.
You have no evidence
to support your claims.
Why tear this family apart?
So how about that guacamole?
We make it right
here at the table.
I'll just give you guys
a few more minutes.
How can you sit
there and listen to this?
All we want is for
those kids to be safe.
You are putting them in
danger, under the same roof as...
They are safe, Marie.
You yourself sent
them out of the house.
And I brought them back.
Look, whatever you think he did,
this is not an
ongoing situation.
WALT: Skyler. No.
They need to
understand. It's in the past.
It's over. There is
nothing to go after here.
There's nothing to accomplish.
MARIE: How can we
believe anything you say?
There's no telling where
the lies begin and end.
That affair of yours,
did that even happen?
WALT: Please. Look,
Junior just found out
that my cancer is back.
He's already facing the idea
of living without his father.
To put this on top of that?
It's just not right.
I swear to God,
you start throwing
the word "right" at me...
What I mean... Was it right
to run a drug empire?
There is no drug
empire. Lying to your son,
to all of us, is that right?
What do I have to do
to make you believe me?
Why don't you
kill yourself, Walt?
SKYLER: What?
MARIE: Just kill yourself.
This whole thing dies with
you. That's what you're saying?
Is that Hank should just let
it go and wait for you to die.
Well, maybe you should
just go ahead and die, then.
That is not a solution.
HANK: No, it's not a solution.
He's not getting off that easy.
SKYLER: Jesus, Hank.
And the same goes for
you if you stick with him.
Both of you think you're just
gonna walk away from this thing?
Never gonna happen.
That is not what we're
saying. Enough with the bullshit.
You're not gonna negotiate
your way out of this thing.
There's only one solution:
Step up, be a man and admit
what you've done. That's it.
There is no other option.
[SIGHS]
Let's go.
WALT: My name is
Walter Hartwell White.
I live at 308 Negra Arroyo Lane,
Albuquerque, New Mexico, 87104.
This is my confession.
If you're watching this tape,
I'm probably dead,
murdered by my
brother-in-law, Hank Schrader.
Hank has been
building a meth empire
for over a year now and
using me as his chemist.
Shortly after my 50th birthday,
he asked that I use
my chemistry knowledge
to cook methamphetamine,
which he would then sell
using connections that he made
through his career with the DEA.
I was astounded. I...
I always thought Hank
was a very moral man
and I was particularly
vulnerable at the time,
something he knew
and took advantage of.
I was reeling from
a cancer diagnosis
that was poised to
bankrupt my family.
Hank took me on a ride-along
and showed me
just how much money
even a small meth
operation could make.
And I was weak.
I didn't want my family
to go into financial ruin,
so I agreed.
Hank had a partner,
a businessman
named Gustavo Fring.
Hank sold me into
servitude to this man,
and when I tried to quit,
Fring threatened my family.
I didn't know where to turn.
Eventually, Hank and
Fring had a falling out,
and things escalated.
Fring was able to arrange...
Uh, I guess...
I guess you call
it a hit on Hank.
It failed, but Hank
was seriously injured
and I wound up
paying his medical bills,
which amounted to
a little over $177,000.
Upon recovery, Hank
was bent on revenge.
Working with a man
named Hector Salamanca,
he plotted to kill Fring.
The bomb that he
used was built by me.
He gave me no option in that.
I have often
contemplated suicide,
but I'm a coward.
I wanted to go to the police,
but I was frightened.
Hank had risen to
become the head
of the Albuquerque DEA.
To keep me in line,
he took my children.
For three months he kept them.
My wife had no idea
of my criminal activities,
was horrified to
learn what I had done.
I was in hell.
I hated myself for what I
had brought upon my family.
Recently, I tried
once again to quit,
and in response,
he gave me this.
I can't take this anymore.
I live in fear every day
that Hank will kill me,
or worse, hurt my family.
All I could think to do
was to make this video
and hope that the world
will finally see this man
for what he really is.
Who do you think
he's shown this to?
No one. It's a threat.
It's what he will do
if I don't back off.
I think you should
show this to Ramey.
Just get ahead of it.
That video is a
bunch of lies, Hank.
Anybody who knows you will know.
A hundred and seventy-seven
thousand dollars?
Hell is he talking about?
Marie?
They told me it was
gambling money.
What was gambling money?
Oh, Jesus Christ, Marie.
Oh, God, no. How was
I supposed to know?
How was I to know
where it came from?
Why were they paying my
bills? What about my insurance?
Insurance wouldn't have
covered the treatment you needed,
and I... I just wanted
the best for you.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I knew that
you would refuse it,
and without it, you may never
have been able to walk again.
Oh, Christ, Marie.
You killed me here.
I mean, it's the...
It's the last nail.
That's the last
nail in the coffin.
What do we do?
If I were you, I'd
be more nervous.
Ugh. Jesus.
It's always the desert.
[SIGHS]
Uh, I already
checked it. It's clean.
I wouldn't have driven
it here if it wasn't.
Get one of these, by the way.
Reads radio
signals. Much easier.
What does he know?
[SIGHS]
I mean, he knows
you're Heisenberg.
But I figure not much else,
otherwise, you know,
you'd be locked up.
What did he say exactly?
He wants me to
inform on you for him.
Tell him everything we did.
Anything else?
I don't think he's told
the rest of the DEA.
Why do you say that?
Just him being
there all by himself,
and, plus, he was
acting kind of shady.
Seemed like he didn't
want the other cops
hearing what he had to say. Mm.
Are we gonna talk
about the rain of caca
the kid brought down upon us?
Want to hazard a guess what
his little charity drive cost you?
Why don't you go
take a walk, Saul?
Jesse, will you let me help you?
I don't like to see
you hurting like this.
Maybe it's time for a change.
What kind of change?
I don't know.
I don't know, maybe...
Maybe it's time
for you to just...
leave all of this behind.
Just get out of town.
Don't look back.
Saul knows a man.
He specializes in giving
people new identities.
He would move you
someplace far away
and set you up with
a whole new life.
Yeah, I know,
sounds a little extreme.
But maybe it's
exactly what you need.
You know, I really think
that would be good for you.
A clean slate.
All right, just think about it.
You get a job,
something legitimate,
something you like.
Meet a girl, start
a family, even.
Hell, you're still so
damn young. Heh.
And what's here
for you now anyway?
[SIGHS]
I tell you, if I could,
I'd trade places.
A whole lifetime ahead of you
with a chance to
hit the reset button.
In a few years,
this might all feel like nothing
more than a bad dream.
Would you just, for once,
stop working me?
What are you talking about?
Can you just stop working me
for, like, 10 seconds straight?
Huh? Stop jerking me around?
Jesse, I am not working you.
Yes. Yes, you are.
All right, just drop the
whole concerned-dad thing
and tell me the truth.
I mean, you're acting like
me leaving town is all about me
and turning over a new leaf,
but it's really... It's
really about you.
I mean, you need me gone,
because your
dickhead brother-in-law
is never gonna let up.
Just say so.
Just ask me for a favor.
Just tell me you don't
give a shit about me,
and it's either this...
It's either this
or you'll kill me the
same way you killed Mike.
I mean, isn't that
what this is all about?
Us meeting way
the hell out here.
In case I say no.
Come on.
Just tell me you need this.
[SOBBING]
Your change.
If you'll hand this to your
car wash professional
and have an A-1 day.
[EASY-LISTENING MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Skyler?
Skyler, I've got my
chemo in about 45 minutes.
Can you take over
the register for me?
Skyler?
It worked,
and we're fine.
Okay?
We're fine.
[SIGHS]
So Palmer and Castanares
are sitting on that jerkoff
Saul Goodman's office,
keeping an eye on Jesse
Pinkman. Yeah, I put them on it.
You wanna explain that to me?
Yeah. Right.
Why the hell should
I know anything?
They're just my guys, after all.
You gotta tell me
what's going on.
Pinkman is A.P.D.'s
problem, not ours.
You got a history with this kid.
If he catches wind
that you're trailing him
and this explodes, he could sue.
Look, if I can't explain this to
Ramey, I gotta pull my guys.
Fine. Take them off.
I said, take them off.
What else you want?
I'm going out for a while.
You have that 3:00.
Will you be back?
You know what, it's gonna
have to be another day.
Reschedule it.
Last chance. You sure there's
nobody you wanna say bye to?
Nobody at all?
No.
This is it. Once I make the
call, there's no take-backs.
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
Uh, I need a new dust filter
for my Hoover Max Extract
Pressure Pro, model 60.
Can you help me with that?
Yeah, pickup.
He's hot. Um, not
"hot" hot, just a little hot.
Currently out on bail.
Yeah, he knows the rules.
One hour. Okay, he'll be there.
And done.
Okay, this guy's fee is 125.
Your benefactor asked me to
send you out with something extra.
Get you started, you know?
Keep you sitting pretty
until you get into the
groove of your new life.
Provided, of course,
you don't toss it out
the window on the way.
Seriously, this
is the last of it,
so you might wanna think
about making a budget.
Whoa, what are you doing?
You can't fire up a doob here.
Put that out.
I mean it. Put it out.
Look, Mr. Natural,
I'm not gonna let you
sabotage this thing.
This guy is not gonna take
you if you show up high,
so stop screwing around,
or it's both our asses.
Right. Well, that's a start.
Now, give with the dope.
[SIGHS]
[SCOFFS]
Christ.
Some people are
immune to good advice.
I'm gonna get a
bag for this cash.
Don't even think
about lighting up again.
Francesca, we got any bags?
For money. Money-sized bags.
Huell will drop you
at the pickup spot,
then he's gonna get
the hell out of there.
You got that?
Guy won't pick up the
kid if he's got company.
You got a phone?
Cops took it.
All right, in case
something goes wrong,
guy doesn't show,
whatever, you give me a call.
Seriously? Hello Kitty?
Seriously, it's free.
We got a beggars-choosers
situation here,
so stop busting my balls.
Corner of Juan Tabo and Osuna.
You, you're gonna sit and wait.
This guy's punctual
with a capital P.
Okay? So don't move.
Don't get up and
get an ice cream.
Just stay put like a good boy.
He'll pick you up, you pay him.
He'll take your ID, he'll
give you a new one.
Goodbye, Jesse Pinkman.
Hello, Mr. Credit to Society.
So do I get to pick where I go?
Well, it's your life. I
imagine you get a say.
Want a suggestion?
How about Florida?
You get a tan, meet
the Swedish bikini team,
you know, swim
with the dolphins.
What about Alaska?
Alaska. Okay, well,
that's a different vibe.
I never figured you
for a moose lover,
but whatever floats
your boat. Alaska.
Alaska's good.
Anywhere you can get a
fresh start is gonna be good.
You ready?
Yeah.
Take care, Jesse.
All right.
HUELL: Excuse me.
[♪♪♪]
Hey, man, you can't go in there!
[LOCK CLICKS]
He a no-show?
Why didn't you call?
Why didn't you...?
[GRUNTING]
Stop! Unh! Code red!
Huell! JESSE: No! Hey!
Hey! Get in here!
[BANGING ON DOOR]
Back off!
You, stay where you are.
What? I don't know what
happened here. What did I do?
You stole it off me.
You and him, you took it
out of my pocket, didn't you?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Calm down. Yes. Okay.
I had Huell lift your dope.
I told you I couldn't risk
the guy not taking you.
No! Before. The cigarettes.
You stole the cigarette.
What? The ricin cigarette!
You had him steal it off of me!
And all for that
asshole Mr. White!
He poisoned Brock!
He poisoned Brock, and
you... You helped him!
Okay, Jesse, calm down.
Say it again!
Tell me one more time
to calm down! Come on!
I'm sorry. Yes. Okay.
I had Huell lift your
cigarette, but Walt made me.
He told me he was helping
you, he was saving you.
I never would've agreed to it
if I'd known what
he was gonna do.
Jesse, you gotta believe
me. I didn't want any of this!
Back up!
[GROANING]
Get off me! What
do I pay you for?
[PHONE DIALING]
Hey, it's me. We
got a big problem.
Eighteen, 19 and 20.
Actually, you gave
me a 5, not a 1.
Oh, I... I did.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
Um, here you go.
Thank you for your honesty.
Oh, and please give this to
your car wash professional.
Have an A-1 day.
[SIGHS] God.
Hey. Hi.
What's going on? Not much.
[SIGHS]
Yeah? Nothing?
Nope. Things are fine.
Good. Why?
Oh, no reason.
You know what I
found the other day
is that the... The... The latch
on the soda machine wasn't...
latching.
It's... It's catching every time
that I stock that darn thing.
So I thought I'd check it out.
Great.
[EASY-LISTENING MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[SKYLER SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
SKYLER: Thank you.
[REGISTER WHIRRING]
Oh. Exact change. I like
that. Thank you very much.
Okay.
And please give this to
your car-care professional
and have an A-1 day.
Thank you. Thank you.
I just remembered they
gave me a prescription
to go pick up, so I forgot.
I'm gonna go head on
over to the drugstore, okay?
Yeah, okay. All right.
[DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTING]