[WHEELS SCRAPING]
BOY: That was nasty, man.
[COUGHS]
[♪♪♪]
[BOYS CHUCKLING IN DISTANCE]
[FLIES BUZZING]
[♪♪♪]
Hello, Carol.
[SQUEEZE'S "IF I DIDN'T LOVE
YOU" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
♪ A soap suds
Stickle back navy ♪
♪ A scrubbing
brush Landing craft ♪
MARIE: She's so cute.
WALT: I know, isn't she?
She takes after her mother.
[CHATTERING]
[WALT LAUGHING]
Well, thank goodness for that.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[CHATTERING CONTINUES]
♪ Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye ♪
SKYLER: Okay, everybody,
since you were so good
and you ate all your
dinner, everybody.
MARIE: Is sweetie hungry? Sweetie,
pumpkin pie, this one's for you.
That one's for you.
[CHATTERING CONTINUES]
♪ Tonight it's
love By the fire ♪
♪ The wind plays
Over the coals ♪
♪ Passionate looks
Are my fancy ♪
[SKYLER LAUGHING]
WALT JR.: She's got a
lot more hair than you do.
MARIE: Yes. You wear
that so well. You do.
SKYLER: Look at what I
have. Special one for you.
MARIE: Oh, my God,
Skyler. I'll take the pink one.
SKYLER: It's a pink one.
MARIE: Oh, Skyler.
SKYLER: I know, right?
Well, actually, they were
my idea. You are all welcome.
MARIE: You are the devil.
SKYLER: Oh, my gosh.
[SKYLER & MARIE LAUGH]
WALT: Hey, buddy.
Ready for a cold one?
No, no.
Not feeling 100 percent.
Oh, I hope it's not
something you ate.
No, no. I just...
We have Pepto, Uncle Hank.
Yeah.
Uh, no, I'm good, I, uh... I
think we need to shove off.
MARIE: Yeah, okay.
Yeah, yeah. Oh. Okay.
MARIE: Sorry,
Skyler, I hate to leave...
SKYLER: No, no. Don't
worry about it. I have help.
And by that, she means
me. MARIE: Ha, ha.
SKYLER: That is correct.
MARIE: Holly can help.
Let's go send them on
their way. SKYLER: Yeah.
WALT: Let's say goodbye
to auntie and uncle.
MARIE: Been too long.
Say, "Bye, auntie."
Bye, sweetie, bye-bye.
You know, it's been about 100
years since we've been bowling.
SKYLER: Then how about Thursday?
MARIE: Oh, that sounds great.
Thank you for having us.
SKYLER: Absolutely.
Take care of him.
Hey. You okay to drive?
Yeah.
All right, well, feel better.
Say, "Bye, Uncle Hank. Bye-bye."
"Bye, Uncle Hank.
Bye, Aunt Marie."
All right, let's get started
on those dishes. Come on.
You. You.
No, you. You.
Washing, okay?
I'll dry. You wash.
SKYLER: You're a good
washer. Hello, Carol.
Oh, hi, Walt.
MARIE: Europe.
I can't believe it. Were you
there when she said that?
Yeah.
You okay? Your stomach okay?
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine. Okay.
God, Jesus, Europe.
I just...
And, you know, where they
were three or four months ago.
She was talking about it
like a second honeymoon.
We need to go to Europe.
We could go. Yeah.
Have it be like a
business trip, you know?
It could, um, be
Italy. To Lake Como...
[♪♪♪]
[MARIE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Hank? Hank?
Hank? You okay?
Hank!
Oh, my God. Hank?
Hank? Hank?
No. Are you okay? I'm good.
MARIE: Call an ambulance!
Call an ambulance!
Okay. You okay?
Just take a breath. Yeah.
Oh, God, sweetie.
HANK: An accident. It happens.
MARIE: I'll make
the appointment.
All you have to do is
show up. HANK: For what?
Three hours in the
emergency room, all for nothing.
All they did was rule
out a heart attack.
What if it happens again?
It won't happen again.
How can you know that?
You can't say what it was.
Marie, baby. I'm okay. I'm
fine, trust me. Discussion over.
And do not tell
Skyler. What? Why?
Just don't.
There's nothing to be
embarrassed about. Hank?
[♪♪♪]
[CHATTERING]
[MAN & WALT SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Luis.
Enrique. Ooh.
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
Hi.
Okay.
SKYLER: Here you go. There's
complimentary coffee inside.
Have an A-1 day.
WALT: Air fresheners
are high-margin, right?
At 30 cents wholesale? Yeah.
Right. So I'm thinking
we reorganize the display.
Separate the food scents
from the nature scents.
I mean, does bubble gum belong
anywhere near ocean spray? No.
And pine is still our
biggest seller, right?
So maybe we move that
over to the cash register,
by the 5-hour Energy drink.
Sure. That'd be
fine. Yeah, yeah.
Come here.
Speaking of the business,
the story comes first.
The story is is that we
are car wash owners,
pure and simple.
But if our story is that
the car wash is successful,
then what do successful
car wash owners do?
They buy more car washes.
Listen.
Skyler, you'll be laundering
that money for years.
Decades.
Wouldn't two be better than one?
Well, there's Gentle
Hands over by Kirtland.
I do love that location.
I'll think about it.
Yeah. Right, right.
To be continued.
Okay.
Good morning. Welcome to A-1.
Just the regular, please.
Well, we're having a
special on hand wax, 21.99
if you're interested in getting
rid of those water spots.
Just the regular is fine.
Okay. Well, there's
complimentary coffee inside
while you're waiting.
Have an A-1 day.
Please give this to your
car wash professional,
and have an A-1 day.
[SMOOTH JAZZ MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[WHISPERING] Sixty-eight
percent. And falling.
Good morning. May I
have your ticket, please?
I knew there would be a
drop in quality, but 68 percent?
This is not what I agreed to.
[WHISPERS] I left a viable
operation. The rest was up to you.
[IN NORMAL VOICE] May
I have your ticket, please?
I'm only asking for a few days,
a week at most.
Call it a tutorial.
That's the standard wash.
Fix this. Get the
ship back on course.
We'll make it worth your while.
That'll be 14.95, please.
Listen, this is a
complicated situation.
There are a lot of moving parts.
None of which are my concern.
You're putting me in a box here.
You know what could happen.
[WHISPERS] Again,
none of my concern.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
There's your change,
and if you'll hand this to
your car wash professional...
And have an A-1 day.
Listen...
It'll only be a few
more minutes.
There's some complimentary
coffee, if you like.
What's up?
Just wondering who
washes a rental car.
Walt, who was that?
She's a former
business associate
who wants me to go back.
And I won't.
[BUZZER BUZZES]
Enrique, this one's finished.
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
Get out of here.
Now.
Excuse me?
Never come back here.
Do you understand me?
I... Go.
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
[CAR PULLS AWAY]
[DOOR OPENS]
MARIE: Hey. Hey.
Oh, thanks.
You going in today?
Uh, no. No, no.
Good. You know,
stay out of there
till you're sure you're better.
Yeah. Stay home, rest,
don't even think
about work. Okay.
All right? I'll see
you later. All right.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Morning, Mrs. Schrader.
Hey, guys. What's going on?
Dropping these off.
Where'd you like them?
Bring them around to
the garage, guys. I got it.
Have a good day.
You too.
Boss, Janice said to tell you
a few of them might
not have indexes.
We could give you a
hand sorting through them.
No, I got it, thanks.
All right.
ARTIE: Well, see you,
boss. HANK: Okay.
Okay, uh...
[JIM WHITE'S "WORDMULE" PLAYING]
♪ Your world is in flames
There ain't even a name ♪
♪ For the feelings you feel
As you watch it all burn ♪
♪ There's a girl in the distance
She's calling your name ♪
♪ But the name
That she's calling ♪
♪ Is not your name ♪
♪ She calls wordmule
Wordmule, wordmule ♪
♪ But it's plowing the
field That wordmule ♪
♪ Wordmule, wordmule ♪
♪ But it's plowing the field ♪
♪ My friends, Look
out for hustlers ♪
♪ For preachers, for shysters ♪
♪ Them silver-tongued saints
That pretend to do good ♪
♪ 'Cause they're geeks
Biting chicken heads off ♪
♪ With their witty rejoinders ♪
♪ They ain't nothing
But greasy fast food ♪
♪ Wordmule ♪
♪ Yeah, wordmule ♪
♪ Some got it Wordmule ♪
♪ It will eat them
live That wordmule ♪
♪ Uh-huh, wordmule
Yuh-huh, wordmule ♪
♪ It's plowing the field ♪
BADGER: Dude, you
are tripping. I'm not dead.
I'm on the starship Enterprise,
macking on Yeoman Rand
while the Andorian
with the disruptor
is back on Talos
IV, or whatever.
PETE: What do you think all
those sparkles and shit are?
Transporters are
breaking you apart, man.
Down to your molecules and
bones. They're making a copy.
That dude who comes
out on the other side?
He's not you.
He's a color Xerox.
So you're telling
me every time Kirk
went into the transporter
he was killing himself?
So over the whole series,
there's, like, 147 Kirks?
At least.
Dude, why do you think McCoy
never likes to beam nowhere?
Because he's a doctor,
bitch. Look it up. It's science.
[REGGAE MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
I ever tell you about
my Star Trek script?
Star Trek script?
Yeah. I gotta
write it down, is all.
The Enterprise is five
parsecs out of Rigel XII.
Nothing's going on.
Neutral zone is quiet.
The crew is bored, so they
put on a pie-eating contest.
The whole crew's in the galley.
They're eating tulaberry pies.
Tulaberry?
Tulaberries, from
Gamma Quadrant, yo.
That's Voyager, dude.
Okay, blueberries, then.
They're eating
blueberry pies Better.
As fast as the replicator
can churn them out:
[MAKING BLEEPING NOISE]
Finally it's down to just
three: Kirk, Spock and Chekov.
Okay, Spock always
wins these things.
How is Spock gonna beat Kirk,
yo? Spock's like a toothbrush.
Look at Kirk. He's
got room to spare.
Spock has total Vulcan
control over his digestion.
You wanna hear this or not?
Yeah. Yeah, go.
Okay. Finally, Kirk,
he can't take it
anymore. He yorks.
Now it's just down
to Chekov and Spock.
But Chekov, you see,
he's got a whole fat stack
of quatloos riding on this,
and he has figured
out a way to win.
He's got Scotty back
in the Transporter Room
locked in on Chekov's stomach.
Every time Chekov eats a pie,
Scotty beams it
right out of him.
Where's he sending
them? The toilet?
Space. Oh!
There's blueberries
just floating out there,
frozen, because it's in space.
And Chekov is just
shoveling them into his mouth
Spock's like, "I can't believe
this Russian is defeating me."
Meanwhile, Scotty's in
the Transporter Room
fiddling with levers when
Lieutenant Uhura comes in.
She's got, you
know, her big pointies,
and Scotty's fingers
are all sweaty.
No. Chekov screams.
He sprays blood
out of his mouth.
Scotty beamed
his guts into space.
No way!
[CHUCKLES]
Hey, man, where you going?
You're missing the best part.
WOMAN: Just fill this
out, bring it back to me.
[HOWE'S "THE BATTLE HYMN OF THE
REPUBLIC" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[MAN COUGHING]
[SIGHS]
[SNORING]
Yo.
Yo!
[SIGHS]
You know you can't
smoke that up in here.
FRANCESCA: Yeah, Jesse
Pinkman's out here smoking pot.
Give me a break, man.
Pinkman. He'll see you now.
SAUL: Woody Harrelson,
live and in person.
Pull up a bong and take a seat.
Hey, I'm kidding about the
bong. Don't be doing that.
Uh, sorry to keep you
on ice out there, kid.
If I'd known it was you...
Well, that Francesca,
I've warned her before.
One more time and
it's back to the DMV.
So, uh, are we on our own today?
Barn door open.
Barn door?
Oh.
So how is the maestro?
Things have been
quiet on this end.
I haven't seen him.
Just as well, probably.
That whole thing
in the jails. I mean,
when they start
to whack lawyers,
that's when I draw the line.
This goes to Kaylee Ehrmantraut
and that goes to
Mr. and Mrs. Albert Sharp.
315 East Pueblo.
It's up in White Horse.
It's 2 and a half
million each. Total of 5.
[LOCK CLICKS]
Mr. and Mrs. who?
Drew Sharp's parents.
Drew Sharp? Uh,
that's the kid on TV?
The missing...? So
but why would you...?
Scratch that. Heh. I don't know,
and I don't wanna know. Uh...
The thing is, what
those folks want
is to know what
happened to their boy.
A sack full of cash
on their doorstep?
That's just gonna
raise more questions.
Kaylee Ehrmantraut?
That's Mike's granddaughter?
So this is Mike's
money? It's mine.
It's your money. Okay.
And you're giving it to
Kaylee Ehrmantraut?
It's what Mike wanted.
So you and Mike, uh,
you've been in touch?
So we're just
talking about charity?
Yeah.
Okay, look, you know, um,
shelling out money to
the ex and her little boy,
I kind of get it.
I mean, kind of.
But this, ha, ha, this
is a bridge too far.
I'm sorry to say, kid,
but you're still gonna be two
miracles short of sainthood.
[CHUCKLES]
Brass tacks. Okay,
my job is to advise,
and my advice is,
come on, already.
Mike left one step
ahead of the boys in blue.
You better believe his
family's on the radar.
A couple million bucks shows
up, they're gonna snatch it.
The feds have already
taken Kaylee's money twice.
What, are you
going for a hat trick?
I'll freaking do
it myself, Saul.
No, no, no! I was
just thinking out loud.
Enough bullshit, Saul. Are
you gonna do this or not?
Yes, yes. Absolutely.
I live to serve.
And, kid, you might
wanna think about
cleaning up a little,
getting some rest.
You've looked
better. Just get it done.
You know who this is?
Don't hang up on me.
Yeah, there's a problem.
There's 5 million of
them here in my office.
No, no, don't.
Just hold on to it.
Yes.
Ye...
Calm down.
I'll handle it.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Déjà vu, huh?
Jesus.
All right, look,
you wanna talk me through this?
What you were thinking?
What you asked Saul
to do. I mean, come on.
It's just nonsensical.
Do you...?
Do you have any
explanation at all?
Blood money. What?
It's like you said.
It's blood money.
I sa...?
Jesus. Okay, yes,
all right. I said that.
I did.
But it was in the
heat of the moment.
I was trying to win an argument.
All right? And I was wrong.
This is your money.
Come on, you've earned it.
Drew Sharp.
That is a terrible
memory, no doubt about it.
But, son,
you need to stop focusing
on the darkness behind you.
The past is the past.
Look, nothing can
change what we've done.
But now that's over.
You're out.
And so am I.
That's right. I'm done.
I've been out for about a month.
But there is nothing
left for us to do
except to try
to live...
ordinary, decent lives.
Why Kaylee Ehrmantraut?
She needs someone
looking after her.
Mike is perfectly capable
of looking after his
own granddaughter.
I don't think so.
I don't think he is capable.
I don't think he's coming back.
What...? What are you saying?
You doing what you did,
offing Mike's guys?
If he was out there,
you'd have to look
over your shoulder
for the rest of your life.
And that's not how you do
things. So I think he's dead,
and I think you know that.
I don't know that.
I don't.
Listen to me.
I did not kill Mike.
The last time that I saw him,
he had his bag, the
one that I brought him.
And he got into his
car, and he drove away.
And for all I know,
he's alive and well.
And if...
If he does come back
and he doesn't understand
why I had to do what I did...
well, then, that's on me.
Jesse?
I need you to believe this.
It's not true. It's just not.
So he's out there?
He's okay?
Yes.
Mike is fine, wherever he is.
We both know that he
can take care of himself.
And he's certainly capable
to provide for his own family.
Okay?
Jesse.
I need you to believe me.
Yeah.
Like you said.
He's alive.
Yeah.
Mike's alive.
[WALT SIGHS]
Absolutely.
SKYLER: You've got
to have a counselor.
Are they bringing
in someone new?
I don't know. Um,
maybe she'll be back.
What if she's not? What
are you supposed to do?
What's Louis gonna do?
He's not worried.
Oh, yeah, sure. What's
there to worry about?
It's only college, right?
Right.
College. Nothing more important.
SKYLER: Oh, you know,
Uncle Hank's still not feeling well,
so bowling's off tomorrow night.
WALT JR.: Really?
SKYLER: Really.
So you're spared a
night out with the family.
You do not have to
look so happy about it.
I'll be right back.
WALT JR.: Um...
So if bowling's off,
can I get a late curfew?
[GRUNTING]
[VOMITING]
[RETCHES]
Are you gonna
turn off the light?
Have you seen Leaves of Grass?
Hm?
My book.
Walt Whitman. Dark
green hardcover.
I didn't even know we had that.
Hm.
You don't think Junior...?
You're kidding, right?
Well,
it'll show up.
What's wrong with Hank? Mm...
It's a stomach bug, sounds like.
He hasn't been to work all week.
[SIGHS]
Well, good night.
Night.
[♪♪♪]
Mister. Can you help me out?
Spare some change?
Hey.
Come back.
Yeah. You. Come here,
I got something for you.
[ZIPPER UNZIPPING]
Here.
Take it.
Go ahead.
Just take it.
[♪♪♪]
Take it.
Yeah.
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTING]
MAN: Anything you want
us to tell Steve Gomez?
Says he's worried about you.
Yeah. Tell him I already
got two grandmas.
Listen, tell everybody
more work and less worry.
ARTIE: Guess we
better hit it. Yeah.
Yeah.
WALT: Hey, guys. SCOTT: Walt.
How are you? WALT:
Good to see you.
SCOTT: How you doing?
WALT: Well, you know, I
can't complain. Heh, heh.
How's your son's arm? I
was thinking about that.
ARTIE: Back to 100
percent. Going to district.
WALT: Gonna be
exciting. This Saturday?
ARTIE: This Saturday morning.
I think first pitch
is at 10 a.m.
Yeah, yeah. It'll be fun.
WALT: Should be a big crowd.
Guys, you're still on
the clock here! Let's go.
ARTIE: See you, Walt.
WALT: See you, Artie.
All right, Scott. Be well.
They're good guys, huh?
Yeah, they're good guys.
Well, it's good to
see you up and about.
Yeah. How are you feeling?
Well, you know.
I've been better, but...
Yeah. Have you...?
Did you get to see
a doctor? I mean,
when one of these things
lasts more than three days,
you really should
get that checked.
Yeah, no, I did, and I'm fine.
I'm, what they say, on
the upswing, you know?
Mm. Good. Good to hear. Yeah.
When I heard you weren't
going in to work, I... Well...
Looks like you have
the work coming to you.
Perks of being the boss, huh?
Eh, you know...
How's, uh...?
How's things at the car wash?
Good. Yeah?
Yeah, really good.
Hey, did you have any
of that potato salad?
I don't know. Maybe. Maybe.
Yeah, I mean, no
one else got sick,
so I probably
shouldn't worry about it.
Well, Skyler will be
very happy to hear
that you're feeling better.
Which reminds me,
I better get back to it.
If there's anything I can do...
Feel better.
[SIGHS]
You know...
you're gonna laugh,
but I have to ask
you about this.
Believe it or not, I
found this on my car.
I mean, it looks just
like the GPS tracker
that we used on
Gus Fring, doesn't it?
Back when we were
tracking him, just the two of us.
You wouldn't know anything
about this, would you, Hank?
You okay?
I gotta say, I
don't like the way
you're looking at me right now.
It was you.
All along, it was you!
You son of a bitch.
You drove into traffic to
keep me from that laundry.
Calm down.
That call I got, telling me
Marie was in the hospital,
that wasn't Pinkman.
You had my cell number.
You killed 10 witnesses
to save your sorry ass.
Listen to me. You
bombed a nursing home.
Heisenberg. Heisenberg.
You lying, two-faced
sack of shit.
Hank.
Look, I don't know where this
is coming from, Hank, but just...
I swear to Christ,
I will put you under the jail.
Take a breath, okay?
Listen to yourself.
These wild accusations,
they could destroy our family.
And for what?
You don't give a
shit about family!
Hank, my cancer is back.
Good.
Rot, you son of a bitch.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
I wanna beat this thing, I do.
I'm back on chemo,
and I am fighting like hell.
But the truth is, in six months,
you won't have
someone to prosecute.
But even...
Even if somehow you were
able to convince anyone
that I was capable
of doing these things,
you and I both know
I would never see
the inside of a jail cell.
I'm a dying man
who runs a car wash.
My right hand to God,
that is all that I am.
What's the point?
Have Skyler bring the kids here.
And then we'll talk.
That is not going to happen.
I don't know who you are.
I don't even know
who I'm talking to.
If that's true...
if you don't know who I am...
then maybe your best course...
would be to tread lightly.
[♪♪♪]