WAITRESS: Here you go.
What happened there?
It's my birthday.
Yeah? Well, happy birthday.
Birthday meals
are free at Denny's.
All you gotta
show is a valid I.D.
I'm good. Thanks.
Really? Free meal. Free is good.
Even if I was, like,
rich, free is always good.
MAN: Thank you. Mmm-hmm.
Okay.
New Hampshire. You're
a long way from home.
How long a drive is that?
About 30 hours, if
all you stop for is gas.
Wow. You headed to California?
No. Here.
Okay.
So, what's here?
Business.
You know, I was in Boston once,
Boston and a little
town called Swampscott,
which is right
outside of Boston.
That's kind of near
New Hampshire, right?
Uh...
Yeah. More or less.
Yeah, I was maybe six,
so I don't really remember it.
I want to say I liked it. They
got this really big aquarium.
Yeah. Great science
museum there.
Excuse me.
Hi. Hi.
My name's Lucy.
I'll be your server.
[PAPER RUSTLING] [DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
I got your word this won't
wind up crossing the border?
It's never leaving town.
Is there a... a manual?
Instruction manual?
I pulled something
off the Internet.
It's in there.
Good luck, I guess.
[COUGHING]
Happy birthday, Mr. Lambert.
[COUGHS]
[CAR ALARM HONKS]
[HONKS]
SKYLER: Jesus,
Walt, the news here...
Gus Fring is dead.
He was blown up along with some
person from some Mexican cartel,
and the DEA has no
idea what to make of it.
Do you know about this?
Walt?
Walt, I need you to...
WALTER: It's over.
We're safe.
Was this you?
What happened?
I won.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[KEYS JINGLE]
Oh, God.
[DOOR OPENS] WALTER, JR.: Dad.
Dad. Hey.
[LAUGHING] Hey.
Serious... You don't have
the TV on? Seriously?
Uh, no, sorry, I... No...
You didn't tell him
about Mr. Fring?
Um, he knows.
I...
Welcome home.
Jesus, Dad, it...
It's all they're talking about.
They... They haven't
said it on TV yet,
but Uncle Hank says he was
this, major, major drug dealer.
I mean, like, holy shit.
Your uncle is safe, right?
How do they know that?
Uncle Hank was
after this guy all along.
He didn't tell us, but he was.
He even took me to
his restaurant one time,
just, like, totally
toying with the guy,
just like "I got my
eye on you," like that.
They figure
Mr. Fring was the one
who put the hit
out on Uncle Hank.
Just somebody got to him first.
Wow. Yeah, wow.
Aunt Marie's still
pretty freaked.
She didn't want us to leave,
but Mom figured it was time.
Huh.
There's still some
agents over there,
but they figure it's over.
Like, when this hits the news,
Uncle Hank is
going to be a hero.
Yeah.
I mean, even more
so than before.
Seriously. [TURNS ON TV]
See... See if it's on TV.
Yeah, yeah, I want to.
Just... Just give me a
couple minutes, huh?
[TV PLAYING]
[HOLLY COOS]
Hi.
Hi, sweet pea.
Oh, Daddy missed you so much.
Yes, he did.
I know. I missed you, too.
Well, don't you think I
rate a "hello," at least?
Hello.
Hello to you, too.
So, are you gonna
talk to me here?
Are you gonna...
You gonna show some kind of...
I don't know... Some
kind of mild relief
that I'm alive?
I am relieved, Walt.
And scared.
Scared?
Scared of what?
You.
[HOLLY COOS]
Hey.
[COOING]
Hi.
Hmm.
[EXHALES]
Oh, shit.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
Jesus, just say it already.
Tell me "I told you so."
Get it out of your system
before you need, like,
dialysis or something.
It's exactly like
Boetticher's drawings.
Where were the two bodies?
Over by the freight
elevator. Over there.
No idea who they were?
Nah, not much left.
Apparently, the teeth
do this popcorn thing
when they get too
hot, so they tell me.
Whoever torched
it did it up right.
Fring, you magnificent bastard.
[CHUCKLES]
Huh. What do you
figure that was?
I don't know. Some
kind of lab equipment?
Maybe a camera?
Come on. Be nice. Just be nice.
Come on. Hey. Hey!
You be nice. Just be nice.
Let Wendell in there.
If Wendell doesn't
eat, nobody eats.
Yeah.
[MAN SPEAKING SPANISH]
[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
It's Gustavo.
He's dead.
[HORN HONKS]
[BRAKES SCREECH]
Son of a bitch.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Hold up! Hold up!
Get out of my way, kid.
Mike, wait a minute,
all right? Let him talk.
"Let him talk." I am done
listening to this asshole talk.
Now, get out of my way.
He's got something you
need to hear, all right?
What did you do, Jesse?
Do you even know?
Do you even know
what you've done?
Yeah, he saved his own
life is what he's done.
One more word...
Mike. Mike.
If you kill him, you're
going to have to kill me.
Come on.
Oh, Jesse.
Jesus.
What is it with you guys?
Honest to God.
May I?
Look, whatever differences
you and I have, they'll keep.
Right now we've
got bigger fish to fry.
Bigger fish.
The video cameras.
Gus kept cameras
on us at the lab,
at the laundry, God
only knows where else.
And, of course, when I say "us,"
I'm including you.
Mike.
Mike, if he taped
all that shit...
Us cooking, you picking up...
If Gus had a record of that and
the police get to it before we do...
You son of a bitch.
Mike, it's all on
tape somewhere,
or a hard drive.
Where?
Where did he keep it?
He had a laptop in his office.
Kept it in the back
of the restaurant.
It all fed straight to there.
What?
Keys, scumbag.
It's the universal
symbol for keys.
MIKE: Meter fraud.
Yes, yes, it's a big deal.
Guy rigs his meter so
he's paying two cents less
for first-class postage.
I'm here to tell you
that the USPS takes
that very seriously.
It's money out of your pocket.
It's money out of my pocket.
I was hoping...
Now, look, sarge.
Do you think we could
work together on this thing?
Do you folks have it over there?
Could you tell
me that, at least?
Yeah.
Well, thanks for your help.
Uh, Inspector Clark...
Inspector Dave Clark,
like the Dave Clark Five?
Oh, before your time.
Well, you feel free to call
me day or night at this number.
Yes, sir. No, you as well.
Mmm-hmm. Thank you.
Oh, yeah.
We're boned. [CELL PHONE SNAPS]
Well...
You know how they say,
"It's been a pleasure"?
It hasn't.
Are you going to tell
us about the laptop?
Where you going? I'm gettin'
the hell out of dodge, kid,
and so should you.
It's just a matter of time.
Mike, where is the laptop?
What the hell
difference does it make?
They got it. End of story.
[SCOFFS]
APD, Northwest Area
Command, on 2nd.
They tagged it, they filed it,
it's in the system,
and they locked it in
their evidence room.
All right.
All right. So...
Describe the building.
[CHUCKLES] Describe the...
How about I describe Fort Knox?
And what are you going to do?
Are you going to put
on your black leotard
and go dangling
on a clothes line?
It's a building full of cops.
What else do you need to know?
And why in the hell
am I talking to you?
Mike, we gotta do something.
I am doing something.
He's good with this stuff.
Just give him a chance.
Now, you look.
That laptop might as
well be on the Moon.
They build these evidence rooms
like bank vaults
because guess what.
Lunatics like you
want to break into them.
But unlike a bank vault,
this is a place that is
guarded 24 hours a day
by the police.
There's no way you're
getting it out of there.
Who said that we have
to get it out of there?
We just need to
destroy what's on it.
Oh, so now you want to
blow up a police station.
I don't believe I said that, no.
Nursing home full of old
folks just whet your appetite.
Now you want to
kill a bunch of cops.
I never said anything
about killing anybody.
I am, however, considering
the possibility of a device.
A device. Yes, a small device.
Say this device gets
filed into evidence.
Now, it is inside that room.
What about a magnet?
You want to commit
a whole other crime
just to get this bomb
of yours into evidence.
Who said bomb? I said a device.
Yo, what about, like, a
magnet? An incendiary device.
One quick fire is
all it would take.
You don't think they
have fire suppression?
I'm not talking
about sprinklers.
I'm talking about Halon,
because Halon doesn't
destroy evidence.
A magnet, though, maybe
like... All right, so a bomb, then.
Maybe we plant a bomb outside.
Oh, actually I knew a
crew out of Fort Worth
that tried to blow up an
evidence room from outside.
About all they did was
take out a couple of hedges.
You are probably talking about
2 feet of reinforced concrete.
Or what about a magnet?
What magnet? What about it?
You know, just a... [WHOOSHES]
[SMACKS]
[POPS]
WALTER: So what do you think?
Expensive.
Leaving aside engineering,
rigging some kind of
alternate power source,
my primary sticking point
is I actually need the thing.
As you gentlemen can
see, it's paying the bills.
But I mean it's
feasible, doable?
Hey, we're living in a time
of, uh, string theories
and God particles.
Feasible, doable?
Yeah, sure, why not?
Expensive.
What would you put it in?
What about that? Does it run?
We can get it running.
What's the box made of?
Plywood and aluminum,
just what you need.
All right, so you
want to talk money?
Step into my office.
WALTER: Hey, listen. Um...
I don't actually have
any money right now.
My wife... There's
an IRS issue anyway.
I'd appreciate it if you
could spot me my share.
I'll pay you back.
Yeah. Whatever.
Right.
You coming?
If you have any brains,
you'll take that money you saved
and you'll skip town...
Today. Right now.
You don't think this can work?
Is that a serious question?
Mike, this is a three-man job.
The only way I know
it won't work for sure
is if we don't have you.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR] [GASPS]
[SIGHS] Come in.
[WHISPERING] Oh. Get in.
Close the door.
[NORMAL VOICE] What did
we say about you coming here?
Yeah, speaking of things
that tend to rile you up,
uh, the police, they may call.
Let me... Let me
back up a little.
Can I... Can I sit down?
I'm going to sit down.
Okay, why are the
police going to call?
May call you. Distant,
outside possibility,
but on the off-chance, I want
you thinking one thought...
Hogan's Heroes.
Sergeant Schultz. Do you
remember Sergeant Schultz?
"I know nothing. I see nothing."
Do you remember how
he... I want you like that.
Okay, Saul, why
are the police...
There was an incident
with Beneke, with the, uh...
Oh, God.
And it's... Oh,
Jesus. What incident?
An act of God. [CHUCKLES]
There's no right.
There's no wrong.
I mean, it just...
That's the best phrase.
It fits, but we got a problem.
Ted's dead.
Sorry?
Ted is dead?
No. No, no.
He just woke up.
OLD JOE: Right-o,
that should do 'er.
All right, watches off.
Necklaces, earrings,
rings, bracelets...
Gold. These are non-ferrous.
Better hope.
What about that stuff
you young guys wear
on the end or your pricks?
Speak now or
forever sing soprano.
What's up with that, by the way?
Why would anybody
wanna put a metal ring
through the end of their prick?
What are you looking at me for?
All right, uh, guns, knives,
tools, keys, plates
in your head,
artificial hips.
Check your pockets for
me one more time, please.
Oh, uh, credit cards.
You want that plastic
working come Miller time.
You know, I can foresee a lot of
possible outcomes to this thing,
and not a single one of
them involves Miller time.
P.M.A.
Positive Mental Attitude.
Uh, okay, I think
we're good to go.
All right, where do
you want me with this?
Start 40 feet out.
That's more than
the length of the room.
Who's doing the honors? Me.
Flip that switch, turns it on.
Twist this here. That's
your power control.
All right. Everybody ready?
Yeah. Okay.
Fire in the hole!
WALTER: All right, you ready?
[CLICKS]
[LOW HUMMING]
[CLUNKS]
Fingers crossed it don't yank
the drive shaft through the floor.
[HUMMING CONTINUES]
Anything?
No. Still working.
All right, start
walking forward slowly.
[HUMMING INCREASES]
Whoa. Whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Yeah. That did it.
Yes.
Whoa.
[HUMMING STOPS]
Yeah, bitch!
Magnets! Oh!
How many batteries is this?
That there's 21,
wired in series,
so 21 times 12, 252 volts.
Can you add 21
more, wired in parallel?
Up the amperage?
Everything goes flying
in that evidence room,
it's gonna make
one hell of a noise,
and there goes your
element of surprise.
Won't matter.
Sixty seconds, we'll be gone.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[HEART MONITOR BEEPING]
Um, excuse me.
Hi. Who are you looking for?
Um, Ted Beneke.
I'm a friend of his.
But if it's not a
good time, I could...
No, no, no, this is fine.
I'm just finishing up.
Come on in.
[GASPS]
Hey, Ted.
NURSE: I tell you,
he's been a real champ.
His color's better, and
his blood pressure's up.
We are going to have you
eating solid food in a day or two.
I bet you money.
That's wonderful.
All right, I'm just
down the hall.
Ted.
Can you hear me?
Yes.
Ted, I just...
I don't even know...
Skyler...
I haven't said anything...
to anyone.
I told them it was an accident.
I tripped and fell.
That is all they know.
I just...
I've... I've got children.
Family.
I swear to you.
Please.
I just...
I will never breathe
one word of this.
Good.
[ENGINE STARTS]
It should be about a quarter
of the way down on the left.
We'll do a loop and come
around the other side.
Turn here.
Right up there.
That's the wall.
Oh, what the hell is this?
There's some big-ass
hump in the way.
So just drive over it.
All right. Come
on, you can do it.
Take it easy. Take it easy.
You got it.
[RATTLES]
WALTER: Cut it.
It's, like, 8 feet away.
Is this cool? Is
this close enough?
It'll work.
[HUMMING]
[SOFT HUMMING]
[HUMMING CONTINUES]
[OBJECT CLINKING]
[RUSTLING]
[HUMMING CONTINUES]
[OBJECTS CRASHING]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[ALARM BLARING]
Mr. White, let's go.
Hang on.
Let's just go! Hang on.
Mr. White, let's
get out of here.
Just one minute.
[GRUNTING]
[HUMMING CONTINUES]
[GRUNTING] Turn
it off! Turn it off.
[CLICKS] [HUMMING STOPS]
OFFICER: Jacocks, you okay?
Outside! Outside!
JESSE: Oh!
Yes! Bitch!
Shut up. Oh. Yeah.
What exactly are
you celebrating?
You left the truck behind.
WALTER: So what?
So what?
So what if they find prints?
And what if they trace it
back to the wrecking yard?
They won't.
There's no prints.
I made sure of that.
There's no paperwork
on the truck,
the magnet, or the batteries.
Untraceable salvage, all of it.
I made sure of that, too.
Well, you got all the answers,
so you tell me, Answer Man,
did all that even work just now?
Yes. It worked.
I'm supposed to
take that on faith?
Yeah?
Why?
How do we know?
Because I say so.
[CAMERA CLICKING]
07-66-26432.
Gutierrez, Alvin B.
Roofing hammer.
Undamaged. Bag still sealed.
11-58-73321.
Fring, Gustavo.
Samsung laptop computer.
Damaged. Glass screen
is broken and in pieces.
Bag still sealed.
11-58-73317.
Fring, Gustavo.
Framed photograph of two men.
[GLASS RATTLES] Damaged.
The glass is broken,
and photo has
slipped out of its frame.
Bag appears to be slightly
punctured by broken glass.
Hmm. Check it out.
That's not on the manifest.
SAUL: All right, so first off,
I'm not a marriage counselor.
Nor do I take
sides in this thing.
And, not taking sides, mind you,
but you did put her in
charge of your money,
which I advised
against, if you'll recall,
all of which is not to be
construed as an "I told you so."
I'm just walking you
through my mental process,
so to speak.
So, she comes to
me with a problem.
She's been cooking
Beneke's books,
he's in Dutch with the IRS,
and once they audit,
it's rio de caca for
the both of them,
to which I say, "Hey, let's
involve Walt in this discussion,"
to which she says, "No,
let's cut Beneke a check
"so's he can pay off the IRS."
Again, not taking sides,
but she really was
trying to protect you.
A little feedback
here might be nice.
"Let's involve Walt
in this discussion."
Yeah, that's what I told her.
She said no.
And you didn't argue the point.
You didn't think to contact me.
You were a tad preoccupied
at the time, if you'll recall.
Okay. So, you
took it upon yourself
to give away
$622,000 of my money
to a man who had been
sleeping with my wife.
[SIGHS] She's my
client, same as you.
Does this arrangement
get a little tricky at times?
Absolutely.
But I try my best, you
know, ethically, in my duty...
Ethically?
I'm sorry. I must
be hearing things.
Did you actually just use the
word "ethically" in a sentence?
You're not Clarence
Darrow, Saul.
You're a two-bit
bus-bench lawyer,
and you work for me.
Yeah, well, Clarence Darrow
never had a client like you
ask him for something...
Like this.
Okay? Yeah, I put my
ass on the line for you.
Huell, too. Huh?
He's got fingers like hotdogs.
He could've easily
busted this in two
and killed everyone in the
office, but do I complain?
No. Beg, borrow, or
steal, I'm your huckleberry.
I go the extra mile.
Only you never told me that
kid would wind up in the hospital.
You know...
Take that thing and
get the hell out of here.
You and me, we're done.
What are you...
Come on. Hey.
Hey.
We're done when
I say we're done.
SKYLER: [CHUCKLING]
Yes, you are...
[HOLLY SQUEAKS]
Hey.
I heard what happened to Ted.
He's not going to talk.
Yeah.
I forgive you.