[GARAGE DOOR WHIRRING]
You can come on out.
It's an actual store. ED: Mm-hm.
I guess I figured
"vacuum cleaner repair"
was a term of art.
If you would step right
here on this blue spot.
Leave your luggage
where it is for the moment.
[SIGHS]
That good?
Sure. What about this?
I'll Photoshop that out.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Oh, Nebraska.
What's in Nebraska?
You. From now on.
It's gonna take me some time
to get your new situation fixed.
Until then, you're
gonna be staying here.
I got a place
downstairs, out of sight.
It's not the Ritz-Carlton,
but it's comfortable
enough for short-term.
How short-term?
Considering you got
your face up on buses
and billboards all over town,
I'm thinking, uh, two days.
Maybe three.
Only thing is,
and I don't like to do this,
but, uh, you'll
have a bunk mate.
Oh, yeah? He's still here?
For the moment.
He's a special case.
Gonna take some doing.
How's he holding up?
You be the judge.
[♪♪♪]
RAMEY: We will find Hank.
Steve too.
They're out there, and
we're gonna find them.
You have my word.
Sir.
[♪♪♪]
RAMEY: Call it in, get
her out of here. Move.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[♪♪♪]
JESSE [ON VIDEO]:
I, uh, get to his door,
and I could hear music inside.
Like squeaky voices.
And I thought, you
know, maybe, uh...
[SNIFFLING]
I knocked on his door.
The music stopped, and
then he was right there.
When he saw the
gun, he thought...
Hey, Kenny.
Does this pussy cry
through the entire thing?
[ALL LAUGHING]
Just watch.
JESSE: He kept saying that, you
know, "You don't have to do this."
His eyes were so big.
[VIDEO FAST-FORWARDING]
Such a bitch. They high-fived
He won't quit.
Because it worked.
Then, you know, we turn around,
and there is this
kid on a dirt bike
looking at us.
Drew Sharp.
That kid that went
missing up in White Horse.
It's him.
And then out of nowhere,
Todd, that Opie,
dead-eyed piece of shit,
pulls out a gun
and shoots the kid.
HANK: This is Todd
Alquist we're talking about?
He killed Drew Sharp?
Boom. Like it was nothing.
[VIDEO PLAYER BEEPS]
TODD: Hey, Uncle Jack. Hold up.
We should keep him for a while,
get a couple of
cooks under our belt.
You seriously giving me this
turn-the-other-cheek crap?
He ratted you out, personally.
We still got 600
gallons of methylamine.
Meth? Who gives
a shit about meth?
We won the lottery here.
We've got all the
money in the world.
You're talking to me
about selling crank?
I mean, this is
millions, Uncle Jack.
No matter how much you got,
how do you turn your back on more?
You little...
son of a bitch.
[LAUGHING]
It's that Lydia woman.
You're sweet on her, you
little bastard. Ha, ha, ha.
Hey, Kenny, you believe this?
Hey, it's all about
this right here, huh?
[MEN LAUGHING]
Come on.
You can do better.
That one's so uptight,
probably got a wood
chipper for a coochie.
Stick it in down there,
you're pulling back a stump.
[MEN LAUGHING]
Aw, what the hell.
Heart wants what
the heart wants, right?
Let's go back and watch some
more of that crybaby rat, huh?
[MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[♪♪♪]
[MEN CONTINUE SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY IN DISTANCE]
[DOOR CLOSES IN DISTANCE]
[♪♪♪]
How thick is it?
This is mild steel?
Uh-huh.
No, this would be cash.
What?
Nothing.
Hey, you know what?
Make yourself useful.
Give me a list of
hitters, mercenaries.
Yes, yes, I remember.
You've got "concerns."
Don't worry. We'll take
the time to vet them.
Make sure there are no
undercover cops on the team.
Five should do it,
providing they're the
right men for the job.
I'm gonna hate
myself for asking,
but who are we hitting?
Jack Welker and his men.
They murdered Hank.
They stole my life's work.
I don't know any hit men.
You know a guy who knows a guy.
Just get me the contacts.
Anybody in that world.
I'm paying top
dollar. We'll find them.
You mind if I give you a
nickel's worth of advice?
Just for old time's sake?
You're worried about
your wife and kids?
Don't leave.
The way things are now, some
people... Not me, mind you,
but some people might say
you're leaving her high and dry.
Some people would
be ignorant on the facts.
Some people wouldn't know
that as far as the
police are concerned,
Skyler is a blameless victim.
[SCOFFS]
No, no, no. Go ahead.
Get it off your chest.
Go on.
The phone call was a
smart move. Kudos to you.
Odds are it was recorded.
It'll play great for a jury.
It might even
buy her a mistrial.
In a year and a half.
Until then, if they don't
have you, they go after her.
There's no point.
She knows nothing.
Well, too bad. She's
got nothing to trade.
I hate to be a downer here,
but there are two
DEA agents missing,
presumed dead.
Think the feds will let that go
because you hit
the ejector seat?
First thing they're gonna do,
they will RICO your wife
and kids out of the house.
That condo is gone.
Your bank accounts,
they're frozen.
Her picture is probably on
TV right now, next to yours.
Who's gonna hire her?
Money is no problem.
Well, I don't mean
to contradict you,
but getting it to
her, impossible.
The feds are praying
that you'll make contact.
The Internet, the
phone, it's all tapped.
Hey, Mike was no dummy.
But every time he
tried to get his nest egg
to his granddaughter,
it ended up in
Uncle Sam's pockets.
So you propose what?
Stay. Face the music.
I mean, how much
time have you got left?
You walk in with
your head held high,
be the John Dillinger of the
Metropolitan Detention Center.
How bad is that?
And you bring a barrel
full of drug money.
Maybe that soothes
some troubled waters.
Maybe they let your
family stay in the house.
After all, the house predates
the criminal enterprise.
God, you think I want to run?!
This is the last
thing that I want.
This... This changes nothing.
What I do, I do for my family.
My money goes to my children.
Not just this barrel. All of it!
I'm going to kill Jack
and his entire crew,
and I'm gonna take
back what is mine
and give it to my children.
And then, and only then...
am I through.
Do you understand?
Everything good?
Define "good."
You're set. Time to go.
You'll be a little longer.
I'm still working
on transportation.
Change of plans.
He's coming with me.
No. No, that's not...
We're going together.
I can use him.
I'll give you two a minute.
Hey, I'm a civilian. I'm
not your lawyer anymore.
I'm nobody's lawyer.
The fun is over.
From here on out,
I'm Mr. Low-Profile.
A douche bag with a job
and three pairs of Dockers.
If I'm lucky, month from
now, best-case scenario,
I'm managing a
Cinnabon in Omaha.
You're still part of this,
whether you like it or not.
Sorry. I don't think so.
You remember what I told you?
It's not over until...
[COUGHING]
[CONTINUES COUGHING]
[GASPING]
It's over.
[COUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
MAN 1: Do you want us to cuff her
now? Would that make you feel better?
MAN 2: Your client admits to...
[MAN 1 SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
MAN 1: Her day
of reckoning is now.
[SPEAKING IN DISTORTED VOICE]
MAN 1: by the time
this goes to trial.
Is she even listening?
Mrs. White?
Are you following all this?
Do you understand
what's happening here?
Yes.
I understand.
I understand I'm
in terrible trouble.
I understand that you will
use everything in your power
against me and
my children unless...
Unless I give you Walt.
But the truth is, I can't
give you what you want.
I don't know where he is.
[SIGHS]
All right, go and discuss
this with your lawyer here.
Rack your brain.
And hope you can come up
with something we can use.
[SLURPING]
WOMAN [OVER
RADIO]: Four-seventeen?
Four-seventeen. No activity.
[HOLLY CRYING]
[HOLLY CONTINUES CRYING]
[SKYLER GASPS THEN GRUNTS]
[SKYLER WHIMPERING]
[♪♪♪]
Ma'am, is there anybody
else in the house?
What about your son?
If I go look in his room,
am I gonna see him?
He's not gonna pop
out and surprise me?
If this guy takes his hand
away, are you gonna scream?
He's at his friend's house.
He's been there all week.
Please, please, don't
hurt my baby. Please...
TODD: Ma'am.
Please.
We got a lot of respect
for your husband.
There's just something
that we gotta straighten out.
Okay, we know that you've
been talking to the police,
and that's okay.
You gotta do that.
But you've seen some people.
Like that lady who
came into the car wash.
The one with the black hair.
You said anything about her?
No.
You sure about that?
I didn't.
The police don't need to
know anything about her.
Okay, ma'am, I'm
gonna need you to say it.
I will not
say anything about her. Ever.
I swear.
Okay.
When we leave, you're
not gonna go running
to those police
officers out front?
No.
Okay.
Because you really don't
want us coming back.
[♪♪♪]
[HOLLY CRYING]
[SKYLER PANTING]
[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[CHATTERING]
WOMAN: Uh-huh. Sure.
Don't. Stay where you are.
We'll talk like this.
Okay.
So that thing that
we talked about,
I went to Mr. and
Mrs. White's house...
You don't have to say the name.
Sure. And it went really good.
I mean, the message was
received loud and clear.
The message? Yeah.
Look, I know you did
your best. I just think...
Hi. What can I get you?
Chamomile tea
with soy milk, please.
And I'll need more stevia. Sure.
The person we're
discussing saw my face.
You're not Western Union.
We can't just settle for
you sending messages.
Really, if you'd been there,
I think you'd see it different.
We threw a real scare into her.
She seems like a nice lady
watching out for her kids.
So you're not going to
have a problem with her.
I can pretty much guarantee it.
I wish I had your certainty,
but I'm not like
you and your uncle.
I'm just... I'm not
used to this kind of risk.
We're gonna have
to take a break.
I have 50 pounds
vacuum-packed and ready to go.
And I wish you all the
luck in the world with it.
It's 92 percent.
I'm sorry?
Ninety-two percent.
Truly? Tested it twice.
And it's blue, just like before.
Ninety-two. That's
Heisenberg level.
He's not with you?
Well, next best thing. Pinkman.
They're looking for Pinkman.
Well, they're not
going to find him.
He's with us, and he's
not going anywhere.
Ms. Quayle, this is
what your guys in Europe
have been begging for, right?
I just think we
work together good.
We make a good team.
I think it's kind of
mutually good.
Ninety-two percent.
[GROANS]
Unh.
[GRUNTING]
Mr. Lambert, welcome
to New Hampshire.
All right.
Let's have a look at this place.
You got about a month's
worth of food on hand.
Most of it is canned goods,
but there's steaks
in the freezer.
You got a generator
outside, works on LP.
Ought to be enough in
the tank to last the winter.
It's only 15 amps,
but that ought to
do for the lights,
the TV and the freezer.
That's a wood-burner.
Ought to warm the
place up pretty good.
Plus you can cook on it.
On the TV front, the
reception's pretty much nil.
You got some
mountains in the way.
Weather is right, you might
be able to catch Montreal,
but mostly you'll
be limited to DVDs.
Mr. Magorium's Wonder Emporium.
Two copies. Hm.
I'm not much of a movie guy.
I'll make a supply
run next month.
You want something else
to watch, put it on the list.
Supply run. Heh.
Fifty thousand dollars
for a trip to Costco.
It's risk. And risk is what
you're paying me for,
not toilet paper.
Risk and a 4400-mile round trip.
Mr. Lambert,
my clients and I
don't usually have
an ongoing relationship.
Normally you and I would have
already gone our separate ways,
but you're you.
Where's the phone? No phone.
Up here, ice storms
equal service calls,
equal you in cuffs.
Internet? Same deal.
Also satellite, cable
TV, drop phone, car.
You want news, I'll bring
the Albuquerque papers.
Whatever you need,
just put it on the list.
Put it on the list. Yeah.
Look, I have
business to conduct.
Your business is your business.
My business is keeping
you out of custody.
You are the target of
a nation-wide manhunt.
Your face is all over TV.
You are the hottest client
I have ever had, by far.
It stands to reason you've
got to keep out of sight.
And what's keeping me
from walking out that gate?
Nothing.
There's a little one-horse
town eight miles down the hill.
There's not a thing
on God's green earth
that I can do to stop
you going down there.
All I'm saying is...
if you leave this place,
you will get caught.
And I gotta tell you,
if I find out that you've
left the reservation,
I won't be coming back.
That is for my own
safety. You understand?
Sure.
Know how to work the stove?
The flue can be
tricky. Yeah, I got it.
You paid good money for this.
You got two acres up here,
lots of woods, nice, warm place.
Seems to me just the spot
for a man to rest up
and think on things.
If you look around,
it's kind of beautiful.
You've been very
helpful. Thank you.
See you in a month.
[♪♪♪]
[WALT COUGHING]
Tomorrow.
Oh. Huh.
[JESSE GRUNTING]
Come...
[GRUNTING]
KENNY: Oh, so you're just too
good to eat with the rest of us, huh?
TODD: It's not for me.
KENNY: Damn, man, seriously.
KENNY: That's not
my chocolate chip, is it?
You're gonna spoil him.
TODD: Hey, you awake?
Uh, yeah.
We had some Ben & Jerry's.
There's peanut butter
cup and AmeriCone Dream.
I didn't know what you liked,
so I got you some of each.
There you go.
So that batch that you
just cooked was 96 percent.
Kind of figured you
deserved a little something.
Thanks.
Well, better get some sleep.
Tomorrow's gonna be a big day.
Got a whole new batch.
Hey, Todd. Yeah?
Would you mind leaving
the tarp off tonight?
Well, might get cold.
No, I don't mind. I just...
I just wanna see the stars.
Sure. Okay.
Thanks.
Well, good night, Jesse.
Night.
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTING]
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay.
[GRUNTING]
Come on, bitch.
[♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
Go ahead! Do it!
Just kill me now and get it over
with, because there's no way
I'm doing one more
cook for you psycho fucks!
[DOORBELL RINGS]
ANDREA: Yes?
Hi, ma'am. How
you doing tonight?
You're Andrea, right?
How can I help you?
You know Jesse Pinkman?
Right? Well, I'm
a friend of his.
My name's Todd.
I'm sorry to bother you so
late, but it's nice to meet you.
How is Jesse? Is he okay?
Yeah, he's okay.
Actually, I brought him with me.
Jesse's here?
Yeah, he's right over
there in that truck.
ANDREA: Where?
[MUFFLED SCREAM]
No!
Just so you know,
this isn't personal.
[SILENCED GUNSHOT]
No!
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
[SOBBING]
Whoa, hey, settle down.
Settle down.
Hey, remember.
There's still the kid.
[PANTING]
[GASPS]
[WALT COUGHING]
I brought you a couple
of cases of Ensure.
Maybe put a little
weight on you.
Jesus.
I can barely read this.
Ah. Almost forgot.
Without a prescription, I
had to take an educated guess
and shotgun it.
One of these
ought to come close.
Oh.
Did you check on them?
Is Skyler in a better place?
No, she's still at that
place off of Eubank.
Kids are both still with
her for the moment.
There's no court date yet.
The news was talking
about a grand jury,
but they didn't say when.
I saw her public defender on TV.
Looks like a deer
in the headlights.
Think I got socks
older than him.
What are they doing for money?
She's doing taxi
dispatch, part-time.
Leaves the baby with a
neighbor when she goes in.
I saw her shopping one time.
She looks pretty good.
And she's using her maiden name.
I wouldn't take that personally,
under the circumstances.
Those working for you?
Yeah, yeah.
I took a run by your old house.
The auction's still pending.
They put a fence up around it.
They put up a fence?
Seems like the place got to
be kind of a tourist attraction.
Kids breaking in.
The neighbors complained,
so the bank put up a fence.
You ready? Hm?
Yeah.
ED: Sorry about last time.
It should go better now.
I watched a couple
of YouTube videos.
It's all about finding the vein.
Give it to me. I'll do it.
Here, you do it.
Make a fist. Tight. There we go.
All right, it's just...
Stick.
That's it. Okay. Hey.
Pretty good. There you go.
Think I had worse
my last physical.
I will see you on...
Let's see.
Afternoon of the 15th.
Stay a little longer?
Yeah, I got a long
trip ahead of me.
Two hours?
I'll give you another $10,000.
Please.
Ten thousand.
One hour.
Cards?
[DRAWER OPENS AND CLOSES]
All right, well...
The game will be seven-card.
I'll deal, since you
are encumbered.
One of these days,
when you come up here,
I'll be dead.
My money over there.
What happens to it then?
What if I ask you to
give it to my family?
Would you do it?
If I said yes...
would you believe me?
You wanna cut the cards?
No.
A king.
Two kings.
[WIND WHISTLING]
[FIRE CRACKLING]
[COUGHING]
[RING CLINKING]
[GRUNTING]
[COUGHING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[PA BEEPS]
WOMAN [OVER PA]: Flynn
White to the principal's office, please.
I'm sorry to pull
you out of class.
It's your aunt Marie.
It sounds very important.
You can take it in here, okay?
Okay.
Here he is.
Thank you.
Hey, Aunt Marie.
What's...? What's going on?
Hold on a sec, honey.
ANNOUNCER [ON TV]: Look
at those numbers for Denver.
Things haven't gone their way.
Son, it's me.
Please, don't let on.
Carmen is nearby,
right? She cannot know.
Son, are you there?
Yes.
It's so good to hear your voice.
I, uh...
Son, the things
that they're saying
about me.
I did wrong. I made
some terrible mistakes.
But the reasons were always...
Things happened
that I never intended.
I never intended...
[WALT SNIFFLING OVER PHONE]
Listen, son, we
don't have much time.
Is Louis' family still
at 4848 Newcombe?
Son, your friend, Louis Corbett,
does his family still live in that
same place up on Newcombe?
Yes.
Okay, good. Okay,
he's a good kid.
He's like you. He'll understand.
I'm sending Louis a package.
Now, it's addressed
to Louis, but it's for you,
your mother and your sister.
There's money inside.
About $100,000. Okay?
I think.
It was all that I
could fit into the box.
It has to be a secret.
If anyone says a word,
the police will take it.
[CRYING]
I wanted to give
you so much more.
But this is all I could do.
Do you understand?
Son?
Can you hear me?
Do you understand?
You want to send money?
Yes. Good.
Good, good.
So you'll talk to Louis, right?
You killed Uncle Hank.
You killed him!
Listen. Wait.
Wait, son. Please...
No. What you did to
Mom... You asshole.
You killed Uncle Hank.
Listen to me. You've
got to listen to me.
Just shut up.
Just stop it. Stop it.
I don't want anything from you.
I don't give a shit.
You need this money.
You killed Uncle
Hank. You killed him!
Your mother needs this money.
It can't all be for nothing.
What you did...
Please. Please.
Just shut up. Shut up.
Will you just...?
Just leave us alone.
You asshole!
[SNIFFLING]
Why are you still alive?
Why won't you just die already?
Please...
Just... Just die.
[LINE DISCONNECTS]
ANNOUNCER 1 [ON TV]: Wagner
hasn't had to be really stellar tonight.
Made solid saves
back in the first period.
[ANNOUNCERS SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY ON TV]
ANNOUNCER 2: You
know, that's probably...
Going back, look at
Wagner's numbers,
it seems like he's one of
the last goalies in the league.
They don't wanna put
pressure on this guy.
ANNOUNCER 1: Kevin Granato looks
to make a move, had the puck taken.
Denver comes back
out the other way.
[COINS JINGLING]
ANNOUNCER 1: By Graham
Melanson off Rycroft. Who else?
[LINE RINGING]
Boy, he's been all
over the ice tonight.
MAN [OVER PHONE]: DEA,
Albuquerque District Office.
How may I direct your call?
I'd like to speak to the agent
in charge of the Walter
White investigation.
Who may I say is calling?
Walter White.
MAN: Hello? Hello?
Sir? Sir, are you still there?
ANNOUNCER 2 [ON TV]: This is not
just a goalie out there, it's a whole team.
ANNOUNCER 1: Two forty-nine
remaining in the third period.
BARTENDER: You
ready for that drink now?
Dimple Pinch. Neat.
BARTENDER: You got it.
ANNOUNCER 1: And Melanson,
with a good look, makes the save.
ANNOUNCER 2: That's why you
need good, solid breakout passes.
Matt Peterson...
Englehart wins the draw,
back to Peterson,
goes behind the net, makes
a terrible breakout pass,
goes right to Hackard.
He just winds up,
puts it on net here.
Turnovers, turnovers.
When you get turnovers in the
offensive zone, chances happen.
Hopefully it won't happen again.
ANNOUNCER 1:
Turnovers generally...
[CHANNELS CHANGING ON TV]
WOMAN 1: I wasn't
sure you'd come.
MAN 1: I'm not staying...
MAN 2: Is this
transfer good on the...?
WOMAN 2: Darker
than a normal rosé...
MAN 3: For us, it's always
been science first, and...
Wait, would you...?
Would you...?
Would you go back, please?
MAN 4: ShamWows...
ELLIOTT: More of a by-product.
There. GRETCHEN: Exactly.
BARTENDER: What, this? Yes.
ROSE: But just
yesterday, your charity,
the Gretchen and Elliott
Schwartz Foundation,
announced a $28 million grant
for drug-abuse treatment centers
throughout the Southwest.
ELLIOTT: Charlie, the
Southwest is our home,
and we couldn't just ignore
what's going on in
our own backyard.
ROSE: But I'm sure you're
aware that there are people
who suggest other motives.
Andrew Ross Sorkin
of The New York Times
wrote a column suggesting
that the grant was a
kind of publicity maneuver
to shore up the stock price
of Gray Matter Technologies
because of your
association with Walter White.
ELLIOTT: That's
not exactly the way...
ROSE: To cleanse
yourselves, so to speak,
of having a
methamphetamine kingpin
as cofounder of your company.
ELLIOTT: Charlie, I'm
glad you brought that up.
I have to believe that the
investing public understands
we're talking about a person
who was there early on,
but who had nothing to do
with the creation of the company
and still less to
do with growing it.
ROSE: So, what was
Walter White's contribution?
ELLIOTT: You know,
to be honest... Honey?
The company name.
We came up with it by
combining our names.
"Schwartz" means "black."
Black plus white makes gray.
Hence Gray Matter Technologies.
ELLIOTT: Exactly.
As far as I can recall,
his contribution
begins and ends there.
ROSE: There are continuing
reports of blue methamphetamine,
considered his
signature product,
throughout the Southwest
and some evidence of
reaching as far as Europe.
So my question is,
is Walter White still out there?
GRETCHEN: No, he's not.
You sound very sure.
GRETCHEN: I am.
I can't speak to this Heisenberg
that people refer to,
but whatever he became,
the sweet, kind, brilliant man
that we once knew
long ago, he's gone.
ROSE: But to be
absolutely clear...
[♪♪♪]
[GUN COCKS]
COP 1: Police! Hands!
Show us your hands.
MAN: What's going on?
COP 2: Let's see your hands!
[♪♪♪]