[BOTH SIGHING]
Yo, so, what's next?
We wait.
You don't got like
eight more anal things
we gotta do first?
The reaction has begun.
Yeah, I know. So how long?
Well, if we had a freezer,
the condensed liquid
would cool more quickly
because, of course, this
is an exothermic reaction
which means "giving off heat."
And our desired product is...
Put me into a
coma, why don't you?
What did you just say?
What? What? Nothing.
Huh.
No, no, no. Not in here.
Duh. Like I'm an idiot.
Yeah. Like you're
an idiot. Dick.
[SIGHS]
[GRUNTS]
God. Jesus. God.
Shut up. Oh, wow.
WALT: Bogdan. Bogdan says
I'm not doing the receipts right.
Well, he's got a
bug up his butt.
He's got a stick up his butt?
He's got a bug up his butt
about the receipts, anyways.
So anyway, he's
insisting that I...
He's demanding that I stay
and look over his system
and I cannot get out of it.
Yeah.
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[SIGHS]
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
WALT [OVER PHONE]:
Hi, honey. It's me.
Hey, you. What's going on?
Nothing much.
I, uh, was just,
um, calling to say I'm sorry,
but I'm gonna be late tonight.
Bogdan. He's got
a bug up his butt.
That's okay. I wasn't planning
anything special for dinner, so.
In fact, you could take pity
on us and bring a pizza home.
They're having a
two-for-one at Venezia's.
At this point, I could eat
a whole one by myself.
Yeah, yeah, sure. I
can pick up a pizza, heh.
Hopefully Bogdan
won't keep me too late.
He better not. Trust me,
he does not want to piss off
a hungry, pregnant woman.
Ooh! What's that sound?
SKYLER: I just sold
your favorite piece.
The hideous crying clown. Wow.
Yeah, and I got 9 bucks
more than I paid for it.
Shows what I know about art.
Hey, what do you
think about Holly?
For the baby's name.
Do you like it?
I think I really like it.
Holly. Yeah, it's nice.
Let me think about it.
Just feels right, you
know? It's my new favorite.
Well, it's a
front-runner, for sure.
[JESSE GRUNTING]
[SIGHS]
Listen, I was thinking, um,
maybe we can have a little
family time this weekend.
Oh, yeah? Yeah.
You know, just take a drive.
The almost four
of us. Heh-heh-heh.
Maybe we can head
up the Turquoise Trail,
stop at Tinkertown, maybe
grab some lunch in Madrid.
Oh, my God. We haven't
been there in forever.
I know. Yeah.
So why don't we just do
that? Take a little break?
Sold. Sounds fun.
Holly. It's growing on me.
Yep. Me too.
All right, well, I had better
go and get this in the mail.
Why don't you call me, uh,
when you're on your way home?
Will do. Love you. Love you too.
[JESSE CONTINUES GRUNTING]
[♪♪♪]
[GUNFIRE]
[HANK GROANING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTING]
Ah. JACK: Whoa.
Simmer down there, sparky.
What the hell did
we just walk into?
TODD: Hey, Uncle Jack, I
don't see Jesse Pinkman.
He was right here before.
JACK: Anybody got
eyes on Pinkman?
MAN: No.
JACK: What do you figure?
He may be headed
down that gully there?
That's the way I'd go.
JACK: Frankie,
Lester, go find him.
Jack.
These guys are DEA.
[GROANS]
[GUN COCKS]
WALT: No, Jack!
No, Jack! Jack! Jack!
No! No, don't!
Jack, don't. No.
No, Jack, Jack, Jack! Jack, no!
Jack, no. Don't kill him.
MAN: Uh-Uh, back it up.
Don't kill him,
Jack. Get back here.
JACK: The hell not? He's DEA.
No, ah, he's family.
Say again?
He's my family.
He's my brother-in-law.
JACK: Didn't cross your
mind to maybe tell us
you had a DEA agent
for a brother-in-law?
Did you know about this? I
called you off, remember?
I told you not to come.
Well, it seems to me
we did you a solid.
WALT: You weren't
supposed to be here.
Too late now. How's
about you telling me
what was going
down out here? Hmm?
You and your
brother-in-law don't seem
to be getting along too well.
It doesn't matter. It
doesn't concern you.
JACK: We just wasted his partner
here and he's wearing a bullet,
so, yeah, I'd say it
does concern me.
This is between him and me.
No cavalry coming? No.
You bet your ass
the cavalry's coming.
No, no, no! Jack...
[GRUNTING]
Jack! No, the DEA
doesn't know about this.
Not yet.
Hank.
Nothing can change
what just happened,
but you can walk
out of here alive
if you just promise us
that you'll let this go.
Heh, yeah, I thought as much.
Sorry, man. Just no
scenario where this guy lives.
No, no, no, listen!
I have money!
I have money! It's
buried out here. It's...
[SIGHS]
It's $80 million.
Eighty million.
So that's what got
this party started, huh?
But this money of yours won't
do me much good in prison.
WALT: You can go anywhere.
You can do anything.
Think about it.
You can have any
future that you want.
Jack.
Eighty million.
And all you've got to do
is let him go.
JACK: That's a hell of an offer.
What do you think, fed?
Would you take that deal?
It's Hank.
His name is Hank.
How about it, Hank?
Should I let you go?
My name is ASAC Schrader.
And you can go fuck yourself.
Hank, listen to me.
You gotta tell him...
You gotta tell him now
that we can work this out.
Please. Please.
What? You want me to beg?
You're the smartest
guy I ever met.
And you're too stupid to see
he made up his
mind 10 minutes ago.
Do what you're gonna do...
[INAUDIBLE]
[WALT CRYING]
JACK: Pretty
specific directions.
Most people tell me
to be somewhere,
they say, "West on
the 40, this or that exit,
second gas station
on the left." You know?
This here? This is
a whole other story.
That fancy phone of yours,
where does it
say this is exactly?
Yeah.
Look at this. They
even brought a shovel.
MAN: Jack, no sign of Pinkman.
[WHISTLES]
All right.
Says this is it right here.
Dig.
[MAN 1 LAUGHS]
MAN 1: What's that? A
barrel? Couple barrels?
MAN 1: Jesus. MAN 2: Hell, yeah!
MAN 1: Oh, Jesus.
Would you look at that?
MAN 2: Hell, yeah!
MAN 3: Goddamn.
[ALL CHEERING AND LAUGHING]
What are you waiting for?
Yeah, boss. Hell, yeah.
Let me get on this side.
MAN 2: Get that
out of there, man.
[THUDS]
[♪♪♪]
[CHATTERING]
JACK: Okay. Pull
a barrel off the truck
and load it in the Chrysler.
Seriously? Jack.
That's like 10 or 11
million right there.
You sure you wanna do that?
You gonna make me say it again?
Go, go. Chop, chop.
Jesus, what's with
all the greed here?
It's unattractive.
Hey. Hey.
I'm leaving you a barrel.
Boys are gonna load it for you.
You got the keys to these cuffs?
I'm sorry for your loss.
My nephew here, he respects you.
He would never forgive me
if things went another way.
Also you caught
me in a good mood.
So here's what's gonna happen.
You're gonna get in your car,
and you're gonna drive
out of here, all right?
No hard feelings.
Understand me?
We square?
Hey, man, I gotta
know we're square,
or we're gonna have
to go that other way.
Pinkman.
You still owe me.
If you can find
him, we'll kill him.
Found him.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
JESSE: No!
Get off me!
Get off!
[GRUNTING]
No, no.
[GUN COCKS]
Good to go?
TODD: Hey, Uncle Jack.
Well, he was out
here with those feds.
Right? Working with them.
Should we maybe find
out what he told them first?
Because, I mean, he had
to have told them some stuff
that might not be
too good for us.
And I'll bet we could get
it out of him back home.
I mean, I can do it.
Me and him, we got history.
And then, you know, we'd
take care of the job after that.
Works for me. Work for you?
FRANKIE: Let's go, pal. No. No!
No! No! WALT: Wait.
I watched Jane die.
I was there. And
I watched her die.
I watched her overdose
and choke to death.
I could have saved her.
But I didn't.
[ENGINE REVS]
[CAR BEEPING]
[ENGINE SPUTTERS]
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHING]
[♪♪♪]
[PLAYING "TIME'S A GETTING
HARD" BY EDDY ARNOLD]
[WALT GRUNTING]
♪ Time's a gettin' hard boys ♪
♪ Money's gettin' scarce ♪
♪ Times don't get
No better boys ♪
♪ Gonna leave this place ♪
♪ Take my true
love By her hand ♪
♪ Lead her through the town ♪
♪ Say goodbye to everyone ♪
♪ Goodbye to everyone ♪
♪ Had a job a year ago ♪
♪ Had a little home ♪
♪ Now I've got no place to go ♪
♪ Guess I'll have to roam ♪
♪ Take my true
love By her hand ♪
♪ Lead her through the town ♪
♪ Say goodbye to everyone ♪
♪ Goodbye to everyone ♪
♪ Every wind that blows, boys ♪
♪ Every wind that blows ♪
♪ Carries me To some new place ♪
♪ Heaven only knows ♪
♪ Take my true
love By her hand ♪
♪ Lead her through the town ♪
♪ Say goodbye to everyone ♪
♪ Goodbye to everyone ♪
[WALT COUGHING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Hi. Hello.
That truck belong to you?
It does.
I'd like to buy it.
It's not for sale.
Hey, Walt, it's me.
Um, just thought
I'd try you again.
We were just wondering
when you thought you'd be back
so just give us a call
whenever you can.
Bye.
[MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Hey, Aunt Marie.
MARIE: Hey, sweetie.
Haven't seen you for a while.
What have you been up to?
Oh, you know. This and that.
Your mom and I need to
talk, so thought I'd stop by.
Well, I, uh, wish
you'd called first.
This isn't the best time.
Well, Flynn looks like
he can hold down the fort.
Why don't we go
into your office?
I got it.
Okay, honey. Thanks.
Marie, I have nothing
to say. Well, I do.
So you can just
sit there and listen.
I got a call from Hank.
He arrested Walt
three hours ago.
It's over.
"Dead to rights" I
believe is the expression.
Hank and Steve Gomez are working
with a former associate
of Walt's, Jesse Pinkman,
whom I know you know,
and Pinkman has supplied
them with everything they need.
Hank is booking
Walt as we speak.
And I, for one,
could not be happier.
I almost didn't come here.
Christ, I barely even
know who you are,
and I sure as hell don't know
if I can ever trust you again.
And then I think about how
you were so upset with Walt
and how you wanted
the kids out of the house,
and all of this makes me believe
that there has got
to be hope for you
that whatever he did
to you can be undone.
All I know, all I have been
forcing myself to remember
is that you are my sister.
And so I'm here.
[WHIMPERS]
Marie... Everything changes now.
And you have got
to prepare yourself.
Hank will help you as much
as he can. I know he will.
And I will support
you through this.
But I have conditions.
Give me every single
copy of that obscenity
that the two of you made
to discredit Hank. That DVD.
Every single copy.
You understand me?
Answer me. Do you understand me?
Yes.
Good.
Now dry your eyes
and get Flynn in here.
You are going to
tell him everything,
and I mean everything.
He deserves to know
the truth from his family.
Not a bunch of
uniformed strangers.
No. No. No, he cannot know.
You tell him, or I will.
There's no way around this.
He needs to know, and
he needs to know now.
[JESSE WHIMPERING]
[THUDDING]
JESSE: No.
[GROANING]
Look, I gave you
what you wanted.
Come on, man, please.
Hey, please.
I told you where to
find the tape, okay?
MAN: Yup.
Hey, just go.
Just go there. Just go
to his house and get it.
We're on it. Get it!
No one else knows about
it. Just me and his partner.
Okay. No one else
knows, I swear!
[♪♪♪]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTING]
[WHIMPERING]
Let's cook.
You're completely
out of your mind.
It's the truth.
MARIE: It is, Flynn.
Then both of you
are out of your minds.
You're full of shit, is
what you are. Both of you.
If this is true, then how
could you keep this a secret?
I mean, why? Why
would you go along?
I'll be asking myself
that for the rest of my life.
So you're saying all this
time you were lying about this?
Uh, I mean, so you're
saying you're a liar.
You just admitted it.
So were you lying then,
or are you lying now?
Which lie is it?
Flynn, honey, your mother
is telling you the truth.
Right here, right
now. Believe it.
You know what?
This is bullshit.
Baby... WALT JR.:
I wanna talk to Dad.
Your dad's in custody.
You can't talk to
him for a while.
I'm calling Uncle Hank.
MARIE: I've tried.
He's not answering.
He's probably in the
thick of it with your father.
Honey, I know this is
a lot to process, Flynn,
but if you could just
breathe, just try to breathe,
and just trust...
Really? Really?
Try to breathe?
[DOOR OPENS]
Oh, my God.
[CRYING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
MARIE: Go home.
Just take the kids home,
okay? Go home and regroup.
I'll stop by later.
[CAR BEEPING]
Flynn?
Could you put your
seatbelt on, please?
Please. It's not safe.
You're shitting me, right?
If all this is true and
you knew about it,
then you're as bad as him.
SKYLER: Whose truck is that?
WALT JR.: Dad?
[WALT GRUNTING]
Listen, I need you to come
inside and pack right now.
Mom, Aunt Marie, they
said that you were arrested?
No, just...
You're some kind of drug dealer?
No, just come
inside, please. Now.
Come inside. Come on.
Go, go, go.
Dad, stop. Just
talk to me, please.
Our priority right
now is to pack.
Uncle Hank, they
said he arrested you?
I will discuss all
of this later, okay?
WALT JR.: Just tell me
what... Just listen to me!
Go into your bedroom
now, grab anything important.
You understand? Go.
Now. Both of you. Go.
Walt.
Why are you here?
Skyler, please, will you
just go get your things?
For you and the kids.
Now. This is our priority.
Hank had you in custody.
He wouldn't just let you go.
Where is he?
Where's Hank? I, uh...
I negotiated... Negotiated?
Uh, yes. What does that mean?
It means we're fine, okay?
We are. We're fine.
Everything is gonna be fine,
but we need to leave right now.
All right? Can we do that?
SKYLER: What happened?
Where is Hank?
WALT JR.: Why do
we need to leave?
I need both of you to trust me.
Right now, okay?
Please, just work with me here,
and I promise I will explain
everything later, okay?
Where is Hank?
Skyler.
I have $11 million
in cash right outside.
We can have a fresh start.
Whole new lives.
All we have to do is go.
We have to go right now.
That's all we have to do.
You killed him.
You killed Hank.
What? No, no, no.
SKYLER: You
killed him. No, no, no!
I tried to save him.
WALT JR.: Uncle
Hank is dead? I...
Mom, it can't be true.
It just can't be true.
WALT: Just stop, please.
Everything is gonna be okay.
Everything's gonna
be fine, I promise,
but we need to leave right now.
WALT JR.: Dad, what's
going on? Talk to me.
Just stop for one second.
WALT: Look, I told
you to get your things.
WALT JR.: Stop walking
away. WALT: There is no time.
WALT JR.: Tell me
about Uncle Hank.
WALT: No, just drop it! WALT
JR.: What's wrong with you?
WALT: We're going.
We're going right now.
WALT JR.: You have
to tell me. Dad, wait.
What happened to
Uncle Hank? What...?
Get out.
Skyler, I promise you,
we will figure this out.
Enough. Mom, what are you doing?
Skyler, put the
knife down, please.
I promise you, everything...
SKYLER: Don't say one more word.
Get out of here now.
Skyler...
Get out!
[GASPS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
WALT JR.: Stop it!
Just stop! Just stop!
[HOLLY CRYING]
WALT: Let go! Let go!
SKYLER: Get away from us!
WALT JR.: Just stop! Stop!
Dad, stop it! Stop!
Mom, stop it.
Stop, Dad. Stop it now. Stop.
Stop! Just, please, stop!
Stop it! Stop! Stop it!
[GRUNTING CONTINUES]
[ALL BREATHING HEAVILY]
What the hell is wrong
with you? We're a family!
[HOLLY CONTINUES CRYING]
[♪♪♪]
We're a family.
[SKYLER CRYING]
WALT: What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Yeah, I need the police.
My dad, he pulled
a knife on my mom.
He attacked her. He's dangerous.
I think he might
have killed somebody.
Yeah.
He's still here.
Yeah, he's still in the house.
We're at 308 Negra Arroyo Lane.
308 Negra Arroyo Lane!
You've gotta come quick.
Hurry, hurry. Oh, God, no, no!
Oh, my God. No.
Walt, no! Walt! WALT JR.: Mom!
SKYLER: Walt, please, no!
No! No! No!
[ENGINE REVS]
Walt, no! Let her go!
You can't take her!
Let her go, please!
Let her go! Walt!
Walt, please, no!
Walt, no! Walt, please!
Walt, no!
Walt, please, no!
Walt, please!
Please, stop! Walt!
[♪♪♪]
WALT: Say, "Da-da."
Da-da. You say, "Da-da"?
There. Get rid of that
stinky old diaper, huh?
Don't be sad. Where's
your belly button?
Where's your belly button?
There. Now, don't
you feel better?
You're all nice and dry. Oh.
That feels good? Oh, I know.
You were so wet and so cranky,
but now you feel
better, don't you?
Next order of business is to
get you a brand-new car seat.
Won't that be nice, Holly?
[WHIMPERING]
Mama.
MAN: Confirming the abduction.
Amber Alert. Holly White.
Female, 18 months.
Blond hair, blue eyes.
Was last seen wearing a pink
and white jacket, pink pants.
Abductor is the father.
He was in handcuffs.
Hank had him in handcuffs.
MAN: Bald head, goatee,
gold wire-framed glasses.
[PHONE RINGING]
MAN: Are you expecting a call?
SKYLER [ON RECORDING]: Hi,
you've reached the White family.
Please leave a message.
WALT [OVER PHONE]:
Skyler, it's me. Pick up. Pick up.
That's him. That's my
husband. I need you to pick up.
MAN: Start tracing the landline.
The number's 505-177-8987.
I know you're
there, so pick it up.
Skyler, you hear me?
Need the location
of an incoming caller.
Answer the pho...
Walt, where's Holly?
Are you alone?
No police?
No. No police.
Where are you? Where's Holly?
Walt!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Why can't you do
one thing I say?
What? This is your fault.
This is what comes
of your disrespect.
I told you, Skyler.
I warned you for a solid year.
You cross me, there
will be consequences.
What part of that
didn't you understand?
You took my child.
Because you need to learn.
You bring her back.
Maybe now you'll listen.
Maybe now you'll
use your damn head.
You know, you
never believed in me.
You were never grateful for
anything I did for this family.
"Oh, no. Walt. Walt,
you have to stop.
You have to stop this.
It's immoral. It's illegal.
Someone might get hurt."
You're always whining
and complaining
about how I make my money,
just dragging me down,
while I do everything.
And now...
Now you tell my son what I do
after I've told you and told you
to keep your damn mouth shut.
You stupid bitch.
How dare you?
I'm sorry.
You have no right
to discuss anything
about what I do.
What the hell do you
know about it, anyway?
Nothing. I built this.
Me. Me alone. Nobody else!
You're right. You're right.
You mark my words, Skyler.
Toe the line,
or you will wind
up just like Hank.
Walt.
Tell me what happened.
Where is Hank?
Please.
We need to know.
You're never gonna
see Hank again.
[WHIMPERS]
[CRYING]
He crossed me.
You think about that.
Family or no.
You let that sink in.
SKYLER [OVER PHONE]: Walt.
I just want Holly back.
Please, Walt.
Just come home.
I've still got
things left to do.
[WHIMPERS]
[VOICE SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY OVER SPEAKERS]
MAN: Hey.
[BABY CRYING]
[♪♪♪]