[BEEPING]
Hey, Darla. How you
doing today? Hey, Dan.
I'm looking for
something in a Markowski.
That'd be, uh, Dennis Markowski?
That's the one.
[BEEPING]
Oh, and I've got my, uh,
paralegal with me today.
Paralegal? Coming
up in the world.
You know it.
[INAUDIBLE]
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey, Dennis.
Have a seat.
[ROCK MUSIC ON EARPHONES]
You hear about Chow?
Yeah, people say
he skipped town.
He's dead.
It wasn't me.
It wasn't a message.
It wasn't payback.
It was a mistake
made by a third party
who has since been
dealt with. You got it?
Yeah. The second thing.
The deal you had with
Fring, it's still in place.
Okay.
Don't "okay" me.
You got something to say?
Mike, I'm keeping my mouth shut.
The laundry was
right above the lab.
There's no way I could
say I wasn't in on it.
I'm looking at eight
years minimum.
But I'm doing my time
like I'm supposed to.
I'm no rat, and you know it.
What else is there to say?
All due respect, what
are we talking about here?
The deal is the deal.
How's the deal the deal?
The feds took
away my hazard pay.
My wife comes to me and asks me
where the mortgage is coming from.
I got nothing to tell her.
I knew the risks. We all did.
But that wasn't the deal.
And I know for a fact they
got Holt and Perez yesterday.
Now, it's not gonna be me,
but absent the hazard pay,
sooner or later,
someone's gonna flip.
No one's flipping.
Everyone gets their
hazard pay, including you.
I appreciate what
you're saying and all,
but the man is dead.
Okay? The lab's a
hole in the ground.
I just don't see it.
I've got something new.
It's just starting up. It's
gonna make you whole.
Something new? With
the feds looking at you?
How?
"How" is my business.
Hanging tight's your business.
Your family's gonna be fine.
You will be made whole.
Now, you got my word.
You need more?
No, Mike. I'm good.
MIKE: Who's next?
That's your choice.
APDs got Martinez across town.
McGann's up in Sandoval.
The Sandia tribal cops
are holding him for the feds.
[ALARM BUZZES]
And Holt and Perez are
in lockup in Los Lunas.
You don't mean to
get to them all today?
Yeah, I do.
Hey, let's go! Open up!
[ALARM BUZZES]
[♪♪♪]
[HUMMING]
[DOOR CLOSES] Back here!
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, hi. How was your day?
Um, are... Are you
moving back in?
Yeah. I'll keep
the condo for now.
Selling it in this
market, I'd get killed.
But, yeah, I'm home.
It's time.
Do you, uh, really
think that's a good idea?
Yes.
[LABORED BREATHING]
[LABORED BREATHING CONTINUES]
SAUL: So you bring
him here? Come on.
The three of us,
we're the three amigos.
All for one, one for all.
We don't need a fourth amigo.
Saul, Mike knows the
business. He knows distributors.
Mike's okay. He's okay?
He said he was
gonna break my legs.
And don't tell me he
didn't mean it, okay?
'Cause he gave me the dead
mackerel eyes. He meant it.
WALT: Saul, Mike threatened
me. He threatened Jesse.
He probably threatened someone
before breakfast this morning.
It's what he does.
Come on. Grow a pair.
Let it be noted that I
do this under duress.
Duly noted.
All right. Let him in, Huell.
Mike, I'm extending
you the... Uh-huh.
Now that we're all together,
here are the ground rules.
Division of labor. I
handle the business.
Making the stuff,
that's your end.
I don't tell you how to mix
your chemicals and whatnot,
and you do not tell me
how to take care of business.
Is that absolutely clear?
Sure.
All right. Let's take the tour.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey, you're okay with that?
Yes.
He handles the business,
and I handle him.
SAUL: Clearly, we're talking
about renting, not buying.
You need an ongoing business,
someplace you can slide in, do
your thing, and remain anonymous.
I'm not gonna mince words.
This is your best bet.
Got machines running,
forklifts, people
coming and going.
You're gonna stay
way under the radar.
And the owner's solid.
He can't wait to
throw up a curtain wall,
stack some boxes in front of it,
give you all the space you need.
After that, he's got his
business, you've got yours,
and never the twain shall meet.
It's outstanding. Am I right?
Machines like this,
gotta be plenty of power.
What about the smell?
Ah. More good news.
I've been here when
it's up and running.
This place stinks already.
You'll blend right in.
How many employees?
Ha. I knew you'd ask.
Sixteen illegals,
all highly motivated to
stay deaf, blind, and dumb.
You'll want to
vet them, I'm sure.
Yes, indeed.
So what do you say, maestro?
Huh? Is it unanimous?
You know, I worked in a box
factory one summer in high school,
and I haven't seen
one of these in years.
Trip down memory
lane. That's perfect.
You know what this is?
It's a corrugator.
It uses steam and salt to
crimp kraft paper for cardboard.
And it makes a hell of a
racket doing it, which is great.
Right?
No.
Steam and salt.
When this thing is running,
it's like a jungle in here.
Shit. It'll ruin the product.
You can't just hop
down to Costco
and get a couple dehumidifiers?
What... Fine. Fine. Moving on.
Spacious, isolated location,
no humidity,
and you get all the
free tortillas you want.
That's the special
feature of this place.
I don't know.
It'll make the tortillas
smell like cat piss.
Somebody's bound to notice that.
All right. Well, there's gotta be
some kind of workaround, right?
It's a technical problem.
You guys are technical guys.
You know, be creative.
Put your heads together.
Anything food-related is gonna have
unannounced government inspections.
All I'm asking is that
you keep an open mind.
Danny's already set some space
aside behind the skee ball games.
[SCOFFS] No.
Hell, no.
I know it's a long shot.
All I can say to
recommend this one
is we're talking about
an owner here who is,
how should I put
it, highly amenable.
Look, I get it. Just say
no, and we'll go get dinner.
All right. So I'll start.
No way we're cooking in here.
No space, nowhere
for the smell to go.
Look at that door.
That thing rolls up, and
we're open to the world.
MIKE: I don't know
if anybody noticed,
but there's a cop shop
a quarter of a mile away.
The hammer comes down, it's
gonna be Custer's Last Stand.
It's perfect.
What?
How are we gonna
fit a lab in here?
Who said here?
WALT: A house is infested.
Termites, cockroaches, whatever.
Homeowners hire a
pest control company.
Truck rolls up,
homeowners leave.
The crew tents the house.
They bomb the place with poison.
The house stays
like that for days.
No one looks twice
at a tented house.
Now, maybe there's a
strange smell coming out of it.
Does someone think
to investigate? No.
Does anyone go inside? Hell, no.
And that's where we'll cook.
They tent, what, three,
four houses a week?
So we pick the one
that's best for us.
Enough floor space, easy access.
Once the tent is up,
we go in, we cook a batch,
we bomb the place, and leave.
So we gotta move in
and out for every cook?
Set up the lab, cook, and
then take everything down?
It's challenging but doable.
Tell me about these guys.
Uh, Mr. Ponytail on
the sidewalk, that's Ira.
He's the owner. On
the roof is Sandor.
The ladder's Fernando,
and down below, that's Todd.
The pest control
operation is legit.
I mean, they're
licensed, they're bonded,
they do as good a
job as anyone in town,
but they're also top-drawer
second-story men.
"Second-story"?
B&E artists.
They're burglars.
Yeah. I mean, hey,
they play it smart.
They don't boost anything
while they're on the job.
They copy the keys, locate
the valuables and alarms,
and they sell that
information to other crews.
Or, after a decent interval,
they'll come back and
lift the goods themselves.
And you know them how?
Oh, I've been pulling their
chestnuts out of the fire,
legally speaking,
for five years.
Ira and his guys are good.
I mean, they know how
to keep their mouths shut.
And if you buy them,
they're gonna stay bought.
You can check
into them yourself.
I will, if it comes to that.
So, do we take a vote?
Why?
[HORN HONKS]
[PLAYING CLASSICAL MUSIC]
[DISCORDANT NOTES]
We sound great.
Rock on, man. Solid.
That Yamaha's got
a real nice touch.
You like the sound?
It's huge, huh?
Yeah, it's real nice, but we're
looking for something else today.
You got any roadie cases?
For sure. What
size? Biggest you got.
[PLAYS NOTE]
That'll fit through, like,
a regular-size doorway.
You got it. Follow me.
Top of the line.
Recessed hardware, foam lining,
quarter-inch laminated walls,
three-inch casters.
Height is good, width is good.
How much weight will this hold?
It's rated for 900 pounds.
[FEEDBACK SOUNDING]
So unless your band plays
lead bricks, you should be okay.
[PLAYING DRUMS]
We're gonna need,
uh... [PLAYING GUITAR]
Hey, man, I'm trying to do
business over here, bitch.
Sorry. He's, like,
overly enthusiastic.
Anyway, um, I'm
gonna need four of them.
Four? That gonna be layaway?
'Cause I need to see
a bunch of IDs for that.
No, man, cash.
Okay. Hey, uh, you know what?
I'll throw in stenciling.
What's your band called?
SKINNY PETE: Damn, brother!
Not asking no questions, but it sure
looks like you're back in business.
No joke. You way
back in business, man.
Look at this.
Yeah.
Oh! You're stacking the benjies
till the rubber band pops.
Yeah, yeah.
All's we're saying is, we
know you're major league now.
But if there's ever anything
else you need from us...
Any way we can
get in on this at all.
Little stuff, big stuff.
We would be all over it.
You know, uh, maybe someday.
That's cool.
I guess we better hit it then.
Yeah. Keep on
keeping on, brother.
Later. Yeah.
[DOOR CLOSING]
MIKE: Okay, it is the
same job as always.
You go out, you inspect,
you deal with the
customers, regular drill.
Everything's the same
except for one important detail.
No stealing. No stealing.
Not a toothpick, not the spare
change between the couch cushions,
not the panties
out of the hamper.
Nothing. And I mean nothing.
And if you're out
with your buddies
and they ask if you
got a hot tip on a B&E,
you tell them you got nada.
You're out of the
game. The bottom line is
that these houses are out
of bounds now and forever.
Got it?
All right.
From time to time, you're
gonna see these two.
Now, as far as you're
concerned, they are ghosts.
You don't see them.
You don't hear them.
You don't say "good morning."
You don't speak
unless you're spoken to.
On the other hand,
if they tell you to jump,
you don't ask what for,
you jump.
Now, you need a name for them?
You call them "Yes,
sir" and "No, sir."
You got any problems,
you come to me.
JESSE: Here's the deal.
The finishing
tank's a tight fit.
And with this motor
you've got on top...
WALT: The agitation motor.
The agitation motor here on top,
the tank's not
gonna fit in the box.
It's just, uh...
It's just too tall.
You know, I thought we'd
put a collar on the tank
and carry the motor in separately,
alongside the condenser.
And on the day, we just
kind of twist it into place,
you know, while
we're setting up.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's good. Yeah.
That will work.
And Joe and his
guys can build it, right?
Yeah. You know, they're,
uh... They're up for it.
Joe already bought a tig
welder for the aluminum work.
And, you know,
I figure if they can pull off the
magnet, they can handle this.
Now, listen, about the smell...
About keeping it out of people's
drapes and furniture and whatnot...
When I was down
in Mexico, they, uh...
There was this big,
big plastic hospital tent
they set up inside of
the... [LOCK CLICKING]
Oh, shit. Sorry. [DOOR OPENS]
Oh, hi. Sorry.
No, no, no. We were
just, uh, wrapping up.
Um, this is my, uh...
Friend. Hi. Walt.
Nice to meet you. You too.
JESSE: This is, uh, Brock.
Hi, Brock. I'm Walt.
I've heard a lot about you.
Hi. Hi.
I understand you
were in the hospital.
And Jesse told me that
you were very brave.
Yeah. A man of few words.
I'm sorry. He mostly just
wants to play his game.
Oh, I know that.
I have two of my own. A boy
and a girl. [VIDEO GAME NOISES]
Well, I should,
uh... I should go.
I was thinking I could
make us all some dinner.
Are you sure you don't wanna...
Yeah. Won't you stay
for a beer at least?
Sure. Why not? A
beer sounds good.
Thank you.
[VIDEO GAME NOISES]
[SIGHS]
How are you today, sir?
Hello. We're good.
Good. How are you?
Family all packed
up, ready to go?
Okay, here you're acknowledging
that you've removed all pets
and plants from the house
and that food has been removed
or double-sealed in the
bags we provided. Uh-huh.
And this acknowledges that
you've removed or bagged
any medicines,
tobacco, and pet foods.
Better make sure
you got any medicine
you might need for
the next couple of days.
It's already in the car. Okay.
Holy crap.
How much poison are you using?
It's not how much, it's
getting it to where it's needed.
Those are your foggers.
They disperse the
fumigate into the structure
where it'll eliminate
any nymphs or larvae
as well as the
full-grown blattodea.
So, uh, do we
have all your keys?
Any extras on here you
might wind up needing?
No. I'm good. Okay.
This last one here acknowledges
that you have been informed
that you may not
reenter the premises
until it has cleared the
post-fumigation inspection.
So you're gonna
get them all, right?
We'll kill 'em dead.
That's a guarantee.
Sir? Uh, sir?
Yes?
There's a nanny-cam
in the living room clock.
I disabled it. I just
thought you should know.
What's your name?
Todd, sir.
[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING]
[HISSING]
Hey, cheers.
Yeah.
You know, I've gotta say,
seeing you with Andrea
and that little boy...
[CHUCKLES] It was nice.
Yeah. It's good, right? Yeah.
[CHUCKLES] Yeah.
And the way she looks at you...
Oh-ho. You think?
Oh, definitely.
[CHUCKLES]
So, is it, um... Is it moving
in any particular direction?
Uh, I don't know.
Maybe. Yeah. You
know, sometimes I think,
you know,
if it feels right, then...
If it feels right,
it feels right.
Sometimes you just
gotta listen to your gut.
I mean, instant family.
What more can you ask, right?
Absolutely.
MOE: Cut the cards.
Have you thought
about what your plan is?
You know, vis-a-vis honesty?
You mean how much
she knows about this?
Mmm.
Um... [MUTES TV]
She doesn't know anything.
I mean, you know,
she's not stupid.
She knows I'm into something,
but she could make
a pretty good guess.
But I never told her anything.
I'm not gonna.
Okay.
I mean it.
I know you do.
Jesse, I can't pretend that
this doesn't affect me. It does.
But with everything
that we've been through,
the two of us...
This has to be your decision.
I mean, you've earned that.
Seriously?
Yeah.
Secrets create barriers
between people.
I'm speaking from
experience, believe me.
All that you've done,
it's a part of you, and...
I mean, if you choose to spend
the rest of your life with this person,
then you'll have to decide
how much you'll share with her.
Meaning what? Like everything?
Like Gale?
I'm just trying to
say that I trust you,
and I know you'll
make the right call.
If she loves you,
she'll understand.
[TV SOUND AUDIBLE]
They're leaving streaks.
This more ethnic-looking
one, he's doing a great job.
But the other one is
going back and forth
like he's scrubbing a wall.
They have to go in circles,
or you're going
to leave streaks.
That's pretty basic, right?
Uh, I don't mean to
tell you your business.
It's just... It's simple
quality control.
So, I've got some good news.
Guess what.
What?
No, really. I want you to guess.
Marie, I really...
Okay. Hank's back at work.
That's wonderful. Yeah.
Sure, they love him now, but where
were they when he needed them?
Merkert and all the rest, they just
about laughed him out of the office
when he told them
about that chicken man.
As far as I'm concerned,
too little too late.
If it were me, I'd tell
them all to go to hell.
Do I sound bitter?
But it's... It's what
he wants, right?
Yeah, it's doing him good.
I mean, his PT is
going gangbusters.
He's hardly using
his cane at all.
And thank you for that, really.
I mean, god knows where he'd be
if we had to go
through his health plan.
I'm just glad he's
feeling better.
So, speaking of which,
we have another
big event coming up.
Have you thought about
what you're gonna do?
Walt's birthday.
Whatever you need, I'm here.
Mmm, yeah. I, um...
I don't think we're gonna
do anything this year.
What are you talking about?
Of course we're
gonna do something.
Skyler, he was diagnosed
around his birthday, right?
I...
So it's been a whole year.
Listen, I've had my
problems with Walt.
Why he wouldn't come to the
house when we were all practically...
Whatever. Water
under the bridge.
But at this point, every
year is precious. We are...
What are you doing?
Uh... You don't smoke.
You haven't smoked
since college.
You can't be serious!
With the baby and Walt?
Skyler, you're not smoking
around the baby, are you?
And you can't smoke here.
There's gotta be some
rule or regulation, I'm sure.
You can't force your employees
to breathe secondhand smoke.
I know for a fact
that that is illegal.
Marie, shut up.
What?
I'm sorry. Please don't
speak to me like that.
I am simply saying that
you... Will you shut up?
Hey... Shut the hell up.
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up! Please stop...
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up!
[CRYING]
JESSE: That's a 5.23.
WALT: 5.23.
Last one.
[SCALE BEEPS]
5.26.
That comes to 49.27.
Good yield, right?
That is an excellent yield.
All right.
[GAS HISSING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey, Marie.
How you doing?
Where is Skyler?
In the bedroom. She's resting.
Is everything okay?
Breakdown? What does
that... What does that mean?
It means I don't know
what else to call it.
But I've never seen
her like that, ever.
Well, what did she say
when she was yelling?
Nothing.
She just yelled,
"Shut up, shut up,"
over and over again.
Did you know she's smoking?
Occasionally, maybe.
It's not a regular thing.
Oh, I just wish I had
gotten your message.
"Messages," Walt.
Plural. I probably
called you five times.
I'm not leaving here until I
know what's got her so upset.
Are you gambling
again? Is that what this is?
Please, God, tell me
the cancer isn't back.
No.
It's not the cancer.
Well, something happened.
I don't mean to
point the finger,
but this didn't just
come out of nowhere.
It's time to tell me
the truth, Walt. All of it.
I mean it.
You're right.
[SIGHS]
You heard about Ted Beneke?
The accident?
What accident?
Oh.
Um...
A couple weeks back,
Ted took a fall, a bad one.
He gave himself a concussion,
and, uh, fractured
a couple vertebrae.
He's still in the hospital.
He may never walk again.
Oh, my God. I... I didn't...
I didn't know. I'm
so sorry to hear that.
Yeah.
But that couldn't
explain Skyler's...
Uh, yes. Yes, it could.
You do know, right? You...
You must know.
Oh, God.
She was having an affair.
With Ted Beneke?
And listen. It wasn't...
It wasn't
ongoing or anything, and...
Well, Skyler and
I have been trying
to put things back together.
And then... Then the
accident happened,
and she got...
[SIGHS]
Look, Marie, I'm begging you.
Please, keep this to yourself.
I don't want Hank
to think less of her.
Or me.
When did you, um...
Was she... I'm gonna go.
Okay. All right.
[SIGHS]
Thank you.
I'm sorr... No.
[DOOR CLOSES]
MAN: Ouch! That looked nasty.
Hey, you okay?
I'm good.
Really?
Yeah.
[VIDEO GAME CONTINUES]
[AUTOMATIC GUNFIRE ON TV]
[YELLING]
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
[LOUD BLAST]
Come on. You want
to fuck with me?
Okay.
You little cockroaches.
WALTER, JR.: Dad, wait.
You want to play games? Okay. I
play with you. Come on. Wait. Wait for it.
WALTER: This is it.
WALTER, JR.: Wait. Wait for it.
Wait. You wanna
play rough? Okay!
Say hello to my little friend! WALTER,
JR.: "Say hello to my little friend!"
Nice! Just... You like that?
Hey, Mom, uh, feeling better?
Hey. Hey, why don't you
join us, if you feel up to it?
We have popcorn. I think
there's some pizza left.
If you're up to it.
Yeah, Mom. Join us. Die!
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
Oh, my God. Look.
Look. You whores!
WALT: Oh! Everyone dies
in this movie, don't they?
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
Okay.
For you and you and me.
$367,000 each.
Ooh. Wait a minute.
After the dealers got their cut,
we should be
looking at 1,379,560.
Mike, you're short.
You're almost 300,000 short.
You're forgetting about the
mules. They get a flat 20%.
The what? The drivers.
They're the ones that take the
product from us to the dealers.
And so, transportation
is worth 20%?
They are taking a risk.
$275,000 worth of risk?
Wow.
What did Gus pay his mules?
Gustavo Fring didn't use mules.
He didn't need them.
He spent 20 years
building his own distribution.
He had 16 refrigerator
trucks running his product.
And do you know
where they are now?
Government impound.
You don't like paying 20%? Maybe
you shouldn't have killed the guy.
Hey, hey, hey.
There's still over a million
bucks here, all right?
That's for one cook.
And since you're putting
on the green eyeshade,
my supplier and I
came to an agreement.
The methylamine
was free this time.
But brace yourself,
because the next
barrel is gonna cost big.
Can we continue, or you got
anymore burning questions?
Okay, kid.
You fronted us
120 to get us going.
So that's 40 from him and me.
120.
Yes. Thank you, Jesse.
Okay.
Now, Ira gets 110 for
our piece of the business
and 25 per cook.
That is 45
from each of us.
Ira's guys get 10 each per cook.
Goodman's cut, 18,000 from each.
Legacy cost, $351,000.
That's 117,000 each.
"Legacy cost"?
I got nine guys.
You don't know them, but they
were part of the previous operation,
and they know a lot.
And right now, some of them
are in jail and more will be soon.
The feds rico-ed
their hazard pay,
so we are gonna make 'em whole.
"We are gonna make them whole"?
What is this "we"?
These were Gus's
employees, not ours.
They might have been Gus's
employees, but they're my guys.
So what are they doing
to further our interests?
The cops are looking
at them very closely.
We don't want them
furthering our interests.
So we are paying them, why?
Because it's what you do.
Oh.
It's what you do.
[CHUCKLES]
My guys are keeping
their mouths shut.
We make 'em whole.
One hand washes the
other. It's as simple as that.
Huh.
It sounds like a
simple shakedown,
simple as that.
We're paying for their
silence. That's blackmail.
Business is my end.
This is business. End of story.
This is your problem.
It should come out of your end.
Hey. Hey. Just
take it out of mine.
All right? Go for it.
I don't care. Just take it.
Well, Jesse, thank you,
but no.
I'll pay my share.
Go ahead.
[SIGHS] Let me
tell you something.
This
is how it's gonna be
from here on out.
My guys are an
ongoing expenditure,
so you best get yourself
comfortable with it.
137,000.
[LAUGHS]
That's less than with Fring.
Listen, Walter.
Just because you
shot Jesse James
don't make you Jesse James.
MIKE: Tomorrow.
How are you feeling?
Okay, I guess.
Broke it off with Andrea.
I had to.
She's gonna tell Brock.
I'm still gonna take
care of the rent and stuff.
It's the right thing to
do, but, you know...
I meant this.
How are you feeling
about the money?
You're looking at it wrong.
When we worked for Gus,
we were cooking
200 pounds a week.
This last batch was great,
but we didn't even
crack 50 pounds.
We maybe cleared less money,
but we got a bigger piece of the pie.
It's like you said,
we're owners, not employees.
I've been thinking about Victor.
Yeah?
Yeah.
All this time,
I was sure that
Gus did what he did,
to send me a message.
Maybe there's another reason.
Like what?
Victor trying to cook
that batch on his own?
Taking liberties that
weren't his to take?
Maybe he flew too
close to the sun,
got his throat cut.
[METAL DOOR WHIRRING]